<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-11-14T10:45:03.889Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-11-14T10:45:03.889Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In One Minute : Hibernate]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rakeshkr2/in-one-minute-hibernate-53g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rakeshkr2/in-one-minute-hibernate-53g"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hibernate is the umbrella for a collection of libraries, most notably Hibernate ORM which provides Object/Relational Mapping for java domain objects.
Hibernate's primary feature is mapping from Java classes to database tables, and mapping from Java data types to SQL data types. Hibernate also provides data query and retrieval facilities. It generates SQL calls and relieves the developer from the manual handling and object conversion of the result set.
The mapping of Java classes to database tables is implemented by the configuration of an XML file or by using Java Annotations. When using an XML file, Hibernate can generate skeleton source code for the persistence classes. This is auxiliary when annotations are used. Hibernate can use the XML file or the Java annotations to maintain the database schema.





  
  
  Resources




Official website - Downloads, Tutorials, Documentation, Community, ...
Hibernate Wikipedia Article
Vlad Mihalcea's Tutorials
Hibernate DZone Examples - Step-by-step Hibernate Examples / Tutorials for beginners.
Java Persistence with Hibernate
High-Performance Java Persistence]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rakesh KR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #820 英伟达采用形式验证来验证软件安全性]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15252-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15252-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T09:14:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[英伟达采用形式验证来验证软件安全性

英伟达软件安全副总裁说，“面向测试的软件验证对安全来说根本不起作用，你可以对提供给用户的功能的质量有一个衡量标准，但对于安全问题，就没有什么作用，……很难知道你是否已经完成了。”幸运的是，有可能用数学方法证明你的代码的行为与它的规范精确一致。这个过程被称为“形式验证”。英伟达采用软件形式验证行业解决方案 SPARK 来证明软件的安全性。在几年前进行过概念验证后，现在许多英伟达产品在使用 SPARK 组件发布。


消息来源：AdaCore



老王点评：形式验证是个好方法，但是不是那么容易掌握和推行。




JavaScript、Java、Python、Kotlin 和 Rust 开发者增长惊人

根据 SlashData 去年夏天从 163 个国家的 26000 多名开发者调查统计而成的第 23 期《开发者国家报告》，JavaScript 仍然是最大的编程语言社区，全球估计有 1960 万开发者每天都在使用 JavaScript；在过去的两年里，Java 社区的规模已经从 830 万增加到 1650 万，而同期开发者只增加了 50%；Python 在过去两年中增加了约 800 万新的开发人员；Kotlin 和 Rust 社区的规模在过去两年里都翻了一番。


消息来源：ZDNet



老王点评：开发人员越来越倾向于使用主流开发工具，所以流行的越发流行，但是这样就会扼杀一些创新。




密码学家建议考虑非晶格的后量子密码算法

目前许多密码学系统的安全性是基于大数的因数分解的，但因数分解的一个怪癖使其容易受到量子计算机的攻击。因此人们对上世纪 90 年代提出的“晶格密码学”寄予厚望，美国 NIST 选择的四个后量子密码学标准有三个采用晶格密码学。RSA 算法名称中的 S，Adi Shamir 对此表示担忧，“从某种意义上说，我们是把所有鸡蛋放在同一个篮子里”。今年夏天早些时候，一个有前途的后量子密码学方案不是用量子计算机，而是用一台普通的笔记本电脑破解的。


消息来源：Slashdot



老王点评：确实如此，只有一种抗量子的密码理论，很难说会不会被发现潜在的弱点。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Effective Speech Recognition System]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/liubovzatolokina2022/how-to-build-an-effective-speech-recognition-system-3be2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/liubovzatolokina2022/how-to-build-an-effective-speech-recognition-system-3be2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T08:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern voice applications use AI algorithms to recognize different sounds, including human voice and speech. In technical terms, most of the voice apps perform either voice recognition or speech recognition. And while there is no big difference between the architecture and AI models that perform voice/speech recognition, they actually relate to different business tasks. So first of all, let us elaborate on the difference between them.
Voice recognition is the ability to single out specific voices from other sounds, and identify the owner’s tone to implement security features like voice biometrics. 
Speech recognition is mostly responsible for extracting meaningful information from the audio, recognizing the words said, and the context they are placed in. With this we can create systems lik…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liubov Zatolokina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AudaOS — Make a powerful presentation visual and interactive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/audaos</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/audaos"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T08:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This past year, we've been working on a completely new approach to presentations and decks in private beta.  While we're still super early, we're excited to open things up today, and wanted the Product Hunt community to be among the first to try out the product.

AudaOS is a new approach to working with presentations. Let you start storytelling remotely, easily to share and present your work on the web. create presentations, screen recordings and screenshots, and easily add voiceover and markups. Make your point without having a meeting.

What can you do with AudaOS:

🧪 Share status updates
Instead of scheduling a 30-minute meeting, send out a quick update with visuals for reference, and let everyone watch when they have time.

🎥 Record a tutorial
No more hard-to-follow bulleted lists—just record your screen as you walk through the steps, and show everyone how it’s done.

📌 Streamline onboarding and tech support
In place of time-consuming PDFs, PPTs, emails, and in-person training, use AudaOS to create how-to videos and send them to anyone who needs support.

📒 Deliver a sales proposal
Pitch prospects with large teams without complicated scheduling, and give them a presentation they can pass along to other stakeholders.

📑 Walk through a design
Give clients the context they need by presenting layouts and explaining your thought process, so they get the complete picture.

🧲 Give client feedback
Review scheme with video feedback that they can easily digest—and you can easily create during late-night grading sessions.

✨ And more
There are so many other features waiting for you to try out. Analytics, Asset Management for team, and Upload multiple file types(.ppt/.pdf/.docx/.jpg/...) to get you started right away.

As first time founders, it's a dream come true to launch on Product Hunt.  We look forward to your feedback and sincerely appreciate the support! 🙌
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Protect Your Brand?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/oxylabs-io/how-to-protect-your-brand-2md4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/oxylabs-io/how-to-protect-your-brand-2md4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T08:08:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you wondering how to protect your brand? Well, this post will help you find your way.
It’s not a secret that taking care of a brand's reputation isn’t an easy task. Plenty of counterfeits seek to lay their hands on ideas, products, and creative works that aren’t theirs. To protect a company’s good name, you have to scan loads of websites worldwide, combat geo-restrictions and IP blocks. Sounds harsh, right? Proxies and specialized scraping tools are here to help. They'll get you to the desired content anywhere on earth and keep you safe from unwanted IP bans.
Challenges you may face:
Property protection
Scalability
Restricted geo-locations
Uplift your brand protection operations
With our scraping solutions, your day-to-day brand protection routine will go smoothly and bear fruit. You c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oxylabs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[poxi.page — Your own corner of the web - drag & drop, rotate & draw]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/poxi-page</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/poxi-page"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T08:03:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://chrome.google.com/websto...

-- 𝗦𝗵𝗼𝘄𝗰𝗮𝘀𝗲 --
https://poxi.page/shared/home-313
https://poxi.page/karu
https://poxi.page/meatblood
https://poxi.page/shared/tde-6711
https://poxi.page/frede
https://poxi.page/porter-robinso...
https://poxi.page/shared/space-c...
https://poxi.page/Cco0orn

Tech: Svelte & Svelte Kit

Discord: https://discord.gg/yy9FCDURuq (150+ members and growing!)
Twitter: https://twitter.com/98mux  (Updates and changelogs!)
Reddit: https://www.reddit.com/r/poxi/ (Very new, help me kickstart this!)

Create your own corner of the web: https://poxi.page
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Polestar-Tuned Polestar 2 is the best Polestar]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897425</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897425"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T08:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The chassis department just couldn’t help itself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Instant Writer — Get help on your writing instantly by the No1 AI writer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/my-instant-writer</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/my-instant-writer"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T08:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://www.myinstantwriter.com/... an app which uses GPT-3 to help with any type of writing tasks, the whole goal initially was to get a lot of my writing task done instantly to make more time to code and build software. Then I found myself introducing it to some friends and colleagues at work and they started using it for things I didn't intend to use for, like as a starting point to some writing assignment, to aid with writers block, hell in applying for jobs, to write cover letters, important outlines of a topic, quick read on the most important aspects of a topic, I quickly launched a MVP which currently soared to over 35 users in just two weeks and users converting to the premium plan which gives access to up to 2000 word count!! Give it a try, you won't regret it, and please let me know what you think.🤞🏾


Going through any issues comment or email at support@myinstantwriter.com
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JUnit Cómo parametrizar un test]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gekyzo/junit-como-ejecutar-un-test-con-parametros-4cp3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gekyzo/junit-como-ejecutar-un-test-con-parametros-4cp3"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JUnit cuenta con una serie de funcionalidades orientadas a ejecutar tests en nuestra aplicación. 
tests parametrizados, que nos permiten poder declarar los valores que necesitemos fuera del propio test.
Para entender su funcionamiento supongamos que nuestra aplicación cuenta con un validador de códigos bancarios IBAN, que comprueba si un valor determinado cumple el patrón esperado en dichos códigos.
Los códigos IBAN utilizados en esta publicación han sido generados mediante la web http://randomiban.com/?country=Spain
class IbanValidator {
    // Regex pattern that an Iban must match
    static final String PATTERN = "^ES[0-9]{2}[0-9]{20}$";

    boolean isValid(String iban) {
        return iban.matches(PATTERN);
    }    
}

Ahora supongamos que tenemos un test sobre esta clase con la sig…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ciro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 metrics to track in your open source community]]></title>
        <id>70298 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/community-metrics"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[5 metrics to track in your open source community
Georg Link
Mon, 11/14/2022 - 03:00

            
The core of open source is about using, sharing, and collaborating in software creation. With its roots in the free software movement and ensuring the rights of software users, open source has evolved from being solely the work of volunteers and hobbyists to also include the enterprise.
Collaborative software development has taken on a new dimension in the last 5 to 10 years. Today open source makes up 58% of software in the enterprise. In fact, 63% of companies in a 2021 survey indicated wanting to increase their use and engagement with open source.
Open source is everywhere and forms the digital infrastructure we rely on. The US issued a directive mandating more software supply chain securit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Georg Link</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make swap better with zram on Linux]]></title>
        <id>70277 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/customize-zram-linux"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Make swap better with zram on Linux
David Both
Mon, 11/14/2022 - 03:00

            
Zram is a compressed RAM disk on Linux. Lately, it's been put to use for swap space on many distributions. In my previous article, I introduced zram and demonstrated how to use it. In this article, I cover some of the ways you can customize how your system puts zram to use.
Augmented swap
Zram swap can be augmented with standard secondary storage devices. Adding some traditional swap space can be especially useful on systems with low amounts of RAM. (Such augmentation isn't normally useful on hosts with very large amounts of RAM.)
If you do choose to augment swap with some type of storage device, hard drives do still work but are significantly slower than using SSD in either SATA or m.2 formats. However, t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Both</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Top MacBook Apps for College Students]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stephanreynolds/8-top-macbook-apps-for-college-students-591a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stephanreynolds/8-top-macbook-apps-for-college-students-591a"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T07:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technological advancements have eased human life to a great extent. The digital trend has also ruled over the academic world. If you love digital classrooms and want to enjoy that engaging environment all the time, use top MacBook apps for college students.
Developers have introduced several MacBook applications to help college students easily keep up with their studies. Here are some of the widely used apps that make college life more productive, organized, and painless.
1. Organizer Apps
You can organize everything without losing scraps with assignments and papers. iStudiez Pro is a potential organizer app designed specifically for students. It allows tracking assignments, class schedules, essay deadlines, grades, exam dates, and everything.
2. Utility & Uninstaller Apps
You can add and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephan Reynolds ✪</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500+ Tailwind UI Components, Templates, and UI Kit (Free and Premium)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tailwindcss/tailwind-components-templates-ui-kit-20lp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tailwindcss/tailwind-components-templates-ui-kit-20lp"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T07:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are looking for a complete Tailwind CSS UI Library with all essential UI Components, Sections and Templates - this is where TailGrids steps in.
TailGrids is a Tailwind CSS UI Component library specially crafted for Web Apps, Marketing, E-Commerce, and Dashboard Web Interfaces.
The goal of creating this library is to provide you with all Readymade Tailwind CSS UI Components, Blocks, Sections, and Web Templates to make your web development lifecycle more efficient with Tailwind CSS. We are giving you 500+ free, premium, and multifunctional Tailwind UI components. 




All the UI components will help you build a customized website. TailGrids packed with the interfaces you need for your custom websites, such as data-rich dashboards, e-commerce shops, web app user interfaces, high-conver…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TailGrids</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 Google Ads Extensions for Shopify Stores]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gloriamaldonado/top-5-google-ads-extensions-for-shopify-stores-534h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gloriamaldonado/top-5-google-ads-extensions-for-shopify-stores-534h"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T07:49:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you utilize Google Ads for your Shopify store, you should unlock its full potential as an important marketing strategy. Starting off by understanding what Google Ads extensions provide would serve as a great way to help you along the way.
Coming up with quality ads always adds to your overall quality as a Shopify store owner. It’s not enough to create good ads and improve your website so that you can improve the user experience, however. You should make sure that you provide extra information to help users.
That’s where the Google Ads extensions come into play. 
Google Ads Extensions are add-ons that let you increase the space your ads cover on Google searches. With these extensions, you can improve the effectiveness of your ads by providing more detailed information on your products. 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloria Maldonado ✪</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Superpage — Design any Saas using single kit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/superpage-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/superpage-2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T07:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Header Image Invisible due to Zero Height after Update to 6.1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ingosteinke/wordpress-header-image-invisible-due-to-zero-height-after-update-to-61-3m10</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ingosteinke/wordpress-header-image-invisible-due-to-zero-height-after-update-to-61-3m10"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T07:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After my customer's web hoster updated WordPress from 6.0.2 to 6.1, the responsive hero header images were not visible anymore. Comparing the HTML source code and CSS styles, we found the problem and the solution.
After I posted the problem on StackOverflow, unsurprisingly, apart from the obvious and correct suggestion to ask it on wordpress.stackexchange.com, instead of answers it attracted downvotes without any further comments, so I realized DEV, as a more helpful and inclusive community, might be a better place to share our insights. 
Our hero header images were no longer visible in a full-site-editing enabled block theme (originally based on Block Base) as their computed height changed zero pixels.
Changing the style from height: 100% to height: auto made the images appear again, but …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ingo Steinke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next 13 - Data fetching]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dailydevtips1/next-13-data-fetching-13eb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dailydevtips1/next-13-data-fetching-13eb"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T06:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data fetching is nothing new in Next, but they simplified how this works.
You might remember getServerSideProps and getStaticProps from the previous React versions. Those are no longer needed. In return, we get one uniform way of fetching data!
The recommended way of fetching data is using server components, as discussed in the previous article.
According to the docs, there are a lot of benefits from fetching from server components:
Access to backend services like database and API that don't run on the client
Keep your secure keys on the server so they don't leak to the client
Fetch and render in the same environment
Caching your renders on the server
Send less JavaScript to bundle
One important note is that they recommend you refetch data over passing it down.
They changed to use the fetch Web API, which is fantastic. It's a super powerful API, so happy to see this choice.
Fetch will always return a promise so we can await the result; by default, it's a cached request/results.
Let's show you an example.
In our component, we can create a data fetching function that would look like this.
async function getData() {
  const res = await fetch('https://jsonplaceholder.typicode.com/todos');

  return res.json();
}

Our component itself can then use this function like this.
export default async function AccountPage() {
  const table = await getData();

  return (
    <ul>
      {table.map((todo) => (
        <li key={todo.id}>{todo.title}</li>
      ))}
    </ul>
  );
}

And yep, that's it, simple.
It's also a great abstraction to move towards a unique concern architecture by simply making the components as small and self-sufficient as possible.
We also get many options around the fetch API that we can leverage, but it might be best to review them once we need them.
Thank you for reading my blog. Feel free to subscribe to my email newsletter and connect on Facebook or Twitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bongers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023 年将至，该如何优雅地记录看过的书籍和电影]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76786</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76786"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T06:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2014 年，那时候我还在读大三，某一天突然萌发了一个想法，要将自己看过的书和电影记录下来。我隐隐约约感受到，沉淀自己的精神生活，竟然让我觉得人生充满意义。记录的瞬间让我觉得会有成就感；等哪天，拿起这份清单，我可以清楚回顾某段时间内看过了哪些书籍和电影，也从侧面知晓当时精神生活的丰富程度
从那时起，我的记录习惯从未断绝过，不知不觉已经 8 年。从最初的用豆瓣记录，到使用纯文本 Markdown 记录，到自己搭建博客，再到使用公众号留言自动生成博客的方式记录。有些方式比较 Geek，不适合普通人，直到去年，我开发了一款 App，来满足跟我有同样需求的普通用户
这就是「已阅：书影记录」，一款快速记录自己看过的书籍和电影的 App，并支持将精美的观影列表和书单海报一键分享给朋友。献给所有希望构建自己精神角落的人

细数曾经那些不够好用的工具
为什么要开发「已阅：书影记录」呢？我综合对比了市面上多款工具，发现如果想要记录自己看过的书籍或电影，使用的方式不外乎以下几类
Excel
这是一类以 Excel 为代表的纯手动记录工具，除了 Excel 还包括在线文档、Notion 甚至是手写到自己的笔记本等
这个方式无疑费时费力，且数据是死的，很难被二次利用（如灵活筛选、统计、分享等）
让人惊讶的是，用这个方式记录的人还真不少，毕竟大部分人找不到更好的办法
豆瓣
豆瓣很伟大，是中文互联网上最全面的书影音资料库。功能上非常丰富，但是正因为它太全了，很难在这个垂直功能上做到极致

豆瓣记录的步骤比较麻烦，且默认会被分享到公共领域，下图是豆瓣和已阅的记录界面对比

 
「豆瓣」和「已阅」的记录界面对比
无法快速回顾，比如我想查看 2022 年看过了哪些书或我看过的所有五星电影，豆瓣都无法支持
「已阅」可以方便地筛选
分享功能缺乏自定义，比如我想自定义分享 2022 年看过了哪些书或我看过的所有五…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>伊塔奇呀</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🤖 Brand New Engineering Jobs - Week #46 of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shman/brand-new-engineering-jobs-week-46-of-2022-4c5d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shman/brand-new-engineering-jobs-week-46-of-2022-4c5d"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T05:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey,
remote engineering jobs to help you find your next remote position.
Today, I have 16 of 2931 new jobs I want to share with you. Check out all our new jobs from companies like Prime21 AG, FitXR, Jobheron, Bally‘s Interactive, inFORM GmbH, Applied Blockchain Ltd, Banked, inoSYSTEMS GmbH, Planet, Client Server, Strategic Agenda, Techem Energy Services GmbH, Cera, baramundi software AG, Binance, Hireful Agency and more below! 👇
Let's dive in.
Security Engineer @ Prime21 AG
Senior Unity Developer @ FitXR
Software Engineer @ Jobheron
Data Engineer @ Bally‘s Interactive
Informatiker/In, Java @ inFORM GmbH
Senior Full Stack Developer @ Applied Blockchain Ltd
Back End Engineer @ Banked
Cloud @ inoSYSTEMS GmbH
Learning Engineer @ Planet
Software Developer @ Client Server
Senior Full Stack Developer @ Strategic Agenda
DevOps Engineer @ Techem Energy Services GmbH
Senior Data Analyst @ Cera
IoT @ baramundi software AG
Java Engineer @ Binance
Senior .Net Developer @ Hireful Agency
Check all 2931 new engineering jobs. You can find the original post here: 🤖 Brand New Engineering Jobs - Week #46 of 2022.
I also share new jobs on our Twitter: @remoteindexco
By the way, do you have any feedback for me? Feature requests? Companies I should add? I built Remote Index for remote workers like you (and me), so I want to hear what can be improved.
You can reach me on Twitter @shmannet at any time.
Many thanks 🙂
Kamil]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kamil Kwiecien</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to become a 10X developer 😝]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hb1998/how-to-become-a-10x-developer-23og</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hb1998/how-to-become-a-10x-developer-23og"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T05:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Okay! the title is not fully a click bait, Hear me out. 
I'll be discussing about what tools and techniques i use to improve my efficiency as a developer, which may not have made me a 10X engineer but surely did improve my productivity.

by far the most effective technique you can do to improve your speed is reducing your reliance on the mouse when coding. No matter how fast you are with the mouse, the constant switch between mouse and keyboard not only slows you down but also makes you more fatigued. I also learned touch typing very recently and however not much it did help me with my keyboard mastery. I would say knowing what to type is more important than how fast you type. 
check out this article where it claims we can save a month of our lifetime by using keyboard shortcuts instead of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Habeebur Rahman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slazzer 3.0 — Remove image background automatically]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/slazzer-3-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/slazzer-3-0"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T04:57:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[影深 – 让 Firefox 变成小说阅读器，为 .TXT 文件自动生成目录、识别标题、主题样式。效果非常赞，书虫必备]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43899</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/yingshen-for-firefox/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T04:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[影深是一个开源的 Firefox 扩展，它能在打开 .txt 文本文件时自动生成目录、识别标题，并可以修改主题样式、字体大小，让 Firefox 瞬间变成小说阅读器，效果非常赞。@Appinn 来自发]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mailtap — The best way to convert networking to actionable emails]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/mailtap</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/mailtap"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T04:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@daniel_bolus and I came up with when we were riffing on different ideas. We thought it would be cool to have a simple QR Code generator that lets you start an email exchange with someone by instantly opening up an email with a greeting and your address populated. 

We thought this was a huge time saver to exchange information as well as a way to keep the conversation going with your new connection! We added text messaging and LinkedIn options as well.

Let us know what you think!

Bilal
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Action Cable with React and Rails.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/f53/using-action-cable-with-react-and-rails-2o9f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/f53/using-action-cable-with-react-and-rails-2o9f"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T04:13:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro


Earlier this week I wanted to use Action Cable for its nice two way connections. I ended up crying trying to understand the documentation as there is no good examples for implementing it anywhere.
Even worse, there are absolutely no tutorials for using it with React.
I wrote this guide to try and fill that void.
This Guide assumes you:
already have a functioning app with React on top of Rails.
have a User table that:


stores logged in user_id inside session[:user_id]







If you dont have any of that, consider starting with my react rails template
For a finished project that implements this tutorial, look at my react rails chat app, which is built off of that template.
Action Cable requires you to use postgresql.
If you dont have an rails app yet, follow this guide fully
If you …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>F53</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[通过反序列化利用JDBC后门]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11837</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11837"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T02:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[通过反序列化利用JDBC后门]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[13 个从头开始构建的独立 Linux 发行版]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15251-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15251-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T01:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[时至今日，世界上已经有成百上千种不同的 Linux 发行版。

它们中的大多数都可以被划归为三个大类 : Debian、Red Hat（Fedora）以及 Arch Linux。

使用基于 Debian/Ubuntu、Red Hat/SUSE 或者 Arch 的 Linux 发行版自然有它们的优势。它们很受大众欢迎，因此它们的包管理器能够提供大量的软件包。

然而，有一些用户更倾向于使用从头开始构建、独立于 DEB/RPM 这类包管理系统之外的发行版。

在这篇文章当中，我们将列出一些优秀的独立 Linux 发行版。


注意 : 显然，下面的列表显然不会包括一些广受欢迎，通常作为创建新发行版的基础的发行版，如 Debian、Ubuntu 和 Fedora 等。此外，列表顺序不分先后，没有特定的排名。


1、NixOS



NixOS 最初发布于 2003 年，NixOS 建立在 Nix 包管理器之上。它每年发布两个版本，通常是在 5 月和 11 月。

NixOS 可能不是一个直接面向新用户或普通用户的发行版。然而，其独特的 包管理 方法吸引了各种用户。

此外，它仍然支持 32 位系统。

其他特性：


构建隔离的包

可靠的升级，并且具有回滚功能

可重现的系统配置



NixOS


2、Gentoo Linux



Geetoo Linux 是一个主要针对操作系统专家的独立 Linux 发行版。它是为那些希望自由定制、微调和优化操作系统以满足其要求的用户而构建。

Gentoo 使用 Portage 包管理器 来创建和安装软件包，通常还允许你针对你的硬件来优化它们。Chrome 的开源版本 Chromium OS 便是使用 Gentoo 作为其核心的。

不要忘记，Gentoo 是 仍然支持 32 位…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[如何提高 Ubuntu 和其他 Linux 系统中的扬声器音量]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15250-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15250-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T00:24:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[以下是如何在 Ubuntu 和其他 Linux 发行版中提高笔记本和桌面的音量的方法。


你有没有觉得你的 Ubuntu 笔记本的音量太小，尽管你把音量调到了 100%？我相信你有过。主要原因是：很明显，笔记本电脑的扬声器输出强度比大型扬声器要低。

此外，Ubuntu 和其他发行版将默认的最大音量设置为 100%，也就是 0dB（分贝）。0dB 是最大音量的参考值。做个比较，如果你把音量设置为 -10dB，这意味着你的音量比最大的 0dB 安静。

VLC 和一些媒体播放器允许你将音量提高到 200%。在最新的 Ubuntu 中使用一些设置，你可以将音量进一步提高。


注意：在你尝试和使用以下方法之前，请记住，每个扬声器都有其制造商设定的硬件限制。偶尔一次，播放超过 100% 的音频是可以的。但是，连续放大到更高的分贝可能会使输出的音频失真，并且从长远来看可能会损坏你的扬声器。因此，在使用时要小心谨慎，并有所限制。


在 Ubuntu 和其他发行版中提高扬声器音量

对于最新的 Ubuntu 22.04 及以上版本（GNOME）

从应用菜单中打开“设置Settings”，进入“声音Sound”标签。

启用 “过度放大Over Amplification” 开关。在你启用的那一刻，你应该看到音量条被扩大了。



现在你可以享受音量提升来听音乐了。

Fedora、Arch Linux 和其他发行版

如果你使用带有 GNOME 的 Fedora 工作站，你将看不到上述选项，因为这是 Ubuntu 特有的设置。见下面。



因此，对于任何其他 Linux 发行版（Arch、Fedora、RedHat 等）或桌面（KDE、Xfce、LXQt 等），打开终端并安装 PulseAudio 音量控制器。

Fedora、RedHat Linux、OpenSUSE 等基于 RPM 的发行版：

sudo dnf install pavucontrol


对于 Arch Linux、Manjaro：

sudo pacman -S pavucontrol


基于 Ubuntu 的非 GNOME 发行版：

sudo apt install pavucontrol


如何使用

安装后，从应用菜单中打开 pavucontrol，它应该有个 &ldquoulseAudio Volume Control” 菜单项。



总结

记住，上述方法可以提高整个系统的扬声器音量。这意味着系统的声音和警报也会受到影响。所以，要记住这一点。正如我前面提到的，如果连续使用，提升扬声器音量超过 100% 可能会导致扬声器变形或损坏。

我希望这个教程能帮助你提高系统音量。如果你遇到问题，请在评论栏里告诉我。


via: https://www.debugpoint.com/boost-speaker-volume-ubuntu/

作者：Arindam 选题：lkxed 译者：geekpi 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hunt for the FTX Thieves Has Begun]]></title>
        <id>6371149f0dce9984f0039c8b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ftx-hack-theft-crypto-tracing/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T23:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious crooks took hundreds of millions of dollars from FTX just as it collapsed. Crypto-tracing blockchain analysis may provide an answer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hunt for the FTX Thieves Has Begun]]></title>
        <id>6371149f0dce9984f0039c8b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ftx-hack-theft-crypto-tracing/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T23:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious crooks took hundreds of millions of dollars from FTX just as it collapsed. Crypto-tracing blockchain analysis may provide an answer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Electric doesn’t mean boring—Porsche’s EV future includes plenty of power]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897439</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897439"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T23:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We look at the new Macan platform and ride in a 1088-hp electric race car.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Space Force’s X-37B spaceplane returns to Earth after over two years in space]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/13/23456718/space-force-x-37b-spaceplane-returns-two-years-falconsat-8</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/13/23456718/space-force-x-37b-spaceplane-returns-two-years-falconsat-8"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T22:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The X-37B came back to Earth on November 12th at 5:22AM ET. | Image: Space Force
    

  
The Space Force’s mysterious X-37B spaceplane landed back on Earth after spending a record-breaking two and a half years (908 days) in orbit. It landed at NASA’s Kennedy Space Center in Florida on Saturday, November 12th at 5:22AM ET, marking its sixth successful mission so far.
While the agency is pretty tight-lipped as to what exactly the Boeing-built spaceplane does, it did reveal that it deployed the FalconSat-8 developed by the US Air Force Academy in October 2021. This small satellite carried five experimental payloads and is still in orbit now. It hosted the Naval Research Laboratory’s photovoltaic radiofrequency antenna module as well, which is designed to convert solar rays into microwave energy and “transmit power to the...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overlap 2.0 — Time zones made simple]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/overlap-2-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/overlap-2-0"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T22:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Layout
The updated layout makes reading all your locations and times easier. The time for collapsed locations now remains visible, and the whole location shifts color to indicate availability as you scrub through time. Adding a new location, choosing a date, and seeing the overlap graph have all been moved to buttons across the bottom of the screen.


Overlap Graph
The graph has a new look and animation


Themes
Three new themes have been added.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRYO — Try on 500+ lifelike products using augmented reality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tryo</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tryo"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T21:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter reportedly cut thousands of contractors without warning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/13/23456554/twitter-reportedly-cut-thousands-contractors-without-warning-layoffs-elon-musk</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/13/23456554/twitter-reportedly-cut-thousands-contractors-without-warning-layoffs-elon-musk"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T21:08:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Illustration by Alex Castro / The Verge
    

  
Twitter eliminated a large number of contract employees on Saturday, affecting anywhere from 4,400 to 5,500 workers, according to Platformer’s Casey Newton. As noted by Platformer and confirmed by other reports from Axios and CNBC, most contract employees didn’t receive any notice that they’ve been terminated and only found out after losing access to the company’s email and internal communications systems.
The job cuts follow layoffs that culled about half of Twitter’s workforce and slashed 15 percent of its trust and safety team. Platformer first reported about the mass firings on Saturday night, which span both US-based and global employees working in content moderation, real estate, marketing, engineering, and other departments.
T...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yavaca — Quit working during your time off]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/yavaca</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/yavaca"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T20:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yavaca gives COWORKERS a path forward with their work via a self-service tool that provides clarity into workarounds and alternatives while you are OOO.

✌️Yavaca gives YOU peace of mind knowing that you can unplug while taking time off with minimal disruption to your coworkers and in-progress projects.

😸Yavaca gives YOUR LOVED ONES happiness and connection since you can be fully present and engaged during your time off with them.

With the holidays approaching, I invite you to try Yavaca during your upcoming time off. 

And I double dog dare you to fully unplug while you’re out. Can you do it? 🐶
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tech Landscape — Trending tech products newsletter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tech-landscape</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tech-landscape"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T19:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RepliQ — 1 video + 1 csv = 1000's of videos that drive more leads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/repliq</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/repliq"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T18:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Fix your companies. Or Congress will,’ Senator Ed Markey warns Elon Musk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/13/23456230/elon-musk-senator-ed-markey-fix-your-companies-congress-will-twitter-warning</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/13/23456230/elon-musk-senator-ed-markey-fix-your-companies-congress-will-twitter-warning"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T18:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Illustration by Lille Allen / The Verge
    

  
Senator Ed Markey (D-MA) told Elon Musk, “Fix your companies. Or Congress will,” after Musk snarkily replied to the senator’s concerns about fake verified accounts on Twitter, and suggested Markey’s real account “sounds like a parody.”
On Friday, Markey sent out a tweet containing a link to a letter he wrote to Musk, criticizing the new $7.99 per month Blue with verification subscription. The letter cites a report from the Washington Post that details how a reporter was able to easily create a fake verified account impersonating Markey and calls on Musk to address the issue. “Twitter must explain how this happened and how to prevent it from happening again,” Markey writes.


One of your companies is under an FTC consent decree. Auto...

  
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[InstaWP — Supercharge your WordPress development workflow in seconds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/instawp</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/instawp"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto.com sent $400 million to the wrong recipient, but got it back this time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/13/23456044/crypto-dot-com-accidentally-sent-400-million-wrong-recipent-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/13/23456044/crypto-dot-com-accidentally-sent-400-million-wrong-recipent-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T16:26:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Illustration by Alex Castro / The Verge
    

  
Crypto.com just admitted to making another very large and concerning clerical error: it mistakenly sent 320,000 in Ethereum (~$416 million USD) to another cryptocurrency exchange, called Gate.io, about three weeks ago (via Web3 Is Going Just Great). In a post on Twitter, Crypto.com CEO Kris Marszalek says the company was supposed to send the crypto to one of its cold, or offline, wallets, but accidentally sent it to a “whitelisted” address belonging to its corporate account at Gate.io. 
This all unfolded after Marszalek publicly posted the company’s cold wallet addresses to provide transparency about what the exchange does with its funds. After digging into Crypto.com’s transactions, one user, Conor Grogan, points out that the exchange...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcastpage.io — No-code website builder for podcast, audio & video creators]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/podcastpage-io-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/podcastpage-io-2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T15:16:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Best USB-C Cables (2022): For iPhones, Android Phones, Tablets, and Laptops]]></title>
        <id>62b97bc32944b6cfb7625f47</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-usb-c-cables/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unravel the tangled world of cords and find the ones you need to charge your gadgets and transfer data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simon Hill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Best TV Streaming Devices for 2022 (4K, HD): Roku vs. Fire TV vs. Apple TV vs. Google]]></title>
        <id>5aeb210a4eef286ed17e4266</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-4k-streaming-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've tested dozens of ways to watch stuff on 4K or HD TVs. These are our favorites.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Medea Giordano, Jeffrey Van Camp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Formerly Incarcerated Job Seekers Need More Than Training]]></title>
        <id>6356aaa7e53b9bdcb463c5e9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/employment-prison-jobs-digital-reputation/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reentry programs help, but tech companies must also modify their hiring systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Lageson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three-Way Entanglement Results Hint at Better Quantum Codes]]></title>
        <id>63694685d7f2f1953e687022</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/three-way-entanglement-results-hint-at-better-quantum-codes/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A team of physicists has entangled three photons over a considerable distance, which could lead to more powerful quantum cryptography.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Parshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open source Directory Sync (by BoxyHQ) — Real-time sync with your customers' user directories]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/open-source-directory-sync-by-boxyhq</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/open-source-directory-sync-by-boxyhq"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T12:33:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Anker MagGo Charger Defeated My Battery Anxiety]]></title>
        <id>636ecdfbc7672aac035d7a34</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/anker-maggo-charger-rave/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anker’s iPhone MagSafe accessories may look like power packs, but they are actually little bundles of life-changing joy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Speight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I'm Obsessed With Bloody Marys. This Is the Best Mix I've Tried]]></title>
        <id>635185da3363e916e706cdcc</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/haand-toma-bloody-mary-kit-rave/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You don't have to say a ghost's name three times in the mirror. The Haand x Toma Brunch Kit makes bloody brunches easy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Medea Giordano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For many disabled patients, the doctor is often not in]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897136</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897136"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T11:16:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some doctors avoid patients with disabilities, and barriers to routine care abound.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Undark Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #819 大众汽车制造了一辆时速 20 公里的《星际迷航》船长椅]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15249-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15249-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T09:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[大众汽车制造了一辆时速 20 公里的《星际迷航》船长椅

挪威大众汽车公司声称已经制造了一把办公椅，它不仅看起来配得上《星际迷航》中的船长，而且还能用自己的五个轮子在办公室里行驶，速度高达每小时 20 公里。它的可更换电池可以行驶 12 公里。而且，它还有很多装备：360 度防撞传感器、“倒车”摄像头、带加热的刺绣座椅、派对灯、触摸屏显示器、USB 充电器、口袋式的“后备箱”，甚至还有拖车。


消息来源：The Verge



老王点评：也许只是营销噱头，如果是真的，就可以买来在办公室开车了~




苹果自带的应用无视用户隐私设置

有专家发现苹果应用商店向该公司发送用户在应用中的几乎所有信息，尽管 iPhone 的隐私设置声称在关闭时 “完全禁用设备分析的共享”。研究人员发现，这个问题在苹果的大部分内置 iPhone 应用套件中都存在。测试发现，苹果在收到这些数据的同时，还能识别你和你的设备，包括 ID、手机类型、联网方式等等。有用户已经于周四在加州联邦法院提起集体诉讼。


消息来源：Gizmodo



老王点评：果然规矩都是给别人定的。




谷歌继续资助 GlobalFoundries 提供开源芯片免费制造服务

谷歌资助 GlobalFoundries，为开源项目开放了资源并承担了费用，在 130 纳米工艺上制造其早期芯片，并计划将升级到 90 纳米工艺。他们已经为 350 个独特的芯片设计提供了实现，其中约 240 个得以成功制造。


消息来源：phoronix



老王点评：这才是气魄啊。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[求将照片转为「手绘头像」的应用]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43895</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/photo-to-hand-painted/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T09:06:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[来自问题频道的问题：有没有一款将照片转为手绘头像的应用啊？免费的 @Good 同学推荐了下面这款应用： 波波头像 不要嫌弃，免费版应用也需要生存之道，波波头像有广告、需要联网使用，支持多种风格： 注意]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notificationpro — Convert your visitors into customers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/notificationpro</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/notificationpro"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T08:31:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://notificationpro.simplef.net
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agency Hunt — 300+ resources with templates on ClickUp to build an agency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/agency-hunt</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/agency-hunt"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T08:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use a hashmap in Java]]></title>
        <id>70310 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/hashmap-java"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use a hashmap in Java
Seth Kenlon
Sun, 11/13/2022 - 03:00

            
In the Java programming language, a hashmap is a list of associated values. Java uses hashmaps to store data. If you keep a lot of structured data, it's useful to know the various retrieval methods available.

More on Java
What is enterprise Java programming?
An open source alternative to Oracle JDK
Java cheat sheet
Red Hat build of OpenJDK
Free online course: Developing cloud-native applications with microservices
Fresh Java articles
Create a hashmap
Create a hashmap in Java by importing and using the HashMap class. When you create a hashmap, you must define what constitutes a valid value (such as Integer or String). A hashmap holds pairs of values.
package com.opensource.example;
import java.util.HashMap;
public clas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Kenlon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VIA.DELIVERY — Buy online pickup anywhere for online stores & D2C brands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/via-delivery-3</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/via-delivery-3"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T07:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://via.delivery/demo

And this Friday, we finally went live on one massive online retailer. Perry Ellis international. You can now test it on: 

https://www.perryellis.com
https://www.cubavera.com
https://www.originalpenguin.com
and others.

I have never seen so many orders going through the platform. Online shoppers choose it nationwide, with California, Texas, New York, Illinois, and Washington in the lead. Mostly urban and suburban areas.
Testing it on smaller retailers, we know that the NPS score is 75-80, while other carriers usually have 30-40 ish.

Read more on:
https://risnews.com/perry-ellis-...

https://via.delivery/press_about_us


I appreciate your feedback and Upvotes. 

And if you want to see this shipping option in other online stores, please mention them in the comments below (like XYZshop.com). That will help us to get there.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Send to Telegram for Google Chrome – 发送网页、图片、链接、文字到 tg 机器人]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43891</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/send-to-telegram-for-google-chrome/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T07:55:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Send to Telegram for Google Chrome 是一款简单易用的 Chrome 扩展，用来在浏览器上发送网页、图片、链接、文字到 tg 机器人。@Appinn 感谢 @S 同学在]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Common-Collections1 分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11835</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11835"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T07:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Common-Collections1 分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SocialBoat for Women — AI Powered fitness game for women]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/socialboat-for-women</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/socialboat-for-women"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T07:47:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@SocialBoat

Today we launch SocialBoat for Women. Motivation to create this came from my mom's (@seema_jain3) fitness journey. I have seen the hardwork and struggles she put in to get fit and how it essentially transformed her life. 

Some critical problems that I saw -
1. Lack of time 
My mom used to manage the home, and this essentially made her mornings and evenings very busy. Mid day is usually too hot to workout outside and fitness centers are usually closed at this time.

I would see her get up at 5am :sunny: everyday, to go for her quick 30 minute walk.

2. Lack of relevant programs 
My mom gained a lot of weight post her pregnancy, and she struggled to find any relevant programs to lose it. Most gyms had male oriented bulk up programs, and fitness classes were usually too intensive for her.

She started learning Yoga from a book, and then Pilates from YouTube videos. She tells me it took her 4 years to gain the confidence she had back in college.

3. Her New Program for women 
After her at home transformation, she learnt jazz and hip hop dance, performed at multiple venues around the country and recently started a fitness program for women called - Yogalates. An amalgamation of yoga, pilates and dance for women.

She takes classes on zoom and more than 100 women have joined her program.

Scaling up the concept 
Our goal with SocialBoat is to take some of these learnings and make high quality fitness accessible to >100M women around the country.

- A program one can follow from their home
- Is accessible anytime during the day
- Tailored to women specific needs
- Evolves with different life stages

Excited to see how people at ProductHunt find it. Please reach out to us if you have any questions or suggestions!

Thank you
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[我使用的 4 款开源编辑器]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15248-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15248-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T07:39:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[分享一些我最喜欢的开源写作工具。


在我的职业生涯中，我已经写过很多东西，主要是作为一名 IT 顾问，创建产品文档作为给的客户可交付成果。这些文档通常针对不同操作系统和软件产品提供说明。

自 2018 年，我开始在 www.opensource.com 上发表关于开源软件的文章。当然，我使用开源软件进行协作。接下来我将介绍我使用过的四款开源编辑器。

1、Vi

Vi 也被称为 Vim（LCTT 校注：此外不确，Vi 和 Vim 是两个软件，只是 Vim 取代了 Vi，并以 vi 的名字运行。），是我学习的第一款开源编辑器。这是我在计算机科学课程中学习的编辑器，并且我所有的 C 语言编程都是通过它完成的。自 1995 年以来，实际上我一直使用它作为命令行编辑器。这款工具有多个迭代版本，以至于我都可以为之写一系列文章了。我只想说，在我的日常使用中，我坚持使用它的基本命令行形式，并进行最小的定制。

2、LibreOffice Writer

Writer 是 LibreOffice 开源办公套件的一部分。它是由文档基金会Document Foundation维护的全功能文字处理器。它支持行业标准格式，例如开放文档格式 （ODF）、Open XML 和 MS Office DOC、DOCX。可以在其官方网站上 了解有关 Writer 的更多信息。

3、Ghostwriter

Ghostwriter 是一个用于 Markdown 的文本编辑器。它有一个很好的实时查看器和语法指南或备忘单功能。访问官方网站 了解更多内容。

4、Gedit

Gedit 是许多 Linux 发行版中的基本图形编辑器，被描述为“用于 GNOME 桌面的小型轻量级文本编辑器”。我最近开始使用它来创建 Asciidoc 格式的文章。使用 Asciidoc 的好处是语法易于管理并可导入到 Drupal 等 Web 渲染系统中。通过 Gedit Wiki 了解许多提示和技巧。

编辑文本

开源世界中有大量编辑软件。随着我继续写作，这个列表可能会增加。我的主要目标是格式简单。我希望我的文章易于在互联网平台上导入、转换和发布。

你的写作风格、功能需求和目标受众将指导你确定首选工具。


via: https://opensource.com/article/22/10/open-source-editors

作者：Alan Formy-Duval 选题：lkxed 译者：Donkey-Hao 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gumcrm — The CRM for Gumroad creators]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/gumcrm</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/gumcrm"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T07:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zeldata — The best all-in-one ERP for entrepreneurs and businesses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/zeldata</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/zeldata"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T05:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[如何从 Ubuntu 21.10 及以后版本中删除 Firefox Snap]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15247-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15247-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T03:25:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu 21.10 “Impish Indri” 及之后的版本将 Firefox Snap 设为默认浏览器。如果你不喜欢 Snap，可以通过以下方式将其删除并使用库存版本。


关于 Snap 是否是 APT 的更好替代品，一直存在争议。而许多用户更喜欢 Snap 系统，也有一些人非常讨厌它。Ubuntu 和 Canonical 认为它是 Linux 的最佳安装仓库和包管理工具之一。 Snap 被讨厌的主要原因是它的启动很慢。然而，这个论点是另一篇文章的内容。

从 Ubuntu 中删除 Firefox Snap 版本

所以，如果你还没有 听说过这件事，Ubuntu 21.10（和所有后续版本）默认提供 Firefox Snap 包。因此，当你从 Ubuntu 21.10 开始安装时，默认的左侧停靠区的快捷方式是 Firefox 的 Snap 版本。你可以使用以下各种方法对其进行验证。





如果你因为 性能 和存储问题而不喜欢 Snap，可以通过以下命令将其删除。

如果已经打开，那么关闭所有 Firefox 实例。

打开一个终端。然后运行以下命令：

sudo snap remove firefox


等待命令完成。这将从你的系统中删除它的 Snap 可执行文件，并断开 Firefox 与各种系统服务的连接。但是主目录下的 Snap 目录仍然存在。你可以使用以下命令手动删除它：

cd ~/snap
rm -r firefox


安装 Firefox 替代方法

现在，当你删除了 Firefox，你可以通过以下方式来使用此浏览器。

方法 1 – 使用 PPA（推荐）

在使用此方法之前，请确保如上删除了 Firefox 的 Snap 版本。

有一个 官方 Firefox PPA，由其开发团队维护。你可以将此 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[使用这个多功能的 Linux 命令转换音频文件]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15246-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15246-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T02:43:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SoX Sound Exchange 甚至可以为你的音频文件添加特效。




我工作需要使用音视频媒体，不管你处理哪种媒体，你肯定知道标准化是一种有价值的工具。就像你不会试图把一个分数加到一个小数上而不转换其中一个一样，我已经知道，把不同格式的媒体组合起来并不理想。为了方便用户，大多数爱好者级应用程序使转换过程不可见。然而，对于那些需要控制媒体细节的用户的灵活软件，会通常让你自己提前将媒体转换为所需的格式。我有一些最喜欢的音频转换工具，其中之一就是号称“音频的瑞士军刀” —— SoX。

安装

在 Linux 或 BSD 上，可以从软件存储库或 Ports 树中安装 sox 命令（，以及一些有用的符号链接）。

你也可以从 Sourceforge.net 上安装 SoX。它不经常发布，但它的代码库往往是稳定的，所以如果你想要最新的功能（如 Opus 支持），构建它是容易和安全的。

SoX 主要提供了 sox 命令，但是创建了一些有用的符号链接：play、rec 和 soxi。

使用 SoX 获取文件信息

SoX 可以读取和重写音频数据。它是否存储重写的音频数据取决于你。在有些情况下，你不需要存储转换后的数据，例如，当你将输出直接发送到扬声器进行回放时。然而，在进行任何转换之前，最好首先确定要处理的是什么。

使用 soxi 命令也可以收集音频文件信息。soxi 会符号链接到 soxi --info。

$ soxi countdown.mp3
Input File（输入文件）    : '/home/tux/countdown.mp3'
Channels（通道数）       : 1
Sample Rate（采样率）    : 44100
Precision（数据精度）      : 16-bit（16 比特）
Duration（时…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe Podcast — AI-powered audio recording and editing, all in the web]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/adobe-podcast</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/adobe-podcast"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T01:31:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Literal for Figma — Turn screen recordings into screenshots]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/literal-for-figma</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/literal-for-figma"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T01:13:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The weekend’s best deals: Buy two get one free video games, Razer Blade, Apple, GoPro and more]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1895882</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1895882"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T21:09:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We also have deals on streamers, laptops, our favorite smartwatch for the outdoors, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Gaskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cabana 6 Design System for Figma — Design system for Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/cabana-6-design-system-for-figma</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/cabana-6-design-system-for-figma"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T14:57:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wishbear — Personal wishlists for friends & family]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/wishbear</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/wishbear"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T14:23:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@tw__ recently got into programming and so we decided to build a small project together. It was important to us that it had a manageable scope but was still useful. So we agreed to build a wishlist app that let's you organize your wishes and share them with your friends and family.

There are already dozens of apps like this out there with similar features, but we found them incredibly frustrating and confusing to use, therefore our goal was to try and build an app that works better and has a more modern look.

Some highlights of the Wishbear 🐻 app:

- 👤 No registration required, starting to use the app is literally just a single click of a button. Your session will be stored in your browser but you can submit your email address at any time in order to access your wishlists on other devices.

- ✨ When you add a wish from a link to an online shop, the product details will be loaded for you automatically. That works for almost every shop out there, with a few exceptions that don't provide metadata or block our crawler.

- 🔐 Visitors of your wishlist can mark your wishes as reserved so that nothing is given away twice.

Give it a try, it's really easy to get started and we'd love to hear what you think!

Cheers,
Niklas & Thomas
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alexa Might Not Get Much Smarter Than It Is Right Now]]></title>
        <id>636e90efe20b7b4375263936</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/amazon-alexa-reportedly-losing-money/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: Apple pays for more emergency satellite tech, LG is working on a stretchy screen, and we answer all your burning questions about Mastodon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boone Ashworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Claim Your YouTube Handle]]></title>
        <id>6365678a1d1ddb0aa029e11b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-claim-youtube-handle-set-up/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way you identify yourself on the platform is changing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Nield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Introduces Twitter Mayhem Mode]]></title>
        <id>636e769e32968364ac1a7b69</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-twitter-security-mayhem-roundup/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: US midterms survive disinformation efforts, the government names the alleged Lockbit ransomware attacker, and the Powerball drawing hits a security snag.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruv Mehrotra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How “Wordle editor” became a real job at The New York Times]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897094</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897094"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T13:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduling the daily five-letter puzzle is more demanding than you might think.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16 Best Subscription Boxes to Gift (2022): Services We Love]]></title>
        <id>6183f2be936b3fd5e3e2de91</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-subscription-gift-boxes/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have options for plant lovers, foodies, pet owners, and even those who are hard to shop for with these gifts that keep on giving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Medea Giordano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York Voted to Protect the Planet. California Did Not]]></title>
        <id>6369461a7484c01b9b6e9656</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/new-york-voted-to-protect-the-planet-california-did-not/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voters in two influential states came to opposite conclusions on climate-related ballot measures to fund environmental protections and electric vehicles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jackie Flynn Mogensen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Never Have I Ever — Popular party game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/never-have-i-ever-5</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/never-have-i-ever-5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T12:55:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dung beetle moms protect their offspring from a warming world by digging deeper]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897112</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897112"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T12:44:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Climate change has forced dung beetles to modify their nesting behaviors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Conversation</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Dark ships” emerge from the shadow of the Nord Stream pipeline mystery]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897100</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897100"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T12:15:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Satellite monitors found 2 vessels with their trackers turned off in area of explosions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 Apple TV 4K review: HDR10+ rounds out an already excellent streaming box]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897225</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897225"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T12:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lower price makes this mostly unchanged device much more appealing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[13 Best Deals: Camera Bags and Sex Tech]]></title>
        <id>636d68f08480c23aec34bdf4</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/weekend-deals-november-12-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're hot on the heels of Black Friday, and the discounts are rolling in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gear Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now’s the Time to Snag L.L. Bean’s Classic Duck Boots]]></title>
        <id>636d0e481f24b6f9091f7b77</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/review-ll-bean-duck-boots/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even with all the modern advances in winter footwear, I love these 110-year-old L.L. Bean Duck Boots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Jancer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyXtools: Python + Hacking — Collection of hacking & python scripts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/pyxtools-python-hacking</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/pyxtools-python-hacking"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T11:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[innerchats – inner dialogues — Intuitive insightful self-talk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/innerchats-inner-dialogues</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/innerchats-inner-dialogues"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T09:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #818  Linux 帮助 Windows 11 支持旧打印机]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15245-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15245-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T08:22:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 帮助 Windows 11 支持旧打印机

也许你有一些古老的激光打印机或一体机，但是它们没有 Windows 11 驱动程序。而 Linux 在支持旧硬件方面明显更好，如果驱动程序仍然可以编译，它就不会被删除。现在你可以通过在 WSL 内运行的 OpenPrinting 中使用旧打印机进行打印。这之所以可以实现，还要感谢 WSL2 支持了 systemd，从而支持 Canonical 的 Snap 版的打印机应用。


消息来源：The Register



老王点评：没想到 WSL 还有这种好处！




DeviantArt 为作品添加 AI 许可标签

著名艺术网站 DeviantArt 推出了自己的 AI 艺术生成器 DreamUp。为了让艺术家控制他们的作品，DeviantArt 让他们可以选择该工具是否可以使用他们的风格作为直接灵感。并在不允许 AI 使用的作品页面添加特定的标签。DeviantArt 也鼓励其他创作者平台采用这种方法，以确保艺术家仍然能够与在线观众分享他们的作品。


消息来源：Engadget



老王点评：确实应该形成一种行业规范，或者新的许可证惯例。




一根普通光纤传输全球互联网流量

通过将 55 种模式的信号射入单芯光纤，该团队能够以每秒 1.53 Pbps 的数据速率进行传输。1Pbps 相当于 100 万 Gbps。据估计，整个全球互联网的带宽只有不到 1Pbps，这意味着这根光纤足够处理全球所有的互联网带宽。虽然这不是最快的传输速率，之前有日本研究机构达到了 1.84 Pbps 的速率，但这个纪录的意义在于，它是使用标准覆层直径为 0.125 毫米的光纤实现的，很大程度上与现有的基础设施兼容。


消息来源：Tom's Hardware



老王点评：带宽扩展的太快，说不准以后个人设备也需要几个 G 的带宽了。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Python: 7 of my favorite resources]]></title>
        <id>70285 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/learn-python"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Python: 7 of my favorite resources
Don Watkins
Sat, 11/12/2022 - 03:00

            
I made a decision recently that I wanted to learn more Python so I could improve my instructional skills and broaden the horizons of my students. In the process, I have discovered these excellent resources that have me learning new code and improving my understanding of Python in general.
1. Teach your kids to code
I began the Python journey about seven years ago when I discovered connections between Apple LOGO and the Turtle module in Python. The Linux computer I was using at the time defaulted to Python 2.7, and I soon discovered that I wanted to use Python 3. I managed to get it installed and began writing some simple programs using the Turtle module. After reading Dr. Bryson Payne’s Teach Your Ki…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Don Watkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[scalelogo — We make logos, differently]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/scalelogo</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/scalelogo"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T07:44:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Athlete Alone — Mental health for athletes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/no-athlete-alone</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/no-athlete-alone"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T06:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daylight — Capture special moments with your friends]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/daylight-82970dd4-9717-42fa-8747-c190288905e7</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/daylight-82970dd4-9717-42fa-8747-c190288905e7"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T06:39:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ballot — Decentralized onchain voting app on Stacks blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ballot</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ballot"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T06:26:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loot — Honey for SaaS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/loot-5</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/loot-5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T06:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FindMyPackage — The easiest all-in-one package tracker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/findmypackage</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/findmypackage"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T04:20:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[使用 GNOME Boxes 将虚拟机镜像移动到另一台主机]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15244-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15244-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T03:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[本指南介绍了使用 GNOME Boxes 将虚拟机镜像移动到另一台主机所需的步骤。


GNOME Boxes 是由 GNOME 项目创建的虚拟化程序。此程序用作 libvirt 的前端。libvirt 是用于管理平台虚拟化的开源 API、守护进程和管理工具。它支持不同的虚拟化技术，如 KVM、Xen、VMware ESXi、QEMU 等。

如果你想使用 GNOME Boxes 创建虚拟机，请参阅本指南。

在本教程中，我将解释如何将任何虚拟机镜像文件（已使用 GNOME Boxes 创建并运行）移动到不同的主机并运行它。

这样，你不再需要从操作系统重新安装虚拟机。此外，它是便携式的，你可以将虚拟机镜像放在 U 盘中。

如何使用 GNOME Boxes 将虚拟机镜像移动到另一台主机

我希望你已经在 GNOME Boxes 中创建了一个虚拟机。如果没有，请查看 本指南。

GNOME Boxes 和 libvert 使用以下目录存储虚拟机镜像和配置。如下所述，你需要仔细备份每个文件。

GNOME Boxes 将虚拟机的物理镜像（通常为数 GB 大小）保存在以下路径中。对于你的每个虚拟机，你都会在其中找到一个镜像。

~/.local/share/gnome-boxes/images/




将图像文件复制到新主机的路径：~/.local/share/gnome-boxes/images/。

将 libvirt 的 XML 配置从以下路径复制到新主机的相同位置。

~/.config/libvirt/qemu/




在上述路径中，你应该会看到每个虚拟机的单独 xml 文件。复制你需要的那个。

在你当前的系统中打开以下文件。

~/.config/gnome-boxes/sources/'QEMU Session'


复制属于你的虚拟机的部分（从 [display ... 到本部分的末尾）。你可以使用名称轻松找到它（看下面的 last-seen-name）。



在另一台主机上打开相同的上述文件并将复制的内容附加到末尾。保存文件。

关闭新主机中的所有应用，包括 GNOME Boxes。

现在打开 GNOME Boxes，你应该会看到你的虚拟机和它的内容一起被移动到新主机中。

你现在可以拥有一个可以轻松携带和移动的便携式虚拟机。请记住，目标机器应该安装了 GNOME Boxes 才能完成这项工作。


via: https://www.debugpoint.com/move-virtual-machine-image-another-host/

作者：Arindam 选题：lkxed 译者：geekpi 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lua 值得学习吗？]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15243-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15243-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T03:19:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lua 是一个有趣而强大的语言，随着各个版本的推进，功能愈发的强大，开发者群体也在不断的增长。这篇文章我们将探索一下它的各种前景。


Lua 是一个脚本语言，它面向过程、函数式编程，甚至可以是 面向对象的。它使用类 C 语言的语法，但却是动态类型，具有自动内存管理和垃圾回收功能，使用基于寄存器的虚拟机来解释字节码。这些特点使得它对于初学者来说是个很好的语言，同时也是经验丰富的程序员的强大工具。

虽然与 Python 和 JavaScript 相比，Lua 现在已经有点儿黯然失色了，但是 Lua 拥有的一些优点使得它在许多的重大软件项目中很受欢迎。Lua 很容易嵌入到其他语言当中， 这意味着你可以在（例如）Java 编写的代码中包含 Lua 文件，就像原生的 Java 代码一样运行。这听起来就像魔法一般，现在有许多项目如 luaj 使得其成为可能，之所以可以实现，正是因为 Lua 就是为此而设计的。部分出于这种灵活性，你可以在许多游戏、图形应用的程序中发现 Lua 脚本的身影。

就像其他任何事情一样，做到完美是需要时间的，但 Lua 是很易于学习（并且有趣）的语言。它是一种一致的语言、一种带有有用的错误消息的友好的语言，并且可以在网上轻松找到许多有用的资料。那么就让我们开始吧！

安装 Lua

在 Linux 下，你可以使用发行版自带的包管理来安装 Lua。例如，在 Fedora、CentOS、 Mageia、OpenMandriva 以及类似发行版中：

$ sudo dnf install lua


在 Debian 以及基于 Debian 的系统中：

$ sudo apt install lua


对于 Mac，你可以使用 MacPorts 或者 Homebrew：

$ sudo port install lua


对于 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon MK30 — The new design for Prime Air’s delivery drone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/amazon-mk30</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/amazon-mk30"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T02:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[in 7 years.

Like, has the USPS even launched a single drone delivery??
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artshop — Create AI art and make it your wall art]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/artshop</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/artshop"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T01:57:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quivr — Play Cupid and vote on someone's best match]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/quivr-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/quivr-2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T00:36:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[20 Best Early Black Friday Deals: Robot Vacuums, iPads, Instant Pots]]></title>
        <id>636e5fce5b833e6d21b64f74</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-early-black-friday-deals-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T00:22:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The big sale isn’t here quite yet, but you can already get killer deals on laptops, streaming sticks, tablets, and even Instant Pots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louryn Strampe, Gear Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BotCircuits — Build next-gen conversational apps without coding skills]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/botcircuits-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/botcircuits-2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T00:04:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Southeast US has hit the roof of CDC’s respiratory illness level scale]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897339</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897339"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T23:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uptake of flu shots is lagging this year, CDC says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LockBit ransomware suspect nabbed in Canada, faces charges in the US]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897321</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897321"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T23:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automation features make LockBit one of the more destructive pieces of ransomware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Control, one of ray tracing’s first killer apps, is getting a sequel]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897331</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897331"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T23:08:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of PC gaming's proudest new franchises is going big.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeviantArt upsets artists with its new AI art generator, DreamUp [Updated]]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897247</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897247"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T22:47:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Confused artists discover their work will be used for AI training by default.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jot — AI ad copy hub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/jot-12</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/jot-12"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T22:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA says its SLS rocket is good to go for a launch attempt next Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897239</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897239"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T22:28:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["If we didn’t design it to be out there in harsh weather we picked the wrong launch spot."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Airloupe — Client galleries for creators]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/airloupe</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/airloupe"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T21:56:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safe Solo — Stay safe by checking in]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/safe-solo</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/safe-solo"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T21:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future exists now: Bringing William Gibson’s The Peripheral to television]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1891572</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1891572"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T21:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ars chats with series producers Jonathan Nolan, Vincenzo Natali, and Scott Smith.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktoberfest 2022 Contributors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hacktoberfest-2022-contributors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hacktoberfest-2022-contributors/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T20:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp participated in Hacktoberfest (a month-long celebration of open source) again this year. We wanted to take a moment to thank all of our wonderful contributors for the effort they put in to help us continue to improve our curriculum and learning resources. Thank you for your contributions to open]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naomi Carrigan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk proposes turning Twitter into a bank to avoid bankruptcy]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897185</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897185"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T19:31:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musk aims to grow Twitter users by 1 billion, then link accounts to debit cards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Belanger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leica’s “Leitz Phone 2” has a giant 1-inch camera sensor, magnetic lens cap]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897062</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897062"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T19:16:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've got to rebrand an existing phone, the Aquos R7 is a good starting point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tovo — File management made simpler, cheaper & predictable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tovo</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tovo"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T18:56:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk’s Twitter chaos tosses outrageous insulin pricing into the spotlight]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897097</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897097"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T18:20:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fake pharma account ignited fury over insulin pricing by falsely saying it's now free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fallout of the FTX Collapse]]></title>
        <id>636e8d8e627a555fd99f22f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-fallout-of-the-ftx-collapse/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Sam Bankman-Fried's crypto empire crumbles, its customers, and other crypto traders, are paying the price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Khalili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Razer’s new wireless mouse has an exceptionally customizable scroll wheel]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897031</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897031"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T17:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's just hope the wheel's not too rattly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scharon Harding</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robots will roam a university to study “a socio-technical problem”]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1896911</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1896911"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T17:23:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robots will wander a Texas campus so researchers can study human-robot relations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JS Copy an Object – How to Clone an Obj in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/clone-an-object-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/clone-an-object-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T17:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A JavaScript object is a collection of key-value pairs. It is a non-primitive data type that can contain various data types. For example: const userDetails = {   name: "John Doe",   age: 14,   verified: false }; When working with objects in JavaScript, you may sometimes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surface Pro 9 teardown reveals modular parts, Microsoft’s 2023 repair plans]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897014</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897014"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T17:11:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft says it will offer parts, manuals, and retail repair in early 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Purdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Your Own Mastodon Instance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-your-own-mastodon-instance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-your-own-mastodon-instance/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T16:29:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastodon is a decentralized, federated social media platform based on the  ActivityPub [https://www.w3.org/TR/activitypub/] protocol. It allows you to follow and interact with friends across multiple instances.  In this article, you will learn how freeCodeCamp set up our own Mastodon instance - and how you can too. What is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naomi Carrigan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is YAML? The YML File Format]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-yaml-the-yml-file-format/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-yaml-the-yml-file-format/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T16:20:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YAML is one of the most popular languages for writing configuration files. In this article, you will learn how YAML compares to XML and JSON - two languages also used for creating configuration files. You will also learn some of the rules and features of the language, along with its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guidde — How-to videos made simple]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/guidde-video</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/guidde-video"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T15:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meal Kits Like Blue Apron Get My Picky Kids to Eat Real Food]]></title>
        <id>634ed8e904d20e5d7c550aed</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/blue-apron-rave/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you tearing your hair out trying to feed a family of picky eaters? Try a subscription service like Blue Apron.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrienne So</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Office Setup Guide: Webcams, Desks, Chairs, and More (2022)]]></title>
        <id>5e7d0a1471c756000932081e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/work-from-home-home-office-gear-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gear can make or break your home office setup. Here’s our ultimate list of nearly 100 items, from monitors and desks to webcams and chairs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian Chokkattu, Gear Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Tech’s Layoffs Will Fuel the Industry's Future]]></title>
        <id>636d36b20757f7d06dd271f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/plaintext-big-techs-layoffs-will-fuel-the-industrys-future/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: The dotcom recovery, a history-making online purchase, and the highway to climate hell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Problem With Spinning Spacecraft]]></title>
        <id>635bc62be53b9bdcb463c64a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-problem-with-spinning-spacecraft/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To send astronauts on long-term space missions, it’ll take rotating habitats to produce artificial gravity. But that’s trickier than you might think.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhett Allain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Columbia's Ski-Jacket Tech Is Going to the Moon]]></title>
        <id>636c3397f31adb902c7b824d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/columbia-jacket-tech-moon-lander/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the US returns to the lunar surface next year, the lander’s outer panels will be wrapped in the same reflective material that lines cold-weather parkas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Wolman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16 Best Wireless Earbuds (2022): Truly Wireless, Cheap, Luxe, and More]]></title>
        <id>5d3f2e4877f7410008d5316c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-wirefree-earbuds/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ready to cut the cord? These are our favorite buds that will never, ever get tangled.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Parker Hall, Jeffrey Van Camp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Despite Big Layoffs, Tech Workers Are Still in Demand]]></title>
        <id>636c1c5bab9086067e9f2688</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/despite-big-layoffs-meta-twitter-stripe-tech-workers-are-still-in-demand/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tens of thousands of job cuts have rocked the industry, but unemployment among tech workers remains low—and plenty of companies are desperate for talent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amanda Hoover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter Is on a Collision Course With Europe]]></title>
        <id>636d5c60ab9086067e9f268d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-europe-elon-musk/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Layoffs leave only two people in the company’s Brussels office, just as Europe prepares to enforce sweeping new tech rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Morgan Meaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Great Truffle Shortage Is Coming]]></title>
        <id>636d5dfba3291a07ef8cdbd7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/climate-change-truffle-hunting/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harvests of the fungi are plummeting as Europe gets drier, pushing the prices of some varieties to eye-watering heights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Baraniuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Dark Ships’ Emerge From the Shadows of the Nord Stream Mystery]]></title>
        <id>636d7ff21f24b6f9091f7b8f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/nord-stream-pipeline-explosion-dark-ships/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Satellite monitors discovered two vessels with their trackers turned off in the area of the pipeline prior to the suspected sabotage in September.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[在外独居，我想分享下我如何面对孤独]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76378</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76378"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T10:49:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[前言
在经历了成都连续的半个月高温居家办公，以及两周的疫情封控后，我思考了一下关于城市生活与孤独的关系，以及如何排解孤独，理解孤独。在这一个多月中，我一直是一个人在屋子里，未曾踏出家一步。我不是一个爱做饭柴米油盐的人，就这样，在家中面对着日复一日的琐事，面对没有人可以说话的孤独，面对着工作、生活的焦虑。在与安静和极度的自由的碰撞里，除了偶尔的空虚与崩溃以外，我想分享一下我如何逐渐的找回自己的生活节奏，并喜欢上一个人安排自己的方方面面。
孤独是什么

如果我们所期待的人际关系数量和质量与我们当前实际情形存在较大差距，就会产生令人不悦的厌烦、悲伤和绝望的孤独体验（de Jong Gierveld et al.，2006）。

孤独有两种：
其一是社会隔离，指缺少朋友和熟人的社交。
你或许也有这样的感受，常常用「社恐」来武装自己，鲜少与人交流。那怕是点个外卖、出门买个东西都是能不交流就不交流。性格内向的人更喜欢和自己交流，陶醉在自己所热爱的精神世界之中。在周末和假期，相比和朋友出去游玩他们更倾向于选择在家中折腾自己的爱好，渐渐的在和陌生人交往时变的畏惧，不知所措。久而久之，除了身边寥寥无几的挚友以外，几乎没有任何的交流，孤独感进一步加深。
其二是情感隔离，指缺少亲密而深厚的情感关系。
人生活在社会中，总是会渴望着被他人理解的。有的人虽然辗转于各种聚会，时时刻刻都沉浸在热闹场合之中，但是浮于表面的热闹并不总是意味着有人真正了解自己。可能你真正渴望的目标无人诉说，心中的艰苦无人知晓。理解就像是人生的底色，我们渴望着，但却不可能有人能完全理解自己。
孤独的危害
对于大部分人来说，长期保持孤独是有一定危害的。
在生理上，长期孤独的人血压更高，更容易发生应激反应。在晚上的时候孤独也会让人辗转反侧，不仅睡眠质量下降，免疫力也会随之一起走下坡路。
在生活中，孤独有时候也会带来不少的麻烦，比如因…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dluck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fintece — Organize & manage your finances in Notion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/fintece</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/fintece"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T09:49:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenCore Legacy Patcher – 为老款 Mac 电脑（2006 年以后）安装最新 macOS Ventura 13 操作系统]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43886</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/opencore-legacy-patcher/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T09:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenCore Legacy Patcher 是一个开源项目，用来让老款 Mac 电脑（2006 年以后）也能安装最新 macOS 操作系统。@Appinn 感谢 @蚁工厂 的推荐。 在苹果不久前发]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[jpress代码审计分享]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11832</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11832"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[jpress代码审计分享]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to switch from Twitter to Mastodon]]></title>
        <id>70312 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/switch-twitter-mastodon"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to switch from Twitter to Mastodon
Jessica Cherry
Fri, 11/11/2022 - 03:00

            
Like many people, I find social media somewhat exciting and also...a bit much. Sometimes you get deep-fried in algorithms, tracking data, and ads catered especially for you. You lack administrative control over what you want to see, especially on the old platforms many of us are used to. As usual, you must look to open source to fix the problem. And that's exactly what Mastodon, an open source microblogging community, does.
With Mastodon social, not only are you working with open source software, but everything is decentralized, which means you can pick what you want to see partly based on the instance you want to occupy. Mastodon uses separate instances, each with its own code of conduct, privacy o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Cherry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drop swap for zram on Linux]]></title>
        <id>70276 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/zram-swap-linux"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drop swap for zram on Linux
David Both
Fri, 11/11/2022 - 03:00

            
I spend a lot of time playing (I mean working) on my computers, and I've found a lot of interesting things. One that has most recently come to my attention is the zram0 device. I first noticed it when working on one of my Opensource.com articles several months ago. It showed up in the output from the lsblk command:
# lsblk
8:0    0 931.5G  0 disk
8:1    0   600M  0 part
[...]
252:0    0     8G  0 disk [SWAP]

It's identified as swap space, which is what first piqued my curiosity, so I did some exploration. Zram was originally called "compcache," which stands for "compressed cache." It turns out that zram is a tool for creating an in-RAM compressed cache, specifically for use as swap space.
But Why?

More Linux res…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Both</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Java安全]关于Rhino的一些姿势利用]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11831</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11831"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T04:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Java安全]关于Rhino的一些姿势利用]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[可逆打码 – 居然可以「涩图打码，付费解码」😂]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43883</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/kenidama-for-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T04:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[可逆打码是一款有趣的 Windows 工具，它可以为图片添加马赛克，但只需要输入密码，即可去掉马赛克，还原图片。@Appinn 来自发现频道，开发者 @lzn1007 自荐：可以无损解码的打码软件。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C3P0反序列化常用方式及不出网利用]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11830</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11830"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T02:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C3P0反序列化常用方式及不出网利用]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s New Robot Sparrow Can Handle Most Items in the Everything Store]]></title>
        <id>636d46204af1e10e2d86c4ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/amazons-new-robot-sparrow-can-handle-most-items-in-the-everything-store/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T21:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sparrow could shift the balance between humans and machines in the company’s warehouses, using machine learning algorithms and a custom gripper.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s New Robot Sparrow Can Handle Most Items in the Everything Store]]></title>
        <id>636d46204af1e10e2d86c4ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/amazons-new-robot-sparrow-can-handle-most-items-in-the-everything-store/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T21:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sparrow could shift the balance between humans and machines in the company’s warehouses, using machine learning algorithms and a custom gripper.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia’s Sway Over Criminal Ransomware Gangs Is Coming Into Focus]]></title>
        <id>636bda4e06a9fc0e80b10a6d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/russia-ransomware-gang-connections/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T19:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Questions about the Kremlin’s relationships with these groups remain. But researchers are finally getting some answers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Convert an Int to a String in C++ – Integer Cast Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-an-int-to-a-string-in-cpp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-an-int-to-a-string-in-cpp/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T18:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Type casting or type conversion is the process of converting a variable from one data type to another.  Type casting can be done implicitly or explicitly.  Implicit type casting gets done automatically via the compiler, while explicit type casting is done by the developer. In this article, you'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Error: error:0308010c:digital envelope routines::unsupported [Node Error Solved]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/error-error-0308010c-digital-envelope-routines-unsupported-node-error-solved/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/error-error-0308010c-digital-envelope-routines-unsupported-node-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T18:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you work with Node.js and command line interface solutions like Webpack, create-react-app, or vue-cli-service, you might have encountered the error,  Error: error:0308010c:digital envelope routines::unsupported. You’re not alone, because I’m currently getting it too: The React app indeed failed to start: In this article, you’ll learn how to fix]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[They Got Acquired — Helping entrepreneurs sell their company]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/they-got-acquired</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/they-got-acquired"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T18:32:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[14 Companies That Sold After Launching on Product Hunt 💸

I’m Lexi Grant, founder of They Got Acquired.

When I was selling my content company, I hit a snag: I didn’t know where to go for support for my “small” acquisition.

Most of the information and advisors I found online related to big deals. Where can we go for resources and people to help with 6- and 7-figure exits?

That’s why I launched They Got Acquired, a media company that helps entrepreneurs sell their business. 

We do this by sharing stories of founders who exit, shedding light on deals that are too small to be covered in mainstream tech media but can be life-changing for founders. 

We also publish reports that go deep on the metrics behind these deals — so you can see what other companies looked like when they sold, who t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Jamstack? Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/jamstack-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/jamstack-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T18:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have heard the term Jamstack and have been wondering what it means. Well, the Jamstack is nothing more than a modern way of building web applications.  Jamstack takes advantage of existing technologies – which we'll discuss in a minute. The result is better performance, improved security, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damilola Oladele</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fuzz Web Applications using FFuf – Web Security Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-security-fuzz-web-applications-using-ffuf/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-security-fuzz-web-applications-using-ffuf/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T17:21:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building strong authentication systems is crucial for web applications. Now that many businesses have a growing online presence, a malicious actor taking control of your website can be devastating. In this article, we will learn how to use Ffuf, a fast web fuzzer written in Go. You will learn how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protest Is Risky at Egypt's COP27. That Won't Stop Activists]]></title>
        <id>636aadb5fb8d8044171209e5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/protest-activist-risk-egypt-cop27-climate-talks/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T16:40:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the international climate summit in Sharm el-Sheikh, long-standing restrictions on protesters and dissidents are front and center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramin Skibba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Personalized Crispr Therapy Is Designed to Attack Tumors]]></title>
        <id>636ae1d90a504da323ffd05a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/crispr-personalized-cancer-therapy/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T16:32:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a small study, researchers modified patients’ immune cells to target their particular cancer—but it only worked for a third of volunteers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Mullin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Reason for Meta’s Massive Layoffs? Ghosts in the Machine]]></title>
        <id>636d260c0757f7d06dd271f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/meta-layoffs-overhiring/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T16:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The social media company's failed projects required thousands of staffers who swelled the ranks and never left.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk's Twitter Blue Verification Is a Gift to Scammers]]></title>
        <id>636d252677d2621bc8030710</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-blue-check-verification-buy-scams/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T16:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone can get a blue tick on Twitter without proving who they are. And it’s already causing a ton of problems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk's Twitter Blue Verification Is a Gift to Scammers]]></title>
        <id>636d252677d2621bc8030710</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-blue-check-verification-buy-scams/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T16:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone can get a blue tick on Twitter without proving who they are. And it’s already causing a ton of problems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming in TypeScript – Full Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/programming-in-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/programming-in-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T16:10:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript is a typed superset of JavaScript that compiles to plain JavaScript. TypeScript provides better error checking than JavaScript. This is because TypeScript uses a static type system, which means that the type of a variable is checked before the code is executed. We just published a 5-hour TypeScript course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Your Google Stadia Refund—and What’s Included (2022)]]></title>
        <id>6335dc7af089af1e9dc445ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-get-your-google-stadia-refund/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T15:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is taking the unprecedented step of paying back users for all the games they bought on its cloud gaming platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Ravenscraft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia’s New Cyberwarfare in Ukraine Is Fast, Dirty, and Relentless]]></title>
        <id>636aa8641d1ddb0aa029e13c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/russia-ukraine-cyberattacks-mandiant/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T15:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers see updated tactics and tools—and a tempo change—in the cyberattacks Russia’s GRU military intelligence agency is inflicting on Ukraine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[13 Best Mechanical Keyboards for PC (2022): Gaming and Work]]></title>
        <id>5cd9a1adbaf0a36e85079bb2</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-keyboards/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’re looking to boost your productivity or your Fortnite stats, these are the top typing peripherals for the job.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaina Grey, Eric Ravenscraft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stay Organized on Outdoor Adventures With This Rugged Bin]]></title>
        <id>63615af51341ae5cc2594c41</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/rux-70l-storage-bag-rave/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rux 70 is a collapsible grab-and-go storage box made for beach days and camping trips. It even has a companion checklist app to help you pack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gilbertson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-Bullying Apps Are Popular. But Do They Work?]]></title>
        <id>635c3a5159d2df7b4dab3b5f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/anti-bullying-apps-schools-children/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tech promises to help defeat bullying, but larger and glaringly obvious problems remain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christina Wyman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Elegoo Mars 3D Printer Is the Nerdy Gift That Never Stops Giving]]></title>
        <id>6350144f2721236bcb158481</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elegoo-mars-3d-printer-rave/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finally, a 3D printer that’s useful to have in the house (if you’re a huge geek).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Ravenscraft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What You Should Know About Switching to Mastodon]]></title>
        <id>636bffd08480c23aec34bda8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/gadget-lab-podcast-574/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week on Gadget Lab, we do our best to break down the social media platform many Twitter users are flocking to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Billion-Dollar Crypto Collective Is Tearing Itself Apart]]></title>
        <id>636c3adf77d2621bc8030707</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/makerdao-rune-christensen-decentralize/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the world’s biggest crypto groups just voted to back its enigmatic founder. The only problem is, no one understands his plan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Khalili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Tweet Before Dying]]></title>
        <id>636aa3553505151fbc0b01e2</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/tweet-dying-revolutionary-internet/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The revolutionary internet is over, and we don’t have much to show for it. A new start is out there, somewhere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Ford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 websites to learn Frontend-web development faster]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/qbentil/5-websites-to-learn-frontend-web-development-faster-3cid</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/qbentil/5-websites-to-learn-frontend-web-development-faster-3cid"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T11:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #html #css]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bentil Shadrack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I build a Documentation site using Docz]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/documatic/how-i-build-a-documentation-site-using-docz-57kk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/documatic/how-i-build-a-documentation-site-using-docz-57kk"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #beginners #react #javascript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Vishwakarma, Documatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Big Fight Over 403 Very Small Wasps]]></title>
        <id>636ab13d5835030b1507e8a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/big-fight-small-wasps-taxonomy-biodiversity/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earth is teeming with unknown species, and they’re dying off faster than ever. Now biologists are battling over an old question: how to catalog life?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brooke Jarvis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GrammarlyBot — Make your READMEs readable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/grammarlybot</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/grammarlybot"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T10:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tailscan for Tailwind CSS — The ultimate developer tool for Tailwind CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tailscan-for-tailwind-css</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tailscan-for-tailwind-css"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T10:48:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Classes are purged: I couldn't use Chrome Devtools to design and build my website like I was used to because all the unused classes are purged from the CSS! Great for performance on production, but not during development.

❌ No real-time feedback: The alternative was to switch back and forth between my browser and code editor for every class change wasn't much better, it took ages!

🤔 What if the full power of Tailwind was at your disposal where you need it most: the browser?

Introducing Tailscan:
✅ Design and build with Tailwind right within the browser
✅ Debug visually in seconds
✅ Discover how any Tailwind-based website is built

Tailscan gives you the full power of the JIT engine in the browser, on any website. Chaining variants? You got it! Arbitrary values? Sure!

You can also use your own Tailwind config, and Tailscan will support all generated classes right away!

And once you're done building, copy the class list, element or whole section into your code editor! It's that simple!

To celebrate the launch, I've added a limited number of early bird deals.
Grab the deal before it runs out

I'd love to hear your questions, feedback and comments. Thank you very much 🙌

Have a great day!

Erwin
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android 上网课时，有什么办法防止放口袋里的误操作？]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43878</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/pocket-online-classes/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T09:16:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[来自微博里 @小众软件 的问题：android浏览器看在线视频（网课）有什么办法锁屏，这样可以把手机放口袋不会误操作？ 青小蛙的第一反应是…上网课不应该认真听讲呢？为啥要把手机放到口袋里？]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 key differences between Twitter and Mastodon]]></title>
        <id>70313 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/twitter-vs-mastodon"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[4 key differences between Twitter and Mastodon
Don Watkins
Thu, 11/10/2022 - 03:00

            
Social media is not always sociable, and sometimes we need a sufficient impetus to change what we do and what we read. I began using Twitter as a replacement for my RSS reader in 2008, which revolutionized how I read and learned up to that point. Tweets from educators and free and open source (FOSS) advocates worldwide kept me informed and engaged in a learning network that was without equal. That's changed over the past half dozen years, and recently a change in ownership and the shaping of what I read was driven more by an algorithm than by my personal interests and choices. During a yearly meetup of correspondents and editors of Opensource.com a few years ago, Seth Kenlon suggested giving Ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Don Watkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audit your sharding database algorithm]]></title>
        <id>70297 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/audit-sharding-database"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Audit your sharding database algorithm
Yacine Si Tayeb, PhD
Thu, 11/10/2022 - 03:00

            
Thanks to the ShardingSphere community's continuous review and feedback to develop features such as data sharding and read/write splitting, our team found that some users create many shards when using the data sharding feature.
In such cases, there can be 1,000 physical tables corresponding to a sharding logical table, which disturbs users.
For instance, a SELECT * FROM t_order statement will lead to a full-route, which is obviously not the case for OLTP. This SQL can be placed in another Proxy to avoid blocking other requests.
However, if users are not familiar with Proxy or how to write a where condition and don't know that sharding is not supported in this condition, a full-route is still r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yacine Si Tayeb, PhD</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Vulnhub] Me-and-My-Girlfriend-1]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11827</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11827"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T07:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Vulnhub] Me-and-My-Girlfriend-1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CleanMyMac X VS 360安全卫士Mac｜功能对比]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43869</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/cleanmymac-x-vs-360safemac/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T06:09:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CleanMyMac X 作为一款主打清理 Mac 电脑系统的软件，已经有 13年的历史了。想必 Mac 用户多少都听说过。而 360安全卫士 Mac 版本，对于传统的 Mac 用户来说，还嫌的有些陌]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Bootstrap 5 in Spanish by Building a Portfolio Website – Bootstrap Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-bootstrap-5-in-spanish-by-building-a-portfolio-website-bootstrap-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-bootstrap-5-in-spanish-by-building-a-portfolio-website-bootstrap-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T05:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome! If you speak Spanish and you want to practice your HTML and CSS skills, create responsive websites with Bootstrap 5, and build your portfolio website, then this course is for you. In this article, you will find a brief introduction to responsive web development and Bootstrap 5. You will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weblogic CVE-2020-2551 绕过NAT网络分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11825</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11825"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T02:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weblogic CVE-2020-2551 绕过NAT网络分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Hell Happened to FTX?]]></title>
        <id>636bf17f0757f7d06dd271ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ftx-collapse-binance-crypto-deal/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T18:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The collapse of crypto exchange FTX opens opportunities for rival exchange Binance—and raises questions about the sector’s sustainability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Khalili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Countries Hit Hardest by Climate Change May Finally Get Their Due]]></title>
        <id>636a3eae5835030b1507e8a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cop27-climate-reparations/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T17:11:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After 30 years of talk about forcing wealthy polluters to compensate those bearing the brunt of climate damage, the COP27 conference seems poised to act.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Barber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[透过信息架构 看各笔记软件]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76736</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76736"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T15:18:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[我在 如何搭建知识库 中，将知识库的结构分为了「树状结构」和「网络结构」两种。
树状结构是自上而下的，网络结构是自下而上的。
但知识还有多少种结构呢？为什么是这两种？
知识本质上是信息的一种，想了解知识的结构，也可以类比信息的结构。一直以来我回答不好这个问题。
日复一日，在日常使用知识库和产品经理的工作中，无论是对知识库中的每一张知识卡片进行整理，还是在工作中经常需要查看数据库的数据结构，都将我指向一个词「信息架构」
于是，我想起了那本经典的的「北极熊」之书 —— 《信息架构 超越 Web 设计》
并且，我在这本三年前读过的书里，找到了现在的我想要的答案。

信息结构
在《信息架构》这本书中，将信息分为了以下三种结构
组织系统：组织结构可以分为互补的三种结构
层级结构
以数据库为导向的模式
超文本

信息结构会定义用户浏览的主要方式。适用于信息架构的主要组织结构包括层级结构 、以数据库为导向的模式和超文本，每种组织结构都有其优缺点。在某些情况下，只使用一 种是合理的。但在很多情况下，需要以互补的方式使用这 3 种组织 结构。 —— 《信息架构》第六章

看到这三个结构，我恍然大悟，觉得非常了不起。
简单的三种结构，几乎可以用来解释现在所有的笔记软件。
下面我将介绍每一种结构在知识库软件中的运用。结合我日常的使用经历，也给出一些建议。
（注：目前市面上可以作为知识库的软件有很多。我只选取我有使用过的软件作为本次功能的介绍。也就是 Notion、Obsidian、Logseq、wolai…）

信息结构会定义用户浏览的主要方式。适用于信息架构的主要组织结构包括层级结构 、以数据库为导向的模式和超文本， 每种组织结构都有其优缺点。

层级结构
层级结构，即是上一层级包括下一层级的结构。
层级结构的优势和劣势都很明显。优势是其层次清晰，劣势是维护成本高。
层级结构的广度和深度均不宜…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>潦草学者</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Quiet Invasion of 'Big Information']]></title>
        <id>636167b2079462a79d02d6c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/big-information-relx-privacy-surveillance-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google and Facebook's privacy violations are common knowledge. But the decisions of a less-known company, Relx, are also impacting people's everyday lives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Lamdan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collective Mental Time Travel Can Influence the Future]]></title>
        <id>63627db400e08e244b10a525</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/psychology-mental-time-travel-politics/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way people imagine the past and future of society can sway attitudes and behaviors. How might this be wielded for good?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shayla Love</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter Users Have Caused a Mastodon Meltdown]]></title>
        <id>636adc98e8c08909bfa4fcf9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-users-mastodon-meltdown/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The network’s servers are overrun by almost half a million new sign-ups, as Elon Musk’s Twitter takeover has thrust it into the spotlight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amanda Hoover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Great Crypto-Cop Brain Drain]]></title>
        <id>636b01903505151fbc0b01e9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-great-crypto-cop-brain-drain/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hunting down crypto criminals is a dying art as law enforcement officers jump in-house.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gian M. Volpicelli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brace Yourself for a Triple Wave of Seasonal Viruses]]></title>
        <id>636adfae1bc1a3ed38dc3b02</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/covid-flu-rsv-tripledemic/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many people haven’t been exposed to common respiratory viruses following the pandemic, meaning they might be more vulnerable to getting ill this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Weiss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made 1200+ ⭐️ stars on a Github repo! Here are some simple tips that helped me!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fredy/i-made-1200-stars-on-a-github-repo-here-are-some-simple-tips-that-helped-me-4eom</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fredy/i-made-1200-stars-on-a-github-repo-here-are-some-simple-tips-that-helped-me-4eom"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T11:25:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #tutorial #react #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fredy Andrei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UPDF – 巨好用的PDF编辑阅读器｜双11薅羊毛必入神器]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43859</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/updf-lia202211/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T09:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[快年底了，各行各业都在冲业绩。各大电商平台也在准备双11活动，屏幕前的你这个双11剁手了吗？节后是不是要吃土了？小编这个双11也入手不少东西，但是除了购买生活用品，我也趁双11入手一些办公学习的神器，]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>开发者推荐账号</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[为 Firefox 打开原生「双击关闭标签页」功能]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43862</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/firefox-double-click-close-tab/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T08:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[有同学在一个很老的内容《Firefox 小技巧 – 双击关闭标签》里说链接都挂了，寻找最新的解决方案。青小蛙看到那是火山同学当年魔改的 Firefox 扩展，经过这么多年，早就不能用了。 但别急，Fi]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why sysadmins should choose Awesome window manager on Linux]]></title>
        <id>70294 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/linux-awesome-window-manager"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why sysadmins should choose Awesome window manager on Linux
Seth Kenlon
Wed, 11/09/2022 - 03:00

            
Awesome is a window manager for the Linux desktop. A "window manager" is a graphical interface that primarily (if not literally) just manages the drawing and arrangement of windows. In practice, even the most rudimentary of window managers actually provides a little more than just the ability to draw a window. Most also provide a pop-up menu so you can launch an application, some provide a dock or panel so you can switch between different applications you have running. They stop short at providing desktop conveniences such as drawing a wallpaper in the background of your screen, mounting and unmounting devices, providing a system tray, and so on. A window manager assumes you can us…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Kenlon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Python in VS Code and Codium]]></title>
        <id>70284 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/python-vs-code-codium"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using Python in VS Code and Codium
Don Watkins
Wed, 11/09/2022 - 03:00

            
Over the past couple of years, I have had the privilege of working with middle school children to introduce them to Python coding and the Raspberry Pi 400. It's been a lot of fun, and the Pi has been a great platform for the students and me. We've used Code with Mu and it's been quite successful. Our aptitude with Python has grown with experience, and so recently I started looking for ways to offer these students more.
I participated in a Python learning class, and during that class I got introduced to Microsoft's Visual Studio Code. I learned a lot in that class about how to set up a virtual environment for Python, and how to configure VS Code for Python programming. During that learning journey, I also g…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Don Watkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[jetty常用渗透总结]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11821</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11821"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T07:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[jetty常用渗透总结]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[凛冬将至，你准备好买羽绒服了吗]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76706</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76706"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T03:23:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐 
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。 
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

又到双十一购物节，说来有趣，每年双十一我都会关注羽绒服这一品类，原因大概是冬天即将到来，我隐约有添购衣服的担忧，可又因为此时我还身穿短袖，买羽绒服有种错季购物的感觉，在将羽绒服加入购物车后往往又放弃下单。于是这些年，每到双十一，我的购物车里的羽绒服更新一次，羽绒服照片成了淘宝的皮肤挂件，年年换新。
我当然是有买羽绒服，但往往不是购物车里那件，我在淘宝上浏览的是万元左右的始祖鸟、Moncler、加拿大鹅，加入购物车里的是两千元左右的北面，但最终购买的是千元以内的波司登和优衣库轻薄款，哦对了，还有老家线下店铺的以纯羽绒服。
不过长期以往，我倒是对羽绒服有了足够多的了解，足以写下这篇有参考价值的文章，帮助人们选购羽绒服。
羽绒服的历史
人类自古以来就有利用动物皮毛御寒的历史，早在原始社会时期，人类祖先就已经初步掌握了将兽皮制作成衣物的方法，用兽皮和树叶蔽体防寒，后来逐渐出现麻、棉、丝等纺织物，人类衣物变得丰富。相对来说，人类利用禽类羽毛御寒的历史要短得多，在唐朝，人们用鹅绒和布混合填充在被子中，在十三四世纪的欧洲，人们用鸭和鹅的羽毛填充进被套中。
直到 1940 年，现代羽绒服才被发明出来，主角是美国的艾迪·鲍尔，作为一名狂热户外运动爱好者，他在一次户外钓鱼过程中差点冻死，于是决心制作一件真正保暖的外套。鲍尔找到了鹅毛的羽绒，又恰逢杜邦实验室在 1938 年发明了尼龙，尼龙织物质地紧密，与棉布相比，尼龙面料可以防止羽绒「钻绒」，于是，他将二者结合，把羽绒填充进尼龙面料的衣服，绗缝锁绒，并将第一件羽绒外套命名为「Skyliner」，申…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>吃饭Bu洗碗</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[通过一个crackme学习逆向基础知识以及Delphi框架]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11818</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11818"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T02:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[通过一个crackme学习逆向基础知识以及Delphi框架]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[强对抗时代下的C2：战神Ares]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11819</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11819"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T02:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[强对抗时代下的C2：战神Ares]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Apple Pay or Google Wallet Instead of Plastic Cards]]></title>
        <id>636a9127f4db157fcdf20ff1</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/money-privacy-security-settings-apple-google-pay/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cash is safe—for now. Contactless payment methods, like Apple Pay or Google Wallet, are more of a threat to the existence of physical cards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reece Rogers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snooze Tabs — Snooze tabs, windows and todos for later]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/snooze-tabs</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/snooze-tabs"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T00:52:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Features:

~ Free:
- Preset times
- Custom date and time to snooze your tabs
- Snooze current, selected or all tabs 
- Customisable keyboard shortcuts  
- Light & Dark theme
- Group tabs title 

~ Pro:
☁️  Cloud sync and backup
✅ Todos tab to snooze
🔁  Recurring snooze
💼 Workspaces
and...:
- Unlimited snooze
- Notification sound
- Auto-group tabs
- Snooze history

It's available as an extension for both Chrome also Firefox browser.

💖 Thanks & Special Discount
Thanks for supporting me, my product and this PH launch~ As a thank you, here's 20% off for the Pro version for all PH hunters 👉 https://gum.co/snoozetabs-pro/PH20
*only valid until end of the day*

Thank you so much, and may God bless you 🙏 🤗
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Race to Bridge the Analog Divide in US Politics]]></title>
        <id>636a86a41bc1a3ed38dc3afb</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/retail-politics-analog-divide/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T21:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing beats in-person efforts to boost a campaign. But rising platforms are helping connect politicians with the rest of us.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Laslo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highlightly 1.0 — Redefining reading making knowledge more accessible to all]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/highlightly-1-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/highlightly-1-0"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T19:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the MongoDB Atlas Hackathon 2022 on DEV!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devteam/announcing-the-mongodb-atlas-hackathon-2022-on-dev-2107</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devteam/announcing-the-mongodb-atlas-hackathon-2022-on-dev-2107"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T18:11:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#atlashackathon22 #mongodb #meta]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Bethencourt, The DEV Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React & NodeJS - Go LIVE with Full-Stack projects fast]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sm0ke/react-nodejs-go-live-with-full-stack-projects-fast-j0h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sm0ke/react-nodejs-go-live-with-full-stack-projects-fast-j0h"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T18:09:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #react #fullstack]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sm0ke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the ‘Election Integrity App’ Built to Purge US Voter Rolls]]></title>
        <id>63657b621bc1a3ed38dc3ace</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/true-the-vote-iv3-app-voter-fraud/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T15:59:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[True the Vote’s IV3 app is meant to catch election cheaters. But it has a fundamental flaw.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruv Mehrotra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the ‘Election Integrity App’ Built to Purge US Voter Rolls]]></title>
        <id>63657b621bc1a3ed38dc3ace</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/true-the-vote-iv3-app-voter-fraud/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T15:59:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[True the Vote’s IV3 app is meant to catch election cheaters. But it has a fundamental flaw.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruv Mehrotra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All your JavaScript code is polluted]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jankapunkt/all-your-javascript-code-is-polluted-3e8l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jankapunkt/all-your-javascript-code-is-polluted-3e8l"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T15:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jan Küster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Speedy Newsletter — Email newsletter maker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/speedy-newsletter</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/speedy-newsletter"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T13:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China’s Digital Yuan Works Just Like Cash—With Added Surveillance]]></title>
        <id>636029fca9269ef97e4efe17</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/chinas-digital-yuan-ecny-works-just-like-cash-surveillance/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Government officials are urging citizens to adopt the official digital currency in a bid to gain more control over the economy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Conrad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists Are Uncovering Ominous Waters Under Antarctic Ice]]></title>
        <id>63693c6c7484c01b9b6e9653</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/scientists-are-uncovering-ominous-waters-under-antarctic-ice/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A super-pressurized, 290-mile-long river is running under the ice sheet. That could be bad news for sea-level rise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After Twitter Staff Cuts, Survivors Face ‘Radio Silence’]]></title>
        <id>63698b970cb0746eb8d6b7ee</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/musk-layoffs-twitter-management/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The long-suffering staffers who remain at the company are scrambling to regroup and adapt to a new management style.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Fauci’s Sign-Off Message]]></title>
        <id>6361a5e7d58ae0592b0f00cf</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/anthony-faucis-sign-off-message/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While America’s top doc fought Covid, deniers fought him. He still can’t figure out why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Meta’s Oversight Board: 2 Years of Pushing Limits]]></title>
        <id>63694a226776a0176c76e527</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/inside-metas-oversight-board-two-years-of-pushing-limits/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg set up the panel to investigate how his company handles controversial posts. Now its members want to transform how social platforms work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ContextMenuForWindows11 – 修改 Windows 11 右键菜单]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43856</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/contextmenuforwindows11/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T08:37:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ContextMenuForWindows11 是一款用来修改 Windows 11 右键菜单的小工具，比如为 .txt 添加使用 EmEditor 打开这个右键菜单。@Appinn 来自发现频道，手]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[安卓APP抓包解决方案(教程)]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11817</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11817"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T06:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[安卓APP抓包解决方案(教程)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CS的RCE利用研究]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11815</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11815"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T02:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CS的RCE利用研究]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SpringBoot和SpringMvc中的Context]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11814</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11814"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T02:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SpringBoot和SpringMvc中的Context]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to 'Quiet Quit' Elon Musk's Twitter]]></title>
        <id>63657ddcd7f2f1953e686ffe</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-quiet-quit-elon-musks-twitter/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T22:34:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The chaos engulfing the platform provides an opportunity to reclaim control of your online life, without logging off for good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Goode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Secret Ballot Is US Democracy’s Last Line of Defense]]></title>
        <id>63651410f65e6e9328cbf0a7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/secret-ballot-voter-intimidation-2022-us-midterms/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T21:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voter intimidation has cropped up in places across the nation, but the voting booth remains the one place where nobody can get to you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Secret Ballot Is US Democracy’s Last Line of Defense]]></title>
        <id>63651410f65e6e9328cbf0a7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/secret-ballot-voter-intimidation-2022-us-midterms/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T21:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voter intimidation has cropped up in places across the nation, but the voting booth remains the one place where nobody can get to you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IRS Seizes Another Silk Road Hacker’s $3.36 Billion Bitcoin Stash]]></title>
        <id>636948fa0d25973ba5f9bc5a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/silk-road-bitcoin-seizure-james-zhong/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T19:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A year after a billion-dollar seizure of the dark web market's crypto, the same agency found a giant trove hidden under a different hacker's floorboards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client-side Routing without the JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/client-side-routing-without-the-javascript-3k1i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-learning/client-side-routing-without-the-javascript-3k1i"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T16:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #solidjs #webdev #performance]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Carniato, This is Learning</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[想要逃离 Chrome？请收下这份 Firefox 终极隐私指南]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76688</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76688"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T15:41:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐 
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。 
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

前言
毋庸置疑，如今的 Chrome 及其他基于 Chromium 的 Blink 内核浏览器因其速度快、网页兼容性好的优点，以绝对的优势占据了浏览器市场的主导地位。但与此同时，因为 Chrome 与 Chromium 被一家号称「不作恶」但处处作恶的公司所拥有，所以经常被诟病存在隐私问题。许多想要逃离 Chrome 统治的人都转向了更加自由的 Firefox 浏览器，尽管其母公司 Mozilla 近年来也是骚操作不断，但 Firefox 仍然是除 Chromium 的 Blink 和 Safari 的 WebKit 外唯一选择。
我曾经也很喜欢用 Chrome（或者说是 Chromium），使用 ArchLinux 作为主力系统的我，官方软件源中使用开源 Chromium 代码编译出的 Chromium 浏览器在当时体验基本与谷歌官方的闭源 Chrome 一致。促使我转向使用 Firefox 的契机开始于一年多前，谷歌限制了第三方浏览器对其数据同步 API 的使用，这样一来各家发行版自行编译的 Chromium 浏览器都失去了账户同步功能，这在当时引起了很多不满。从那时开始，我就开始尝试使用 Firefox 替代 Chromium 作为我的主力浏览器，并最终彻底淘汰掉了 Chromium。
无独有偶，谷歌又宣布将会在 2022 年底彻底禁用 Manifest V2 规范（后来又推迟了半年），作为替代者的 Manifest V3 规范，用谷歌的话说是为了「保护用户隐私」，限制了浏览器扩展的很多权限，其中影响最大的是禁用了 We…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>so1ar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Has Put Twitter’s Free Speech in Danger]]></title>
        <id>636299fb079462a79d02d6c9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-free-speech-musk-takeover/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T14:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authoritarian countries around the world want to suppress criticism and public opinion. Can this new Twitter fight back?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vittoria Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hexagonal architecture as a solution to the obsolescence of UI frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/drouianm/hexagonal-architecture-as-a-solution-to-the-obsolescence-of-ui-frameworks-ej2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/drouianm/hexagonal-architecture-as-a-solution-to-the-obsolescence-of-ui-frameworks-ej2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T13:18:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#vue #react #typescript #architecture]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthieu Drouian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europeans Are Burning Trees to Keep Warm]]></title>
        <id>6365c0b54b3fdcfe4bdf205d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/eu-forests-energy-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sky-high energy prices have people turning to wood to provide a cheaper alternative—and EU laws are helping incentivize this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Gulp of Engineered Bacteria Is Meant to Treat Disease]]></title>
        <id>63625783d05a7e57f9be567c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/this-gulp-of-engineered-bacteria-is-meant-to-treat-disease/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A small study of people with a rare disorder that prevents them from processing protein is an early attempt at creating “living” medicines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Mullin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter’s Ex-Election Chief Is Worried About the US Midterms]]></title>
        <id>6365c3d872734b280f7c5085</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-election-integrity-2022-midterms/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Edward Perez says that “manufactured chaos” by bad actors will be even riskier thanks to Elon Musk’s own mayhem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s Reckless Plan to Make Sex Pay on Twitter]]></title>
        <id>6365442eaec2220e3ecb87f6</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-adult-content-sex-twitter-content-moderation/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T11:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A plan to monetize adult content could make sense from a business and social standpoint. In practice, Twitter won’t be able to pull it off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olivia Snow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust Easy! Modern Cross-platform Command Line Tools to Supercharge Your Terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/deepu105/rust-easy-modern-cross-platform-command-line-tools-to-supercharge-your-terminal-4dd3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/deepu105/rust-easy-modern-cross-platform-command-line-tools-to-supercharge-your-terminal-4dd3"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T09:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#rust #terminal #linux #macos]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deepu K Sasidharan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Commons JXPath 远程代码执行(CVE-2022-41852)]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11813</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11813"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T09:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Commons JXPath 远程代码执行(CVE-2022-41852)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PostgresQL JDBC Drive 任意代码执行漏洞(CVE-2022-21724)]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11812</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11812"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T08:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PostgresQL JDBC Drive 任意代码执行漏洞(CVE-2022-21724)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[我在 app 里做了一下「赛博朋克：边缘行者」里的拖影效果]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76679</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76679"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T07:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[本次更新：
前几天看了「赛博朋克：边缘行者」，觉得里面的拖影效果非常有趣，就在 app 里做了一下。

App 介绍：
CUBE 是一款结合 iOS 软硬件新特性来完成实时特效的 app ，希望大家在手机上就可以玩到有趣的特效。 以我看过的热门影音作品为灵感，已经完成下面三个主要特效：
LiDAR 扫描效果：
日本女团 Perfume 在 Flow 的 MV 中大量使用点云这种技术，而正好配备 LiDAR 的 iPhone 可以感知深度，生成点云。
 
采样实时图像与 LiDAR 扫描仪生成的深度图，生成 3D 粒子（点云）。至多可生成 3,000,000 个粒子。
将生成的 3D 粒子与现实世界的场景混合在一起，让你感觉身处超现实世界。

Matrix 效果：
之前 黑客帝国 4 上映，黑客帝国又变成热门话题，就很想复刻一下经典的 code rain 。
 
这一次会选蓝色药丸还是红色药丸？

液态金属效果：
 
既然都提到了黑客帝国，那么终结者也不能不提。贯穿全系列的液态金属杀手也是经典之一。CUBE 带你回到 1991 年，化身成为詹姆斯·卡梅隆所拍摄的电影「终结者 2：审判日」中的终结者 T-1000 。

App Store
 
兑换码：
如果你对上面三个特效感兴趣，你可以在这里找到兑换码。
（我把码都放到一个 notion page 里，可以回复用掉的兑换码编号，方便我编辑。）
https://boringseries.notion.site/CUBE-392d7f454b2a4ceabae44ef478c87f4b]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>少数派77122655</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[感受读书上瘾的快乐]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76659</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76659"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T07:07:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[如何让枯燥的读书像看剧、享受美食、打游戏一样快乐？
读书上瘾模型，让读书成为一个上瘾循环。

上学的时候我比较喜欢玩游戏，但是在图书馆有很好的学习看书的氛围，游戏玩得比较少。毕业后，不再有看书的氛围了，玩游戏的频率逐渐增加，从每周1天增加到2天、后来逐步增加到7天，每天都玩游戏。
那个时候我意识到已经游戏上瘾了，打游戏占据了太多的时间，所以决定戒掉游戏，经过几次尝试，终于在2020年把游戏戒掉了。

即从游戏上瘾转变为读书上瘾，读书包括输入和输出两个步骤。输入指的是看书，从去年开始在豆瓣记录读书情况，利用周末和工作日的被动等待时间，每个月最多读过11本书。
输出分为写、说、实践3种形式。

写，发表长篇博客或简短的书评。
说，分为线上和线下两种形式，线上指在各个自媒体平台发布读书视频；线下指面对面形式，1对1的交流沟通或1对多的分享。
实践，看书不应该只停留在改变认知的程度，还要实践、改变自己的行为习惯。比如看了一本关于运动的书，不仅要有每天都运动的认知，还要付诸于每天的实践行动。

上一次玩游戏是在2020年，接下来详细介绍如何从游戏上瘾转变为读书上瘾。
 
 
Part 1 什么是上瘾？
一 上瘾的原理
二 戒上瘾的思路

提高行动成本
模块说

Part 2 读书上瘾模型
三 Step 1：选一本我需要的书

3.1 分析我想要的是什么
3.2 选书的途径
3.3 适当难度：最高学习效率15.87%
3.4 选择自己能承受的成长模式

四 Step 2：创造时间

4.1 人生需要做减法
4.2 时间管理系统/任务管理系统，GTD
GTD step 1 捕捉
GTD step 2 整理
GTD step 3 执行

4.3 时间颗粒度
4.4 实例演示：如何使用GTD
时间管理相关软件
使用GTD的一天


五 Step 3：输入：寻找适合自己的阅读方式

5.1 拆…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jogging</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【键盘观望】看看最近有趣的键帽。2022.11（1）]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76531</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76531"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T06:07:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[本文仅代表个人观点，用于记录和观望一些键帽。

PBTFANS KABUKI-CHO 歌舞伎町
2022.4 
IC Base
这套键帽是由设计师OAY （罗马音？大概能翻译成哦呀，语气词）设计的第二套键帽，此前他还设计过pbtfans的深海来客，感兴趣的可以看我之前盘点的蓝色系键帽。
这套歌舞伎町键帽，灵感来源于日本的歌舞伎町——东京的娱乐中心之一。电影院、电玩舞厅、酒吧等等，从深夜到黎明，也是为数不多的大型红灯区，我对于歌舞伎町最深刻的印象则是来自于《银魂》中主角团所居住的歌舞伎町一条街。
配色：

这次的配色非常丰富，主要还是由于个性部分选用多种不同色彩。键帽整体底色以深蓝暗色调为主，而字符和个性选用明亮的色调，如同霓虹灯招牌的颜色，侧面烘托出歌舞伎町“不眠之街”的名号，到深夜依然灯火通明、灯红酒绿。
个性部分：
大货版本
这次的现货销售是直接将个性和base进行了捆绑，还包含了四个颜色的盖帽。
个性部分主要由歌舞伎、酒精和没事组成，以及歌舞伎町的招牌和著名的“一丁目”。颜色上也是选择非常丰富，盖帽倒是提供了一种略微复古但俏皮的感觉，七字回车则是意味着现代的电力为这般灯红酒绿提供了便利。
搭配展示：
该键帽已经开售有一段时间，所以已经有玩家提供了实拍的照片，有这些实物图，能更好的帮助我们来判断是否购入。
乐总拍摄阿门JV拍摄Vanthic Noel 拍摄
键帽信息：
材质：PBT材质
高度：原厂高度
工艺：二色工艺
厂商：PBTFANS
淘宝有售卖，据悉歌舞伎町卖的很好，货量有限，kbd自己的店铺已经卖完了，经销商仍有现货。 
个人评分:7-8（深色键帽非常耐看，歌舞伎町的主题也很新鲜，个性颜色丰富,PBTFANS代工水平不错）
购买建议：喜欢这个主题的值得入手，现货也无需等待

KeyKobo Poltergeist 吵闹鬼
2022.9

这套键帽是由设计师SXM…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>车不能快</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[白菜价的国产暗尖怎么样？12款3~15元钢笔横评对比]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76673</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76673"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T03:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[前言
仔细翻了翻我个人的钢笔产品分享，和大家讨论过的都是以著名品牌的钢笔产品为主，对于国内钢笔品牌主要还是分享英雄旗下的经典产品与创新之作，毕竟其它钢笔品牌以我个人的眼光去看，都是没有太多购买意义的产品。
对于钢笔入门我始终推荐白金preppy系列、白金小流星系列、百乐78g、凌美狩猎者这些海外品牌的平价款式。
但因为英雄的关系，国人对于暗尖结构的钢笔有着相当的偏好，并且海外知名品牌如今也没有任何纯粹的现产暗尖钢笔产品。所以如今暗尖钢笔的赛道上全是国产钢笔品牌，并且价位主战场就是十元上下的低端市场，本篇中，我在某多多以零售价格，购买了十余款销量出色的国产暗尖，文内将从暗尖钢笔的用料、设计、特点来对它们进行全面的横评对比，希望能为大家了解这些产品带来帮助。
暗尖钢笔的发源与如今价位分布

暗尖钢笔发源于人类历史上最为成功的钢笔派克51，其诞生于1939年，暨派克成立51周年，故因此得以型号命名。
派克51的暗尖结构，通过树脂包裹了笔尖，在当年革新性得提高了钢笔的气密性，并根据结构，设计了新一代的毛细供墨系统，达到了更为稳定的书写效果。
在当年，暗尖钢笔以这两点综合的超强实用性，得到了市场的一致认可，直至停产派克51累计销售4000万支，是人类历史上最为成功的系列钢笔。
之所以停产，是因为后续钢笔的气密性与供墨毛细结构材料随着现代工业不断革新，暗尖已经不再具备核心优势。
现在的暗尖钢笔从高到底个人认为是三个层次，首先是派克前年复刻了51，做了个包住明尖的假暗尖，是目前价格最高的笔款，但不怎么值得去买。其次是英雄100代表了国产暗尖金笔，曾经100多元的价格性价比非常好，如今价格普遍要200以上，还是可以买，但没曾经的极致性价比了；最后就是本篇讲的10元上下，国产的钢尖暗尖钢笔！
暗尖钢笔的特点

一、暗尖钢笔因为笔尖露出部分少，书写时可以产生形变的笔尖体积相对较小，所以书写时感…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>老木曾雪菜</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[从2022中科大hackgame web中学习pdflatex RCE和python反序列化]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11809</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11809"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T03:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[从2022中科大hackgame web中学习pdflatex RCE和python反序列化]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[shiro环境下的Servlet内存马注入踩坑日记]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11808</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11808"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T03:09:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[shiro环境下的Servlet内存马注入踩坑日记]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[最近碰到的 Python pickle 反序列化小总结]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11807</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11807"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T02:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[最近碰到的 Python pickle 反序列化小总结]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Your First Client — A complete guide for starting your freelance business]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/how-to-get-your-first-client</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/how-to-get-your-first-client"/>
        <updated>2022-11-06T20:03:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPhone 相机进化之路：38 款 iPhone 图像传感器型号确认（07 - 22）]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76639</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76639"/>
        <updated>2022-11-06T15:06:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐 
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。 
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

在 Android 手机的宣传稿中，我们经常能听到厂商宣传其所搭载的图像传感器型号，例如索尼 IMX***、三星 S5K***、豪威 OV**** 等。但在 iPhone 的宣传中，我们就不曾听过苹果声明 iPhone 使用的图像传感器型号，一般都是使用「传感器面积增大了百分之几」「像素更大更深」「全新的高速传感器」之类的比较模糊的用词，所以对于历代 iPhone 具体使用何种传感器，互联网上有诸多不能明确的信息。此文意在将我自己搜集到的相关信息进行梳理，试图考证它们的可靠性，为之后写作 iPhone 图像传感器进化打下基础。

首先给出我整理后的部分信息，点击图片可看原图，欢迎指正。
截自我的 Notion 页面
主要参考信源
互联网上关于 iPhone 图像传感器的信息参差不齐，大部分信息都没有给出出处，单纯引用某一信源难以有说服力，我综合了部分我比较认可的信源，各位可以自行甄别。
维基百科：Exmor
Exmor 是索尼公司应用在其部分 CMOS 图像传感器上的技术名称。维基百科上的 Exmor 词条收集整理了大量索尼 Exmor 图像传感器及其使用的机型，使用 Ctrl+F 可快速搜索 iPhone 关键词。我将其整理如下表。


Model numberNumber of effective pixelsSensor size (diagonal)Pixel sizeSubpixel layoutUtilizing devices

IMX1453264 x 2448 8Mp5.68 mm (1/3.2")1.40 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>太不巧</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFE-A卡横评及选购指南，「原厂」并不是最好选择！]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76663</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76663"/>
        <updated>2022-11-06T14:18:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[写在最前面，CFE卡贵谁都知道，但是这玩意性能是真的强，不管你现在用不用得着，都建议你收藏一下，虽然现在买不起，但是梦想还是要有的嘛！
CFE-A卡是索尼从A7S3开始使用的新一代高速存储设备，以应对越来越大的视频录制码率。早先使用CFE-A卡的机型都比较贵（A7S3,FX3,A1等），受众并不多。但从A7M4的大卖和FX30的发布，越来越多的用户开始使用支持CFE-A卡的相机，如何选购一张合适的CFE-A卡就成了许多用户头疼的问题。
懂数码的都知道，索尼虽然“爱好广泛”，但唯独没有生产研发存储产品的业务，也就是说索尼的卡都是其他厂家代工的贴牌产品，理论上是不可能干得过拥有独立生产研发存储颗粒的品牌的，所谓的索尼大法黑科技在存储领域也仅仅是索尼粉丝自己加上的滤镜而已。
由于CFE-A卡是索尼独占的新卡型，在发布之初的相当长一段时间里都只有索尼原厂的卡可以选择，因为缺少比较的竞品，让许多人养成了原厂=最好的固有印象。
如今第三方的CFE-A品牌越来越多，索尼原厂卡到底是个什么水平，终于可以有一个正经的横向比较了。
市面上可以做CFE-A卡的品牌有索尼，雷克沙，天硕，和至誉科技四家，笔者手里正好分别有一张拿来比较测试，他们是

索尼原厂的80G，官方售价699;
分别是雷克沙的320G，官方售价5599带读卡器;
天硕的80G，官方售价399；
至誉科技的120G，官方售价1599;

少数派不让带货就不放链接了。

之所以价格区间跨度很大，从几百到几千，主要是为了照顾不同经济实力的用户。
测试采用的读卡器是雷克沙的RW530，是一个CFA和SD卡双卡槽的读卡器，采用USB 3.2gen2接口，两个卡槽可以同时工作，可以实现互拷的功能。

一、性能对比
1、索尼80G

首先出场的是原厂的80G，由于这张卡是在套机里一起售卖的，拆机卡很多，只要六七百。买的人很多，不过大多数都舍…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>食肉库玛</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fibonacci Numbers Hiding in Strange Spaces]]></title>
        <id>635ffd25d58ae0592b0f00c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-fibonacci-numbers-hiding-in-strange-spaces/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent explorations of unique geometric worlds reveal perplexing patterns, including the Fibonacci sequence and the golden ratio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leila Sloman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Mexico’s Beloved Pinyon Jay Is Losing Its Pine Habitat]]></title>
        <id>635ffca700e08e244b10a510</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/new-mexicos-beloved-pinyon-jay-is-losing-its-pine-habitat/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Western landscape’s namesake bird is threatened by climate change, and perhaps by wildfire prevention tactics that thin out the trees they rely on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sara Van Note</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok’s Greatest Asset Isn’t Its Algorithm—It’s Your Phone]]></title>
        <id>63517a45470620c1e69a25e1</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/tiktok-phones-extended-mind-philosophy/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Escaping the platform's addictive grasp means first overhauling our relationship to our devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leo Kim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elevate Your Terminal Experience on The Mac 🧘‍♂️]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/duncanlew/elevate-your-terminal-experience-on-the-mac-3o3m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/duncanlew/elevate-your-terminal-experience-on-the-mac-3o3m"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T20:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #tutorial #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Duncan Lew</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 Icon websites for devs and designers!!!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ymhaah/top-5-icon-websites-for-devs-and-designers-53mh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ymhaah/top-5-icon-websites-for-devs-and-designers-53mh"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T19:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#design #beginners #webdev #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Youssef Hafnawy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An animated guide for Node.js event loop]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nodedoctors/an-animated-guide-to-nodejs-event-loop-3g62</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nodedoctors/an-animated-guide-to-nodejs-event-loop-3g62"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T18:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #node #beginners #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hu, Node Doctors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[快捷指令的野心与无奈]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76652</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76652"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T14:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[作为一名iPhone用户，快捷指令是系统中我觉得很有趣但实际上用得不是很多的应用。
最初对快捷指令的理解仅限于将多个操作步骤简化成一个，最直观的应用就是在功能日益繁杂的APP中实现功能的一键直达，比如疫情期间的健康码。
但深入探究一番后，我认为快捷指令的本质其实是打破各个APP沙盒的壁垒，实现不同应用程序的能力互通，提升个人的自动化水平。
但事情情况并不尽如人意，虽然快捷指令编辑器提供了足够强大的编辑器，但三方应用对其支持并不好，大多数APP还是尽可能期望把用户圈在自己的生态中，没有开放足够的能力出来，这也是一款生态级应用的无奈。
想象中的快捷指令
现在应用商店的APP已经足够多，可以帮助人们解决足够多的问题，但有时候一款应用并不能完全解决某项任务，需要多个应用配合操作，如果用户可以随意调用应用中功能并组合成自己所需要完成特定任务的能力，那么用户体验和效率都将提升到新的高度。
想象一种场景，当我在观看自己感兴趣的外语视频时，因为语言的障碍可能不能足够理解视频内容，我需要一些辅助支持：我希望翻译软件能够帮我把外语翻译成母语，甚至希望语音合成软件将翻译后的语言读出来。孤立地看这个场景中的每个需求，都有应用能很好得实现：视频网站能够提供我感兴趣的内容，翻译软件能将语言进行较高准确度的翻译，语音合成软件能够将文字朗读出来。但是当这三个需求点分布在三个不同的APP时，用户就难以较高效率完成这个场景的任务。实际上每个APP的能力都被封锁在了自己APP里面。

上面说的这个场景我自己就有，但是因为没能使用现有工具很好使用，只得自己动手做了一个插件，可以朗读B站上面带有字幕的视频，因为微软的中文语音合成做得比较好，所以先放在Edge浏览器上了，目前还只支持带外挂字幕的视频，大家感兴趣也可以使用。

B站视频字幕朗读（中文同传）插件地址-> Microsoft Edge Addons
现实中的快捷指令
虽然当前快捷指令还不够优秀，但对于日常效率的提升还是有一定帮助的，特别是对于实现与苹果自带应用的互通。
举个使用的例子，每天早上我会用笔记软件记录一下昨日回顾、思考以及今日的计划，对于今日计划，我希望用待办应用去跟踪计划中事项的状态，但是手动把写过的东西在另一个APP里面再写一遍实在是太过愚蠢，于是我就写了快捷指令去实现。

实际使用中，只要选择对应的文本并在共享表单中点击对应的操作就可以同步到系统自带的提醒事项中，在mac上还可以添加快捷键一键实现（应该还可以通过「自动化」省去手动操作这一步）。
当前的快捷指令有三个亮点：

在快捷指令的编辑上采用图形化拖拽操作，相对于写脚本，这种操作显得更加友好，并且也可以支持自定义脚本的加入，甚至让我一度觉得学编程的第一个应用是用快捷指令写得；
在快捷指令的运行上打通了Siri、小组件以及共享操作，特别是后者，为与三方应用的结合提供了基础的平台；
加入了自动化功能，可以根据一定的规则直接省去了用户主动调用快捷指令这一步。

但要让更多的人在更多场景下使用快捷指令，还有着一些明显的不足：

上手使用上有一些门槛，官方没有详细的教程，虽然提供了一些案例，但是大多数人应该没有耐心仔细去看快捷中心中那些精选的指令是如何实现的，这点Mac上快捷指令前辈「自动操作」可能给点其启示，其中「录制」功能可以通过「我做给你看」自动识别操作中的事件；
快捷指令的分发做得还不够，既然不是每个人都能轻松使用快捷指令，那么获取现成的快捷指令则更加重要，但快捷指令中心中精选的指令本土化、个性化做得并不好，我觉得如果能根据用户所安装的APP来个性化分发常用的快捷指令会更友好；
三方应用的能力开放明显不足，大多数的使用场景还是围绕在苹果自带应用提供的能力，这点极大限制了快捷指令的应用场景；
使用Siri来激活快捷指令时对于指令的识别非常差，官方有说使用快捷指令的名称就可以通过Siri调用，但实际使用时不时语音识别不出来就是调用的指令不正确；

有趣的是，在WWDC2022中，我们看到苹果开始推广App Intent框架，通过为应用开发者提供更多系统级的入口曝光来吸引他们将其应用所能满足的用户意图曝光给系统，从而使得系统可以通过学习用户行为实现跨应用的能力整合。
结语
很多人即使生活中充满重复的事情也不会去探索提高效率方式，因为对比眼前简单的操作，去探究增进效率操作的所花费的学习努力带来的成本更加高，只是把时间线拉得足够远，才能看见效率提升所带来收益。
自动化所存在的意义是帮助人完成任务并节省时间，虽然我们每个人都已经拥有足够多的计算设备，但我们并没有充分发挥其拥有的算力，个人的自动化仍是一个尚待开发的领域。
期待未来的快捷指令能为个人的自动化增添更多的可能性。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>taofuns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[利用Selenium绕过前端js加密及验证码爆破]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11806</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11806"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T13:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[利用Selenium绕过前端js加密及验证码爆破]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（八）CSP篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11805</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11805"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T13:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（八）CSP篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Expands Flood and Wildfire Tracking to More Countries]]></title>
        <id>636458f56e26e2941c119d11</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/google-ai-wildfire-flood-tracking/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: Sony announces a release date and price for its next PlayStation VR headset, Google kills a couple more apps, and everything’s gone explosive at Twitter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boone Ashworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok Admits Staff in China Can Access Europeans’ Data]]></title>
        <id>636523a6dc213ea1c21ed12b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/tiktok-eu-privacy-policy-security-roundup/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: Liz Truss’ phone-hacking trouble, Cash App’s sex-trafficking problem, and the rising cost of ransomware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman, Andrew Couts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenRASP浅析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11803</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11803"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T05:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenRASP浅析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Has Fired Twitter’s ‘Ethical AI’ Team]]></title>
        <id>63651386d481f3fd793dde70</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-ethical-ai-team/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T16:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of a wave of layoffs, the new CEO disbanded a group working to make Twitter’s algorithms more transparent and fair.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Tiangong Space Station Makes China a Major Space Power]]></title>
        <id>636149741341ae5cc2594c3e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/china-is-now-a-major-space-power-tiangong-space-station/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the station's completion, the country now has a long-term platform in orbit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramin Skibba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The UN Climate Talks Are About to Face Maddening Uncertainties]]></title>
        <id>6361670a44675727a4dc55e1</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cop27-un-climate-talks-maddening-uncertainties/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At next week’s COP27 conference, negotiators need to get serious about massively reducing emissions—and fast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Barber, Matt Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APP+1｜用对工具，记账其实很轻松｜八款记账App评测]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76557</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76557"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T07:19:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[记账是我坚持得最久的习惯，到如今已经快4年。
期间有中断过，怀疑过，也尝试过很多不同的工具，发现用对工具的确轻松很多，也更容易坚持。今天就来跟大家分享下我记账这些年的心路历程，希望能帮到正在犹豫记账的你。
我会先讲下我是如何坚持记账，以及记账对我的改变，最后再分享记账应用（附带视频），只想看评测的话可以直接跳到最后哦。
一、如何开始记账
我之所以开始记账，也是因为发现自己每个月钱都不知花哪去了，所以想通过记账来了解自己的收支情况，让自己对生活掌控得更好。
一开始是消费一单就记一次，但太繁琐了，经常会忘记。所以就改成了每天固定睡前记账。但这样，依旧老是忘记，于是我设置了每晚10点的定时闹钟，效果就好很多了。等到养成习惯后，就再也不用设置闹钟了，以后一到那个点，脑子就自动提醒我记账，偶有遗忘，但也慢慢坚持下来了。而且因为我用打卡app，所以如果没记账，那天的记录就会为空，出于强迫症的原因，我也一定会把缺的那天补上。就这么不知不觉坚持了快4年。
但其实，我这种每一笔都记的方式还是比较费劲的，不一定适合所有人，我这里推荐两个降低难度的方式：

别全部都都记，这样太琐碎，而是设置一个额度，高于该额度的支出才记。
是充分利用记账应用，选择有自动同步账单功能，或者支持语音输入的记账应用，下面有推荐类似的App。

二、对记账的反思
那我这样记账4年下来的结果如何呢？
一方面，我的确因此免去了许多不必要的开支，存住了钱，对比起身边一些朋友，有储蓄更踏实，还可以把闲钱拿出来投资理财。
但另一方面，我也明显感觉自己似乎有点 落伍了......当同龄人在炫耀新买的电子产品、潮牌、口红包包时，当别人用钱堆出来一个时髦大方的形象时，其实很难不羡慕。可是让我去购买一些非必需品，这带来的罪恶感，又远大于我得到它的满足感。

是的，记账的习惯，让我的消费习惯变成了——只买有用的东西。
我评估一件东西是否值…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>余弦sine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Javascript Generators: A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/muqsitadam/javascript-generators-a-beginners-guide-1ojf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/muqsitadam/javascript-generators-a-beginners-guide-1ojf"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T23:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #beginners #webdev #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdulmuqsit Adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Harms of Psychedelics Need to Be Put Into Context]]></title>
        <id>636420c37ee13002222188f2</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/psychedelics-side-effects/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T20:14:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As psychedelic therapy trials get bigger and the drugs become more accessible, researchers need to start talking about their potential adverse effects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grace Browne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[最近遇到的Linux内核内存取证小分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11800</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11800"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T18:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[最近遇到的Linux内核内存取证小分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[webpagetest反序列化及ssrf漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11798</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11798"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T17:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[webpagetest反序列化及ssrf漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOLBIN-使用卡巴斯基终端“KES”安装程序执行任意命令]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11797</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11797"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T16:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LOLBIN-使用卡巴斯基终端“KES”安装程序执行任意命令]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[揭秘 2022 诺贝尔物理学奖：量子纠缠与贝尔不等式]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76592</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76592"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T13:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐 
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。 
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

瑞典时间 10 月 4 日上午，诺贝尔奖委员会宣布 2022 年诺贝尔物理学奖授予阿兰·阿斯佩克特 (Alain Aspect)、约翰·克劳瑟 (John F. Clauser) 和安东·泽林格 (Anton Zeilinger)，以表彰他们 「进行了纠缠光子的实验，确立了对贝尔不等式的不成立并开创了量子信息科学」。阿兰·阿斯佩克特、约翰·克劳瑟和安东·泽林格分别利用处于相互纠缠的量子态进行了突破性的实验。在这种情况下，两个粒子即使被分开也表现得如同一个整体。他们的成果为基于量子信息的新技术扫清了道路。
—— 摘自诺贝尔物理学奖官方新闻稿

说实话，在诺贝尔奖委员会正式宣布量子纠缠相关的成果获奖后，我立刻就意识到，互联网上很快就会充斥着各种针对量子纠缠以及量子世界的神秘性相关的科普。这些科普，无论是原创的还是东拼西凑的，无论是专家学者起草的还是各路内容流水线上生产的，都有一个共同的特征：它们往往都喜欢强化量子物理的神秘性和不可理解。
我承认，历史上确实有这么一段时间，即使是 20 世纪初期那些鼎鼎大名的物理学家，都曾为量子相关的物理现象感到困惑。然而，经过一百多年的发展，量子物理的诸多核心概念早就被一代又一代的物理学家里里外外地玩了个遍，以至于许多被科普作家渲染得神乎其神的概念，现正躺在物理系本科生的必修课教材里。
当然，量子力学有它反直觉的地方。但是，现实生活中反直觉的事情还少吗？反直觉并不意味着神秘或不可理解。它只是需要你屏蔽你的许多生活常识，用绝对的理性来思考问题。所以，这篇文章会和你读过的绝大部分科普不同，我不会把量子…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>影转细枫</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Artists: Do Not Fear AI Image Generators]]></title>
        <id>61ba7c7ba08cdc8657dc4958</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/artists-do-not-fear-ai-image-generators/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[True, new systems devalue craft, shift power, and wreck cultures and scenes. But didn’t the piano do that to the harpsichord?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Ford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Algorithms Quietly Run the City of Washington, DC—and Maybe Your Hometown]]></title>
        <id>63617b2dd5a8378824123f92</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/algorithms-quietly-run-the-city-of-dc-and-maybe-your-hometown/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report finds that municipal agencies in Washington deploy dozens of automated decision systems, often without residents’ knowledge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khari Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sci-Fi Dream of a ‘Molecular Computer’ Is Getting More Real]]></title>
        <id>63596e2f81a87b1d767e38f6</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-sci-fi-dream-of-a-molecular-computer-is-getting-more-real/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chemists have long conceptualized tiny machines that could fabricate drugs, plastics, and other polymers that are hard to build with bigger tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max G. Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Peaceful Crowds Turn Into a Deadly Crush]]></title>
        <id>6361724999fe777052767a68</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-peaceful-crowds-turn-into-a-deadly-crush/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It doesn’t take stampeding or unruly behavior to result in massive tragedies like the one in Itaewon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amanda Hoover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Soccer Fans, You're Being Watched]]></title>
        <id>636299d7a9269ef97e4efe41</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/soccer-world-cup-biometric-surveillance/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stadiums around the world, including at the 2022 World Cup in Qatar, are subjecting spectators to invasive biometric surveillance tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vas Panagiotopoulos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[入烧HiFi五年后，这台低端播放器治好了我的精神内耗]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76568</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76568"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T08:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[引言：用惯旗舰的我，为啥突然自购了一台入门DAP？

我承认，这个标题有点蹭过时热搜的标题党嫌疑；但作为一个有着五六年HiFi设备购买经验、分享却极其佛系的用户，收获不能说是经验丰富吧，至少也能说是白忙一场；自从三年以前第一次入手了旗舰级的KANN CUBE之后，为了追求“好马配好鞍”，在便携领域各种入手搭配的旗舰耳塞线材套装，洒出去的钱也有个五位数往上了。虽然标题上写着是对节奏坦克新款播放器V6的体验，但从某种程度上来说，这篇文章也算是玩了这么久的HiFi设备之后，一篇简单的自我回顾和反思文章。
在半个月前，我绝对不可能相信听惯了“旗舰级DAP”的自己会甘于使用一台中低端价位的播放器，即便中低端播放器近年来也的确出现过不少声音表现优秀、拉动价位甚至行业疯狂内卷的机器，但高端播放器毕竟有自己的能力与气场：作为品牌的旗舰，一般都有着最好的用料、最新的功能配置、最前沿的DAC芯片——著名的Astell&Kern甚至没事就和上游的旭化成深度合作，三代SP系列几乎成为AKM全新旗舰DAC的首发平台；同时也倾注着品牌最优秀的音乐理解。
很显然，这些资源优势都是一般中低端播放器很难获得的，所以我现在依旧不怀疑“正经厂牌的高端播放器在综合素质表现上必然优于中低端产品”；以上观点也不代表我认为“所有人都必须和我一样不买个几万块东西就别想快乐听歌”，如果你的天桥9.9耳机已经让你非常快乐，那太好了，什么设备都理应有快乐听歌的权利。我开始怀疑的是，每天没事盯着见底的工资卡、紧了吧唧的盘算着怎么搭配耳机播放器，导致我个人的生活多了一堆需要计较的大小事，这些真的能让我听歌的过程变得更“快乐”吗？

因此这半个月的时间刚好给了我一个机会，你也可以认为这种机会比较祸福相依：我自购的SP1000在半个月前，因为某些极其离谱的外部非质量原因，不慎导致2.5mm接口损坏，被迫返厂维修。设备虽然要修，歌却不能…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JeromeShaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（七）技巧篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11795</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11795"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T08:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（七）技巧篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome扩展安全开发从零到一]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11794</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11794"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T04:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome扩展安全开发从零到一]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[某路由器固件模拟分析及栈溢出漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11793</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11793"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T03:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[某路由器固件模拟分析及栈溢出漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[从高亮到输出：如何用 Readwise 一站式优化你的阅读笔记流程？]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76574</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76574"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T01:24:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[痛点
想想看，平时在阅读上，你做了多少无用功？
勤勤恳恳阅读，认认真真做好高亮批注。你看到自己的思考结果与文章或者书中的文字融于一体，觉得特别安心。
然而，当你需要整理或者调用这些笔记的时候，才发现它们如同断线的珠子，散落在各种地方：
RSS 阅读内容在 feedspot 里； 微信公众号的高亮在 Instapaper 里；Epub 标记在 Marginnote 里；PDF 的高亮和批注在 LiquidText 里面…… 如果不加整理，它们就会在不同的应用中终老。
问题来了，该怎么整理这些散落的阅读笔记？
有的人并不觉得这是个棘手的事情。他们的作息时间，如同钟表一般规律。可以做到每天晚上专门花时间，雷打不动把这些内容整理出来，做好分类，放在 Evernote 或者 Obsidian 里。
但是，这种方法，对于懒人显然不友好。至少我自己，就笃定无法日复一日坚持下去。即便我希望能持续一周这样操作，恐怕都得专门雇个人在旁边监督自己。
幸好，技术的进步使我们不用活得那么悲摧。有一些工具可以帮助我们汇集各种资料，尤其是帮你保管阅读记录和高亮、批注。更好的消息，是这些工具有很多，例如 Readwise, Matter, Diigo, Cubox 和简悦（Simpread）等。
本文我就以自己常用的 Readwise 为例，为你介绍如何自动化汇集整理和利用笔记。希望这些经验也能够帮到你，早日摆脱手动整理阅读笔记的困扰。
Readwise
我是 2020 年 4 月开始使用 Readwise 的。7 天试用期过后，我发邮件找 Readwise 官方申请了个教育优惠，就开始使用了。

Readwise 的特点，是支持非常广泛的信息输入来源，例如我这里已经连接的来源包括 Kindle, Instapaper, Medium, Airr, Twitter, Apple Books 等等。

我在…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>玉树芝兰</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise of Rust, the ‘Viral’ Secure Programming Language That’s Taking Over Tech]]></title>
        <id>63582f1fbb31765d3acdfb15</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/rust-secure-programming-language-memory-safe/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T18:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rust makes it impossible to introduce some of the most common security vulnerabilities. And its adoption can’t come soon enough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to add PayPal checkout payments to your React app]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/paypaldeveloper/how-to-add-paypal-checkout-payments-to-your-react-app-53aa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/paypaldeveloper/how-to-add-paypal-checkout-payments-to-your-react-app-53aa"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T17:25:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #react #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pato, PayPal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make the most of DEV if you’re over Twitter]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devteam/how-to-make-the-most-of-dev-if-youre-over-twitter-4567</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devteam/how-to-make-the-most-of-dev-if-youre-over-twitter-4567"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T13:24:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#watercooler #meta #twitter #career]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Halpern, The DEV Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seeking Psychedelics? Check the Data Privacy Clause]]></title>
        <id>635ae105a398fb738c4b9234</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/colorado-psychedelics-health-privacy-surveillance/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colorado's Proposition 122 wants to let people take psilocybin at healing centers. But sensitive data isn't covered by medical privacy protections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mason Marks</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Vulnerable Place on the Internet]]></title>
        <id>6361b2a70b9dedd635bdb001</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/submarine-internet-cables-egypt/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Underwater cables keep the internet online. When they congregate in one place, things get tricky.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips to become a great software engineer]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jamielivingstone/tips-to-become-a-great-software-engineer-10gf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jamielivingstone/tips-to-become-a-great-software-engineer-10gf"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T10:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#career #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Livingstone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a registration and a login with two-factor authentication on React 🤩]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/novu/creating-a-registration-and-a-login-with-two-factor-authentication-on-react-2p2i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/novu/creating-a-registration-and-a-login-with-two-factor-authentication-on-react-2p2i"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T10:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #node #webdev #javascript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevo David, novu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[浅析NodeJS]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11791</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11791"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T07:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[浅析NodeJS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API安全漏洞靶场crapi的基本介绍和解题思路-第二篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11789</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11789"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T06:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[API安全漏洞靶场crapi的基本介绍和解题思路-第二篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iA Presenter 初体验]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76540</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76540"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T06:20:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iA Writer 是一款非常著名的，以简洁优美的界面和不错的使用体验著称的 Markdown 写作软件（虽然我没用过）。而最近，iA Writer 的开发商 iA.net 发布了一款名为 iA Presenter 的幻灯片制作软件，旨在通过简单的 Markdown 创作出精美的幻灯片。
市面上制作幻灯片的软件已经是数不胜数，除了常见的 PowerPoint、Keynote，还有基于 HTML5 技术的 Prezi、reveal.js、Canva 等，基于文档生成幻灯片的软件也有不少，比如双链笔记软件 Obsidian、文档工具语雀、飞书文档、石墨文档都有演示模式。
在这么多软件之中，iA Presenter 又有哪些优势，值得我们从繁杂的工作中抬起头来呢。
首先说明一下，目前 iA Presenter 还处于一个非常早期的阶段，文中提到的一些内容随时可能会因为软件的版本更新而发生变更。
另外，下文中会将 iA Presenter 简称为 iA Pre。
在此，也感谢 @南山居氪 提供的 iA Presenter 的邀请码。
PowerPoint 发生了什么
似乎现在很多软件都在以一种革命性的姿态来发布——认为自己的诞生能够颠覆一个行业，至少在发布时会伴随着一些阐述自己设计哲学的文章。Roam 和 Arc 是如此，iA Pre 也有些这样的味道。
iA 在其新闻页面上发了两篇文章，主要在说 PowerPoint 等传统幻灯片工具有什么问题，和 iA Pre 怎样使幻灯片更好？。
在第一篇文章1中，iA 认为，以 PPT 为代表的传统幻灯片工具有着入门难、耗时长、会让演讲者忘记他想说的东西、以及搭配 PPT 的演讲大多很无聊，这种无聊是我们的职业杀手以及事业杀手。
iA 怎样使幻灯片更好？
而在第二篇文章2中，iA 提出了他们认为的让演讲和幻灯片制作变得更好的方法：
内容上
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aiokr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML & CSS Features, Tips For a 10x Faster Page Loading Speed]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/koustav/html-css-features-tips-for-a-10x-fast-page-loading-speed-4jop</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/koustav/html-css-features-tips-for-a-10x-fast-page-loading-speed-4jop"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T05:19:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#news #webdev #html #css]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>devkoustav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（六）续集篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11788</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11788"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T04:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（六）续集篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（五）最终篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11790</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11790"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T02:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（五）最终篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 7 Best React Component Libraries to Use in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/amrtcrypto/the-7-best-react-component-libraries-to-use-in-2022-11la</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/amrtcrypto/the-7-best-react-component-libraries-to-use-in-2022-11la"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T18:10:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #react #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amr Tawfik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Your Neighbor Turns You In]]></title>
        <id>635fdf932315f22f91833a36</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/authoritarian-us-neighbors-spy-report/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authoritarian societies depend on people ratting each other out for activities that were recently legal—and it's already happening in the US.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thor Benson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[通过边界代理一路打到三层内网+后渗透通用手法]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11784</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11784"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T02:08:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[通过边界代理一路打到三层内网+后渗透通用手法]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IPC$共享利用姿势]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11783</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11783"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T02:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IPC$共享利用姿势]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[初步理解Phar反序列化 + 分析POP链构造（2022 Bilibili 1024 程序员节第二题）]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11782</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11782"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T01:29:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[初步理解Phar反序列化 + 分析POP链构造（2022 Bilibili 1024 程序员节第二题）]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Need to Update Google Chrome, Windows, and Zoom Right Now]]></title>
        <id>635c5bbfa8552c961517a88e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/google-chrome-windows-zoom-critical-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: Important patches from Apple, VMWare, Cisco, Zimbra, SAP, and Oracle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate O'Flaherty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Folder Structure for NodeJS & ExpressJS project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mr_ali3n/folder-structure-for-nodejs-expressjs-project-435l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mr_ali3n/folder-structure-for-nodejs-expressjs-project-435l"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T09:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#express #javascript #node #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vaibhav Mehta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Docker Extensions Every Developer Must Try]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/docker/9-docker-extensions-every-developer-must-try-1no2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/docker/9-docker-extensions-every-developer-must-try-1no2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T07:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#docker #devops #kubernetes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pavan Belagatti, Docker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[走出内卷牢笼，拥抱无限游戏的自由｜荐书《有限与无限的游戏》]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76484</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76484"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T07:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[很多人会把人生比喻为游戏，因为都需要在既定的规则下，和他人同台竞争谋求最大胜利，读书时的升学排名，就业后岗位的激烈竞争，无一不是要决出个胜负，每个人都要追求赢。
但我们可能从来没有想过，除了参加有输赢的游戏，其实我们还可以选择另一种游戏——没有输赢，可以持续玩下去的游戏。
这便是《有限与无限的游戏》中的观点，它认为世界上至少有有限和无限两种游戏，有限游戏以获胜为目的，无限游戏以延续游戏为目的。
很神奇的是，我之前从《游戏改变世界》这本书中首次知晓该理论时，只是觉得有意思，但对我并没什么启发。

可是真的当我自己看完这本20万字的小书后，对我的影响却是立竿见影的。我读完隔天，在工作上和同事发生冲突时，脑子里一直在想着“不行，我不能像对方一样发火，我要玩的是无限游戏，争一时的输赢的玩不下去了”，因此就忍住了火气，最终也顺利解决了问题。
所以呢今天也为大家推荐这本书，看完后你一定会觉得，哇，原来有些竞争是根本没必要投入的，原来选择还可以有这么多，生活的改变从心态的改变开始，相信你也可以和我一样豁然开朗！
不过该书其实是本哲学书，理解和解读起来有一定难度，而且写法更偏意识流，作者没有特意去构建严密的框架和推理，甚至全书中作者自己都没有直接发表过「无限游戏更好」的结论，所以我会加入个人的理解去解读以便更好地介绍，但我也只是抛砖引玉，建议大家过后去看全书。
一、有限与无限游戏的基本概念
有限游戏有三个显著特征。

它是以取胜为目的，一旦决出胜负则游戏结束，所以称之为有限游戏，注意这里的胜负必须是所有参与者认同，而不是裁判或观众认同。
参与者只能在游戏界限内进行游戏。
有限游戏的规则一经所有参与者认同就生效，且不能改变，否则就是另一个游戏了。

怎么样，听起来是不是很熟悉，几乎跟我们从小到大遇到的竞争一个模式。而无限游戏则恰好是跟它反着来的，它也有三个相对的显特征。

它并非以取胜为目的…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>余弦sine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Election That Saved the Internet From Russia and China]]></title>
        <id>635c726aa8552c961517a891</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/itu-2022-vote-russia-china-open-internet/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-30T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open-internet advocates are breathing a sigh of relief after a recent election for the International Telecommunications Union's top leadership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Ling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Shorthand Optimization Tricks every JavaScript Developer Should Know 😎]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/7-shorthand-optimization-tricks-every-javascript-developer-should-know-4fj5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/7-shorthand-optimization-tricks-every-javascript-developer-should-know-4fj5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-30T06:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #programming #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapajyoti Bose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【键帽大盘点】红红火火，盘点那些火热的键帽——红、橙色系（一）]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76473</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76473"/>
        <updated>2022-10-30T03:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[本专栏所使用资料来源于网络，欢迎友好讨论
上几篇专栏介绍了绿色系、蓝色系，自然少不了光学三原色的另一名成员——红色。这一期来讲讲红色系键帽，方便各位键友选购搭配自己的梦中情键。

GMK Red Samurai 红武士
R1 2018.2 R2 2020
BASE
这套键帽是由设计师Redsun（红太阳）设计而成，同时他也是GMK蓝武士的设计师，gmk四大武士中的两款由他设计。关于这套键帽的灵感来源有两个版本。
在R1的IC中。

作者表示灵感来自于火影忍者中宇智波斑的铠甲颜色

而在R2中

作者则表示灵感来源于井伊直政（日本历史角色）
关于作者灵感来源，我还是更加倾向于R1中的说法，而为何要改口，可能是为了规避版权问题，但我个人觉得，在红武士中其实并不能看出过多来自于漫画中的角色要素，并且忍者和武士也是两种职业，作者关于忍者和武士的定义，好像也并没有非常清晰。
配色：

暗黄、深红、灰黑，低调而不失深度的配色，黑红相间配以金色点缀，经典耐看。
个性部分：

这一套的个性数量和种类都非常丰富“忍”“侍”，其实这一套键帽虽然称之为武士，但里面也融合了非常多忍者的元素，在武器类型中“飞镰”、“团扇”、“手里剑”、“苦无”，都是非常常见的忍者标志性武器，还有一些不明所以的图案。
其实这位作者在R1中的早期个性设计，是带有浓烈火影忍者特色的。
早期个性设计
穿着盔甲的天狗，很显然是宇智波斑的须佐能乎，以及极其明显的神威万花筒写轮眼图案。
但在最终敲定版本中为了规避版权问题进行了大刀阔斧的修改，最终便呈现出一个极具忍者风味的武士主题键帽。
搭配展示：
落叶随风拍摄Pecufo'拍摄Vanthic Noel拍摄是丶你的益达拍摄
搭配建议：
深色无疑是合适的，这套键帽很是百搭，红色、蓝色、黄色，都能驾驭，我个人最喜欢灰色和黑色进行搭配，红色也是很不错的，但过于鲜亮的颜色搭配起来难度还是…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>车不能快</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[談談大衆對形碼的誤解]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76483</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76483"/>
        <updated>2022-10-30T00:44:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[相信大部份人用的都是拼音輸入法。
學會一個非拼音的中文輸入法，是一件好玩的事，這是一項實用的技能，能證明你的智商和學習能力。
以後搞博客，工作，寫作，成為作家，跟人聊天，等等很多地方都能用上。
其實很多人對「形碼」還存在誤解。

誤解一，除了拼音就是五筆。
其實形碼是一衆不以拼音而是字形部件組合來輸入中文的方法。著名的有：倉頡、鄭碼、五筆，等等。
其中五筆是最有名，但又是最難學最難用的。
誤解二，形碼一定比拼音快。
其實形碼並不一定比拼音快，比如我用倉頡打「哈哈哈哈」，我輸入的是「romr romr romr romr 」，而拼音只需要輸入「hhhh 」。
也就是說，在某些特定場合，拼音，簡拼，比形碼還要快。
那形碼的優點是甚麼？形碼不是快，而是準。形碼人的思維是，如果連準確輸入都做不到，那快有甚麼用？
誤解三，五筆（形碼）很難，要背很多字根。
其實是因為五筆的字根太多太難背，才會給人這樣的感受。我用過五筆兩年，我也承認背字根是一個非常高的門檻。
但是，並不是所有形碼都跟五筆一樣難背。倉頡輸入法的字元就比五筆少很多，好記很多，記下根本不費吹灰之力。
誤解四，學個輸入法要浪費很多時間，學會了也沒甚麼用。
這是極其錯誤的想法。中文打字，不管到哪裏，都是實用的技能。現在網上到處都是同音錯字，比如「再在」不分，就是因為拼音輸入法根本打不準。那麼如果你跟別人文字聊天時，或者發表文章時，能做到用字準確，那不就是一個加分項嗎？
因此，花費一點時間，去學一個形碼，是事半功倍的事。一個好的中文輸入法，是可以用一輩子的。而你只需要用掉幾日的時間來學習。

先寫到這裏。我是中文輸入法專家尹卂，目前在用倉頡。有甚麼問題可以在下方留言。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ejsoon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Startups Have a Sellout Problem. There's a Better Way]]></title>
        <id>63481d9808a267a4aad8c050</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/startups-exit-community-ipo-business/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-29T13:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Startups like Meta and Twitter serve as digital infrastructure, but aren't accountable to users. Some startups are trying to chart a new way to exit that focuses on community—not shareholders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED Ideas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[某软件监控页面RCE漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11778</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11778"/>
        <updated>2022-10-29T13:22:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[某软件监控页面RCE漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Operates Secret ‘Police Stations’ in Other Countries]]></title>
        <id>635c2916a398fb738c4b9262</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/china-police-stations-security-roundup/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: The New York Post gets hacked, a huge stalkerware network is exposed, and the US claims China interfered with its Huawei probe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If Musk Starts Firing Twitter's Security Team, Run]]></title>
        <id>635be73651d3e1e46809f063</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-twitter-security-privacy-risks/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T22:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What's next for the social network is anyone's guess—but here's what to watch as you wade through the privacy and security morass.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Type-Safe TypeScript with Type Narrowing]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/type-safe-typescript-with-type-narrowing-5930</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-learning/type-safe-typescript-with-type-narrowing-5930"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T19:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#typescript #javascript #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rainer Hahnekamp, This is Learning</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art of Hitting Disinformation Where It Lives]]></title>
        <id>6356a50d3d83d1af9973abd3</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/disinformation-art-science/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Combating fake news with facts doesn't work because humans are wired for emotion. It's time for more creative tactics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Southern</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk’s Twitter Will Not Be the Town Square the World Needs]]></title>
        <id>635af6043d7842cc349a2206</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-twitter-town-square/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T12:54:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a moment to choose a different path, inspired by the lessons of thriving offline communities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Pariser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe Prepares to Rewrite the Rules of the Internet]]></title>
        <id>6359871f68addec416d5b940</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/europe-dma-prepares-to-rewrite-the-rules-of-the-internet/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Digital Markets Act will force Big Tech platforms to break open their walled gardens in 2023, says the EU’s new ambassador to Silicon Valley.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khari Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome Extensions of the Month - October 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/j471n/chrome-extensions-of-the-month-october-2022-1c0j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/j471n/chrome-extensions-of-the-month-october-2022-1c0j"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T06:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#productivity #webdev #javascript #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jatin Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Master The Art of Content Creation As a Developer?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/patilganesh1010/how-to-master-the-art-of-content-creation-as-a-developer-kpn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/patilganesh1010/how-to-master-the-art-of-content-creation-as-a-developer-kpn"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T03:18:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #tutorial #opensource #career]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Patil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 must-know tips for writing clean code with Javascript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexomeyer/8-must-know-tips-for-writing-clean-code-with-javascript-i4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexomeyer/8-must-know-tips-for-writing-clean-code-with-javascript-i4"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T13:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #refactorit #webdev #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Omeyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Listening to Audiobooks Really Reading?]]></title>
        <id>6312405ea4a22698f6d24aaf</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/is-listening-to-audiobooks-really-reading/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WIRED’s spiritual advice columnist on bardic traditions for a modern age—and why book snobs worry about the wrong things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meghan O'Gieblyn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI's New Creative Streak Sparks a Silicon Valley Gold Rush]]></title>
        <id>635811513c668b3d581922aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ais-new-creative-streak-sparks-a-silicon-valley-gold-rush/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors have got the hots for "generative AI" that can make text and images. But so far, the hype runs ahead of the business results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a VS Code Extension "Todo Tree" can make your coding easier | Todo Tree Configuration | Highlighting Comments in VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/koustav/how-a-vs-code-extension-todo-tree-can-make-your-coding-easier-todo-tree-configuration-and-use-cases-11kc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/koustav/how-a-vs-code-extension-todo-tree-can-make-your-coding-easier-todo-tree-configuration-and-use-cases-11kc"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T05:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#news #vscode #programming #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>devkoustav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM PASS PWN (三)]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11775</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11775"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T01:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM PASS PWN (三)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Real Reason Elon Musk Wants You to Have More Babies]]></title>
        <id>61ba7bbc63820b7f88293089</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/real-reason-elon-musk-population-panic/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People who complain about population aren’t talking numbers—they’re fantasizing about tightening the reins on workers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Virginia Heffernan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[记一次某CMS代码审计]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11774</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11774"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T10:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[记一次某CMS代码审计]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-41852 Apache Commons Jxpath 漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11769</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11769"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T07:29:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-41852 Apache Commons Jxpath 漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hinge Will Try to Thwart Scammers With Video Verification]]></title>
        <id>6356e6b3a8552c961517a850</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hinge-selfie-verification-scammers-bots/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T14:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To combat the scourge of bots and fake accounts, the dating site will ask users to prove their humanity by capturing a video selfie.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Goode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made 10x faster JSON.stringify() functions, even type safe]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/samchon/i-made-10x-faster-jsonstringify-functions-even-type-safe-2eme</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/samchon/i-made-10x-faster-jsonstringify-functions-even-type-safe-2eme"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T12:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #programming #typescript #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeongho Nam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pandemic Uncovered Ways to Speed Up Science]]></title>
        <id>6346eb34f93a1584dc57f38b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/covid-19-open-science-public-health-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There doesn't have to be a trade-off between good research and fast research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saloni Dattani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Please do repeat yourself (DRY is dead)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ralphcone/please-do-repeat-yourself-dry-is-dead-1jbg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ralphcone/please-do-repeat-yourself-dry-is-dead-1jbg"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T20:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#productivity #beginners #codenewbie]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rafal Stozek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Notion-like system with Socket.io And React 😍]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/novu/building-a-notion-like-system-with-socketio-and-react-1hjg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/novu/building-a-notion-like-system-with-socketio-and-react-1hjg"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T12:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #react #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevo David, novu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awesome Websites For UI/UX Inspiration]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-websites-for-uiux-inspiration-5h75</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-websites-for-uiux-inspiration-5h75"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#ux #css #beginners #javascript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Vishwakarma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inversion of Control: Service Locator in Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/inversion-of-control-dependency-injection-in-typescript-1dj9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/inversion-of-control-dependency-injection-in-typescript-1dj9"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T06:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#typescript #webdev #programming #javascript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cristian-Florin Calina, This is Angular</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a multi-language website using React in 3 minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/quocbahuynh/build-a-multi-language-website-using-react-in-3-minutes-4206</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/quocbahuynh/build-a-multi-language-website-using-react-in-3-minutes-4206"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T18:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #javascript #beginners #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>quocbahuynh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Javascript Shallow Copy - what is a Shallow Copy?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/smpnjn/javascript-shallow-copy-what-is-a-shallow-copy-1pc5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/smpnjn/javascript-shallow-copy-what-is-a-shallow-copy-1pc5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T19:43:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #typescript #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Johnny Simpson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Patterns in Software Development]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abdurrkhalid333/design-patterns-in-software-development-4b82</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abdurrkhalid333/design-patterns-in-software-development-4b82"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T19:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#tutorial #opensource #productivity #community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdur Rehman Khalid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Things Strong Developers Do That Drive Their Team Crazy]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jenc/things-strong-developers-do-that-drives-the-team-around-them-crazy-437a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jenc/things-strong-developers-do-that-drives-the-team-around-them-crazy-437a"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T14:40:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#career #senior #intermediate #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jen chan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New git guidelines: We have switched to Conventional Commits]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/visuellverstehen/new-git-guidelines-we-have-switched-to-conventional-commits-1p0c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/visuellverstehen/new-git-guidelines-we-have-switched-to-conventional-commits-1p0c"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T08:28:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#git #webdev #programming #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Malte Riechmann, visuellverstehen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These 10 free APIs will take your programming projects to the next level 👇]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/elliot_brenyasarfo_18749/these-10-free-apis-will-take-your-programming-projects-to-the-next-level-5g24</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/elliot_brenyasarfo_18749/these-10-free-apis-will-take-your-programming-projects-to-the-next-level-5g24"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T08:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #programming #react #javascript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elliot Brenya sarfo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware the Distraction of the Twitter Mob Campaign]]></title>
        <id>635129452721236bcb15848f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hellena-taylor-bayonnetta-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A kerfuffle over Bayonetta voice actor Hellena Taylor’s pay reveals the often hollow structure of social media activism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katherine Cross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazy Loading in images with React JS 😴]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/franklin030601/lazy-loading-in-images-with-react-js-4enm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/franklin030601/lazy-loading-in-images-with-react-js-4enm"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #javascript #performance #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Franklin Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine Could Never Afford to Bet on Starlink]]></title>
        <id>635026f3f1f6a083059bc054</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-starlink-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The internet service tool was essential in the early days of the war with Russia. But the caprices of SpaceX CEO Elon Musk have exposed dangerous flaws.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katherine Cross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Re-Wrote These 10+ Single Lines of JavaScript Code, the Team Lead Praised the Code for Being Elegant]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rida/i-re-wrote-these-10-single-lines-of-javascript-code-the-team-lead-praised-the-code-for-being-elegant-ec</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rida/i-re-wrote-these-10-single-lines-of-javascript-code-the-team-lead-praised-the-code-for-being-elegant-ec"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T04:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #beginners #programming #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rida F&amp;#39;kih</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run your README.md like a notebook in VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sourishkrout/run-your-readmemd-in-vs-code-50l7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sourishkrout/run-your-readmemd-in-vs-code-50l7"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T01:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#vscode #opensource #beginners #devops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Tiedtke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran's Internet Blackouts Are Part of a Global Menace]]></title>
        <id>634db7f67e817d200a6cc6ba</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/iran-mahsa-amini-internet-shutdown/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Repressive regimes are teaching each other how to control protesters' web access with increasingly surgical precision.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yasmin Green</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made a full-stack and type-safe personal site using the t3-stack (Next.js)!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/asheeshh/i-made-a-full-stack-portfolio-site-using-nextjs-and-tailwind-366d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/asheeshh/i-made-a-full-stack-portfolio-site-using-nextjs-and-tailwind-366d"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T18:22:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #beginners #react]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ashish</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Section 230’s Fate Belongs With Congress—Not the US Supreme Court]]></title>
        <id>634d5fefd8c7bf0344fc40bf</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/section-230-scotus-gonzalez-google/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A case heading to SCOTUS claims platforms should be held responsible for their algorithmic recommendations. A history of the statute suggests otherwise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Kosseff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Video Game Store with Medusa and Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/medusajs/how-to-build-a-video-game-store-with-medusa-and-nextjs-kem</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/medusajs/how-to-build-a-video-game-store-with-medusa-and-nextjs-kem"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T11:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #programming #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekekenta Odioyenfe .C, Medusa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Unnatural Future of Physics]]></title>
        <id>6346eaba136a8fc35853e3f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/unnatural-future-physics/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To get a sense of how physicists might solve the “naturalness problem,” I contacted one who calls himself “a deviant by default.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KC Cole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is CORS?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jpomykala/what-is-cors-11kf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jpomykala/what-is-cors-11kf"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T09:36:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #react #webdev #typescript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakub Pomykała</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bruce Willis Deepfake Is Everyone’s Problem]]></title>
        <id>634d9b9173d8e1a1ebea929e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/bruce-willis-deepfake-rights-law/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T18:19:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a fight brewing over how Hollywood stars can protect their identities. But it’s not just actors who should be paying attention.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Bedingfield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a chat app with Socket.io and React Native 🤯]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/novu/building-a-chat-app-with-socketio-and-react-native-k1b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/novu/building-a-chat-app-with-socketio-and-react-native-k1b"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T11:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #programming #reactnative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevo David, novu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Restful API with Golang practical approach]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/firdavs_kasymov/restful-api-with-golang-practical-approach-420a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/firdavs_kasymov/restful-api-with-golang-practical-approach-420a"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T08:42:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#go #tutorial #microservices #devops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Firdavs Kasymov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM PASS PWN (二)]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11768</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11768"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T08:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM PASS PWN (二)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to write a good README]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/merlos/how-to-write-a-good-readme-bog</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/merlos/how-to-write-a-good-readme-bog"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T04:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#github #git #writing #documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merlos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一种隐蔽的利用Django中间件（Middleware）留后门的方法]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11766</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11766"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T02:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一种隐蔽的利用Django中间件（Middleware）留后门的方法]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IIS下.Net 的预编译模式]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11765</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11765"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T02:09:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IIS下.Net 的预编译模式]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SystemTap在应急排查中的应用]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11764</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11764"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T01:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SystemTap在应急排查中的应用]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why We're Breaking Up with CSS-in-JS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/srmagura/why-were-breaking-up-wiht-css-in-js-4g9b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/srmagura/why-were-breaking-up-wiht-css-in-js-4g9b"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T19:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #react #css #typescript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Magura</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Cool Things Boring Old HTML Can Do 🤯]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/6-cool-things-boring-old-html-can-do-3160</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/6-cool-things-boring-old-html-can-do-3160"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T07:17:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #programming #html #javascript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapajyoti Bose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>