<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-11-23T10:39:45.959Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-11-23T10:39:45.959Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wednesday’s top tech news: Hurray for foldable competition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/23/23474840/november-23-2022-tech-news-liveblog</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/23/23474840/november-23-2022-tech-news-liveblog"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T10:16:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newly announced Honor Magic VS. | Image: Honor
    

  
Honor’s second foldable will eventually release outside of China, and people are getting confused about a new car logo.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Best Free Platforms for Hosting Hobby Web Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/refine/5-best-free-platforms-for-hosting-hobby-web-projects-1pjo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/refine/5-best-free-platforms-for-hosting-hobby-web-projects-1pjo"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T10:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Joseph  Mawa
Most developers spend a significant proportion of their private time building side projects. These projects come in different forms and sizes. More often than not, you need to temporarily host these projects on a platform to test, showcase, or obtain feedback.
There are several hosting platforms. Each platform has its strengths and weaknesses. The choice of a hosting platform largely depends on the framework and whether the project you want to host is a back-end, front-end, or full-stack application. Similarly, choose a platform that offers a generous free plan when building a hobby project.
This article will explore the top five platforms with generous free hosting plans. We will highlight how to deploy to these hosting platforms, their strengths, and weaknesses, and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Necati Özmen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We fired you, but keep on working until the last day!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robencom/we-fired-you-but-keep-on-working-until-the-last-day-3gj1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robencom/we-fired-you-but-keep-on-working-until-the-last-day-3gj1"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T09:59:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the last couple of months, my company couldn't find me a project to work on. They work on outsourcing. 
So, about a month ago, they summoned me to the office and told me that they need to let me go, because they still cannot find a project for me. They said I've got 2 months to find a job, so they would give me 2 months salary all the way to the end of December, after which I am officially fired from this company.
Cool, at least they kicked me out with 2 months notice and 2 full salaries.
I actively started looking for a job, KEEP IN MIND that the IT hiring situation globally is in a mess, ALSO it is November/December, the 2 WORST months to get hired, as people would be distracted by holidays and so on...
1 week after that discussion with my boss, he told me that he found me a small project. Hooray, I'm not getting fired after all. No no, you are still getting fired, said the BOSS, but do this project until you leave, WE ARE COVERING IT AFTERALL...
WHAT?? So you want me to shift my focus from finding a job and do your stupid project until I leave? 
Listen, finding a job in our market today is very hard, especially for a backend developer. So I am learning couple (not one) of frontend frameworks and bunch of other HIPPPP technologies so I can FINALLY get hired. I do NOT afford to spend time doing a STUPID project for the company that fired me for not finding a PROJECT for me!!!
What do you think??? What should I do? Should I bluntly tell them off? Or should I do their project? Or what??]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>robencom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tailwind CSS tutorial #20: Font Variant Numeric]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shubhicodes/tailwind-css-tutorial-20-font-variant-numeric-1656</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shubhicodes/tailwind-css-tutorial-20-font-variant-numeric-1656"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T09:23:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the article, we will go into detail on how to use font variant numeric.
Format
font variant numeric



Tailwind Class
CSS Property




normal-nums
font-variant-numeric: normal


ordinal
font-variant-numeric: ordinal


slashed-zero
font-variant-numeric: slashed-zero


lining-nums
font-variant-numeric: lining-nums


oldstyle-nums
font-variant-numeric: oldstyle-nums


proportional-nums
font-variant-numeric: proportional-nums


tabular-nums
font-variant-numeric: tabular-nums


diagonal-fractions
font-variant-numeric: diagonal-fractions


stacked-fractions
font-variant-numeric: stacked-fractions



normal-nums: Using normal-nums will remove each effect of the font-variant-numeric class.
ordinal: This value directly indicates the open type values i.e. ordn. The term makes use of special glyph…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubhangi✨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Honor’s new Magic VS foldable will be released outside China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/23/23474820/honors-magic-vs-price-release-date-features-foldable-smartphone</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/23/23474820/honors-magic-vs-price-release-date-features-foldable-smartphone"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T09:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Honor Magic VS in black, orange, white, and blue. | Image: Honor
    

  
The Honor Magic VS is a new foldable smartphone from the former Huawei subbrand that’s actually planned for release outside China. It uses a similar design to Samsung’s Galaxy Z Fold devices, pairing a large 7.9-inch internal folding display with a smaller 6.45-inch cover display for use while the device is folded. 
“The Honor Magic VS will be our very first foldable flagship to debut in overseas markets and we are confident that it will deliver huge advancements, transforming how people all around the world use their smartphones,” said Honor CEO George Zhao. International pricing and detailed release information is yet to be announced, but in China the device will start at ¥7,499 (around $1,048) for the lowest specced model with 8GB of...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Database Indexing with PostgreSQL]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/foxeyerinx/database-indexing-with-postgresql-eio</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/foxeyerinx/database-indexing-with-postgresql-eio"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T09:10:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indexing is a way to improve reading performance, but it also makes writing performance worse, so consider using indexes in your application based on your use cases.
To demonstrate, I will use an orders table with 10 million records:
create table orders (
  id serial primary key,
  total integer, -- unit: usd
  user_id integer,
  created_at date
);

Then generate:
total: random number in range (1 - 10k)
user_id: random number in range (1 - 100k)
created_at: random date in range (2002 - 2022) (20 years)
The orders table should look like this:
 id | total | user_id | created_at
----+-------+---------+------------
  1 |  7492 |    9968 | 2021-03-20
  2 |  3084 |   81839 | 2008-03-20
  3 |  3523 |   85845 | 2018-12-22
  ...

Let's use explain analyze to see the query plan for this query:
expla…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rinx</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #829 六年后，微软称 WSL 达到一般可用]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15282-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15282-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T09:07:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[六年后，微软称 WSL 达到一般可用

微软官方博客宣布，Windows Subsystem for Linux（WSL）的商店版本已经从预览阶段毕业，进入到一般可用（GA）阶段。WSL 已有六年历史，WSL2 也有两年多历史，支持运行 Linux 图形应用和 GPU 加速，支持 systemd。微软是在去年将 WSL 放到微软应用商店的，支持 Windows 10 和 11。


消息来源：Phoronix



老王点评：居然才成为正式版，合着之前一直算测试版啊。




游戏玩家已达 32 亿

Newzoo 的最新全球游戏市场报告显示，今年全球玩游戏的人数增长了 4.6%，有多达 32 亿游戏玩家。但游戏行业的收入为 1844 亿美元，是 15 年来首次下降，但这仍然比其它行业要好。


消息来源：Tech Spot



老王点评：终究还是游戏挣钱。




英特尔将在第四代至强处理器提供可选的按需服务

英特尔公司的软件定义硅服务（SDSi）被正式称为“英特尔按需服务”，这是一种可以付费购买启用处理器中特定功能的服务。根据计划，英特尔将在明年年初的第四代至强处理器（蓝宝石激流）上提供该功能。英特尔称，“可以选择功能齐全的高级产品，也可以在整个生命周期内随时挑选对其业务最重要的功能。”可以启用的功能包括：软件防护扩展（SGX）、快速辅助技术、动态负载平衡器、内存分析加速器、数据流加速器等等。


消息来源：The Register



老王点评：这给带来了更多的灵活性，可以一次性购买高端芯片，然后根据需要付费启用。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[53 Early Best Buy Black Friday Deals (2022): Phones, Instant Cameras, TVs]]></title>
        <id>6356b7c0a398fb738c4b9197</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-buy-deals-black-friday-2022-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The retailer has a flexible holiday return policy, and the discounts are going strong.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Ravenscraft, Matt Jancer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API Key Leaks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/blst-security/api-key-leaks-bf0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/blst-security/api-key-leaks-bf0"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T08:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is an API key?


API keys are generally assigned to a specific user or application, and they are used to track and control how that user or application is using the API. For example, an API key might be used to track the number of requests made by a user or application, or to limit the amount of data that can be accessed by a user or application. API keys are typically generated by the API provider, and they are unique to each user or application.
API keys are supposed to be secret, but they often end up getting exposed. There are a few different ways this can happen.
API keys are used by developers to access APIs. An API key is a secret code that is passed in to an API request. This key allows the API provider to identify the caller and grant them access to the requested resources or endpoints.
API keys are a convenient way to grant access to specific functionality in an application. However, because they provide access to sensitive data, it is important to keep them secure. There are a few ways to prevent API key leaks:
Use a strong API key management system that can rotate keys and track usage.


Do not store API keys in plain text. Use a secure storage system such as a key management system or a secrets management system.


Use a tool like AWS CloudTrail to monitor API activity and look for suspicious activity.


Educate employees about the importance of security and the risks of sharing API keys.



By following these simple tips, you can help keep your API keys safe and prevent leaks.
In conclusion, take a look at API key leaks in a lighthearted, witty manner! This will help you find API key leaks and avoid them in the future.
Star our Github repo and join the discussion in our Discord channel to help us improve the BLST website!
BLST!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Markopolo AI 2.0 — Time to automate paid marketing for higher returns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/markopolo-ai-2-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/markopolo-ai-2-0"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T08:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[t@markopolo.ai

CHEERS! 🥂
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Resume Builder App with Xata and Cloudinary Using NextJs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hackmamba/how-to-create-a-resume-builder-app-with-xata-and-cloudinary-using-nextjs-4e5c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hackmamba/how-to-create-a-resume-builder-app-with-xata-and-cloudinary-using-nextjs-4e5c"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T08:14:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Resumes play an essential role in getting a job, as it aids in ascertaining a candidate's level of competency for a job role. That said, it needs to be built with care. 
In this article, we will learn how to use Xata, a serverless, branch-able, scalable, consistent, highly available, searchable database to build a resume builder’s backend, and Cloudinary, a cloud-based asset management service, to manage all assets. At the same time, Next.js will be used to handle the front-end development.
Here’s a sneak peek at what we’ll be building
The source code of the project is available here on GitHub
Here is a working demo on CodeSandbox
The video below shows what we will be building in this article.





  
  
  Why Xata and Cloudinary


Xata allows us to combine a Serverless Rela…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Femi Akinyemi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023 Planner — Accomplish your 2023 goals, in 52 weekly sprints.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/2023-planner</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/2023-planner"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T08:10:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Django Material Kit - Free PyPi Library]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sm0ke/django-mkit-open-source-pypi-library-gj4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sm0ke/django-mkit-open-source-pypi-library-gj4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T08:05:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Coders! 
This article presents an open-source theme for Django that can be used and installed as a library. Django Material Kit Library allows integration of a modern Bootstrap 5 Design into any Django project without much effort. Thanks for reading!
👉 Django Material Kit - the library source code
👉 Django Material Kit - LIVE Demo



Material Design, the kit used to style the library, is crafted and released for free by Creative-Tim.  Designed for those who like bold elements and beautiful websites, Material Kit 2 is ready to help you create stunning websites and web apps.







Material Kit 2 is built with over 60 frontend individual elements, like buttons, inputs, navbars, nav tabs, cards, or alerts, giving you the freedom of choosing and combining.
✅ General information
✅ Access the LIVE Demo

✅ Access the playground project
✅ Visualize the configuration & routing
✅ Update the code (minor changes)
This Freebie Bootstrap 5 Design System is coming with prebuilt design blocks, so the development process is seamless, and switching from our pages to the real website is very easy to be done.
Example Pages - If you want to get inspiration or just show something directly to your clients, you can jump-start your development with our pre-built example pages. You will be able to quickly set up the basic structure for your web project. 

Django MKit Library - Team Component 

Thanks for reading! For more resources, please access:
🚀 Free support provided by AppSeed (email & Discord)
👉 More free apps crafted in Flask, Django, and React]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sm0ke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tred — Plant trees as you spend & track your carbon footprint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tred-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tred-2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T08:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NannyML Regression v0.8.0 — OSS Python library for detecting silent ML model failure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/nannyml-regression-v0-8-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/nannyml-regression-v0-8-0"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T08:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Vs NoSQL]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bekbrace/sql-vs-nosql-2nbe</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bekbrace/sql-vs-nosql-2nbe"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T08:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's topic is very important one, especially if you want to become a full stack web developer or a back-end developer. 
What is SQL
what is NoSQL
Guide on how and what to choose and
When would you want to use SQL or NoSQL




Enjoy the video if you want to continue.
Thank You.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bek Brace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Set up automated software testing with this open source platform]]></title>
        <id>70303 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/cerberus-testing"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Set up automated software testing with this open source platform
Antoine Craske
Wed, 11/23/2022 - 03:00

            
Automated testing is an important stage of development. It helps you ensure code quality, discover bugs before they ship, and guarantee that an application works the way it's intended to work. Deployment of automated tests is rapidly becoming a top priority for companies all over the world.
The latest release of the Cerberus Testing platform offers a series of new features and improvements to allow you to easily set up automated tests for your software engineering team.
Intuitive design
The philosophy of Cerberus Testing is to facilitate cross-functional collaboration on automated tests around a shared interface. Usability has been a major focus of the latest version, with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antoine Craske</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build an interactive timeline in React with this open source tool]]></title>
        <id>70299 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/react-timeline-planby"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Build an interactive timeline in React with this open source tool
Karol Kozer
Wed, 11/23/2022 - 03:00

            
For several years, I worked in the TV online and video-on-demand (VOD) industry. While working on a scheduler web application, I realized that there were no good solutions for electronic program guides (EPG) and scheduling. Admittedly, this is a niche feature for most web developers, but it's a common requirement for TV applications. I've seen and analyzed a number of websites that have implemented their own EPG or timeline, and I often wondered why everyone seemed to be inventing their own solutions instead of working on a shared solution everyone could use. And that's when I started developing Planby.
Planby is a React (JavaScript) component to help you create schedules, ti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karol Kozer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Full Stack Content Management System using Next.js, Xata, and Cloudinary]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hackmamba/how-to-build-a-full-stack-content-management-system-using-nextjs-xata-and-cloudinary-iaa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hackmamba/how-to-build-a-full-stack-content-management-system-using-nextjs-xata-and-cloudinary-iaa"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T07:47:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing a website's content is always challenging when developing a modern web application. You can manage the content via a database or a hard-coded JSON file. But, when creating large-scale projects, managing files and databases becomes complex. In these cases, using a Content Management System (CMS) is one of the simple and efficient methods.
A CMS is software used to create and manage content with a team. There are many third-party CMS providers, such as Sanity and Strapi. However, someone once said, "If you want something done right, do it yourself."

Here’s the source code and the final demo if you want to dive directly into the code.
Before diving into this tutorial, you should:
have a solid understanding of HTML and CSS
know JavaScript's ES6 syntax

understand React and how it wor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giridhar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fake Data API]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devsimc/fake-data-api-5123</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devsimc/fake-data-api-5123"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T07:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sampledata api The purpose of SampleData is to make it easier for developers to test out APIs, by providing them with ready-to-use samples.
Sample data is the ultimate source for your web application and API. This is where everything begins, and it’s where you get the bulk of the data your application requires. You simply must have access to a good amount of data before you can start building any meaningful features for your users.
Sampledata API is a premium API used by developers to test their application, It is designed in such a way that it saves developer time and allows the implementation of multiple testing scenarios
Sample Data API is a database of real-world data for developers to use in their applications. It's a platform for entrepreneurs and developers to build apps quickly, share the code behind the app, and access more data than ever before.
If you are starting your first front-end project, we recommend sampling data from demo APIs. Sampledata API allows users to make direct calls to CrowdFlower Data Center directly.
The Sample Data API (SDAPI) is a RESTful web service that makes it easy to access the full list of available sample data. This data is used by mobile applications, websites, and IoT devices.
Fake Data API]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>simc dev CSM®</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LottieFiles Mobile App — Mobile motion canvas to create posts, stories & stickers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/lottiefiles-mobile-app-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/lottiefiles-mobile-app-2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T07:09:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How engineering leaders can have more visibility on their GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kantarci/how-engineering-leaders-can-have-more-visibility-on-their-github-actions-34pb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kantarci/how-engineering-leaders-can-have-more-visibility-on-their-github-actions-34pb"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T07:03:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Engineering leaders are responsible for development processes and their team’s experience. Today’s leaders in engineering must take decisions based on data. What measurements ought to be monitored as the key performance indicators for the team on their CI/CD process? Which specific facts should technical leaders focus on?
‍Serkan Ozal, CTO, and Co-Founder at Thundra  says
Without a proper CI pipeline, it is impossible to send your code bug-free to production. If the failed tests running on your CI are not investigated properly, it is expected that the code will break something in production.
Common things when developers see a failed test or workflow are:
  Re-running the whole workflow from the start
  Try to reproduce the bug on local
  Dig into the log piles
Although the traditional way…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Burak Kantarcı</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly web development resources #125]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vincenius/weekly-web-development-resources-125-2lih</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vincenius/weekly-web-development-resources-125-2lih"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T06:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone, thanks for following my weekly newsletter :) I have open spots for a sponsorship for the coming weeks. Just pass me an email at info@wweb.dev if you are interested!
Sponsored
BlockSurvey



BlockSurvey and get a 60% discount for a lifetime using the code BLACKFRIDAY22 on annual plans.
CSS Clothoid Corners



Meta Tags Generator



Sapling



CSS Timeline



poxi



GitHub Blocks



TourGuide JS



ArrowJS



CSS Pattern



ILLA



Copy & Paste CSS



To see all the weeklies check: wweb.dev/weekly
Enjoyed this newsletter? Help me grow by sharing it with your friends and colleagues.
wweb.dev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vincent Will</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FaceSwap by Movio — Swap the avatar's face with a single click 🎭]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/faceswap-by-movio</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/faceswap-by-movio"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T06:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://www.movio.la/faceswap
Try Movio Now 🔗 https://app.movio.la/guest?sid=ph

🤖 Welcome to the new era of video making with Movio.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[在 Ubuntu 中使用和自定义程序坞]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15281-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15281-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T06:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[当你登录 Ubuntu 时，你会看到屏幕左侧的 程序坞/停靠栏dock，上面有一些应用程序的图标。程序坞（也称为 启动器launcher，或者 面板panel）可以让你快速启动某个常用的应用程序。



我经常使用程序坞。在本文中，我将分享一些关于有效使用程序坞的小技巧，并介绍自定义程序坞的外观和位置的方法。

你将在本教程中学习到以下内容：


程序坞的基本用途：添加应用程序，并使用快捷方式来启动应用程序

自定义程序坞的外观：更改图标大小、图标位置

更改程序坞的位置：可用于单屏和多显示器的设置

在程序坞中隐藏已安装的磁盘图标

自动隐藏或禁用程序坞

使用 dconf-editor 对程序坞进行额外的定制

用其他程序坞应用程序替换 Ubuntu 默认的程序坞


我将在教程中使用 程序坞dock、面板panel和 启动器launcher 等术语，它们的意思是等同的。

如何使用 Ubuntu 程序坞：你必须知道的基础知识

如果你是 Ubuntu 的新手，你需要掌握如何使用程序坞。尽管，在一段时间后你总会熟悉程序坞的功能，但是阅读本文能让你更快地明白。

向程序坞添加新的应用程序（或删除应用程序）

这一步骤十分简单。从菜单中搜索你想要添加在程序坞的应用程序，然后运行它。

正在运行的应用程序会显示在程序坞中，它的图标在程序坞中所有图标的下方。右键单击该图标，然后选择 “添加到收藏夹Add to Favorites” 选项。这会把该应用程序的图标锁定到程序坞上。



从程序坞中删除应用程序的图标，操作起来更为简单。你不需要运行你想要在程序坞删除的应用程序，只需右键单击应用程序图标，然后选择 “从收藏夹中删除Remove From Favorites” 即可。



更改程序坞中的图标顺序

默认情况下，新添加到程序坞…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buzz – 开源、可离线的实时语音转文字工具]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43956</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/buzz-openai-whisper/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T06:34:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buzz 是一款基于 OpenAI Whisper 的开源、可离线的实时语音转文字工具，支持 Windows、macOS、Linux，它可以将麦克风的语音实时转换为文字，也支持将视频、音频文件转换为文]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[micro Dalle-2 — Pay-as-you-go Dalle-2 Image Generator Powered by Bitcoin⚡]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/micro-dalle-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/micro-dalle-2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T04:46:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi Hunters! 👋
micropay.ai is an app which micropaymentizes AI Image Generation. You pay-as-you-go to generate images instead of bulk buying credits or paying for subscriptions.

Problem:
OpenAI, the creators of the Dalle-2 AI model, charge $15 for 115 generation credits. We didn’t want to pay that since we weren’t going to use all of it.

Solution:
We made a website allowing users to pay-as-you-go. Payments are accepted in Bitcoin over the Lightning Network ⚡.

The lightning network was chosen since payments are instant and have zero fees and is what enables us to accept microtransactions.

Please give us any positive or negative feedback you have! This is our first launch and we would love to know exactly what you think.

👇 Follow us on twitter
micropay_ai
dillionverma
haseabamin

Call us 👉 calendly.com/micropay
Join our telegram group 👉  t.me/+zGVesHQRbl04NTA5
Join our reddit community 👉 reddit.com/r/micropay
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[使用doop识别最近commons text漏洞的污点信息流]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11873</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11873"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T04:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[使用doop识别最近commons text漏洞的污点信息流]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WhichIsAI (The Game) — Find the AI-generated image out of a list of real images.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/whichisai-the-game</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/whichisai-the-game"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T04:20:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flocker.app —  A Twitter rescue kit for brands & creators from Unlock Labs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/flocker-app</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/flocker-app"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T04:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PythonSandbox — Write, Run, Debug, Embed and Share your Python Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/pythonsandbox</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/pythonsandbox"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T03:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calmerry for Startups — Take time for your well-being in the startup hustle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/calmerry-for-startups</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/calmerry-for-startups"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T03:02:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[如何修复：“sudo Command Not Found” 错误]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15280-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15280-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T01:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[以下是你如何在 Debian、Ubuntu 和其他发行版中修复 “sudo command not found” 错误的方法。


有时，当你第一次设置或安装 Linux 发行版 时，你在用 sudo 尝试一些命令时，会出现 “sudo command not found” 的错误。

sudo 命令是 “superuser do” 的缩写，它是一个允许用户以管理员权限执行命令的程序。sudo 命令帮助你像管理员用户一样运行程序/命令。

此外，用 sudo 运行命令的用户必须是 sudo 组的一部分。

你看到这个错误的主要原因是该软件包本身没有安装。然而，大多数现代 Linux 发行版都默认提供了这个功能，但有些则没有。

下面是解决这个问题需要遵循的步骤。

故障排除 #1

首先，安装 sudo 包来解决这个问题。打开一个终端，刷新你的系统，并运行以下命令来安装 sudo。

对于 Ubuntu、Debian 和相关发行版：

su -apt updateapt install sudo


对于 Arch Linux：

pacman -S sudo


对于 Fedora、RHEL 等：

su -dnf updatednf install sudo


上述安装完成后，你必须使用以下命令将用户添加到 sudo 组中。

usermod -aG sudo <yourusername>


然后从终端运行 visudo，并运行以下行。按 CTRL+O 和 CTRL+X 来保存和退出。



退出并再次登录使变化生效。

故障排除 #2

在做了上述改变之后，如果你仍然收到错误信息，那么请按照以下步骤操作。

确保你的 $PATH 变量包含 sudo 可执行文件的正确路径。如果 sudo 已经安装，但 $PATH 不正确，你也会得到这个错误。理想情况下，你的路径应该包含以下所有的路径。

echo $PATH


/usr/local/bin:/usr/local/sbin:/usr/bin:/usr/sbin


要改变路径变量，使用以下命令。例如，如果 /usr/bin 不存在，那么你可以通过以下方式添加它。

export PATH=$PATH:/usr/bin


然后注销并登录查看效果。

总结

我希望这个指南能帮助你解决 Linux 发行版中的 sudo 错误。表面上的解决方案很简单，真的。

如果有帮助，或者如果你有任何问题，请在下面留言。


参考



via: https://www.debugpoint.com/sudo-command-not-found/

作者：Arindam 选题：lkxed 译者：geekpi 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk tries to blame ‘activists’ for his Twitter moderation council lie]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/22/23474381/elon-musk-twitter-moderation-council-activist-promise</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/22/23474381/elon-musk-twitter-moderation-council-activist-promise"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T01:27:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kristen Radtke / The Verge; Getty IMages
    

  
Elon Musk is trying to explain why he let Donald Trump and others back onto Twitter, even after he promised that decision would be left up to a content moderation council made up of people with “widely diverse viewpoints.” And wow, his explanation sure is something; in a tweet on Tuesday night, he claimed the council was part of a deal he made with an unnamed “large coalition of political/social activist groups,” implying it was their fault.
Musk claims he made a deal to keep those groups from trying to destroy Twitter’s ad revenue, and that those groups “broke the deal,” and so he no longer has to uphold all that stuff about the council. 
This conversation happened after Musk said that there was “not one permanent ban...
  
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Illustrations by Dorik — 200+ Free Illustrations for your next project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/free-illustrations-by-dorik</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/free-illustrations-by-dorik"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T01:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embracer is ripping a beloved mobile game away from people who paid for it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/22/23474317/deus-ex-go-embracer-onoma-square-enix-shutting-down</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/22/23474317/deus-ex-go-embracer-onoma-square-enix-shutting-down"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T00:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you ever buy Deus Ex Go, the excellent mobile puzzler from Square Enix Montreal that still ranks among the top 150 puzzle games on the App Store despite charging actual money to download? Then you’ll probably be frustrated to hear: Embracer Group, the massive conglomerate that’s gobbling up rights to franchises like Deus Ex and Tomb Raider and The Lord of the Rings and more, has decided you can’t play it anymore.
Three weeks after shutting down the studio that produced it (which had incidentally just finished going through an expensive rebrand), Embracer has decided not only to remove their games from mobile app stores, it’s apparently taking the extra step of making them inaccessible even if you’ve already downloaded them — or in...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Naval Ravikant by Inspirational People — A resource about Naval Ravikant with interviews and more.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/naval-ravikant-by-inspirational-people</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/naval-ravikant-by-inspirational-people"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T00:31:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://naval.ip.new 
https://ip.new | https://www.inspirationalpeople.org
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lucky Carrot Vol.2 — Where people connect to appreciate hard work, say thank you]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/lucky-carrot-vol-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/lucky-carrot-vol-2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T00:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Main Street Data — Stock KPIs, Fundamentals, and Revenue/Expense Segmentation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/main-street-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/main-street-data"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T23:48:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bugasura — Issue tracker for fast moving, modern tech teams.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/bugasura-3</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/bugasura-3"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T23:42:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta researchers create AI that masters Diplomacy, tricking human players]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899693</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899693"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T23:32:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta's Cicero can negotiate or persuade with natural language—just like a human.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s Proof Hate Speech Is More Viral on Elon Musk’s Twitter]]></title>
        <id>637bef894e3a003105d9c7cd</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/heres-proof-hate-speech-is-more-viral-on-elon-musks-twitter/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T23:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers monitoring a “firehose” of public tweets found signs of increasing toxicity—before Elon Musk reversed bans on Trump and other divisive figures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best Black Friday Google deals you can get]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/23473576/black-friday-2022-google-deals-cyber-monday-pixel-watch-buds-nest-chromecast</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/23473576/black-friday-2022-google-deals-cyber-monday-pixel-watch-buds-nest-chromecast"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T23:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pixel 7 (left) and Pixel 7 Pro (right) are some of the many big Google deals going on. | Photo by Amelia Holowaty Krales / The Verge
    

  
It’s a good time to be in the market for some new Google hardware. Google recently kicked off its Black Friday sales promotions on its store, and that set off a chain reaction of the same or better deals being offered all over. While some products on sale are mainstays that see frequent discounts (like the Nest Mini smart speaker for $19.99), there are also excellent deals on the latest flagship phones and accessories. For example, the Pixel 7 Pro is on sale for $749, and the new Pixel Watch is $50 off.
This may just be the tip of the iceberg of this season’s Black Friday sales, as there are all kinds of other early deals worth your attention. So we’ll forgive you if you need a moment to digest it all, but the good thing about these...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Has a Bomb-Sniffing Dog Shortage]]></title>
        <id>637bd9ccd30bfc7692348413</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/us-bomb-dog-shortage/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T22:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finding high-quality detection canines is hard enough—and the pandemic only dug a deeper hole.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best Black Friday deals on gaming laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/23472236/black-friday-2022-gaming-laptop-deals-cyber-monday-acer-asus-alienware-dell</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/23472236/black-friday-2022-gaming-laptop-deals-cyber-monday-acer-asus-alienware-dell"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T22:28:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Asus ROG Zephyrus G14. | Photo by Amelia Holowaty Krales / The Verge
    

  
You’re not just looking for a workhorse. You want a laptop that’s got game. Maybe that means frame rates, maybe even a high-refresh-rate screen for enhanced responsiveness in less demanding games. But above all, you want bang for the buck. That’s why you’re buying right now, during Black Friday week, when some of the best deals (and a bunch of predatory fake ones) show up.
These are the deals that caught my eye — the ones I might consider myself or recommend to a friend, depending on their needs and budget. Let’s start with the least expensive and go from there! 
The best Black Friday gaming laptop deals




The Gigabyte A5 K1 is $729 at Newegg ($470 off) or $749 at Best Buy, a killer deal for midrange specs — an RTX 3060 (130W) and Ryzen...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto and NFTs aren’t welcome in Grand Theft Auto Online]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899726</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899726"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T22:28:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rockstar follows similar recent ban by Mojang and Minecraft.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tuesday’s top tech news: Twitter rebuilds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/22/23472912/november-22-2022-tech-news-liveblog</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/22/23472912/november-22-2022-tech-news-liveblog"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T22:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Illustration by Laura Normand / The Verge
    

  
After cutting two-thirds of its workforce, Elon Musk’s Twitter is ready to hire.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GLOBE — See what is trending around the GLOBE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/globe</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/globe"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T22:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Renew Your US Passport Online]]></title>
        <id>6356c5bb3d83d1af9973abd4</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-renew-passport-online/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T22:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The government soft-launched an entirely digital application process. Here’s what you need to know about eligibility and navigating the website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reece Rogers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FootballSocial.app — Talk Football, with Football people]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/footballsocial-app</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/footballsocial-app"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T21:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[footballsocial.app
It's also open source on Github 👉 samternent/footballsocial
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ProductAssist — Product management as a Service subscription team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/productassist</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/productassist"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T21:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ephemeral environments by Bunnyshell — Quickly spin up dev environments on Kubernetes.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ephemeral-environments-by-bunnyshell</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ephemeral-environments-by-bunnyshell"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T20:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thinking about taking your computer to the repair shop? Be very afraid]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899664</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899664"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T20:51:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not surprisingly, female customers bear the brunt of the privacy violations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calligram — Add natural language search in minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/calligram-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/calligram-2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T20:48:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SciSpace — Your AI assistant to discover and understand research papers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/scispace</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/scispace"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T20:28:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Review: Dell’s 32-inch UltraSharp monitor has a high-contrast IPS Black screen]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1881111</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1881111"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T20:01:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beefed-up image quality topped with a souped-up camera.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scharon Harding</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Outfit Hub — Save time by managing your wardrobe digitally]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/outfit-hub-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/outfit-hub-2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T19:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teamjet Goals OKR Tracker — Free OKR tracker for individuals and teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/teamjet-goals-okr-tracker</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/teamjet-goals-okr-tracker"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T19:33:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major tax-filing websites secretly share income data with Meta]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899620</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899620"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T19:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Financial data was sent to Meta by TaxAct, H&R Block, and TaxSlayer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Belanger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agilefox Standups for Jira — Auto-generate daily standups for your teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/agilefox-standups-for-jira</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/agilefox-standups-for-jira"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T19:16:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android TV will require App Bundles in 2023, should reduce app size by 20%]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899518</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899518"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T19:08:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bundles save space, with the tradeoff that developers give Google the app-signing keys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First efficacy data on bivalent boosters shows they work against infection]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899592</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899592"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T18:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The bottom line is: We need more Americans vaccinated."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LG continues diversifying OLED monitor options; lists 27-incher for $1,000]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899505</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899505"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T18:44:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speed is the name of the game for this one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scharon Harding</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Danish scientists concoct fat-free whipped cream out of lactic acid bacteria]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899464</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899464"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T18:19:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someday our whipped topping could be made from beer-brewing residues or plants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk recruits engineers for “Twitter 2.0” after mass layoffs and resignations]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899533</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899533"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T17:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musk: "People who are great at writing software are the highest priority."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When diplomacy fails: After gifts, Teotihuacan turned on Maya cities]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899432</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899432"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T17:26:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The monkey is the oldest known captive, exported primate in Mesoamerica.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kiona N. Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Light, shadow, reflections, and terror: How a scary game does scary lighting]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899437</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899437"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T17:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our behind-the-scenes look at Callisto Protocol continues with a look at terrifying visuals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Hutchinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Check Warranty Info (CW) — Multiple check the serial numbers of Lenovo, Dell, Apple, HP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/check-warranty-info-cw</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/check-warranty-info-cw"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T17:03:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Race To Save Sam Bankman-Fried’s Other Crypto Exchange]]></title>
        <id>637cfca3668fb4e02b0bef2b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ftx-serum-crypto-exchange/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T16:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the collapse of FTX, a group of volunteers has gathered to try and salvage Serum. But the work is far from straightforward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Khalili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network-crashing leap seconds to be abandoned by 2035, for at least a century]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899455</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899455"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T16:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our 50-year chronological rounding-error nightmare will soon be over.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Purdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft comes crawling back to Steam after years on Epic Games Store]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899491</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899491"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T16:27:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2019, company said Valve's 30 percent commissions were "unrealistic."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk: Paid checkmarks won’t return until Twitter can stop impersonation]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899474</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899474"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T16:20:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Signal contradicts Musk, says it’s not helping to encrypt Twitter DMs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Belanger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Cupra made an electric hot hatch alternative to the Volkswagen ID.3]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899479</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899479"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T16:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cupras drive very differently from VWs; Cupra's head of R&D explains how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Konbert — Convert between data formats with a single tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/konbert</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/konbert"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T15:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[18 Best Wireless Headphones (2022): Earbuds, Noise Canceling, and More]]></title>
        <id>5b8ff23f828b792d4e4b50f0</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-wireless-headphones/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you need workout earbuds or gaming over-ears, these WIRED-tested picks sound like a million bucks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Parker Hall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Best Digital Picture Frames for Sharing Photos (2022)]]></title>
        <id>606222c6512ebc38e9296ee8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-digital-picture-frames/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get your photos off your phone and in front of your friends and family with these connected displays.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Medea Giordano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contestish — Host and manage beautiful online contests easily]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/contestish</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/contestish"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T14:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Arcade-Style Shooting Game with Python and PyGame]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-arcade-style-shooting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-arcade-style-shooting/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T14:41:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating an arcade-style shooting game is a fun project to help you improve your Python and PyGame programming skills. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create a fun game using Python and PyGame. Pete LeMaster created this course. Pete is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PriceTracker — Get the best prices on Amazon with PriceTracker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/pricetracker</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/pricetracker"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T14:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA’s new rocket blows the doors off its mobile launch tower]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899436</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899436"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T14:23:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["This is a dream for many of us who work at NASA."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GeoTagSeo — Geotag your photos like an expert]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/geotagseo</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/geotagseo"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T14:19:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[http://geotagseo.com/ and giving it a try! If you have any further questions, don't hesitate to contact us! We hope this tool can help other agencies with similar challenges!
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[20 Best Sex Toys (2022): Gender Inclusive, Couples, Solo]]></title>
        <id>5ec58eed5bea2fa8333c4edd</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-sex-toys-and-tech/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are our favorite gender-inclusive vibrators, wand massagers, and sleeves to give you and your partner(s) a helping hand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaina Grey, Louryn Strampe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Best Massage Guns and Theraguns (2022): Top Alternatives and Tips]]></title>
        <id>5ec54e3c73e169d072ba2512</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-theragun-percussive-therapy-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Therabody’s percussive therapy devices help soothe achy muscles. Here’s our guide to its lineup—and some cheaper alternatives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Medea Giordano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 11 Best Barefoot Shoes (2022): For Running or Walking]]></title>
        <id>5fa164d6446b4639b3d5b81f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-barefoot-shoes/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our favorite zero-drop, minimalist footwear will let you feel the ground beneath your feet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gilbertson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poll Bot — Easily create functional WhatsApp surveys]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/poll-bot</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/poll-bot"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T13:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AppSecEngineer — Hands-on application security training for teams & people]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/appsecengineer-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/appsecengineer-2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T13:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trek FX+ 2 Review: The Complete Ebike Commuter Package]]></title>
        <id>636018a5079462a79d02d6ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/trek-fx-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s lightweight, easy to use, and a fun entry into the world of electric bikes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrienne So</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dell XPS 13 (2022) Review: Downgraded Performance, Keyboard, Infinity Edge]]></title>
        <id>6373c1f0b25bbf8e38fd5bdb</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/review-dell-xps-13-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iconic Windows laptop loses its crown with a slew of major setbacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Speight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Users Replace Twitter or Learn to Live Without It?]]></title>
        <id>6377931ec5c1d5a3f902e72c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-facebook-bundling-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fate of users who left Facebook may provide clues to a post-Twitter world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Austin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Air Quality Mirrors the Racial Segregation of US Neighborhoods]]></title>
        <id>636bd3541f24b6f9091f7b68</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/air-quality-mirrors-the-racial-segregation-of-us-neighborhoods/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study shows that the more divided a community is, the higher the residents’ exposure to hazardous metals and particulates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katrina Miller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[one sec × Structured Integration — You’ve got things to do: block apps during incomplete tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/one-sec-x-structured-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/one-sec-x-structured-integration"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T12:06:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[enable healthier relationships with technology. 

Structured helps to organize your day, one sec helps you stay focused.

As a result of our common mission, we built a small prototype to link our apps recently. The result worked surprisingly well, so we decided to share it with you!

Both Structured and one sec can be downloaded for free and the integration is part of the free version of our apps. Pro versions with additional features are available, but not required to make use of the integration!

Learn more: https://one-sec.app/integrations...

Get 20% off Structured Pro: https://apps.apple.com/redeem?ct...
Get 20% off one sec pro: https://apps.apple.com/redeem?ct...
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iSOSConnect — Freemium healthcare practice management SaaS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/isosconnect</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/isosconnect"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T12:06:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@codemymobile worked on ISOSConnect: The All-In-One Toolkit for practitioners.
Kim the founder and Julian the product lead have decades of hands-on experience in the UK, in digital, telehealth and direct private practice and are building this product enabling a digital home for the independent health and well-being practitioners who work alone or work privately, some or all of the time, delivering millions of patient contacts every week.

ISOSConnect is Feature packed and is an all-in one toolkit for medical practitioners, it includes:

🟢 Calendar booking system
 
🟢 Practitioner Directory

🟢 Secure electronic notes

🟢 Client record

🟢 Create notes templates

🟢 Audit your notes 

🟢 Multidisciplinary directory

🟢 One to One video consultations

🟢 One-click client connect

🟢 Add multiple calendars

🟢 Track your tasks

🟢 Two way screen sharing

​🟢 Upload and store your own client resources

​🟢 Live chat and resource sharing

​🟢 Create, manage and send your invoices in 1 click

🟢 Group video sessions

​🟢 Feature in practitioner directory

​🟢 Online client booking page

🟢 Automatic reminders

🟢 Automated client booking

​🟢 Session recording
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Filmmakers Can Tweak Your TV Settings in More Ways Than Ever]]></title>
        <id>63757dfc1fb094c5b94def5b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/filmmaker-mode-televisions/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Support is growing for Filmmaker Mode, a setting on newer televisions that makes movies look how the creators intended.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boone Ashworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Moore’s Law Really Dead?]]></title>
        <id>636eabe10dce9984f0039c85</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/moores-law-really-dead/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A postmortem on “Cramming More Components Onto Integrated Circuits”—the most influential article of the 20th century.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Virginia Heffernan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Good Ideas From COP27—and How Likely They Are to Happen]]></title>
        <id>637ba75fcd00500bc152f470</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cop27-five-good-ideas/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Negotiators at the annual UN climate conference managed to eke out some plans for action. Now the challenge is turning dreams into reality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Barber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spokk — Design Feedback Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/spokk-be6360c9-da69-4d3e-8625-f566d53ef0ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/spokk-be6360c9-da69-4d3e-8625-f566d53ef0ae"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T11:47:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tinng — With Tinng, create a fun-filled great workplace.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tinng</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tinng"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T11:40:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hunt for the Dark Web’s Biggest Kingpin, Part 5: Takedown]]></title>
        <id>63503de7101bd9580ff61889</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/alphabay-series-part-5-takedown/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After months of meticulous planning, investigators finally move in to catch AlphaBay’s mastermind red-handed. Then the case takes a tragic turn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[研读Tomcat源码来看URI处理特性]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11871</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11871"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T09:47:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[研读Tomcat源码来看URI处理特性]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[R-Factor — React & Redux Refactoring Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/r-factor</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/r-factor"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T08:59:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://limesquid.com/r-factor/
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Planner + Growth Mindset Worksheets — Gain clarity, consistency, & courage to move forward]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/planner-growth-mindset-worksheets</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/planner-growth-mindset-worksheets"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T08:58:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LotlyCard — Reboot your wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/lotlycard</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/lotlycard"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T08:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find bugs with the git bisect command]]></title>
        <id>70320 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/git-bisect"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Find bugs with the git bisect command
Dwayne McDaniel
Tue, 11/22/2022 - 03:00

            
Have you ever found a bug in code and needed to know when it was first introduced? Chances are, whoever committed the bug didn't declare it in their Git commit message. In some cases, it might have been present for weeks, months, or even years, meaning you would need to search through hundreds or thousands of commits to find when the problem was introduced. This is the problem that git bisect was built to solve!
The git bisect command is a powerful tool that quickly checks out a commit halfway between a known good state and a known bad state and then asks you to identify the commit as either good or bad. Then it repeats until you find the exact commit where the code in question was first introduced.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dwayne McDaniel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Rust calls to C library functions]]></title>
        <id>70305 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/rust-calls-c-library-functions"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Rust calls to C library functions
Marty Kalin
Tue, 11/22/2022 - 03:00

            
Why call C functions from Rust? The short answer is software libraries. A longer answer touches on where C stands among programming languages in general and towards Rust in particular. C, C++, and Rust are systems languages, which give programmers access to machine-level data types and operations. Among these three systems languages, C remains the dominant one. The kernels of modern operating systems are written mainly in C, with assembly language accounting for the rest. The standard system libraries for input and output, number crunching, cryptography, security, networking, internationalization, string processing, memory management, and more, are likewise written mostly in C. These libraries r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marty Kalin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google A.I. DUET — Play along with A.I. Enjoy some duet.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/google-a-i-duet</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/google-a-i-duet"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T07:54:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallels Desktop 18 最新优惠码：黑五 75 折促销]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43433</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/parallels-desktop-18-coupon-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T04:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Parallels Desktop 18 是一款高性能的 macOS 虚拟机，可以用来在 Mac 电脑上以运行普通程序的方式，运行 Windows、Linux，甚至再运行一个 macOS 系统，方便随]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[23 岁的电子日记本 eDiary 4.0 即将发布：我的白日梦]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43947</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/ediary-4-coming-soon/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T04:20:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[被开发者称称为「我的白日梦」的电子日记本软件 eDiary 4.0 即将发布，其中 Windows 版本将于未来 1 个月内发布，Android 将在半年后发布，也计划了 macOS 版本，未来发布。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Validate URLs in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-validate-urls-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-validate-urls-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T04:12:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Uniform Resource Locator (URL) is what leads you to a page or file on the internet. URLs serve as the addresses of things on the internet. All valid URLs follow certain patterns. So if you know those patterns, you can determine whether a URL is valid or not in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #828 Ubuntu 正在为即将发布的昉・星光 2 RISC-V 板做准备]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15279-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15279-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T02:05:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu 正在为即将发布的昉・星光 2 RISC-V 板做准备

今年夏天，Ubuntu 为赛昉科技的昉・星光 RISC-V 单板计算机发布了官方镜像，而现在正在为即将发布的昉・星光 2 准备新的镜像。昉・星光 2 在几个月前宣布，将在年底陆续发货。它使用 SiFive 的 U74 四核 RISC-V SoC，运行频率高达 1.5GHz，有 2GB 到 8GB 的内存，双千兆以太网。除了 Ubuntu，他们还在努力支持多个 Linux 发行版。


消息来源：Phoronix



老王点评：新的板子更强大，价格也不贵，我觉得树莓派并不一定是最好的选择了。




英伟达称融化的 RTX 4090 是因为电源线没插好

在英伟达宣布它正在调查关于其 RTX 4090 显卡的电源线融化和燃烧的报告数周后，他们认为大多是因为电源线没插好而导致急剧发热。4090 使用了使用新标准的电源连接器，因而需要专门的适配器。调查显示，这个适配器在设计上缺乏正确插入指示，因此没有完全插好的电源线会急剧发热，从而融毁电源线和 GPU 等设备。


消息来源：The Verge



老王点评：虽然可能是用户没插好，但是其实归根到底是产品设计不够好。




高性能计算越来越多采用液冷

随着 400W 的 CPU 和 700W 的 GPU 的出现，对这些部件的冷却已经不能风扇所能满足的了。本周在达拉斯举行的超级计算会议上，展示了一些冷却设备，其中将冷板连接到 CPU、GPU 上的直接式液冷可以散掉 80%-90% 的热量；也有一些采用浸入式液冷，整个设备浸入在冷却液中或在密闭的机箱中注满冷却液。报告称，预计到 2026 年，液体和浸入式冷却设备的支出将达到 11 亿美元，占热管理支出的 19%。


消息来源：The Register



老王点评：只能说现在的计算设备越来越热了。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recruiting Emails AI by Dover — Use AI to make cold recruiting outreach easier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/recruiting-emails-ai-by-dover</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/recruiting-emails-ai-by-dover"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T00:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPhone 14 Pro Mockups — Stylish scenes for UI/UX presentations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/iphone-14-pro-mockups</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/iphone-14-pro-mockups"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T22:22:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“
              Hi producthunters! 
Meet our new 3d pack - iPhone 14 Pro Mockups. Super stylish, eye-catching set with different mockup scenes. 

🌈 What’s inside:
• 10 different shapes
• High resolution
• Premium quality
• Figma file

Also check the presentation page. We tried to make it stylish and attractive 😍. And don’t forget to use of promo code to get -30% discount.
 We’ll be glad to hear your feedback in the comments 😊
Happy creating!
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo goes after fan-made custom Steam “icons” with DMCA takedowns]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899399</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899399"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T21:23:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SteamGridDB images for five Switch games could "lead to consumer confusion."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta cracks down on teen “sextortion” on Facebook, Instagram]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899386</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899386"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T21:08:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Teens will finally have a way to proactively stop the spread of intimate images.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Belanger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calling all space nerds: New documentary Good Night Oppy will give you all the feels]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899171</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1899171"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T20:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ars chats with director Ryan White about recreating Mars from rover's perspective, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Autonomous Vehicles Join the List of US National Security Threats]]></title>
        <id>637be42e4e3a003105d9c7ca</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/autonomous-vehicles-china-us-national-security/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T20:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawmakers are growing concerned about a flood of data-hungry cars from China taking over American streets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Ling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feo — No-formula solution for business planning online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/feo</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/feo"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T18:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Founder's Guide to Corporate Taxes — Everything you need to know about your startup tax deadlines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/founder-s-guide-to-corporate-taxes</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/founder-s-guide-to-corporate-taxes"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T16:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The freeCodeCamp Mobile App – Learn to Code Right On Your Phone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-mobile-app-curriculum-update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-mobile-app-curriculum-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T16:23:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am happy to announce that the freeCodeCamp mobile app is finally ready to accept beta testers. 🧑‍💻 The mobile development team just pushed a big update with many helpful improvements. A big part of this is update is the implementation of the freeCodeCamp curriculum, AKA /learn. We are still]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sem Bauke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[在你的 Linux 家庭实验室上运行 Kubernetes 的 5 个理由]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15278-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15278-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T16:01:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 的优势不仅在于它能够做什么，还在于知道它能为你做什么。




在 树莓派家庭实验室上运行 Kubernetes 的 5 个理由 这篇文章中，我解释了为什么推荐在家里使用 Kubernetes。其中的理由相对来说会有点随意，并且主要于关注结果。除了 Kubernetes 好用的功能之外，还有其他几个应将 Kubernetes 包含在你自己的计算机的理由。

（LCTT 译注：家庭实验室Homelab 指的是安置在你家里的一个服务器或者多服务器的组合配置。在之上托管了多个服务和虚拟系统，以此来进行测试、开发，或者提供家庭功能用途。）

1、Kubernetes 是基于 Linux 而建立的



Kubernetes 有很高的知名度。对于一些人来说，Kubernetes 是一种神秘技术，有一个不好念的名字；而对另一些人来说，Kubernetes 就好像是牧羊犬放牧羊群一样，可以帮助他们管理过多的容器；对于其它人来说，Kubernetes 是一种 云cloud 的操作系统，是 实效云开发effective cloud development 的一个有用的界面；对于大多数人来说，Kubernetes 可能是他们从未听说过的后端软件。正如人们所想的那样，Kubernetes 具有所有这些能力，甚至有更多的功能。

并非每个人都以相同的方式使用 Kubernetes，但如果你主要的工作是系统管理，你会发现 Kubernetes 只是又一个 Linux 命令。

我有一件 T 恤，上面写着 “容器就是 LinuxContainers are Linux”，它的意思是显而易见的。容器技术使用 cgroup，来运行包含一个或一组应用程序的最小 Linux 操作系统镜像。当你运行容器时，实际上你就是在运行 Linux。虽然 Kubernetes 能在许…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[如何在 Ubuntu 中安装最新的 LibreOffice]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15277-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15277-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T15:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[在 Ubuntu 和其他 Linux 中安装最新的 LibreOffice 版本的快速指南。


自由开源的办公套件 LibreOffice 有两个版本：社区版和企业版。“社区” 版是为那些希望获得最新的尖端软件技术的早期采用者准备的。而 “企业” 版本更加稳定，可能不包括所有的最新功能，但它是生产环境和专业工作的理想选择。

在 Ubuntu 和其他 Linux 中安装最新的 LibreOffice

1、删除预安装的 LibreOffice

Ubuntu 和其他的 Linux 发行版带有预安装的 LibreOffice。这可能不是最新的，这是因为发行版有特定的发行周期。在进行新安装之前，你可以通过以下命令删除 Ubuntu 及其衍生发行版中的的旧版本。

打开一个终端并运行以下命令，以删除 Ubuntu 和相关发行版中的已安装的 LibreOffice。对于其他发行版，你可以使用发行版的软件包管理器将其删除。

sudo apt remove –purge libreoffice*
sudo apt autoclean
sudo apt autoremove


然后重启以确保一切正常（尽管你也可以跳过这一步）。

2、从网站上下载安装

前往 官方下载页面. 并通过从下拉菜单中选择类型下载 “最新的” 版本。对于 Ubuntu 和其他衍生产品，请选择 .deb 文件。



下载后，提取文件；你应该看到下面的所有软件包。



在提取文件的位置打开终端，并按顺序运行以下命令。首先，你需要安装 ure 包，其次是核心包，然后是所有的基本包。最后，就是主要的 LibreOffice 软件包。下面是一组典型的命令。你需要更改为具体版本的版本号。

sudo dpkg -i libobasis7.0-ure_7.0.4.2-2_amd64.deb
sudo dpkg -i libobasis7.0-core_7.0.4.2-2_amd64.deb
sudo dpkg -i libobasis7.0*


sudo dpkg -i libreoffice7.0*


如果你使用的是 Fedora Linux 或 Red Hat Linux，请按照上述相同的顺序使用 dnf 命令。



等待安装完成。完成后，你可以通过应用程序菜单找到 LibreOffice。



这应该完成安装最新 LibreOffice 的步骤。如果你不想遵循上述方法，请参阅以下选项。

通过 PPA 安装

如果你想通过 PPA 安装它，请按照以下步骤操作。确保在上面的第 1 步中删除现有的 LibreOffice。

sudo add-apt-repository ppa:libreoffice/ppa


最后，运行以下命令从这个官方 PPA 安装最新的 LibreOffice 5.4 系列。

sudo apt update
sudo apt install libreoffice


安装后，你可以通过 Dash 搜索启动 LibreOffice。



通过 Snap 和 Flatpak 安装

如果你是 Linux 用户，你可以尝试 LibreOffice 独立的可执行文件，它在 Snap 或 Flatpak 等沙箱中运行。

要通过 Flatpak 安装 LibreOffice ，请访问 这个页面 进行设置，然后运行以下命令进行安装：

flatpak install flathub org.libreoffice.LibreOffice


同样，对于 Snap 版本，使用以下命令进行安装：

sudo snap install libreoffice


如何升级到最新的 LibreOffice 版本？

如果你不想删除 LibreOffice 但想升级到最新版本，请阅读我们下面的完整指南。


在 Ubuntu、Linux Mint 和 Windows 中升级到最新的 LibreOffice


如果你在安装最新的 LibreOffice 时遇到问题，请随时留言。


via: https://www.debugpoint.com/install-latest-libreoffice-ubuntu-linux/

作者：Arindam 选题：lkxed 译者：littlebirdnest 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 Best Apple Watch Accessories (2022): Bands, Chargers, Cases, and Screen Protectors]]></title>
        <id>6220f63a9621fbc9faf148e3</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-apple-watch-accessories/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You finally caved and bought one. These are our favorite straps, screen protectors, chargers, and cases to go with your smartwatch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrienne So</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16 Best Cheap Headphones and Earbuds for $100 or Less (2022)]]></title>
        <id>5c6730ca7029bd0a760fde8a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-headphones-under-100/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You could fill a stadium or two with all the cheap headphones out there. We tested a ton to help you pick the right pair.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Parker Hall, Michael Calore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Entrepreneur Flutter App UI Kit 2.0 — Build your next big app with 36+ pre-built templates.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/entrepreneur-flutter-app-ui-kit-2-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/entrepreneur-flutter-app-ui-kit-2-0"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T14:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Microsoft Surface: Which Models to Buy or Avoid (2022)]]></title>
        <id>5aa7fd9e877d8568608e9819</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/microsoft-surface-buying-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you can’t decide whether to get the 2-in-1 Windows tablet hybrid, traditional laptop, or desktop, we’re here to help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brenda Stolyar, Scott Gilbertson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Google Searches Are Quietly Evolving. Here’s What’s Next]]></title>
        <id>637406f42ea97fb0c6f28a46</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/google-search-shopping-ads-malware-trends/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We went behind the scenes to make sense of Shopping, Ads, and the changes that will shape your internet searches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omar L. Gallaga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Google Searches Are Quietly Evolving. Here’s What’s Next]]></title>
        <id>637406f42ea97fb0c6f28a46</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/google-search-shopping-ads-malware-trends/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We went behind the scenes to make sense of Shopping, Ads, and the changes that will shape your internet searches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omar L. Gallaga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 7 Best Luxury Gifts (2022): Devialet, Prada, Rimowa, Urwerk]]></title>
        <id>6377e51f5fde9b7339093b63</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-luxury-gifts/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve selected seven precious objects sure to appeal to those with the most discriminating tastes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeremy White</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turns Out Fighting Mosquitoes With Mosquitoes Actually Works]]></title>
        <id>63753cb74e550ec12107a81a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/genetically-engineered-mosquitoes-population/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New evidence indicates that an effort to stamp out disease-carrying insects is working. The key? Mosquitoes genetically engineered to kill off their own kind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Mullin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start Design System — All the help you need in building your design system.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/start-design-system</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/start-design-system"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T12:23:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://startdesignsystem.com/](...

Contains
📚 Component libraries
📝 Blogs
🎞️ Video tutorials
🎙️ Podcasts 
📇 Upcoming events

Check it out and let me know what you think.

AMA.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IDWise Identity Verification, eKYC & AML — Next-gen AI-based global ID verification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/idwise-identity-verification-ekyc-aml</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/idwise-identity-verification-ekyc-aml"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T12:19:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Copyright Lawsuit Could Shape the Future of Generative AI]]></title>
        <id>6374264a0dce9984f0039cb9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/this-copyright-lawsuit-could-shape-the-future-of-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Algorithms that create art, text, and code are spreading fast—but legal challenges could throw a wrench in the works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Copyright Lawsuit Could Shape the Future of Generative AI]]></title>
        <id>6374264a0dce9984f0039cb9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/this-copyright-lawsuit-could-shape-the-future-of-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Algorithms that create art, text, and code are spreading fast—but legal challenges could throw a wrench in the works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[55 Early Target Black Friday Deals (2022): Video Games, Headphones, and Dyson Vacuums]]></title>
        <id>6375146c4e550ec12107a819</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/early-target-black-friday-deals-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The retailer has a price match guarantee for anything bought until December 24, so get ahead of your holiday shopping list without worry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Medea Giordano, Julian Chokkattu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ebooks Made Me Fall Back in Love With Reading]]></title>
        <id>6377188607aaf5e4eb27d0ba</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/kindle-ebook-digital-reading-rave/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forget the nostalgia of paper and embrace the near-infinite library.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louryn Strampe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tiny Aerosols Pose a Big Predicament in a Warming World]]></title>
        <id>6373ebcc691ed08cc4b98991</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/tiny-aerosols-pose-a-big-dilemma-in-a-warming-world/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fossil fuels are rapidly heating the planet, but their aerosols also help cool it. Just how much, though, is a major uncertainty in climate science.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Leak Details Apple's Secret Dirt on Corellium, a Trusted Security Startup]]></title>
        <id>636c07636f531d47fb071232</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/corellium-nso-group-darkmatter-apple-lawsuit/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 500-page document reviewed by WIRED shows that Corellium engaged with several controversial companies, including spyware maker NSO Group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lorenzo Franceschi-Bicchierai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #827 使用 AI 来创建幻灯片]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15276-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15276-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T10:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[使用 AI 来创建幻灯片

一家初创公司借助 DALL-E 的 API 创建生成性的幻灯片（PPT），其产品旨在让用户在几分钟内，而不是几小时内创建幻灯片。他们发现，对于他们的大多数用户来说，“在几次尝试中可以得到一些有助于实现其观点的东西。”并且，他们还计划利用 GPT-3 对文件进行总结，添加到幻灯片中。


消息来源：Venture Beat



老王点评：这倒是一个好的应用，以后做 PPT 不用那么费劲就可以做出来了。




AI 辅助编程公司 Kite 关闭和宣布开源

成立于 2014 年的 AI 辅助编程公司 Kite 比 GitHub Copilot 起步更早，但很遗憾的是未能建立起一个盈利机制。Kite 虽然有 50 万月活跃开发者用户，但他们的支付意愿很低，仅仅提高程序员的编程速度 18% 并不能说服工程经理们掏钱。Kite 宣布停止运作，公开大部分源代码，项目托管在 GitHub 上。


消息来源：Kite



老王点评：看来 AI 替代人类进行编程，还有比较长的道路。




安全专家两年间秘密帮助解密勒索软件

安全研究人员在 Zeppelin 勒索软件的加密机制中发现了漏洞，并利用这些漏洞创建了一个工作的解密器，他们自 2020 年以来用于帮助受害公司恢复文件而不向攻击者付款。原本他们在 2020 年 2 月已经准备好了一份技术报告，但推迟了发布，以避免勒索黑帮知道，并悄悄帮助被勒索的机构恢复数据。可能是察觉了这种帮助解密的情况，现在 Zeppelin 采取了多次加密的方式来勒索赎金。


消息来源：Bleeping Computer



老王点评：说到底，勒索软件也是存在 bug 的，这就是和安全专家的博弈。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cubox – 可能真是那个理想中的网络收藏工具]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43941</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/cubox/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T09:53:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cubox 是一款跨平台的网络收藏工具，通过浏览器扩展、客户端、手机应用、微信转发等方式，将网页、文字、图片、语音、视频、文件等内容保存起来，再经过自动整理、标签、分类之后，就可以随时阅读、搜索。有点]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Git: 3 commands to level up your skill]]></title>
        <id>70324 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/advanced-git-commands"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Git: 3 commands to level up your skill
Dwayne McDaniel
Mon, 11/21/2022 - 03:00

            
When I talk to people about Git, almost everyone has a strong reaction to the git rebase command. This command has caused many people to change directory, remove the repository, and just re-clone to start over. I think this comes from misconceptions about how branching actually works, a pretty terrible default interface, and some merge conflicts mucking things up.
Git squash
If you've ever made a lot of commits locally and wish there was a way to smash them all down into a single commit, you're in luck. Git calls this concept "squashing commits." I discovered the concept while working on documentation. It took me over a dozen commits to finally get a bit of markdown just right. The repo maint…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dwayne McDaniel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Git tips for technical writers]]></title>
        <id>70308 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/git-tips-technical-writers"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[7 Git tips for technical writers
Maximilian Kolb
Mon, 11/21/2022 - 03:00

            
As a technical writer working for ATIX, my tasks include creating and maintaining documentation for Foreman at github.com/theforeman/foreman-documentation. Git helps me track versions of content, and to collaborate with the open source community. It's an integral part of storing the results of my work, sharing it, and discussing improvements. My main tools include my browser, OpenSSH to connect to Foreman instances, Vim to edit source files, and Git to version content.
This article focuses on recurring challenges when taking the first steps with Git and contributing to Foreman documentation. This is meant for intermediate Git users.
Prerequisites

You have installed and configured Git on your system. You…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maximilian Kolb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[适合程序员的十大 Linux 发行版（2022 版）]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15275-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15275-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T07:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[我们点评了为程序员和开发人员提供的十大最佳 Linux 发行版（2022 版），以帮助他们完成工作和个人项目。


程序员和开发人员在其工作或项目中会使用各种工具和应用程序，包括代码编辑器、编程语言编译器、附加组件、数据库等。如果你对现代开发者的工作流程进行分类，它包含以下典型的工作流程：


访问代码库

编程

调试

测试

部署


而这种典型的工作流程可能需要各种工具。一个标准的清单可能是这样的：


代码编辑器

简单的文本编辑器

网页浏览器（网页开发者需要所有变体）

数据库引擎

一个本地服务器

编程语言相应的编译器

调试器

监测或剖析工具（可执行文件或网络版）


可以说，与 Windows 相比，Linux 是编程的最佳选择。（出于几个原因，我在本文中不对 macOS 进行比较。）Linux 是最佳选择的主要原因是，与 Windows 相比，在 Linux 发行版中已经预装具有现代技术的软件包和应用程序，或非常容易安装。

因此，在这篇文章中，我们想列出 2022 年最适合程序员的 Linux 发行版。

2022 年适合程序员的十大 Linux 发行版

1、Fedora Workstation



也许这个名单中最完美的 Linux 发行版是 Fedora Linux。它用于桌面的默认 Workstation 版通过其选择的软件包带来了正宗的 GNOME 桌面体验。

Fedora Linux 的默认安装为你提供了所有主要的开发包，开箱即用。它们包括 PHP、OpenJDK、PostgreSQL、Django、Ruby on Rails、Ansible 等。

通过 dnf 软件包管理器安装更多的应用程序是非常简单的，如 VS Code 编辑器和其他软件包。你也可以借助“软件Softw…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一键生成短视频，批量制作自媒体视频的利器 – 万彩微影（限时送会员福利！）]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43934</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/animiz-microvideo/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T06:05:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[新手小白想入门短视频制作，应该从哪个软件开始呢？或者一些文章自媒体博主想要转战短视频，能否把文章一键变视频？接下来要给大家介绍的万彩微影这款软件，能实现大家制作短视频的大部分要求，很厉害！目前在智能领]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[如何修复：“bash wget Command Not Found” 错误]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15274-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15274-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T01:53:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[以下是你如何在 Debian、Ubuntu 和其他发行版中修复 “bash: wget command not found” 的错误。


著名的 wget 工具被用来通过终端从 URL 下载任何文件。它是 Linux 终端中最流行和最快速的工具之一。

作为一个 GNU 工具，wget 带来了一些奇妙的功能。你可以实现各种目的，如从网上提取信息、下载文件、暂停/恢复等。

然而，许多 Linux 发行版 在默认安装时并没有附带这个工具。因此，当你想用 wget 下载一些文件时，你会得到 wget 命令未找到的错误。

修复它其实很容易。

修复 wget 命令未找到

你所需要做的就是打开终端，运行以下命令来安装 wget。

对于 Ubuntu、Linux Mint、elementaryOS、Debian 和相关发行版：

sudo apt install wget


Arch Linux：

pacman -S wget


对于 Fedora（虽然它默认包括）：

sudo dnf install wget


安装后，你就可以使用 wget 程序了。你也可以通过检查其版本来验证它是否正确安装。

wget --version


如何使用 wget

下面是一些关于如何使用 wget 的例子。

命令的语法如下：

wget [选项]… [URL]…


例如，如果我想下载 Ubuntu 的 ISO 文件，那么我可以运行下面的命令，用 URL 直接下载。

wget https://releases.ubuntu.com/22.04.1/ubuntu-22.04.1-desktop-amd64.iso




同样，你也可以使用上述命令下载，或者，通过下面描述的几个开关组合。你也可以通过 wget --help 命令得到这个：


-t, --tries=NUMBER 设置重试次数为 NUMBER（0 为不限）

--retry-connrefused 即使连接被拒绝，也要重试

--retry-on-http-error=ERRORS 逗号分隔的 HTTP 错误列表，以便重试

-O, --output-document=FILE 将文件写入 FILE 中

--nc, --no-clobber 跳过那些会下载到现有文件的下载（即覆盖它们）

--no-netrc 不要试图从 .netrc 中获取证书

-c, --continue 继续已部分下载的文件

--start-pos=OFFSET 从 OFFSET 位置开始下载

--progress=TYPE 选择进度条类型

--show-progress 在详细模式下显示进度条

--N, --timestamping 不重新获取文件，除非比本地文件新

--no-if-modified-since 在时间戳模式下不使用条件性的 if-modified-since 获取请求的资源

--no-use-server-timestamps 不以服务器上的时间戳来设置本地文件的时间戳

--S, --server-response 打印服务器响应

--spider 不下载任何东西

-T, --timeout=SECONDS 设置所有的超时值为 SECONDS 秒

--dns-timeout=SECS 将 DNS 查询超时设置为 SECS

--connect-timeout=SECS 将连接超时设置为 SECS

--read-timeout=SECS 设置读取超时为 SECS

--w, --wait=SECONDS 在两次检索之间等待 SECONDS 秒（适用于检索的 URL 超过 1个）

--waitretry=SECONDS 在检索的重试之间等待 1 到 SECONDS 秒（适用于检索的 URL 超过 1 个）

--random-wait 在两次检索之间等待 0.5WAIT 到 1.5WAIT 秒（适用于检索的 URL 超过 1 个）


总结

我希望这个指南能帮助你解决 Linux 发行版中的 wget 错误。显然方案是非常简单的。

如果有帮助或者你有任何问题，请在下面留言。


参考



via: https://www.debugpoint.com/wget-not-found-error/

作者：Arindam 选题：lkxed 译者：geekpi 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[突破系统限制，使用 Alfred Workflow + Pass 在任意登录表单填充用户名与密码]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76909</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76909"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T01:44:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐 
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。 
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

最近一时兴起，又在从 1Password「逃离」。这次找到了一款在终端环境下运行的密码管理器 Pass，不仅开源免费，而且还能使用 PGP 算法进行加密，从各种角度来说，都是 1Password 不错的替代品。
话虽如此，单纯使用终端来管理密码始终不太方便。在几经研究之下，终于利用 Alfred 和 AppleScript 研究出可用于系统全域的自动填充系统（而不仅仅是在浏览器范围内）。
话不多说，先看疗效。

在这篇文章中，我会简单地描述如何利用 Pass 构建一个密码保险库，并尝试与 Alfred Workflow 连接起来，完成密码自动填充。
安装 Pass 并初始化保险库
注：本文着重于讲解使用 Alfred Workflow 配合 Pass 快速填充密码，因此本节内容将会较为简略。你可以在互联网搜索相关资料获取更多教程。
要安装 Pass，叫出 macOS 用户的的老朋友 Homebrew 就行。
brew install pass
由于 Pass 不利用主密码、而是 GPG 密钥对来完成保险库加密，因此这个过程中会额外安装 GnuPG。对于大部分普通用户而言，我个人推荐再额外安装诸如 GPG Suite 的密钥管理工具。你可以前往 GPG Suite 的官网 下载到 GPG Suite。
安装好 GPG Suite 之后，打开 GPG Keychain 程序，你可以看到一些密钥展示在屏幕上。

点击顶部「新建」按钮，然后填写你的姓名、电邮地址和一些额外信息。密码（Passphrase）可以不填（可以之后再设置），但…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AstrianZ</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fun with console.log() 💿]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lissy93/fun-with-consolelog-3i59</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lissy93/fun-with-consolelog-3i59"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T21:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #tooling #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alicia Sykes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-42920 BCEL 任意文件写漏洞]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11866</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11866"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T16:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-42920 BCEL 任意文件写漏洞]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一万年日记：我想让这个世界记得，你曾经来过]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76907</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76907"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T15:56:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[茨威格在《人类群星闪耀时》一书中写道：

一个人生命中的最大幸运，莫过于在他的人生中途，即在他年富力强时发现了自己的人生使命。

从这个角度，我属于无敌幸运那一拨。
21 岁五脏滚烫的年纪，我就被自己的人生使命劈中了。
​我认定我的幸福是以一个旁观者的角度审视自己的人生旅途；如果居然行有余力，那以一个故事采集者的角度去记录更多普通人的一生，赋予我们卑微又炽热的生命以超越时空的伟大意义，是我责无旁贷的使命。
是的，我当时一文不名，但幻觉丰沛。

有一天，我们都会死去
尸体烂在泥土里。
死亡并不是一件特别可怕的事
可怕的是该在何处安置我们的故事呢？
有那么一天，我们的故事也会死去
一想到这些
我就克制不住的难过起来

按剧本我接下来应该奋不顾身的投入到这份伟大的事业中，或者年少成名，鲜衣怒马；也或许撞了个头破血流，终究败给了庸俗的生活。
无论结局如何，都该是一段轰轰烈烈的故事。
但我没有，我毕业就跑去上班了，而且一上上了九年。
你能明白么？就是那种人，一边很怂，担心明天的面条米饭、柴米油盐；一边又雄心壮志誓要扼住命运的脖子，像海明威笔下的那个老头一样去大海深处跟鲨鱼搏斗。
我觉得自己就是这种人，一个小心翼翼的猛士。
中途倒是有尝试启动项目，赶在 Web 时代余晖，完成了 80% 第一版本的工作。
接着女儿就出生了，过了几年昏天黑地的日子。那时还没有现在这么成熟的摸鱼技术，工作和老婆孩子都要照顾，人生使命这种事情只能往后放一放。
这一放，距离我被命运劈中过去了十六年。
但真正的爱情经得起考验，真正的使命也经得起等待。
十六年，杨过从唇红齿白变的鬓角飞霜，还是从断肠崖顶跳了下去。
十六年，这事儿一直都在我脑子里一刻不停歇的发着光。现在我变秃了，也变强了，终于可以给她一个交待。
 
这个立志于为普通人树碑立传的新产品，定名「一万年日记」。
其实比起日记，叫传记更准确一些。
截至公元 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>不许任性</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Declutter Your Home Screen]]></title>
        <id>636e78dcab9086067e9f26d7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-declutter-your-home-screen/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tidy up your phone and get back to basics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Nield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master & Dynamic MW75 Review: Premium Sound, Premium Price]]></title>
        <id>63599762721498963daf9a90</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/master-and-dynamic-mw75/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These high-end headphones bring fantastic fidelity everywhere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Parker Hall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Shower Power Pro Is a Hassle-Free, Hydro-Powered Shower Speaker]]></title>
        <id>6375ead15bad9cf74491b03a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/shower-power-rave/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bluetooth-enabled Shower Power Pro has a turbine to generate energy so you rarely need to recharge it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian Chokkattu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midwives Are an Overlooked Climate Solution]]></title>
        <id>637618c8d0a7e54d87737b2f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/midwives-climate-change-reproductive-health/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These frontline birth workers already know how to assist during floods, fires, and earthquakes. They could be doing more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sloat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Explanation for How Fireflies Flash in Sync]]></title>
        <id>63728bf0a987df54c26b26e9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/a-new-explanation-for-how-fireflies-flash-in-sync/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Field research uncovers clues about the beetles’ coordinated blinking and confirms that a novel form of “chimeric” synchrony occurs naturally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Sokol</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[win pwn初探（一）]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11865</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11865"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T12:28:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[win pwn初探（一）]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Embraces Twitter's Radical Fact-Checking Experiment]]></title>
        <id>637836104fb21507b424cef0</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-embraces-twitters-radical-crowdsourcing-experiment/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The project allows users to suggest short notes that add missing context to viral tweets. It could change how social platforms operate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Miller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get verified on Mastodon with WordPress]]></title>
        <id>70315 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/verified-mastodon-wordpress"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get verified on Mastodon with WordPress
Seth Kenlon
Sun, 11/20/2022 - 03:00

            
As users migrate away from Twitter, many wonder what the equivalent of the famous blue checkmark is on Mastodon. Ignoring debates about how anyone can be sure of anyone's true identity online, it's easy to verify yourself on Mastodon when you have a WordPress site.
1. Get your verification code
Sign in to your Mastodon account and click the edit profile link under your Mastodon handle.
  
Image by: 
(Seth Kenlon, CC BY-SA 4.0)
In the Edit Profile screen that appears, scroll down to the Verification section. This section contains a special verification code. Click the Copy button to copy your verification code to your clipboard.
  
Image by: 
(Seth Kenlon, CC BY-SA 4.0)


            
More open source …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Kenlon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[微软输入法plus – 让输入法回归专注]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43930</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/ms-input-method-plus/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T07:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[本文来自发现频道，作者：@dog，原文链接：https://meta.appinn.net/t/topic/38111 微软输入法plus 给 Windows 系统默认的微软输入法添加了一张高效美观的]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DLL注入学习：复现一个简单的消息钩子]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11863</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11863"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T03:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DLL注入学习：复现一个简单的消息钩子]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Date Command – How to Query the Terminal to Get Dates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-query-the-terminal-to-get-dates-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-query-the-terminal-to-get-dates-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-19T19:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux has many utility tools that help you quickly find the answer to your questions. But many devs aren't aware of them. In this article, you will learn a command that has exceptional benefits.  For example, say you want to take a look at your calendar to plan a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Destabilizing Hack-and-Leak Operation Hits Moldova]]></title>
        <id>6377ad71e9158002679f7437</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/moldova-leaks-google-privacy-settlement-world-cup-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-19T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: Google’s location snooping ends in a $391 million settlement, Russian code sneaks into US government apps, and the World Cup apps set off alarms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Marine Lab in the Path of Climate Change’s Fury]]></title>
        <id>63728b6892528f1523cb94dc</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-marine-lab-in-the-path-of-climate-changes-fury/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DeFelice Marine Center sits on a strip of land that dangles into a bay. Staff is living, working, and adapting to the climate crisis in real time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boyce Upholt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JAVA TransforMap&LazyMap链]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11861</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11861"/>
        <updated>2022-11-19T10:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JAVA TransforMap&LazyMap链]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[17 open source technologists share their favorite keyboards]]></title>
        <id>70278 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/favorite-keyboards"/>
        <updated>2022-11-19T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[17 open source technologists share their favorite keyboards
Opensource.com
Sat, 11/19/2022 - 03:00

            
Keyboards are necessary to work with a computer system whether it's for coding, writing, or moving around items in a spreadsheet. They allow access to a computer's peripherals and are used to get deep into the operating system of any computer. Keyboards come in all shapes and sizes. Some are more comfortable to use than others. We asked our community members to share the best (and the worst) keyboard they'd ever used. Some of the answers might surprise you!
Top 4 favorite keyboards
Keyboards rank right after editors and languages on the official list of things that programmers argue about.
My favorite keyboards:
NeXT Extended Keyboard: With the pipe in the right place.
Apple Mac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opensource.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[「键盘观望」来看看最近有趣的键帽 2022.11（2）]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76814</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76814"/>
        <updated>2022-11-19T01:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[本文仅代表个人观点，用于记录和观望一些键帽。
个人评分部分为主观部分，会根据厂家状态、设计、以及个人喜好权重评分，仅供参考。
键帽

GMK
老牌德国键帽厂，不过工期越拖越长，品质也有些不太稳定，但仍旧是铁王座
Tenshi 天使 「misotsu」
来自 IC 信息贴
这款键帽是由设计师misotsu（或许我们可以叫他味增酱）设计，这款键帽是他设计的第一款键帽，也是一款我认为设计得很不错的二创作品，原型是麻枝准的名作Angel Beats（天使的脉动）！
原作宣传图
这套键帽的灵感来自于剧中高人气女角色——立华奏
立华奏角色图
配色：

配色方面，选择了珠宝白、紫罗兰宝石色、豆奶白，取自角色发色和服饰颜色。以珠宝白和紫罗兰宝石色作为基调，复古点缀其中，整体观感偏冷色系。比较契合角色给人的印象，很少有表情变化，同时也非常寡言，「无心」和「冰冷」。
个性部分：

在个性键帽部分，我个人认为是中规中矩，忠于原作的设计。天使登场的羽毛和翅膀，学生服饰的领结，代表战斗能力的Hand sonic（音速手刃），七字回车设计则是Hand sonic 五代形似莲花，是因为可爱而制造的武器。而贯穿作品的暗线，跳动的心脏——女主角与男主角的羁绊，来自于男主角生前捐赠的心脏跳动在女主角的身体里，正如作品标题所示——Angel Beats（天使的脉动）！
渲染展示（仅供参考）：

金属个性：

这枚金属键帽的个性图案，是来自于角色最喜爱的食物——麻婆豆腐。
桌垫：

桌垫 Angel's Down

桌垫 Fallen from grace
键帽信息：
材质：ABS材质
高度：原厂高度
工艺：二次成型
个人评分：5—10
对于二次创作键帽会有更高要求，这款键帽忠于原作的设计，是优点也是限制，根本上来说二次创作的作品都会出现这个问题，不过仍旧有厉害的作者能够做出超越原作的改编，这款键帽的颜色设计我觉…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>车不能快</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hoisting in JavaScript with let and const – and How it Differs from var]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-let-and-const-hoisting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-let-and-const-hoisting/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T23:33:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to think that hoisting only happened to variables declared with var. But recently, I learned that it also happens to variables declared with let and  const. I'll explain what I mean in this article. I also have a video version of this article [https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VbHaL_J8Ex0] you can check]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA Will Not Change the James Webb Telescope’s Name]]></title>
        <id>6377e38384f5d2572f8d0a73</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/nasa-will-not-change-the-james-webb-telescopes-name/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T22:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The moniker, which honors a former agency administrator accused of enforcing anti-LGBTQ policies, has long been controversial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramin Skibba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Holmes of Theranos Gets 11 Years in Prison]]></title>
        <id>637670be197cd825272582e8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elizabeth-holmes-theranos-is-going-to-prison/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T22:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former Theranos CEO’s fall is a cautionary tale for eccentric founders and the investors who blindly throw money at their inventions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amanda Hoover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Data Analytics? Data Analysis and Definition for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-data-analytics-data-analysis-and-definition-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-data-analytics-data-analysis-and-definition-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T21:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data analytics is the process of collecting, organizing, and analyzing raw data from different sources. You can then gain insights that'll help organizations make important predictions and decisions.  Data analytics mostly involves studying data trends over a given period, and then extracting useful information from these trends.  Why]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In App Update - How to Notify Users of App Updates in Flutter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/in-app-update-the-flutter-way/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/in-app-update-the-flutter-way/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T21:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you roll out a new version of your application, you want your users to know about it. Whether you fixed a critical bug, added a new feature, or the application just runs smoother or faster – they need to know.  As application developers, we want all of our]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Express +  Node.js Handbook – Learn the Express JavaScript Framework for Beginners [2022 Edition]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-express-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-express-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T18:52:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Express? Express is a Web Framework built upon Node.js. Node.js is an amazing tool for building networking services and applications. Express builds on top of its features to provide easy to use functionality that satisfies the needs of the Web Server use-case. It's Open Source, free, easy to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flavio Copes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Hydra  to Hack Passwords – Penetration Testing Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-hydra-pentesting-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-hydra-pentesting-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T17:28:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hydra is a brute-forcing tool that helps penetration testers and ethical hackers crack the passwords of network services.  Hydra can perform rapid dictionary attacks against more than 50 protocols. This includes telnet, FTP, HTTP, HTTPS, SMB, databases, and several other services. Hydra was developed by the hacker group “The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lume SSG Handbook – How to Create a Static Blog with Lume]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-static-blog-with-lume/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-static-blog-with-lume/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T17:06:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lume is a new static site generator based on Deno. Deno is a JavaScript-based run-time environment that supports TypeScript.  Lume is not built around any specific language. It supports Markdown, Nunjucks, TypeScript, and JavaScript by default. Lume also supports plugins. Some plugins come preinstalled by default. This is why]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Best Password Managers (2022): Features, Pricing, and Tips]]></title>
        <id>5ce3031cfd8c3451c5008275</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-password-managers/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keep your logins locked down with our favorite apps for PC, Mac, Android, iPhone, and web browsers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gilbertson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Luck Getting Elon Musk to Stop Tweeting]]></title>
        <id>63767f081f6fc1913bddf48f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/plaintext-good-luck-getting-elon-musk-to-stop-tweeting/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter’s billionaire new owner is seemingly addicted to his own platform, firing off updates that endanger his own turnaround plan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use a Super-Intense Laser to Kick an Electron out of a Molecule]]></title>
        <id>637737fe07aaf5e4eb27d0bb</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-use-a-laser-to-kick-an-electron-out-of-a-molecule/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By firing pulses quintillionths of a second long, physicists study the fleeting motion of an electron leaving two bonded atoms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Structures In Frontend JavaScript In The Real World (With React Code Examples)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jkettmann/data-structures-in-frontend-javascript-in-the-real-world-with-react-code-examples-3506</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jkettmann/data-structures-in-frontend-javascript-in-the-real-world-with-react-code-examples-3506"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T12:42:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #javascript #webdev #frontend]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Johannes Kettmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[分享一波好用的记账方式]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76886</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76886"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T12:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[前段时间，我和小助理录制了一期关于记账的播客。
我个人记账十几年，并从记账这件事中收获许多，小助理的财务状况也在记账后一点点发生改变，故而我俩一致认为记账对大部分人实现攒钱目标是一功不可没的步骤，于是商量着录了这期节目，希望能给大家分享一些关于攒钱和记账的心得与技巧。
这期播客上线后受到了极大的欢迎，不仅上了首页，收获了3万多播放，200多条互动，还有超过千次的收藏，连评论都获得了100多个赞， 这意外的热度让我非常欣慰。
我们团队有位小伙伴在听完这期播客后，认为对她有巨大帮助，并自告奋勇做这期节目的「课代表」，把节目里的干货做一个系统化的整理，然后分享给大家，下面的文字内容就来自小伙伴精心整理的【课程笔记】，希望能为大家提供到行之有效的方法。
 

一、找一个记账方式
 
记账的方式有很多，包括但不限于Excel、备忘录、各种记账app。
方式不重要，选一个习惯用的，适合自己的就行，但不要在这一步上耽搁太久。

我最一开始记账的时候，下载了一大堆记账app，光挑app就花了一个多礼拜的时间，这就很没有必要。选哪种方式都无所谓，重要的是坚持记账。
我自己偏向用Excel，因为莫名觉得记账app的操作都好复杂啊，而且我更习惯自己去分类。
更倾向用app的朋友，可以试下关哥推荐的时光序app，纯净无广，功能强大，除了记账以外，还可以用做日程提醒。
 
二、先做全年预算
有些支出是不能按月去计算的，因为它不一定每个月都有，这样可以给自己一个整体的规划目标感。
比如保费，它是年缴的；再比如国庆节收到的婚礼请柬可能就比较多，但平常的月份，这部分支出就比较少或者干脆没有。
很多人会把这些开销当成一笔意外支出，但实际上，这种情况每年都会发生，所以咱们可以提前把这部分的年预算给做好，至于到底是哪个月花的钱，就不重要了。
这种规划方式同时能帮我们更好的控制支出，也利于后期复盘。
假设全年总预…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>关哥Emma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Has a Cunning Plan to Save Crypto—but It’s Too Late]]></title>
        <id>6376b06907aaf5e4eb27d0b5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/binance-exchange-save-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchanges want to prove that the market can thrive after the FTX collapse. Despite their efforts, future failures may be inevitable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Khalili, Morgan Meaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pager's App Gives Screenshots Superpowers. That’s Just the Beginning]]></title>
        <id>6373f31392528f1523cb94e8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/pager-link-screenshots/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new startup called Pager lets users make shareable, link-enabled screenshots. They could be a key to a more open web.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Goode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diverse Teams Are Needed to Save the Planet]]></title>
        <id>6376afe598d83b411c64f19d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/wired-impact-diversity-inclusion/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing people with a range of perspectives to the table is the quickest way to solve difficult problems, experts tell WIRED Impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grace Browne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vertical Farming Needs to Grow More Than Salad]]></title>
        <id>6376b022c3549109c89b8b9a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/wired-impact-infarm-vertical-farming/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indoor agriculture promises to massively reduce the water and land needed to support crops. But at the moment, it only works for a tiny percentage of foods.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NodeJS VM和VM2沙箱逃逸]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11859</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11859"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T10:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NodeJS VM和VM2沙箱逃逸]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 亚马逊黑五：三星 SSD 硬盘专场]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43923</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/2022-black-friday-samsung-ssd/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T09:02:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一年一度的黑色星期五将要在下周五到来，不过本周五亚马逊已经正式开启黑五促销，无套路无意外，大概率是一年之中的最低价，最佳购物时间。 亚马逊小哥先给青小蛙发来了三星硬盘专场的几个特价，看看有没有需要的吧]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My favorite Git tools]]></title>
        <id>70319 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/git-tools"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My favorite Git tools
Dwayne McDaniel
Fri, 11/18/2022 - 03:00

            
As with any other technology or skill, just reading about Git cannot make you proficient at it or make you an "advanced" user. Now it's time to dig into some of the tools in Git that I've found useful, and hopefully, that will help you use Git.
Git reflog
In my previous article, I wrote about Git history as a chain of commits, and that's a very good model for most purposes. However, Git actually remembers everything you do with Git, not just commits. You can see your entire recent history with git reflog.
  
Image by: 
(Dwayne McDaniel, CC BY-SA 4.0)
The log that reflog refers to is found in .git/logs, and it's called HEAD. Opening this file, you can quickly see all the actions taken recently. Inside .git/logs/HEAD…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dwayne McDaniel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get verified on Mastodon with your website]]></title>
        <id>70316 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/verified-mastodon-website"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get verified on Mastodon with your website
Seth Kenlon
Fri, 11/18/2022 - 03:00

            
If you're migrating away from Twitter, you might be looking for a way to ensure your followers that you are who you say you are. Ignoring debates of how anyone can be sure of anyone's true identity online, it's easy to verify yourself on Mastodon if you already have your own website. This requires a very basic understanding of HTML, so if you don't maintain your own website, then send this article to your web maintainer instead.
1. Get your verification code
Sign in to your Mastodon account and click the edit profile link under your Mastodon handle.
  
Image by: 
(Seth Kenlon, CC BY-SA 4.0)
In the Edit Profile screen that appears, scroll down to the Verification section. This section contains a spe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Kenlon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1Password Passkeys 将在 2023 年初开始支持无密码技术]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43920</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/1password-passkeys-future/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T06:53:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1Password 在昨天发布了一个视频和 DEMO 页面，演示了将于 2023 年推出的无密码技术 1Password Passkeys 的外观和示例，为一个没有密码的世界做好准备。@Appinn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Mock an API in ONE minute]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ismailkamil/how-to-mock-an-api-in-one-minute-eip</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ismailkamil/how-to-mock-an-api-in-one-minute-eip"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T06:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #tutorial #productivity #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ismail Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[内存对象搜索原理剖析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11857</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11857"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T03:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[内存对象搜索原理剖析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s How Bad a Twitter Mega-Breach Would Be]]></title>
        <id>637260a4d12193bd58db2501</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-mega-breach-what-if/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T01:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk laid off half the staff, and mass resignations seem likely. If nobody’s there to protect the fort, what’s the worst that could happen?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s How Bad a Twitter Mega-Breach Would Be]]></title>
        <id>637260a4d12193bd58db2501</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-mega-breach-what-if/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T01:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk laid off half the staff, and mass resignations seem likely. If nobody’s there to protect the fort, what’s the worst that could happen?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reactjs Protected Route]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/collins87mbathi/reactjs-protected-route-m3j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/collins87mbathi/reactjs-protected-route-m3j"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T20:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #react #tutorial #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Collins Mbathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100+ Most Useful Github Repositories Every Programmer Needs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/johongirr/100-most-useful-github-repositories-every-programmer-needs-32cg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/johongirr/100-most-useful-github-repositories-every-programmer-needs-32cg"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T17:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #programming #github]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Johongir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Twitter Bubble Let Democrats Defy Political Gravity]]></title>
        <id>637647ed07aaf5e4eb27d0ac</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/election-twitter-midterms-trans-kids/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T15:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The midterm elections showed that the far-right's manufactured narrative about trans kids doomed the GOP when they made it policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katherine Cross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dev.to is for webdevs and beginners - I have data to prove it]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/derlin/devto-is-for-webdevs-and-beginners-i-have-data-to-prove-it-54c4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/derlin/devto-is-for-webdevs-and-beginners-i-have-data-to-prove-it-54c4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T14:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #beginners #opensource #meta]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Linder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the Emoji Skin Tone You Choose Matters]]></title>
        <id>636e9f884afa8ea305a9eb9d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/why-the-emoji-skin-tone-you-choose-matters/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WIRED's spiritual advice columnist on whether to use the tone that most resembles your own—or to stick with the original Simpsons-esque color.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meghan O'Gieblyn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the Emoji Skin Tone You Choose Matters]]></title>
        <id>636e9f884afa8ea305a9eb9d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/why-the-emoji-skin-tone-you-choose-matters/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WIRED's spiritual advice columnist on whether to use the tone that most resembles your own—or to stick with the original Simpsons-esque color.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meghan O'Gieblyn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter’s Moderation System Is in Tatters]]></title>
        <id>637589ac197cd825272582e3</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitters-moderation-system-is-in-tatters/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disinformation researchers have spent years asking Twitter to remove toxic and fake posts. After Elon Musk’s staff cuts, there’s hardly anyone to talk to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vittoria Elliott, Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Plastic Packaging Alternative Can Compost in a Year]]></title>
        <id>637587474934747117c34995</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/wired-impact-shellworks-biodegradable-plastic/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[British startup Shellworks is fed up with waste, so it created a vegan material that can be turned into compost.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bureaucracy Is Blocking the Green Energy Revolution]]></title>
        <id>63758a9e5bad9cf74491b038</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/wired-impact-green-energy-bureaucracy/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Jackson, CEO of Octopus Energy, tells WIRED Impact that red tape is causing “disastrous” delays to sustainable energy projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Khalili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What AI-Generated Art Really Means for Human Creativity]]></title>
        <id>63642ed083fe12d97101a106</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/picture-limitless-creativity-ai-image-generators/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence can now make better art than most humans. Soon, these engines of wow will transform how we design just about everything.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lyft Aspired to Kill Car Ownership. Now It Aims to Profit From It]]></title>
        <id>63728f1d2ea97fb0c6f28a35</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/lyft-aspired-to-kill-car-ownership-now-it-aims-to-profit-from-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company once claimed that ride-hail services and robotaxis would make personal cars obsolete. Mounting losses have prompted a rethink.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aarian Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evernote 被 Bending Spoons 收购]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43917</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/evernote-joining-bending-spoons/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T07:56:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evernote 宣布被来自意大利的开发商 Bending Spoons 收购，交易预计将于 2023 年初完成。@appinn Evernote 是著名且老牌的笔记工具，曾经估值高达 10 亿美元，]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fluent Search – 支持工作流的高颜值 Windows 搜索启动器]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43914</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/fluent-search/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T04:11:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[本文来自发现频道，作者：@L_hiil，原文链接：https://meta.appinn.net/t/topic/38094 Fluent Search 是 Windows 下一款有着高颜值且可以自定]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Lab-Grown-Meat Startup Gets the FDA’s Stamp of Approval]]></title>
        <id>637520f6d0a7e54d87737b2b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/lab-grown-meat-approval/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T17:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US regulatory body has signed off on Upside Foods’ cultivated meat—but the company is still figuring out how to make enough of it to sell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telehealth Sites Put Addiction Patient Data at Risk]]></title>
        <id>63189c13036b54662b510390</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/substance-abuse-telehealth-privacy-tracking-tech/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research found pervasive use of tracking tech on substance-abuse-focused health care websites, potentially endangering users in a post-Roe world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lindsey Ellefson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telehealth Sites Put Addiction Patient Data at Risk]]></title>
        <id>63189c13036b54662b510390</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/substance-abuse-telehealth-privacy-tracking-tech/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research found pervasive use of tracking tech on substance-abuse-focused health care websites, potentially endangering users in a post-Roe world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lindsey Ellefson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Stereotype of the Woke Teen Is 'Tárring' Art]]></title>
        <id>63725ab8845dc8670fda4f71</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/tar-art-social-media-stereotypes/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An archetype culled from the depths of social media seems to be short-circuiting screenwriters’ creativity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katherine Cross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React - Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/iambilalriaz/react-best-practices-ege</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/iambilalriaz/react-best-practices-ege"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T13:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #webdev #javascript #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hafiz Muhammad Bilal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Want to Archive Twitter? Good Luck With That]]></title>
        <id>6372872a8cea9c3346926042</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-archive-elon-musk/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The platform's meltdown has shed light on the steep challenge of preserving social media data. But not everything is worth saving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amanda Hoover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Alzheimer’s Scientists, the Amyloid Debate Has No Easy Answers]]></title>
        <id>636a91f27484c01b9b6e9661</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/for-alzheimers-scientists-the-amyloid-debate-has-no-easy-answers/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, potential therapies that attack this brain protein have failed to help patients in clinical trials. Now—surprisingly—a new drug shows promise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grace Huckins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to COP27. Thank You for Not Protesting]]></title>
        <id>6373bbfc454b677de6f65e6e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cop27-protest-restrictions/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At this year’s UN climate conference in Egypt, activists are unable to demonstrate without permission, limiting their ability to voice criticism of the COP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Barber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[优化 Windows 下的多屏体验]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76841</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76841"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T10:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[虽然现在多屏用户逐渐变多，但仍是小众，Windows 也并没过对多屏使用进行太多的优化。所以只好自己动手，于是有了以下一些个人自用的优化设置。
窗口出现位置优化
Windows 系统仅对多屏用户提供了简单主显示器的设置，默认情况下所有新打开的窗口都只会出现在主显示器上，即使你在使用另一个的显示器。而「基于显示器连接记住窗口位置」只能记住上次关闭时所在的屏幕，实用性并不高。

这时微软自家的 Power Toys 里的 FancyZones 就可以派上用场了，除了我们熟知的窗口布局设置外，它还可以调整窗口行为，在这里我们可以通过启用「将新创建的窗口移动到当前 活动的监视器（实验性）」来达到这一效果，美中不足的是动画不够优雅。

窗口出现的问题解决了，但任务栏上默认是显示所有屏幕上的窗口，不能让我们快速区分哪些应用是在当前屏幕下的。

为了解决该问题，如下图所示，Windows 提供了简陋的选项加让人摸不着头脑的翻译。设置后，每个屏幕下的任务栏就只显示当前屏幕下打开的窗口，更符合直觉，不过 Win + 数字 的快捷键就只能在主显示器上使用了。

内容显示优化
现在 Windows 下大部分的应用都适配高 DPI 的，少部分不支持的，也可以通过 Windows 自带的属性 - 兼容性选项来调整。

上面的设置仅解决了单个应用在高分辨率屏幕下的问题，并不能解决应用在分辨率相差太大的显示器间移动时会出现界面变形问题。这时，如果你使用的 AMD 显卡，那你可以通过启用 AMD Radeon Software 里的「超虚拟分辨率」来让低分辨率屏切换到更高的逻辑分辨率，不仅缩小的多屏间的分辨率差距，还有抗锯齿的效果。由于个人没有使用 Nvidia 和 Intel 显卡，相关选项是否存在请自行到显卡设置里翻找。

设置完成后到 Windows 设置调整下逻辑分辨率和缩放即可。

除此之外，对于我们网上冲浪必备的浏览器，它的缩放是固定的，且只有一个设置选项。不知道有没有人跟我一样两个屏幕的缩放比例是不一样的，在两个屏幕间移动浏览器时，网页内容并不会根据 DPI 而变化，导致观感割裂。在这里我推荐一个 FireFox 浏览器插件：ffreszoom，它可以实时感知屏幕宽度的变化，当宽度超过指定值时，自动调整到指定缩放比例。设置前先通过这个网站查看自己的屏幕宽度：http://whatismyscreenresolution.net/，需要将 Firefox 浏览器移动到不同显示器上刷新。

如图所示我的外屏宽度是 1728 px，笔记本内屏为 1024，所以我在两者之间随意取了一个值用于判断，若当前屏幕宽度超过 1600 px，就自动设置缩放为 1.5，也即 150%。若小于 1600 px，则使用浏览器设置里的值。两种缩放无缝切换，只会多了一个缩放的动画。由于本人没使用 Chromium 类浏览器，并没有对应的插件推荐，不过其用户这么多，应该会有类似的插件。

利用「闲置的」触摸板
不知有没有跟我一样喜欢使用笔记本键盘的，且平时一些简单的操作直接用触摸板直接操作。现在 Windows 11 已经支持自定义触摸板多指手势了，但其不能根据不同应用设置不同的手势，例如：A 软件可以用 Ctrl  + W 关闭，但 B 软件只能用 Alt + F4，同一个操作有不同的快捷键。

这时就需要第三方软件了，这里我推荐 GestureSign，界面虽然是 Windows 10 风格，但不影响使用，毕竟设置完就不用再看了。它可以为不同应用的不同快捷键键设置相同的触控手势，手势类型也不再仅限于横平竖直，可以自由发挥。同时软件也内置了一些常用的命令供选择。

上图是我的一些设置，双指一般使用系统默认就不添加上去了。其中个人最爱的是三指滑动切换标签，体验比鼠标点击更加符合人的直觉。对于频繁使用搜索启动器的我，把三指上滑指定为搜索启动器的快捷键，方便呼出。
 
对了，设置前记得把系统自带的相关手势取消掉，不然会冲突。若你仍不习惯使用触摸板，该软件也支持鼠标手势，具体可以自行下载体验。
结尾
以上便是我在使用多屏时遇到的问题，及相关解决方法，希望对多屏用户有帮助。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Not_your_user</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[在少数派，你甚至可以聊足球之卡塔尔世界杯观赛指南]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76813</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76813"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T08:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[卡塔尔世界杯开幕式将于11月21日即下周一举行，在接下来的一段时间，将是全世界足球迷的狂欢月，无论你是不是足球迷，你都将会在各种媒体和社交网络上看到世界杯的信息，从球员的球场表现，到场外的花边新闻；有老将的“老骥伏枥，志在千里”，也有新人的横空出世；有冠军登顶后的春风得意，也有亚军距成功一步之遥却又失之交臂的遗憾……在世界杯举办的一个月里，将诞生许多热血与感动的故事，也少不了令众人津津乐道的段子，总之，这一切都让人无比期待。
世界杯赛程赛制
2022年世界杯将在中东国家卡塔尔举办，这是历史上首次在中东地区举办世界杯。
小组赛分组（来源：国际足联官网）
本届世界杯将有32支球队参加，分成8个小组。

A组：卡塔尔，厄瓜多尔，塞内加尔，荷兰
B组：英格兰，伊朗，美国，威尔士
C组：阿根廷，沙特阿拉伯，墨西哥，波兰
D组：法国，澳大利亚，丹麦，突尼斯
E组：西班牙，哥斯达黎加，德国，日本
F组：比利时，加拿大，摩洛哥，克罗地亚
G组：巴西，塞尔维亚，瑞士，喀麦隆
H组：葡萄牙，加纳，乌拉圭，韩国

世界杯31支参赛队伍由各个洲世界杯预选赛选出，其中欧洲拥有13个参赛名额，非洲5个名额，亚洲4.5个名额，南美洲4.5个名额，北美及加勒比地区3.5个名额和大洋洲0.5个名额。其中的半个名额是附加赛名额，澳大利亚和哥斯达黎加通过附加赛获得世界杯参赛资格。东道主卡塔尔自动获得参赛资格。
世界杯遵循杯赛赛制，分为小组赛和淘汰赛，与欧冠、亚冠等冠军联赛不同，世界杯小组赛为单回合制，每支队伍踢3场小组赛，积分前2名晋级淘汰赛。淘汰赛不再抽签，A组第一对阵B组第二，B组第一对阵A组第二，C组第一对阵D组第二，D组第一对阵C组第二，以此类推，同时，小组前二的两支队伍将分在上下两个半区，保证决赛前不再相遇。
淘汰赛对阵（来源：懂球帝APP）
小组赛将于北京时间11月21日至12月3日凌晨进行，淘汰赛…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>吃饭Bu洗碗</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tomcat回显学习第一弹]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11851</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11851"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T07:21:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tomcat回显学习第一弹]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA’s Huge SLS Rocket Finally Launches the Artemis 1 Moon Mission]]></title>
        <id>636a94143505151fbc0b01e1</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/artemis-1-nasa-moon-mission-launch-sls-rocket-orion/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T07:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the first time since the Apollo era, the agency is preparing for crewed visits to our lunar neighbor. Missions with astronauts are next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramin Skibba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[如何上好一堂线上课？这是我的实践与思考]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76839</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76839"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T06:31:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐 
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。 
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

10 月的国庆小长假刚一结束，准备告诫学生们及时收心、恢复学习状态的长篇大论还没来得及打好腹稿，便伴随着疫情的到来再没机会说出口。小长假结束到校第二天，我所在的城市便由于疫情不得不陆续发出居家线上学习的通知，原本以为一周就能结束的线上学习，一晃眼已经进行了整整 5 周，在这 5 周里，我已经习惯了每天起床一杯咖啡后直接坐到桌前，开始一天的线上课程准备。
教师线下如何授课
在介绍我的线上授课经验之前，有必要先对我当前线下授课的方式进行简单介绍，我所在的小学使用的硬件设备是希沃白板，日常完成备课后，我会到教室使用希沃白板打开 PPT 进行授课。希沃白板的便利之处在于，即便你不使用内置的同名应用「希沃白板」进行备课、授课，它仍然支持打开课件后，直接在课件上使用不同颜色的画笔进行标记、圈画，并支持橡皮擦功能，大大节省了备课时间。
此外，希沃白板通常会配备有投影仪，一般我会在习题讲评课上利用投影仪播放练习单或是课堂作业，来完成习题讲评课；或是在随堂课上实时对学生的作业、作品进行展示。希沃白板还内置了多种工具，我使用频率较高的是其内置的倒计时功能，当课堂上需要进行限时练习或讨论时，它便能派上用场。
居家授课如何复制线下经验
我手上的电脑设备一共有两台，对于使用 Windows 电脑的用户而言，在电脑上直接下载前文提到过的「希沃白板」应用，便能把制作好的课件直接导入希沃（或直接利用希沃制作课件）实现实时圈画、倒计时等常用功能。而我的 Windows 电脑借给了同样有网课需求的同事，因此我可以用来上网课的主要设备就是一台 16+256G 的 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peggy_</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build and Deploy a Node.js Microservices Application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pavanbelagatti/build-and-deploy-a-nodejs-microservices-application-2966</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pavanbelagatti/build-and-deploy-a-nodejs-microservices-application-2966"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T05:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#node #microservices #docker #kubernetes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pavan Belagatti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1800元，打造我的 iPad 数字阅读器]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76830</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76830"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T04:24:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐 
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。 
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

本文提供了一个使用 iPad 进行数字阅读的低成本实用方案。
使用数字工具建立工作流基本上都遵循「收集-整理-阅读-输出」这样一个基本流程。在少数派上已经有很多文章关注了获取信息、收集整理、笔记输出等方面的方法论，但似乎比较少有人专门关注「阅读」这件事情。
阅读好像是一项不言自明、人人具备的技能，但是在数字时代，如何打造自己的数字阅读方案仍然是一个值得讨论的问题。虽然数字设备摆脱了纸质材料笨重的束缚，提供了更多的内容信息来源，但是也带来了新的难题。电脑、平板、手机……什么才是更好的阅读设备？书籍、报刊杂志、网页、社交媒体信息，如何更好的整合多源信息？
我认为，一个好的数字阅读方案应当满足以下要求：

简洁实用、舒适方便，专注于阅读本身；
提供一体化的阅读平台，既能广泛容纳各类来源、形式的内容，又能方便地记录标注笔记，对接后续内容输出；
成本较低，能够为更多人所用。

围绕这些目标，这篇文章介绍了我是如何从自己的需求出发，尝试用 iPad 打造适合自己的阅读工具的，希望能够给大家提供一些参考。
关于数字阅读：我需要什么样的工具
选择有效的工具必须先明确自己的需求。作为一个社科博士研究生以及数字工具的爱好者，我的日常阅读内容与来源大致包括这几个方面：

与个人研究议题相关的中英学术书籍、论文以及报告；
其他书籍，包括人文社科经典、人物传记、非虚构类作品、小说等；
专业媒体与官方资讯，个人关注的信源如财新、晚点、联合早报、澎湃、各类官媒等；
其他互联网信息，来自微信、微博等社交媒体以及其他网站。

在过去，我的阅读方式大致是这样的：…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>littleiron</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PicGo 2.3.1 版本更新发布，来看看更新了什么]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76811</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76811"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T03:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PicGo，一个用于快速上传图片并获取图片 URL 链接的工具。
今年是 PicGo 的五周年，虽然我真的很想推出一个大的正式版 (2.4.0) ，但是平时工作实在忙碌，只能抽空在闲暇时间写写 PicGo，因此没能交出一个让自己满意的答卷。所以本次时隔一年的更新只能以一个小版本更新。
不过对于用户来说，这个小版本还是修复了不少问题以及带来了不少新功能，我挑了其中一些比较有代表性的，快来看看吧。
Features
macOS arm64 的构建版本
从 2.3.1 版本开始，PicGo 也为 arm64 版本的 mac 带来适配的构建版本。为此，PicGo 更新了底层的 Electron 版本，跨越非常大，没少做适配。不过 arm64 版本的原生应用确实速度非常快。
如果你是 macOS 用户，但是遇到了安装、使用的问题，可以参考 PicGo 的 FAQ 最后一条进行处理。
多语言支持
一直以来 PicGo 只有简体中文的界面。从 2.3.1 版本开始，引入了 简体中文 \ 繁體中文 \ English 三种语言的界面。你可以在设置界面中切换语言。如果你想为 PicGo 添加更多的语言支持，欢迎参考贡献指南。
i18n 多语言设置
使用内置剪贴板上传
PicGo 对于剪贴板图片一直是采用脚本的方式获取的，同时不同平台的脚本不一样。但是不同的系统、用户环境会带来脚本执行结果不一定符合预期的情况。例如某些 Windows 用户使用「剪贴板上传」的时候就会遇到脚本报错或者进程残留的问题。因此这个版本新增了一个配置项，可以使用 Electron 提供的剪贴板 API 进行剪贴板图片获取以及上传。如果你遇到了上述的问题，不妨开启这个选项。
使用内置剪贴板上传
日志文件大小控制
2.3.0 版本优化了一些启动相关的日志，但是由于代码和系统的原因，某些用户会遇到写入日志死循环的问题，导致日…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PiEgg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Outlign — Process-driven project management for agencies & clients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/outlign</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/outlign"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T01:24:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[如何快速做出一个合格的PPT：我的思考与实践]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76433</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76433"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T23:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[什么是合格的PPT？
我们做演示幻灯片（后用PPT指代）最好的结果是什么？就是让自己想要传达的目标与听众期待的目标尽量匹配，如何能达成这效果，那就能说这样PPT是合格的。

 
我们拿可以称之为每年“年度最佳PPT”的苹果发布会举例，苹果想要传达的是“我们又创造了一些NB的产品，快来买!"，而用户期待的是“今年又会拿什么让人惊叹的产品跟功能出来震撼到我”，苹果为了传达产品的厉害之处，会用大大的数字突出性能提升百分比，会通过一个个实际使用场景来说明新功能能够帮助用户解决痛点，会通过层层递进的方式，让爆点越来越大，惊喜接踵而来……通过一系列的手段来满足用户的期待，通过发布会让新产品特性，深刻的传达到用户脑中。

 
说完了飘在天上的，再来说些更加接地气的，例如打工人每年必须要做的年终总结PPT。
年终总结大部分人的目标应该是“快看我今年干了好多好多的事，没闲着，给我多点年终奖”，很多初入职场的打工人会把做过的所有事情堆进PPT中，来个十几页，希望领导看到，“我今年都干了这么多事情了，没有功劳也有苦劳吧”，但是这样的PPT不是领导所期望的。

领导其实期望看到的是“你为今年的目标做了什么，有什么成长，明年如何达成目标”，归根到底就是要表现出你这个人如何，有没有潜力，值不值得被激励。还有你的领导也需要对上汇报，你报告里的部分内容将会成为他的汇报内容，他要达成的汇报目标是“今年目标我们团队是这样达成的，整个团队在成长，明年我们将会达成更高的目标”，他要表现出自己是一个合格的团队领导，能够带领团队完成目标，他也希望拿到更多的年终奖或者升职。
看完上面的分析，我想你应该清楚一个合格的年终总结PPT应该怎么做了吧，多写自己是如何的优秀，如何帮助完成了团队年终目标，自己的成长以及明年的计划，对于一些与团队目标关系不大的工作，可以简单带过。
大而广之，其实做任何内容输出，都不要脱离或者偏离自己…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>陈勇_Dennis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Infinite Cloud Is a Fantasy]]></title>
        <id>636287740b9dedd635bdb041</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cloud-data-storage-climate/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's all too easy to believe in the illusion of neverending data storage and streaming. But it's destroying the natural world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Gonzalez Monserrate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Will Pay the Price for Big Tech’s Hubris?]]></title>
        <id>63724ad4b25bbf8e38fd5bb9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/who-will-pay-the-price-for-big-techs-hubris/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WIRED’s editor in chief mulls what lies in store for Elon Musk and Sam Bankman-Fried, plus more thoughts on the past week’s headlines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gideon Lichfield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe’s Cities Are Getting More Crowded—That’s a Good Thing]]></title>
        <id>637318978cea9c334692604f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/europe-cities-populations/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sprawling mass of suburbia has been a disaster for the environment. But now smaller, denser cities herald a renaissance in city living.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hunt for the Dark Web’s Biggest Kingpin, Part 4: Face to Face]]></title>
        <id>63503ad72721236bcb158484</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/alphabay-series-part-4-face-to-face/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The team uses a secret technique to locate AlphaBay’s server. But just as the operation heats up, the agents have an unexpected run-in with their target.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a real-time bidding system with Socket.io and React Native 🤩]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/novu/building-a-real-time-bidding-system-with-socketio-and-react-native-1cj5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/novu/building-a-real-time-bidding-system-with-socketio-and-react-native-1cj5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T10:16:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #react #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevo David, novu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UPack压缩的PE文件头解析及调试]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11847</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11847"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T08:47:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPack压缩的PE文件头解析及调试]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[赶海观察日记：专业赶海人如何赶海？]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76797</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76797"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T06:20:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[会呲水的猫眼螺、遇盐出洞的蛏子、卧沙总是卧一半的蛤蜊……
如果你经常看赶海视频的话，对这些出镜率极高的海洋生物都不会感到陌生。近年来生活类自媒体的蓬勃发展，使得赶海1这一沿海地区的常见活动也得以进入镜头，并逐渐为大众所熟知。
然而，赶海真的像视频里那样，一袋食盐、一把小铲，在沙滩上挖几下，就能轻松收获一桶海鲜吗？镜头之外的真实赶海生活，是什么样子的呢？专业赶海人都如何赶海呢？
居住在北方某沿海城市的我，虽然不是一个专业的赶海人，但几次赶海下来，倒是收获了一肚子见闻，遂整理出这篇观察日记，以飨读者。
赶海群体：什么人在赶海？
第一类是专业赶海人。专业赶海人从外观上是最容易辨别出来的群体，他们的装备专业且齐全，从头戴式探照灯到防水雨裤，从钓竿到抽虾筒。他们干活熟练麻利，且通常不会聚集作业，而是分散开来、独自行动，一人承包一片区域，维持着互不侵犯、心照不宣的默契。对他们来说，赶海是经济收入的重要来源，他们所收获的海产品可用于贩卖，有时也会「拿回自己家做着吃」。
夜钓的大爷，穿着雨裤方便下海放鱼饵。交谈中大爷自述是因身背负债而每晚赶海。摄于10月29日。
第二类是业余赶海人，以村民和游客为主，他们的熟练程度、赶海目的也各不相同。
附近村庄的居民对赶海更熟悉些，更善于寻找海洋生物的呼吸孔。尽管装备不如专业赶海人那么齐全，但他们仅凭一把小铲子和一个小桶，也能有相当不错的收获，足够做一顿饭。一次赶海时，我们碰见了一对年轻的小情侣，听口音像是附近的村民，女生向我展示了当晚的收获——小半桶的狗虾，并「打算回去拿椒盐炒着吃」。
游客则多半是抱着玩乐的心态，将赶海当成一次有趣的家庭活动。
图片来源：网络
赶海攻略：时间，装备和收获
赶海时间
赶海前需要提前查好当地的潮汐时间表，重点关注水位高度和涨潮、落潮时间。每天的落潮时间有所不同，一般初一、十五会落大潮，海水退得更远，给赶海人提供了更广阔的探…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>katejate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（九）番外篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11845</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11845"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T06:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（九）番外篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fluent Search | 一款支持工作流的高颜值 Windows 搜索软件]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76810</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76810"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T06:08:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[平台：Windows 10/11
下载：官网、微软商店（部分功能受限）

Fluent Search 一款不满足于只提供「Fluent 流畅」搜索体验，还想在外观、交互、工作流上进一步拓展的高颜值搜索软件。
Fluent 设计 + 个性化
相关设置页面：外观、特效、主页
颜值就是生产力，这句话在 Windows 平台似乎并没有得到很好的验证，关注 Windows 的用户都知道微软虽有设计规范，但对软件生态的掌控力约等于没有，连自家应用也不一定会及时跟进，更何况第三方软件，因此在 Windows 平台上一款遵守规范且好看的应用是可遇不可求的。身为一款随时随地都有可能跟用户打交道的应用，好看的设计会让用户体验更上一层楼。以下是其三种搜索窗口基础样式：
搜索栏 + 自定义图标、水印窗口窗口 + 主页 = 类开始菜单风格
Fluent Search 不仅自带不同风格的主题，同时也提供大量的选项让其更具个性化，从浅色、深色模式，到窗口样式、大小、字体、图标、水印、颜色、透明材质、动画等都可调整。不同于其它跨平台的应用，基于 C# 开发的 Fluent Search 可以快速跟进 Windows 新设计的同时仍有着原生的性能表现。

「流畅」搜索
相关设置页面：搜索、文件、标签、屏幕、应用内搜索、上下文、网页、进程、应用程序、UI
搜索可以说是该类软件的基本功，一个优秀的索引器决定着它的基础用户体验，Fluent Search 的索引器除了可以搜索文件、目录、设置、进程、应用程序、浏览器（火狐需要安装插件）书签和历史记录，还可以对部分格式进行全文搜索，当你只想查相关内容时，通过 files content 标签即可进行搜索，不过受限于性能，搜索内容需要超过 3 个字符才会进行搜索。
全文搜索
作为一款外国软件， Fluent Search 也提供了中文搜索，全拼、拼音首字母搜索都支持，…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Not_your_user</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring环境下的回显总结]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11844</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11844"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T03:42:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spring环境下的回显总结]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一次对基于thinkphp开发程序的审计]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11838</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11838"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T02:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一次对基于thinkphp开发程序的审计]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter’s SMS Two-Factor Authentication Is Melting Down]]></title>
        <id>6372ad717268ef35e219ba02</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-two-factor-sms-problems/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T01:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Problems with the important security feature may be some of the first signs that Elon Musk’s social network is fraying at the edges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter’s SMS Two-Factor Authentication Is Melting Down]]></title>
        <id>6372ad717268ef35e219ba02</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-two-factor-sms-problems/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T01:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Problems with the important security feature may be some of the first signs that Elon Musk’s social network is fraying at the edges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[浅析PHP GC垃圾回收机制及常见利用方式]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11843</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11843"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T16:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[浅析PHP GC垃圾回收机制及常见利用方式]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[跨平台重构CobaltStrike的Beacon并使行为对主流杀软免杀]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11839</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11839"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T15:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[跨平台重构CobaltStrike的Beacon并使行为对主流杀软免杀]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Phone Can Determine If a Bridge Is Busted]]></title>
        <id>636aa1756776a0176c76e56d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/your-phone-can-determine-if-a-bridge-is-busted/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any smartphone in any car can pick up a span’s unique vibrations. Tracking how that changes over time reveals hidden structural problems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pandemic Bike Boom Survives—in Cities That Stepped Up]]></title>
        <id>636c0e98557521d0988d4fe1</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-pandemic-bike-boom-survives-in-cities-that-stepped-up/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Covid lockdowns prompted a surge of new cyclists. But the trend has faltered in places that didn't build bike-friendly infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aarian Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Man Behind Mastodon, Eugen Rochko, Built It for This Moment]]></title>
        <id>636ed7f60ae5a121565fd72a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-man-behind-mastodon-eugen-rochko-built-it-for-this-moment/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People fleeing Twitter have turned to Eugen Rochko’s alternative. He says social networks can support healthy debate—without any one person in control.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The $6 Billion Shot at Making New Antibiotics]]></title>
        <id>636508c7c3bf45de80681ba9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-6-billion-dollar-shot-at-making-new-antibiotics-before-the-old-ones-fail/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Antimicrobials cost as much to develop as other drugs, but don’t earn the same returns. Congress could give drugmakers a boost, but time is running out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maryn McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awesome Productivity Tools for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-productivity-tools-for-developers-40lj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-productivity-tools-for-developers-40lj"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #beginners #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Vishwakarma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023 年将至，该如何优雅地记录看过的书籍和电影]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76786</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76786"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T06:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2014 年，那时候我还在读大三，某一天突然萌发了一个想法，要将自己看过的书和电影记录下来。我隐隐约约感受到，沉淀自己的精神生活，竟然让我觉得人生充满意义。记录的瞬间让我觉得会有成就感；等哪天，拿起这份清单，我可以清楚回顾某段时间内看过了哪些书籍和电影，也从侧面知晓当时精神生活的丰富程度
从那时起，我的记录习惯从未断绝过，不知不觉已经 8 年。从最初的用豆瓣记录，到使用纯文本 Markdown 记录，到自己搭建博客，再到使用公众号留言自动生成博客的方式记录。有些方式比较 Geek，不适合普通人，直到去年，我开发了一款 App，来满足跟我有同样需求的普通用户
这就是「已阅：书影记录」，一款快速记录自己看过的书籍和电影的 App，并支持将精美的观影列表和书单海报一键分享给朋友。献给所有希望构建自己精神角落的人

细数曾经那些不够好用的工具
为什么要开发「已阅：书影记录」呢？我综合对比了市面上多款工具，发现如果想要记录自己看过的书籍或电影，使用的方式不外乎以下几类
Excel
这是一类以 Excel 为代表的纯手动记录工具，除了 Excel 还包括在线文档、Notion 甚至是手写到自己的笔记本等
这个方式无疑费时费力，且数据是死的，很难被二次利用（如灵活筛选、统计、分享等）
让人惊讶的是，用这个方式记录的人还真不少，毕竟大部分人找不到更好的办法
豆瓣
豆瓣很伟大，是中文互联网上最全面的书影音资料库。功能上非常丰富，但是正因为它太全了，很难在这个垂直功能上做到极致

豆瓣记录的步骤比较麻烦，且默认会被分享到公共领域，下图是豆瓣和已阅的记录界面对比

 
「豆瓣」和「已阅」的记录界面对比
无法快速回顾，比如我想查看 2022 年看过了哪些书或我看过的所有五星电影，豆瓣都无法支持
「已阅」可以方便地筛选
分享功能缺乏自定义，比如我想自定义分享 2022 年看过了哪些书或我看过的所有五…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>伊塔奇呀</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[通过反序列化利用JDBC后门]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11837</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11837"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T02:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[通过反序列化利用JDBC后门]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hunt for the FTX Thieves Has Begun]]></title>
        <id>6371149f0dce9984f0039c8b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ftx-hack-theft-crypto-tracing/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T23:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious crooks took hundreds of millions of dollars from FTX just as it collapsed. Crypto-tracing blockchain analysis may provide an answer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hunt for the FTX Thieves Has Begun]]></title>
        <id>6371149f0dce9984f0039c8b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ftx-hack-theft-crypto-tracing/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T23:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious crooks took hundreds of millions of dollars from FTX just as it collapsed. Crypto-tracing blockchain analysis may provide an answer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extensive List of Best Development Resources - 121 Links to Guides, Cheat Sheets and More List of Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/perssondennis/extensive-list-of-best-development-resourses-121-links-to-guides-cheat-sheets-and-more-list-of-resources-366l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/perssondennis/extensive-list-of-best-development-resourses-121-links-to-guides-cheat-sheets-and-more-list-of-resources-366l"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T15:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #beginners #productivity #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dennis Persson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Formerly Incarcerated Job Seekers Need More Than Training]]></title>
        <id>6356aaa7e53b9bdcb463c5e9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/employment-prison-jobs-digital-reputation/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reentry programs help, but tech companies must also modify their hiring systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Lageson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stand out in a React interview by rendering a list like a pro]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/andyrewlee/stand-out-in-a-react-interview-by-rendering-a-list-like-a-pro-1cn5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/andyrewlee/stand-out-in-a-react-interview-by-rendering-a-list-like-a-pro-1cn5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T08:18:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #javascript #webdev #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Cheat Sheet with 40+ commands & concepts]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/git-cheat-sheet-with-40-commands-concepts-1m26</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/git-cheat-sheet-with-40-commands-concepts-1m26"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T05:51:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#git #github #programming #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapajyoti Bose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 common mistakes new contributors make in Open Source Software]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codergirl1991/7-common-mistakes-new-contributors-make-in-open-source-software-2noo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codergirl1991/7-common-mistakes-new-contributors-make-in-open-source-software-2noo"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T03:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#opensource #webdev #beginners #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tools I Am Using On A Daily Basis]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yuridevat/tools-i-am-using-on-a-daily-basis-4kb7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yuridevat/tools-i-am-using-on-a-daily-basis-4kb7"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T21:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#tooling #productivity #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julia 👩🏻‍💻</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Introduces Twitter Mayhem Mode]]></title>
        <id>636e769e32968364ac1a7b69</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-twitter-security-mayhem-roundup/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: US midterms survive disinformation efforts, the government names the alleged Lockbit ransomware attacker, and the Powerball drawing hits a security snag.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruv Mehrotra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unclutter — Read and collect articles with style]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/unclutter-c9b0437e-5b84-4193-abe3-dee9c861d157</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/unclutter-c9b0437e-5b84-4193-abe3-dee9c861d157"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T09:57:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit post — the idea of a reader mode that doesn’t make all articles look the same. 

Fast-forward to today (and many rewrites later), hundreds of people rely on it daily and contribute to our Open-Source project. I’m excited to finally share it with all of you! 🚀

Here’s what you can do with Unclutter:

Focus: ➤ Remove ads, popups, and other annoyances to read in peace.
Customise: ➤ Improve the readability of articles or enable dark mode everywhere.
Save for later: ➤ Manage your reading queue directly in your browser.
Subscribe: ➤ Follow RSS feeds, newsletters, and blogs with just 1 click.
Highlight: ➤ Select any text to save a quote. Then search across it later.

I’m excited to hear what you all think!
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fallout of the FTX Collapse]]></title>
        <id>636e8d8e627a555fd99f22f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-fallout-of-the-ftx-collapse/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Sam Bankman-Fried's crypto empire crumbles, its customers, and other crypto traders, are paying the price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Khalili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Tech’s Layoffs Will Fuel the Industry's Future]]></title>
        <id>636d36b20757f7d06dd271f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/plaintext-big-techs-layoffs-will-fuel-the-industrys-future/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: The dotcom recovery, a history-making online purchase, and the highway to climate hell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring A Junior’s React Code - 43% Less Code With A Better Data Structure]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jkettmann/refactoring-a-juniors-react-code-43-less-code-with-a-better-data-structure-eam</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jkettmann/refactoring-a-juniors-react-code-43-less-code-with-a-better-data-structure-eam"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #javascript #webdev #frontend]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Johannes Kettmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Dark Ships’ Emerge From the Shadows of the Nord Stream Mystery]]></title>
        <id>636d7ff21f24b6f9091f7b8f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/nord-stream-pipeline-explosion-dark-ships/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Satellite monitors discovered two vessels with their trackers turned off in the area of the pipeline prior to the suspected sabotage in September.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[在外独居，我想分享下我如何面对孤独]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76378</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76378"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T10:49:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[前言
在经历了成都连续的半个月高温居家办公，以及两周的疫情封控后，我思考了一下关于城市生活与孤独的关系，以及如何排解孤独，理解孤独。在这一个多月中，我一直是一个人在屋子里，未曾踏出家一步。我不是一个爱做饭柴米油盐的人，就这样，在家中面对着日复一日的琐事，面对没有人可以说话的孤独，面对着工作、生活的焦虑。在与安静和极度的自由的碰撞里，除了偶尔的空虚与崩溃以外，我想分享一下我如何逐渐的找回自己的生活节奏，并喜欢上一个人安排自己的方方面面。
孤独是什么

如果我们所期待的人际关系数量和质量与我们当前实际情形存在较大差距，就会产生令人不悦的厌烦、悲伤和绝望的孤独体验（de Jong Gierveld et al.，2006）。

孤独有两种：
其一是社会隔离，指缺少朋友和熟人的社交。
你或许也有这样的感受，常常用「社恐」来武装自己，鲜少与人交流。那怕是点个外卖、出门买个东西都是能不交流就不交流。性格内向的人更喜欢和自己交流，陶醉在自己所热爱的精神世界之中。在周末和假期，相比和朋友出去游玩他们更倾向于选择在家中折腾自己的爱好，渐渐的在和陌生人交往时变的畏惧，不知所措。久而久之，除了身边寥寥无几的挚友以外，几乎没有任何的交流，孤独感进一步加深。
其二是情感隔离，指缺少亲密而深厚的情感关系。
人生活在社会中，总是会渴望着被他人理解的。有的人虽然辗转于各种聚会，时时刻刻都沉浸在热闹场合之中，但是浮于表面的热闹并不总是意味着有人真正了解自己。可能你真正渴望的目标无人诉说，心中的艰苦无人知晓。理解就像是人生的底色，我们渴望着，但却不可能有人能完全理解自己。
孤独的危害
对于大部分人来说，长期保持孤独是有一定危害的。
在生理上，长期孤独的人血压更高，更容易发生应激反应。在晚上的时候孤独也会让人辗转反侧，不仅睡眠质量下降，免疫力也会随之一起走下坡路。
在生活中，孤独有时候也会带来不少的麻烦，比如因…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dluck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[jpress代码审计分享]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11832</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11832"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[jpress代码审计分享]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Java安全]关于Rhino的一些姿势利用]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11831</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11831"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T04:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Java安全]关于Rhino的一些姿势利用]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Things I Wish I'd Known When Starting My Coding Journey]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marisabrantley/10-things-i-wish-id-known-when-starting-my-coding-journey-3ga1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marisabrantley/10-things-i-wish-id-known-when-starting-my-coding-journey-3ga1"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T03:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #beginners #codenewbie #devjournal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marisa Brantley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C3P0反序列化常用方式及不出网利用]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11830</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11830"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T02:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C3P0反序列化常用方式及不出网利用]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s New Robot Sparrow Can Handle Most Items in the Everything Store]]></title>
        <id>636d46204af1e10e2d86c4ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/amazons-new-robot-sparrow-can-handle-most-items-in-the-everything-store/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T21:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sparrow could shift the balance between humans and machines in the company’s warehouses, using machine learning algorithms and a custom gripper.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I lost my job, I am depressed.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/supeergabs_/i-lost-my-job-i-am-depressed-17ja</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/supeergabs_/i-lost-my-job-i-am-depressed-17ja"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T21:22:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#job #layoff #depressed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabriela Muñoz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia’s Sway Over Criminal Ransomware Gangs Is Coming Into Focus]]></title>
        <id>636bda4e06a9fc0e80b10a6d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/russia-ransomware-gang-connections/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T19:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Questions about the Kremlin’s relationships with these groups remain. But researchers are finally getting some answers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk's Twitter Blue Verification Is a Gift to Scammers]]></title>
        <id>636d252677d2621bc8030710</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-blue-check-verification-buy-scams/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T16:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone can get a blue tick on Twitter without proving who they are. And it’s already causing a ton of problems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia’s New Cyberwarfare in Ukraine Is Fast, Dirty, and Relentless]]></title>
        <id>636aa8641d1ddb0aa029e13c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/russia-ukraine-cyberattacks-mandiant/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T15:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers see updated tactics and tools—and a tempo change—in the cyberattacks Russia’s GRU military intelligence agency is inflicting on Ukraine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Tweet Before Dying]]></title>
        <id>636aa3553505151fbc0b01e2</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/tweet-dying-revolutionary-internet/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The revolutionary internet is over, and we don’t have much to show for it. A new start is out there, somewhere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Ford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 websites to learn Frontend-web development faster]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/qbentil/5-websites-to-learn-frontend-web-development-faster-3cid</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/qbentil/5-websites-to-learn-frontend-web-development-faster-3cid"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T11:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #html #css]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bentil Shadrack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I build a Documentation site using Docz]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/documatic/how-i-build-a-documentation-site-using-docz-57kk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/documatic/how-i-build-a-documentation-site-using-docz-57kk"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #beginners #react #javascript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Vishwakarma, Documatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weblogic CVE-2020-2551 绕过NAT网络分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11825</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11825"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T02:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weblogic CVE-2020-2551 绕过NAT网络分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[透过信息架构 看各笔记软件]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76736</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76736"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T15:18:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[我在 如何搭建知识库 中，将知识库的结构分为了「树状结构」和「网络结构」两种。
树状结构是自上而下的，网络结构是自下而上的。
但知识还有多少种结构呢？为什么是这两种？
知识本质上是信息的一种，想了解知识的结构，也可以类比信息的结构。一直以来我回答不好这个问题。
日复一日，在日常使用知识库和产品经理的工作中，无论是对知识库中的每一张知识卡片进行整理，还是在工作中经常需要查看数据库的数据结构，都将我指向一个词「信息架构」
于是，我想起了那本经典的的「北极熊」之书 —— 《信息架构 超越 Web 设计》
并且，我在这本三年前读过的书里，找到了现在的我想要的答案。

信息结构
在《信息架构》这本书中，将信息分为了以下三种结构
组织系统：组织结构可以分为互补的三种结构
层级结构
以数据库为导向的模式
超文本

信息结构会定义用户浏览的主要方式。适用于信息架构的主要组织结构包括层级结构 、以数据库为导向的模式和超文本，每种组织结构都有其优缺点。在某些情况下，只使用一 种是合理的。但在很多情况下，需要以互补的方式使用这 3 种组织 结构。 —— 《信息架构》第六章

看到这三个结构，我恍然大悟，觉得非常了不起。
简单的三种结构，几乎可以用来解释现在所有的笔记软件。
下面我将介绍每一种结构在知识库软件中的运用。结合我日常的使用经历，也给出一些建议。
（注：目前市面上可以作为知识库的软件有很多。我只选取我有使用过的软件作为本次功能的介绍。也就是 Notion、Obsidian、Logseq、wolai…）

信息结构会定义用户浏览的主要方式。适用于信息架构的主要组织结构包括层级结构 、以数据库为导向的模式和超文本， 每种组织结构都有其优缺点。

层级结构
层级结构，即是上一层级包括下一层级的结构。
层级结构的优势和劣势都很明显。优势是其层次清晰，劣势是维护成本高。
层级结构的广度和深度均不宜…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>潦草学者</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Quiet Invasion of 'Big Information']]></title>
        <id>636167b2079462a79d02d6c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/big-information-relx-privacy-surveillance-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google and Facebook's privacy violations are common knowledge. But the decisions of a less-known company, Relx, are also impacting people's everyday lives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Lamdan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collective Mental Time Travel Can Influence the Future]]></title>
        <id>63627db400e08e244b10a525</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/psychology-mental-time-travel-politics/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way people imagine the past and future of society can sway attitudes and behaviors. How might this be wielded for good?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shayla Love</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made 1200+ ⭐️ stars on a Github repo! Here are some simple tips that helped me!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fredy/i-made-1200-stars-on-a-github-repo-here-are-some-simple-tips-that-helped-me-4eom</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fredy/i-made-1200-stars-on-a-github-repo-here-are-some-simple-tips-that-helped-me-4eom"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T11:25:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #tutorial #react #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fredy Andrei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[jetty常用渗透总结]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11821</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11821"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T07:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[jetty常用渗透总结]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[凛冬将至，你准备好买羽绒服了吗]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76706</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76706"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T03:23:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐 
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。 
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

又到双十一购物节，说来有趣，每年双十一我都会关注羽绒服这一品类，原因大概是冬天即将到来，我隐约有添购衣服的担忧，可又因为此时我还身穿短袖，买羽绒服有种错季购物的感觉，在将羽绒服加入购物车后往往又放弃下单。于是这些年，每到双十一，我的购物车里的羽绒服更新一次，羽绒服照片成了淘宝的皮肤挂件，年年换新。
我当然是有买羽绒服，但往往不是购物车里那件，我在淘宝上浏览的是万元左右的始祖鸟、Moncler、加拿大鹅，加入购物车里的是两千元左右的北面，但最终购买的是千元以内的波司登和优衣库轻薄款，哦对了，还有老家线下店铺的以纯羽绒服。
不过长期以往，我倒是对羽绒服有了足够多的了解，足以写下这篇有参考价值的文章，帮助人们选购羽绒服。
羽绒服的历史
人类自古以来就有利用动物皮毛御寒的历史，早在原始社会时期，人类祖先就已经初步掌握了将兽皮制作成衣物的方法，用兽皮和树叶蔽体防寒，后来逐渐出现麻、棉、丝等纺织物，人类衣物变得丰富。相对来说，人类利用禽类羽毛御寒的历史要短得多，在唐朝，人们用鹅绒和布混合填充在被子中，在十三四世纪的欧洲，人们用鸭和鹅的羽毛填充进被套中。
直到 1940 年，现代羽绒服才被发明出来，主角是美国的艾迪·鲍尔，作为一名狂热户外运动爱好者，他在一次户外钓鱼过程中差点冻死，于是决心制作一件真正保暖的外套。鲍尔找到了鹅毛的羽绒，又恰逢杜邦实验室在 1938 年发明了尼龙，尼龙织物质地紧密，与棉布相比，尼龙面料可以防止羽绒「钻绒」，于是，他将二者结合，把羽绒填充进尼龙面料的衣服，绗缝锁绒，并将第一件羽绒外套命名为「Skyliner」，申…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>吃饭Bu洗碗</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[通过一个crackme学习逆向基础知识以及Delphi框架]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11818</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11818"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T02:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[通过一个crackme学习逆向基础知识以及Delphi框架]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Apple Pay or Google Wallet Instead of Plastic Cards]]></title>
        <id>636a9127f4db157fcdf20ff1</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/money-privacy-security-settings-apple-google-pay/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cash is safe—for now. Contactless payment methods, like Apple Pay or Google Wallet, are more of a threat to the existence of physical cards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reece Rogers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the MongoDB Atlas Hackathon 2022 on DEV!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devteam/announcing-the-mongodb-atlas-hackathon-2022-on-dev-2107</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devteam/announcing-the-mongodb-atlas-hackathon-2022-on-dev-2107"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T18:11:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#atlashackathon22 #mongodb #meta]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Bethencourt, The DEV Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React & NodeJS - Go LIVE with Full-Stack projects fast]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sm0ke/react-nodejs-go-live-with-full-stack-projects-fast-j0h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sm0ke/react-nodejs-go-live-with-full-stack-projects-fast-j0h"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T18:09:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #react #fullstack]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sm0ke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the ‘Election Integrity App’ Built to Purge US Voter Rolls]]></title>
        <id>63657b621bc1a3ed38dc3ace</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/true-the-vote-iv3-app-voter-fraud/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T15:59:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[True the Vote’s IV3 app is meant to catch election cheaters. But it has a fundamental flaw.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruv Mehrotra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All your JavaScript code is polluted]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jankapunkt/all-your-javascript-code-is-polluted-3e8l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jankapunkt/all-your-javascript-code-is-polluted-3e8l"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T15:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jan Küster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[安卓APP抓包解决方案(教程)]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11817</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11817"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T06:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[安卓APP抓包解决方案(教程)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CS的RCE利用研究]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11815</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11815"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T02:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CS的RCE利用研究]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SpringBoot和SpringMvc中的Context]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11814</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11814"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T02:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SpringBoot和SpringMvc中的Context]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Secret Ballot Is US Democracy’s Last Line of Defense]]></title>
        <id>63651410f65e6e9328cbf0a7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/secret-ballot-voter-intimidation-2022-us-midterms/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T21:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voter intimidation has cropped up in places across the nation, but the voting booth remains the one place where nobody can get to you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IRS Seizes Another Silk Road Hacker’s $3.36 Billion Bitcoin Stash]]></title>
        <id>636948fa0d25973ba5f9bc5a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/silk-road-bitcoin-seizure-james-zhong/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T19:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A year after a billion-dollar seizure of the dark web market's crypto, the same agency found a giant trove hidden under a different hacker's floorboards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client-side Routing without the JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/client-side-routing-without-the-javascript-3k1i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-learning/client-side-routing-without-the-javascript-3k1i"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T16:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #solidjs #webdev #performance]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Carniato, This is Learning</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[想要逃离 Chrome？请收下这份 Firefox 终极隐私指南]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76688</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76688"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T15:41:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐 
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。 
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

前言
毋庸置疑，如今的 Chrome 及其他基于 Chromium 的 Blink 内核浏览器因其速度快、网页兼容性好的优点，以绝对的优势占据了浏览器市场的主导地位。但与此同时，因为 Chrome 与 Chromium 被一家号称「不作恶」但处处作恶的公司所拥有，所以经常被诟病存在隐私问题。许多想要逃离 Chrome 统治的人都转向了更加自由的 Firefox 浏览器，尽管其母公司 Mozilla 近年来也是骚操作不断，但 Firefox 仍然是除 Chromium 的 Blink 和 Safari 的 WebKit 外唯一选择。
我曾经也很喜欢用 Chrome（或者说是 Chromium），使用 ArchLinux 作为主力系统的我，官方软件源中使用开源 Chromium 代码编译出的 Chromium 浏览器在当时体验基本与谷歌官方的闭源 Chrome 一致。促使我转向使用 Firefox 的契机开始于一年多前，谷歌限制了第三方浏览器对其数据同步 API 的使用，这样一来各家发行版自行编译的 Chromium 浏览器都失去了账户同步功能，这在当时引起了很多不满。从那时开始，我就开始尝试使用 Firefox 替代 Chromium 作为我的主力浏览器，并最终彻底淘汰掉了 Chromium。
无独有偶，谷歌又宣布将会在 2022 年底彻底禁用 Manifest V2 规范（后来又推迟了半年），作为替代者的 Manifest V3 规范，用谷歌的话说是为了「保护用户隐私」，限制了浏览器扩展的很多权限，其中影响最大的是禁用了 We…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>so1ar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hexagonal architecture as a solution to the obsolescence of UI frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/drouianm/hexagonal-architecture-as-a-solution-to-the-obsolescence-of-ui-frameworks-ej2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/drouianm/hexagonal-architecture-as-a-solution-to-the-obsolescence-of-ui-frameworks-ej2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T13:18:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#vue #react #typescript #architecture]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthieu Drouian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s Reckless Plan to Make Sex Pay on Twitter]]></title>
        <id>6365442eaec2220e3ecb87f6</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-adult-content-sex-twitter-content-moderation/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T11:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A plan to monetize adult content could make sense from a business and social standpoint. In practice, Twitter won’t be able to pull it off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olivia Snow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust Easy! Modern Cross-platform Command Line Tools to Supercharge Your Terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/deepu105/rust-easy-modern-cross-platform-command-line-tools-to-supercharge-your-terminal-4dd3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/deepu105/rust-easy-modern-cross-platform-command-line-tools-to-supercharge-your-terminal-4dd3"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T09:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#rust #terminal #linux #macos]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deepu K Sasidharan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Commons JXPath 远程代码执行(CVE-2022-41852)]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11813</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11813"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T09:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Commons JXPath 远程代码执行(CVE-2022-41852)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PostgresQL JDBC Drive 任意代码执行漏洞(CVE-2022-21724)]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11812</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11812"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T08:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PostgresQL JDBC Drive 任意代码执行漏洞(CVE-2022-21724)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[我在 app 里做了一下「赛博朋克：边缘行者」里的拖影效果]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76679</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76679"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T07:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[本次更新：
前几天看了「赛博朋克：边缘行者」，觉得里面的拖影效果非常有趣，就在 app 里做了一下。

App 介绍：
CUBE 是一款结合 iOS 软硬件新特性来完成实时特效的 app ，希望大家在手机上就可以玩到有趣的特效。 以我看过的热门影音作品为灵感，已经完成下面三个主要特效：
LiDAR 扫描效果：
日本女团 Perfume 在 Flow 的 MV 中大量使用点云这种技术，而正好配备 LiDAR 的 iPhone 可以感知深度，生成点云。
 
采样实时图像与 LiDAR 扫描仪生成的深度图，生成 3D 粒子（点云）。至多可生成 3,000,000 个粒子。
将生成的 3D 粒子与现实世界的场景混合在一起，让你感觉身处超现实世界。

Matrix 效果：
之前 黑客帝国 4 上映，黑客帝国又变成热门话题，就很想复刻一下经典的 code rain 。
 
这一次会选蓝色药丸还是红色药丸？

液态金属效果：
 
既然都提到了黑客帝国，那么终结者也不能不提。贯穿全系列的液态金属杀手也是经典之一。CUBE 带你回到 1991 年，化身成为詹姆斯·卡梅隆所拍摄的电影「终结者 2：审判日」中的终结者 T-1000 。

App Store
 
兑换码：
如果你对上面三个特效感兴趣，你可以在这里找到兑换码。
（我把码都放到一个 notion page 里，可以回复用掉的兑换码编号，方便我编辑。）
https://boringseries.notion.site/CUBE-392d7f454b2a4ceabae44ef478c87f4b]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>少数派77122655</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[感受读书上瘾的快乐]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76659</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76659"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T07:07:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[如何让枯燥的读书像看剧、享受美食、打游戏一样快乐？
读书上瘾模型，让读书成为一个上瘾循环。

上学的时候我比较喜欢玩游戏，但是在图书馆有很好的学习看书的氛围，游戏玩得比较少。毕业后，不再有看书的氛围了，玩游戏的频率逐渐增加，从每周1天增加到2天、后来逐步增加到7天，每天都玩游戏。
那个时候我意识到已经游戏上瘾了，打游戏占据了太多的时间，所以决定戒掉游戏，经过几次尝试，终于在2020年把游戏戒掉了。

即从游戏上瘾转变为读书上瘾，读书包括输入和输出两个步骤。输入指的是看书，从去年开始在豆瓣记录读书情况，利用周末和工作日的被动等待时间，每个月最多读过11本书。
输出分为写、说、实践3种形式。

写，发表长篇博客或简短的书评。
说，分为线上和线下两种形式，线上指在各个自媒体平台发布读书视频；线下指面对面形式，1对1的交流沟通或1对多的分享。
实践，看书不应该只停留在改变认知的程度，还要实践、改变自己的行为习惯。比如看了一本关于运动的书，不仅要有每天都运动的认知，还要付诸于每天的实践行动。

上一次玩游戏是在2020年，接下来详细介绍如何从游戏上瘾转变为读书上瘾。
 
 
Part 1 什么是上瘾？
一 上瘾的原理
二 戒上瘾的思路

提高行动成本
模块说

Part 2 读书上瘾模型
三 Step 1：选一本我需要的书

3.1 分析我想要的是什么
3.2 选书的途径
3.3 适当难度：最高学习效率15.87%
3.4 选择自己能承受的成长模式

四 Step 2：创造时间

4.1 人生需要做减法
4.2 时间管理系统/任务管理系统，GTD
GTD step 1 捕捉
GTD step 2 整理
GTD step 3 执行

4.3 时间颗粒度
4.4 实例演示：如何使用GTD
时间管理相关软件
使用GTD的一天


五 Step 3：输入：寻找适合自己的阅读方式

5.1 拆…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jogging</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[白菜价的国产暗尖怎么样？12款3~15元钢笔横评对比]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76673</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76673"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T03:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[前言
仔细翻了翻我个人的钢笔产品分享，和大家讨论过的都是以著名品牌的钢笔产品为主，对于国内钢笔品牌主要还是分享英雄旗下的经典产品与创新之作，毕竟其它钢笔品牌以我个人的眼光去看，都是没有太多购买意义的产品。
对于钢笔入门我始终推荐白金preppy系列、白金小流星系列、百乐78g、凌美狩猎者这些海外品牌的平价款式。
但因为英雄的关系，国人对于暗尖结构的钢笔有着相当的偏好，并且海外知名品牌如今也没有任何纯粹的现产暗尖钢笔产品。所以如今暗尖钢笔的赛道上全是国产钢笔品牌，并且价位主战场就是十元上下的低端市场，本篇中，我在某多多以零售价格，购买了十余款销量出色的国产暗尖，文内将从暗尖钢笔的用料、设计、特点来对它们进行全面的横评对比，希望能为大家了解这些产品带来帮助。
暗尖钢笔的发源与如今价位分布

暗尖钢笔发源于人类历史上最为成功的钢笔派克51，其诞生于1939年，暨派克成立51周年，故因此得以型号命名。
派克51的暗尖结构，通过树脂包裹了笔尖，在当年革新性得提高了钢笔的气密性，并根据结构，设计了新一代的毛细供墨系统，达到了更为稳定的书写效果。
在当年，暗尖钢笔以这两点综合的超强实用性，得到了市场的一致认可，直至停产派克51累计销售4000万支，是人类历史上最为成功的系列钢笔。
之所以停产，是因为后续钢笔的气密性与供墨毛细结构材料随着现代工业不断革新，暗尖已经不再具备核心优势。
现在的暗尖钢笔从高到底个人认为是三个层次，首先是派克前年复刻了51，做了个包住明尖的假暗尖，是目前价格最高的笔款，但不怎么值得去买。其次是英雄100代表了国产暗尖金笔，曾经100多元的价格性价比非常好，如今价格普遍要200以上，还是可以买，但没曾经的极致性价比了；最后就是本篇讲的10元上下，国产的钢尖暗尖钢笔！
暗尖钢笔的特点

一、暗尖钢笔因为笔尖露出部分少，书写时可以产生形变的笔尖体积相对较小，所以书写时感…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>老木曾雪菜</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[从2022中科大hackgame web中学习pdflatex RCE和python反序列化]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11809</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11809"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T03:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[从2022中科大hackgame web中学习pdflatex RCE和python反序列化]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[shiro环境下的Servlet内存马注入踩坑日记]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11808</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11808"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T03:09:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[shiro环境下的Servlet内存马注入踩坑日记]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[最近碰到的 Python pickle 反序列化小总结]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11807</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11807"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T02:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[最近碰到的 Python pickle 反序列化小总结]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok’s Greatest Asset Isn’t Its Algorithm—It’s Your Phone]]></title>
        <id>63517a45470620c1e69a25e1</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/tiktok-phones-extended-mind-philosophy/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Escaping the platform's addictive grasp means first overhauling our relationship to our devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leo Kim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elevate Your Terminal Experience on The Mac 🧘‍♂️]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/duncanlew/elevate-your-terminal-experience-on-the-mac-3o3m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/duncanlew/elevate-your-terminal-experience-on-the-mac-3o3m"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T20:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #tutorial #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Duncan Lew</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 Icon websites for devs and designers!!!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ymhaah/top-5-icon-websites-for-devs-and-designers-53mh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ymhaah/top-5-icon-websites-for-devs-and-designers-53mh"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T19:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#design #beginners #webdev #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Youssef Hafnawy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js visualized: Event Loop]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nodedoctors/an-animated-guide-to-nodejs-event-loop-3g62</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nodedoctors/an-animated-guide-to-nodejs-event-loop-3g62"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T18:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #node #beginners #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hu, Node Doctors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[利用Selenium绕过前端js加密及验证码爆破]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11806</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11806"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T13:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[利用Selenium绕过前端js加密及验证码爆破]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（八）CSP篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11805</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11805"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T13:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（八）CSP篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Expands Flood and Wildfire Tracking to More Countries]]></title>
        <id>636458f56e26e2941c119d11</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/google-ai-wildfire-flood-tracking/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: Sony announces a release date and price for its next PlayStation VR headset, Google kills a couple more apps, and everything’s gone explosive at Twitter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boone Ashworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenRASP浅析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11803</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11803"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T05:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenRASP浅析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Has Fired Twitter’s ‘Ethical AI’ Team]]></title>
        <id>63651386d481f3fd793dde70</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-ethical-ai-team/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T16:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of a wave of layoffs, the new CEO disbanded a group working to make Twitter’s algorithms more transparent and fair.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Javascript Generators: A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/muqsitadam/javascript-generators-a-beginners-guide-1ojf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/muqsitadam/javascript-generators-a-beginners-guide-1ojf"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T23:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #beginners #webdev #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdulmuqsit Adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[最近遇到的Linux内核内存取证小分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11800</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11800"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T18:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[最近遇到的Linux内核内存取证小分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[webpagetest反序列化及ssrf漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11798</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11798"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T17:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[webpagetest反序列化及ssrf漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tracardi — Automate Customer Journey - Track Anything]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tracardi</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tracardi"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T15:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi Product Hunt 👋
I’m Risto, a co-founder of TRACARDI.

I am happy to present to you an open-source product that our community has been working on for over a year. It is a free platform for customer journey automation. 
What is TRACARDI?
It’s  a platform that collects data from customer journeys and assigns it to a profile, automates data enhancement, injects micro-frontend apps to your existing page, orchestrates data flow to other systems, facilitates Machine Learning APIs usage. 
With TRACARDI you can:
🌟 Reuse your current infrastructure  - Tracardi doesn’t require the complex integration or dedicated infrastructure. It runs on top of cloud managed services; reusing your existing  infrastructure and spinning up new resources when needed.

🌟 Collect Customer Data - You can collect, in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Artists: Do Not Fear AI Image Generators]]></title>
        <id>61ba7c7ba08cdc8657dc4958</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/artists-do-not-fear-ai-image-generators/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[True, new systems devalue craft, shift power, and wreck cultures and scenes. But didn’t the piano do that to the harpsichord?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Ford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Algorithms Quietly Run the City of Washington, DC—and Maybe Your Hometown]]></title>
        <id>63617b2dd5a8378824123f92</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/algorithms-quietly-run-the-city-of-dc-and-maybe-your-hometown/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report finds that municipal agencies in Washington deploy dozens of automated decision systems, often without residents’ knowledge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khari Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（七）技巧篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11795</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11795"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T08:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（七）技巧篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome扩展安全开发从零到一]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11794</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11794"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T04:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome扩展安全开发从零到一]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[某路由器固件模拟分析及栈溢出漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11793</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11793"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T03:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[某路由器固件模拟分析及栈溢出漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to add PayPal checkout payments to your React app]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/paypaldeveloper/how-to-add-paypal-checkout-payments-to-your-react-app-53aa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/paypaldeveloper/how-to-add-paypal-checkout-payments-to-your-react-app-53aa"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T17:25:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #react #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pato, PayPal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make the most of DEV if you’re over Twitter]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devteam/how-to-make-the-most-of-dev-if-youre-over-twitter-4567</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devteam/how-to-make-the-most-of-dev-if-youre-over-twitter-4567"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T13:24:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#watercooler #meta #twitter #career]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Halpern, The DEV Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seeking Psychedelics? Check the Data Privacy Clause]]></title>
        <id>635ae105a398fb738c4b9234</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/colorado-psychedelics-health-privacy-surveillance/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colorado's Proposition 122 wants to let people take psilocybin at healing centers. But sensitive data isn't covered by medical privacy protections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mason Marks</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips to become a great software engineer]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jamielivingstone/tips-to-become-a-great-software-engineer-10gf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jamielivingstone/tips-to-become-a-great-software-engineer-10gf"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T10:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#career #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Livingstone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a registration and a login with two-factor authentication on React 🤩]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/novu/creating-a-registration-and-a-login-with-two-factor-authentication-on-react-2p2i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/novu/creating-a-registration-and-a-login-with-two-factor-authentication-on-react-2p2i"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T10:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #node #webdev #javascript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevo David, novu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[浅析NodeJS]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11791</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11791"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T07:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[浅析NodeJS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API安全漏洞靶场crapi的基本介绍和解题思路-第二篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11789</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11789"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T06:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[API安全漏洞靶场crapi的基本介绍和解题思路-第二篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML & CSS Features, Tips For a 10x Faster Page Loading Speed]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/koustav/html-css-features-tips-for-a-10x-fast-page-loading-speed-4jop</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/koustav/html-css-features-tips-for-a-10x-fast-page-loading-speed-4jop"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T05:19:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#news #webdev #html #css]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>devkoustav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（六）续集篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11788</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11788"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T04:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（六）续集篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（五）最终篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11790</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11790"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T02:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（五）最终篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 7 Best React Component Libraries to Use in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/amrtcrypto/the-7-best-react-component-libraries-to-use-in-2022-11la</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/amrtcrypto/the-7-best-react-component-libraries-to-use-in-2022-11la"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T18:10:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #react #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amr Tawfik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[通过边界代理一路打到三层内网+后渗透通用手法]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11784</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11784"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T02:08:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[通过边界代理一路打到三层内网+后渗透通用手法]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IPC$共享利用姿势]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11783</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11783"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T02:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IPC$共享利用姿势]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[初步理解Phar反序列化 + 分析POP链构造（2022 Bilibili 1024 程序员节第二题）]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11782</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11782"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T01:29:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[初步理解Phar反序列化 + 分析POP链构造（2022 Bilibili 1024 程序员节第二题）]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Folder Structure for NodeJS & ExpressJS project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mr_ali3n/folder-structure-for-nodejs-expressjs-project-435l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mr_ali3n/folder-structure-for-nodejs-expressjs-project-435l"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T09:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#express #javascript #node #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vaibhav Mehta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Docker Extensions Every Developer Must Try]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/docker/9-docker-extensions-every-developer-must-try-1no2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/docker/9-docker-extensions-every-developer-must-try-1no2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T07:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#docker #devops #kubernetes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pavan Belagatti, Docker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awesome VS Code Extensions for Navigating Large Codebases]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-vs-code-extensions-for-navigating-large-codebases-256n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-vs-code-extensions-for-navigating-large-codebases-256n"/>
        <updated>2022-10-30T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#beginners #webdev #javascript #react]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Vishwakarma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Shorthand Optimization Tricks every JavaScript Developer Should Know 😎]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/7-shorthand-optimization-tricks-every-javascript-developer-should-know-4fj5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/7-shorthand-optimization-tricks-every-javascript-developer-should-know-4fj5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-30T06:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #programming #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapajyoti Bose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Startups Have a Sellout Problem. There's a Better Way]]></title>
        <id>63481d9808a267a4aad8c050</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/startups-exit-community-ipo-business/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-29T13:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Startups like Meta and Twitter serve as digital infrastructure, but aren't accountable to users. Some startups are trying to chart a new way to exit that focuses on community—not shareholders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED Ideas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[某软件监控页面RCE漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11778</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11778"/>
        <updated>2022-10-29T13:22:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[某软件监控页面RCE漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art of Hitting Disinformation Where It Lives]]></title>
        <id>6356a50d3d83d1af9973abd3</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/disinformation-art-science/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Combating fake news with facts doesn't work because humans are wired for emotion. It's time for more creative tactics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Southern</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk’s Twitter Will Not Be the Town Square the World Needs]]></title>
        <id>635af6043d7842cc349a2206</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-twitter-town-square/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T12:54:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a moment to choose a different path, inspired by the lessons of thriving offline communities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Pariser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe Prepares to Rewrite the Rules of the Internet]]></title>
        <id>6359871f68addec416d5b940</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/europe-dma-prepares-to-rewrite-the-rules-of-the-internet/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Digital Markets Act will force Big Tech platforms to break open their walled gardens in 2023, says the EU’s new ambassador to Silicon Valley.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khari Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome Extensions of the Month - October 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/j471n/chrome-extensions-of-the-month-october-2022-1c0j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/j471n/chrome-extensions-of-the-month-october-2022-1c0j"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T06:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#productivity #webdev #javascript #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jatin Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Master The Art of Content Creation As a Developer?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/patilganesh1010/how-to-master-the-art-of-content-creation-as-a-developer-kpn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/patilganesh1010/how-to-master-the-art-of-content-creation-as-a-developer-kpn"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T03:18:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #tutorial #opensource #career]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Patil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 must-know tips for writing clean code with Javascript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexomeyer/8-must-know-tips-for-writing-clean-code-with-javascript-i4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexomeyer/8-must-know-tips-for-writing-clean-code-with-javascript-i4"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T13:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #refactorit #webdev #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Omeyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Listening to Audiobooks Really Reading?]]></title>
        <id>6312405ea4a22698f6d24aaf</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/is-listening-to-audiobooks-really-reading/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WIRED’s spiritual advice columnist on bardic traditions for a modern age—and why book snobs worry about the wrong things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meghan O'Gieblyn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI's New Creative Streak Sparks a Silicon Valley Gold Rush]]></title>
        <id>635811513c668b3d581922aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ais-new-creative-streak-sparks-a-silicon-valley-gold-rush/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors have got the hots for "generative AI" that can make text and images. But so far, the hype runs ahead of the business results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a VS Code Extension "Todo Tree" can make your coding easier | Todo Tree Configuration | Highlighting Comments in VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/koustav/how-a-vs-code-extension-todo-tree-can-make-your-coding-easier-todo-tree-configuration-and-use-cases-11kc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/koustav/how-a-vs-code-extension-todo-tree-can-make-your-coding-easier-todo-tree-configuration-and-use-cases-11kc"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T05:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#news #vscode #programming #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>devkoustav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM PASS PWN (三)]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11775</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11775"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T01:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM PASS PWN (三)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Real Reason Elon Musk Wants You to Have More Babies]]></title>
        <id>61ba7bbc63820b7f88293089</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/real-reason-elon-musk-population-panic/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People who complain about population aren’t talking numbers—they’re fantasizing about tightening the reins on workers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Virginia Heffernan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[记一次某CMS代码审计]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11774</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11774"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T10:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[记一次某CMS代码审计]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-41852 Apache Commons Jxpath 漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11769</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11769"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T07:29:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-41852 Apache Commons Jxpath 漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hinge Will Try to Thwart Scammers With Video Verification]]></title>
        <id>6356e6b3a8552c961517a850</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hinge-selfie-verification-scammers-bots/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T14:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To combat the scourge of bots and fake accounts, the dating site will ask users to prove their humanity by capturing a video selfie.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Goode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made 10x faster JSON.stringify() functions, even type safe]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/samchon/i-made-10x-faster-jsonstringify-functions-even-type-safe-2eme</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/samchon/i-made-10x-faster-jsonstringify-functions-even-type-safe-2eme"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T12:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #programming #typescript #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeongho Nam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>