<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-09-23T10:47:14.049Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-09-23T10:47:14.049Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rad Power offers first e-bike subscriptions in Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/9/23/23368187/rad-power-offers-first-e-bike-subscriptions-in-europe</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/9/23/23368187/rad-power-offers-first-e-bike-subscriptions-in-europe"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T10:46:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The RadRunner e-bike (left) and RadWagon e-cargo bike (right) can now be rented in Berlin. | Image: Rad Power
    

  
Rad Power e-bikes can now be rented in Berlin, via a partnership with local firm Cycle. Monthly subscriptions in the German capital cost €79.90 (about $78) for either a RadRunner utility e-bike or RadWagon e-cargo bike. Subscriptions can be month-to-month or for the entire year.
For context, a brand new RadRunner 2 costs €1,449 in Europe, which is what you’ll pay after 18 months if renting.
Subscription prices also cover repair services which can be booked in the Cycle app if something breaks. And, for an additional monthly fee, there’s a peace-of-mind package which reduces the deductible in cases of damage and theft. The subscription bikes can also be fitted with options like baskets and racks (though it’s not clear if this costs...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Simple Stock Price Tracker in Flutter]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hackmamba/create-a-simple-stock-price-tracker-in-flutter-n0h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hackmamba/create-a-simple-stock-price-tracker-in-flutter-n0h"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T10:19:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trackers are mechanisms, applications, or systems used by investors to track the financial performance of a particular stock. They give investors the required leverage to make a profitable financial decision as an individual or a company.
In this post, we will learn how to create a stock price tracker in Flutter using the Marketstack open API to search for our favourite stock details and save the details on Appwrite’s database.
To fully grasp the concepts presented in this tutorial, we require the following:
Basic understanding of Dart and Flutter
Flutter SDK installed
Xcode with a developer account (for Mac users)
Either IOS Simulator, Android Studio, or Chrome web browser to run our application
Docker installation

An Appwrite instance; check out this article on how to set up an instance…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Demola Malomo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understand call, apply, and bind functions in JavaScript like never before.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/swastikyadav/understand-call-apply-and-bind-functions-in-javascript-like-never-before-575e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/swastikyadav/understand-call-apply-and-bind-functions-in-javascript-like-never-before-575e"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T10:18:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we'll take a detailed look at how call, apply, and bind work in JavaScript.
JavaScript's call(), apply(), and bind() functions are often misunderstood. In this video, we'll clear up the confusion once and for all.
We'll discuss the differences between the three, and when you would want to use each one. We'll also provide examples to help you understand how they work.
By the end of this post, you'll have a deep understanding of how these functions work, and be able to use them in your own code.
So, let's get started.
Before we go any further, there is also a video explanation of this post. You can check it out here.
Now, let's start for real.
Let's say we have an object with name and greet function.
const obj = {
  name: "Swastik",
  greet(age) {
    console.log(`Hello ${this.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Swastik Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The simple guide to understanding Callback functions in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/efkumah/the-simple-guide-to-understanding-callback-functions-in-javascript-3e3e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/efkumah/the-simple-guide-to-understanding-callback-functions-in-javascript-3e3e"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T10:07:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Functions are one of the underlying building blocks in JavaScript. It helps us perform a specific task when it is executed. 
In this post, we take a look at callback functions with easy to follow explanation and examples.
Let's get started.
Before we dive into callback function, let's revisit function in JavaScript
A function, is a block of code that performs a particular task when it is carried out. 
For an operation to qualify as a function, it requires a certain input and return an output, and there should be a clear relationship between the input and the output. 
To use a function, we must define and call it.
Take a look at the code below
// define the function
function sayHi(user){

 console.log(`Hello ${user}`)
}

//callthe function
sayHi("Emmanuel")

In the code above, we define the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmanuel Fordjour  Kumah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Garmin introduces its first smart blood pressure monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/9/23/23368155/garmin-new-smart-blood-pressure-monitor-withings-fda-cleared</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/9/23/23368155/garmin-new-smart-blood-pressure-monitor-withings-fda-cleared"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T09:50:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Garmin Index Smart Blood Pressure Monitor can sync with the Garmin Connect app, keeping all your self recorded health data in one place. | Image: Garmin
    

  
Garmin now has an FDA-cleared (not to be confused with FDA approved) smart blood pressure monitor to accompany its other health-focused wearables. The Garmin Index BPM Smart Blood Pressure Monitor allows users to measure systolic and diastolic blood pressure and syncs that data with the Garmin Connect mobile app that also syncs with Garmin devices like smartwatches, chest straps, smart scales, and bike computers.
“When using the Index BPM as part of the larger Garmin ecosystem, all of your health and fitness data can be viewed right in Garmin Connect, helping to give you a more complete look at your overall health in one app,” said Dan Bartel, Garmin vice president of global consumer sales.
The Garmin Index BPM syncs collected data...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[关于 Linux 和 Git 的创造者 Linus Torvalds 的 20 件趣事]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15063-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15063-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T09:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些已知的、或鲜为人知的事情 —— 这里有 20 件关于 Linux 内核创造者 Linus Torvalds 的趣事。




Linus Benedict Torvalds（林纳斯·本纳第克特·托瓦兹），在 1991 年还是一名攻读硕士的芬兰学生时，他开发了一个类 Unix 操作系统。从那时起，它引发了一场革命：今天，它为大多数 Web 服务器、许多嵌入式设备和 500 强超级计算机 中的每一台提供支持。

我已经写过一些鲜为人知的 关于 Linux 的事实，但这篇文章不是关于 Linux 的，而是关于它的创造者，Linus Torvalds。

通过阅读他的传记《只是为了好玩Just for Fun》，我了解了有关 Torvalds 的许多事情。如果你有兴趣，你也可以 订购一本传记。（这是一个 受益推荐 链接。）

关于 Linus Torvalds 的 20 个有趣事实

你可能已经知道一些关于 Linus 的事情，但是通过阅读这篇文章，你很有可能会了解一些关于他的新趣事。

1、以诺贝尔奖获得者的名字命名

Linus Benedict Torvalds 于 1969 年 12 月 28 日出生于赫尔辛基。他来自一个记者家庭。他的父亲 Nils Torvalds 是芬兰政治家，可能是未来参加选举的总统候选人。

他的名字来自于诺贝尔化学与和平奖的双奖获得者 Linus Pauling 的名字。

2、世界上所有的 Torvalds 都是亲戚

虽然你可能会找到几个名字为 Linus 的人，但你不会找到很多姓 Torvalds 的人 —— 因为“正确”的拼写实际上是 Torvald（没有 s）。他的祖父将名字从 Torvald 改为 Torvalds，并在末尾添加了一个“s”。于是，Torvalds 王朝（如果我可以这么称呼它的话）开始了。
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slack Canvas — A new surface to curate and collaborate within Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/slack-canvas</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/slack-canvas"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T08:43:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Music to sponsor Super Bowl halftime show amidst push into sports]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/9/23/23368143/apple-music-super-bowl-lvii-halftime-show-february-2023-sports-streaming-services</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/9/23/23368143/apple-music-super-bowl-lvii-halftime-show-february-2023-sports-streaming-services"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T08:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Snoop Dogg performs at the Super Bowl halftime show in 2022. | Photo by Michael Owens/Getty Images
    

  
Apple Music will sponsor next February’s Super Bowl halftime show, replacing long-time sponsor Pepsi. In a press release, the NFL says over 120 million people watched the Super Bowl LVI halftime show in February this year, which featured performances from Dr. Dre, Snoop Dogg, Eminem, Mary J. Blige, and Kendrick Lamar. The New York Times reports that the NFL had been shopping the sponsorship deal around for around $50 million, though exact terms of the finalized deal were not made public.
The deal comes as Apple and other streaming service operators are increasingly looking to sports as a source of growth. Apple has already inked deals to broadcast Major League Baseball and Major League Soccer games on Apple TV Plus, while rival Amazon...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Dependabot alerts REST API is now available!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devtical/github-dependabot-alerts-rest-api-is-now-available-4pmf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devtical/github-dependabot-alerts-rest-api-is-now-available-4pmf"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T08:25:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub sends Dependabot alerts when it detects that your repository uses a vulnerable dependency or malware.
For more information, see About Dependabot alerts if you don't know about Dependabot yet.
GitHub announced that Dependabot alerts REST API is now available in public beta.
You must use an access token with the security_events scope to use endpoints with private repositories. You can also use tokens with the public_repo scope for public repositories only. 
GitHub Apps must have Dependabot alerts read permission to use this endpoint.
curl \
  -H "Accept: application/vnd.github+json" \ 
  -H "Authorization: Bearer <YOUR-TOKEN>" \
  https://api.github.com/repos/OWNER/REPO/dependabot/alerts

GitHub Apps must have Dependabot alerts read permission to use this endpoint.
curl \
  -H "Accept: application/vnd.github+json" \ 
  -H "Authorization: Bearer <YOUR-TOKEN>" \
  https://api.github.com/repos/OWNER/REPO/dependabot/alerts/ALERT_NUMBER

GitHub Apps must have Dependabot alerts write permission to use this endpoint.
curl \
  -X PATCH \
  -H "Accept: application/vnd.github+json" \ 
  -H "Authorization: Bearer <YOUR-TOKEN>" \
  https://api.github.com/repos/OWNER/REPO/dependabot/alerts/ALERT_NUMBER \
  -d '{"state":"dismissed","dismissed_reason":"tolerable_risk","dismissed_comment":"This alert is accurate but we use a sanitizer."}']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wahyu Kristianto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🤖 Fresh Engineering Open Positions - Week #39 of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shman/fresh-engineering-open-positions-week-39-of-2022-16c7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shman/fresh-engineering-open-positions-week-39-of-2022-16c7"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T07:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey,
remote engineering jobs to help you find your next remote position.
Today, I have 15 of 441 new jobs I want to share with you. Check out all our new jobs from companies like Mews, Capital One, IQ ESM, Client Server, Black & Veatch, Flexbase, Pachama, Global Channel Management, Inc, Zentech Talent Limited, Qualitest, Mad Collective, Reincubate, Workwise GmbH, TalentTECH, Quarkslab, Trimble Solutions (Uk) Ltd and more below! 👇
Let's dive in.
Senior Front End Engineer @ Mews
Senior Software Engineer @ Capital One
Servicenow Developers @ IQ ESM
Senior Engineer @ Client Server
Electrical Engineer @ Black & Veatch
Webflow Developer @ Flexbase
Learning Engineer @ Pachama
Solution Engineer @ Global Channel Management, Inc
Infrastructure Engineer @ Zentech Talent Limited
Automation Architect @ Qualitest
Engineer @ Mad Collective
Software Engineer @ Reincubate
Health Tech @ Workwise GmbH
Product Engineer @ Quarkslab
Senior Software Engineer @ Trimble Solutions (Uk) Ltd
Check all 441 new engineering jobs. You can find the original post here: 🤖 Fresh Engineering Open Positions - Week #39 of 2022.
I also share new jobs on our Twitter: @remoteindexco
By the way, do you have any feedback for me? Feature requests? Companies I should add? I built Remote Index for remote workers like you (and me), so I want to hear what can be improved.
You can reach me on Twitter @shmannet at any time.
Many thanks 🙂
Kamil]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kamil Kwiecien</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded Systems Weekly #119]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/embedsys/embedded-systems-weekly-119-5a1f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/embedsys/embedded-systems-weekly-119-5a1f"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T07:51:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Mark Russinovich tweeted:
Speaking of languages, it's time to halt starting any new projects in C/C++ and use Rust for those scenarios where a non-GC language is required. For the sake of security and reliability. the industry should declare those languages as deprecated.
Mark is CTO of Microsoft Azure and the author of the famous Sysinternals tools. He knows a lot about low-level developments. I vividly feel the pressure to learn Rust. Do you feel it too?
Happy reading!
A pair of Rust kernel modules
Programming STM32 Blue Pill using makefile
Denis Bodor makes me realise that the project is actually using the file STM32F103C8TX_FLASH.ld which is auto-generated by STM32CubeIDE. Thank you Denis!
I'm Building a Self-Destructing USB Drive
second part.
GCC's new fortification level: The gains and costs
Stand alone SSTV camera
SSTV was. SSTV (Slow-scan television) is a picture transmission method. In this project, this is the method used by the author to transmit images captured by an ESP32-cam via radio. The author's conclusion is that it can be a potential solution when simplicity and low cost are important criteria.
Report: Apple to Move a Part of its Embedded Cores to RISC-V, Stepping Away from Arm ISA RISC-V is eating market share bit by bit. In this case, is it because of technical superiority or simply to avoid licensing fees? what do you think?
F4PGA
Canoo, ADAS Feature Integration Engineer, Full-time, US (Full remote)
Canoo’s mission is to bring EVs to Everyone and build a world-class team to deploy this sustainable mobility revolution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embedded Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Horizon Helvetica® — The “Swiss army knife” of sketch tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/horizon-helvetica</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/horizon-helvetica"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T07:46:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VetrinaLive — Sell digital & physical  goods without transaction fees]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/vetrinalive</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/vetrinalive"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T07:37:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tasquitos Freelance Marketplace — Get more leads, more sales, and more trust by better content]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tasquitos-freelance-marketplace</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tasquitos-freelance-marketplace"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T07:08:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WLB.works — A job seeking website focusing on work life balance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/wlb-works</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/wlb-works"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T07:04:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supabase, Self-hosting with Podman Instead of Docker!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/zakariachahboun/supabase-self-hosting-with-podman-1mhl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/zakariachahboun/supabase-self-hosting-with-podman-1mhl"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T07:03:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supabase, Self-hosting with Podman!


Supabase is an open source Firebase alternative providing all the backend features you need to build a product. You can use it completely, or just the features you need. Start a project with the hosted platform or learn how to host Supabase yourself with podman 👇.
You need to install podman, podman-docker and docker-compose
i'm using linux pop_os
sudo apt-get -y install podman podman-docker docker-compose

in your ~./bashrc file add docker as a podman alias (alias docker=podman)
Now. You have to clone the supabase repo:
git clone --depth 1 https://github.com/supabase/supabase

Then:
# Go to the docker folder
cd supabase/docker

# Copy the fake env vars
cp .env.example .env

Now. You have to configure docker hub mirror in /etc/containers/registries.conf :
sudo nano /etc/containers/registries.conf

Add these lines to the end of the file:
unqualified-search-registries = ['docker.io']

[[registry]]
prefix = "docker.io"
location = "docker.io"

[[registry.mirror]]
prefix = "docker.io"
location = "docker.mirrors.ustc.edu.cn"

Save it! Now. You are ready to install supabase studio:
sudo docker-compose up

Finally. visit http://localhost:3000 to start using Supabase Studio.

In case you face this error:
ERROR: for db  error preparing container 22e6838a1fd10267d63f69ef400000a84a1a857a5e46718003f8a5f63388bb0f for attach: cannot listen on the TCP port: listen tcp4 :5432: bind: address already in use
Just change the POSTGRES_PORT in .env file.
😊 Enjoy!
My Twitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zakaria chahboun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build a dynamic distributed database with DistSQL]]></title>
        <id>70205 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/9/dynamic-distributed-database-distsql"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to build a dynamic distributed database with DistSQL
Raigor Jiang
Fri, 09/23/2022 - 03:00

            
Distributed databases are common for many reasons. They increase reliability, redundancy, and performance. Apache ShardingSphere is an open source framework that enables you to transform any database into a distributed database. Since the release of ShardingSphere 5.0.0, DistSQL (Distributed SQL) has provided dynamic management for the ShardingSphere ecosystem.
In this article, I demonstrate a data sharding scenario in which DistSQL's flexibility allows you to create a distributed database. At the same time, I show some syntax sugar to simplify operating procedures, allowing your potential users to choose their preferred syntax.
A series of DistSQL statements are run through practica…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raigor Jiang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install JDBC on Linux in 3 steps]]></title>
        <id>70200 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/9/install-jdbc-linux"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Install JDBC on Linux in 3 steps
Seth Kenlon
Fri, 09/23/2022 - 03:00

            
When you write an application, it's common to require data storage. Sometimes you're storing assets your application needs to function, and other times you're storing user data, including preferences and save data. One way to store data is in a database, and in order to communicate between your code and a database, you need a database binding or connector for your language. For Java, a common database connector is JDBC (Java database connectivity.)
1. Install Java
Of course, to develop with Java you must also have Java installed. I recommend SDKman for Linux, macOS, and WSL or Cygwin. For Windows, you can download OpenJDK from developers.redhat.com.

More on Java
What is enterprise Java programming?
Red Hat …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Kenlon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GreeningWeb — A widget that makes your website traffic green]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/greeningweb</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/greeningweb"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T06:23:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating custom services in medusa]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dailydevtips1/creating-custom-services-in-medusa-2dkh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dailydevtips1/creating-custom-services-in-medusa-2dkh"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T06:03:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that we know how to use an existing service in our routes. Let's take it to. The next level and see how we can create our service even.
A service is something that you can use throughout your application.
Let's say we want to add a translation service, for instance.
src/services.
If our service is the translateService, we should name the file translate.js (filename without the Service part).
The most basic service file would look like this.
import { TransactionBaseService } from '@medusajs/medusa';

class TranslateService extends TransactionBaseService {
  func() {
    return '';
  }
}

export default TranslateService;

As you can see, the service extends the ‌TransactionBaseService, which gives us access to all the existing and other services.
Let's create a mock demo function so that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bongers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallels Desktop 18 最新优惠码，国庆 75 折]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43433</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/parallels-desktop-18-coupon-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T05:23:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Parallels Desktop 18 是一款高性能的 macOS 虚拟机，可以用来在 Mac 电脑上以运行普通程序的方式，运行 Windows、Linux，甚至再运行一个 macOS 系统，方便随]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shotstack Virtual Hackathon: Build Awesome Media Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shotstack/shotstack-virtual-hackathon-build-awesome-media-apps-3ap7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shotstack/shotstack-virtual-hackathon-build-awesome-media-apps-3ap7"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T04:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're excited to announce the Shotstack's first ever virtual hackathon is starting on 26th September 2022. Shotstack is inviting builders to join us to build awesome media applications. 
Digital media is an integral part of our lives. With the rise of AI and automation, it is evolving as fast as ever. Shotstack API enables builders to rapidly develop and launch media apps so you get to build the next big media product. 
Shotstack's virtual hackathon is a great way to showcase your idea, skills, and get along with the community that have similar interest.
Visit our website to learn about the hackathon.
Register for the hackathon below 👇
https://forms.gle/r2sqyFRmz7Sr7JUVA]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kushal Magar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[palpatine received its first PR]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/batunpc/palpatine-received-its-first-pull-request-532a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/batunpc/palpatine-received-its-first-pull-request-532a"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T04:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[palpatine is now supporting markdown files🎉 It lets you write links in markdown so that when it is rendered into html, the links will be clickable. You can see this in the demo here. This is the initial support of palpatine for markdown files, and we will be adding more features in the future. I appreciate Samina for implementing this feature to address Issue#6 with the following PR respectively.
During PR, we talked over Slack(like almost every developer) and I enjoyed the process. Slack is a great tool for communication and I highly recommend it. It was not something I used to use often, but I noticed it feels much more convenient than any other tool, it supports large files, and screen recordings to be shared, unlike the other tools with limitations on certain sizes. With Samina, we have shared our screens and discussed the implementation. I am confident that we learned a lot from each other. I also implemented similar markdown support into her tool rwar that supports markdown headings. You can see her demo here. The PR I raised was to address issue#6.
After you finalize your changes and give a detailed report to the maintainer through the preferred environment (GitHub issues, Slack, etc.), you can create a PR. Follow the steps below to create a PR:
git checkout -b issue-6 # Create a new branch for your work
git add . # Add all the changes you made
git commit -m "Updating x, y, and z based on changes"
git push origin issue-5

I have been working on the efficiency of the tool and refactoring its readability. I appreciate any feedback on palpatine and also if you missed the first post regarding this project, you can read it here. While this project is something I enjoy wholeheartedly, it is also a project I get grades from. Due to deadlines, quick decisions had to be made, therefore, there is room for improvement.



Links
palpatine
rwar




Repo




PR
Sam's Pull request
My pull request


Issue
Issue#6 to Palpatine
Issue#6 to rwar]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>𝔹𝕒𝕥𝕦𝕙𝕒𝕟 𝕀𝕡𝕔𝕚</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #768 微软 Azure CTO 称 C/C++ 应该被废弃]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15062-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15062-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T04:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[微软 Azure CTO 称 C/C++ 应该被废弃

他在 Twitter 发表了个人观点：“是时候停止用 C/C++ 启动任何新项目了，在那些需要非 GC 语言的场景中使用 Rust。为了安全和可靠性，行业应该宣布这些语言被废弃。”这并不是微软第一次倡导将 Rust 作为提高软件安全的一种手段。三年前，微软安全响应中心（MSRC）表示，“我们认为 Rust 代表了目前 C 和 C++ 的最佳替代品。……MSRC 分配了 CVE 编号的安全问题中，大约有 70% 是内存安全问题。这意味着，如果该软件是用 Rust 编写的，这些内存安全问题很可能已经被消除了。”


消息来源：Dev Class



老王点评：Rust 是一个很有希望，但是仍然不够成熟和完善的语言，不过，C/C++ 程序员们可以开始学了。




Mozilla 发布报告指责操作系统与浏览器的锁定

浏览器市场份额已经急剧减少的 Mozilla 最近发布研究报告，整篇报告并未有什么新的证据和观点。在报告中，Mozilla 警告说，“浏览器市场的竞争对于确保创新和消费者的选择至关重要，更广泛地说，保护开放网络的活力，防止商业巨头试图封锁它。”并称，“相比之下，来自独立浏览器的竞争可以帮助推动新的功能，以及在隐私和安全等领域的创新”。


消息来源：Tech Crunch



老王点评：首先，请把 Firefox 做好，而不是指责别人借助优势扩大份额吧。




被忽视 15 年的 Python 漏洞导致 35 万项目陷入风险

早在 2007 年，就已经有安全研究人员披露了一个 Python 的安全风险，并得到了编号 CVE-2007-4559。遗憾的是，它一直没有获得正式的修复补丁。唯一的缓解措施，也只是在更新后的开发者文档中提示了相关风险。今年早些时候，一位安全研究人员在调查另一个安全问题时，再次发现该漏洞可用于代码执行。该漏洞位于 Python tarfile 包中，预估有超过 35 万个存储库易受该漏洞攻击的影响，且其中不乏重要项目，如 GitHub Copilot。


消息来源：Bleeping Computer



老王点评：又一个开源供应链安全漏洞。任何一个不起眼的小漏洞都可能引起大坝崩溃。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The joy of validating with Joi]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/methmi/the-joy-of-validating-with-joi-51ej</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/methmi/the-joy-of-validating-with-joi-51ej"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T03:58:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Validation is a crucial step. But one look at the lines of IFs spawning from endless checks could send us over to NPM, hoping to find the perfect library.
And one of the validation libraries you would find is Joi. And like its name, it’s a joy to use.
With Joi, you can
Describe your data using a simple, intuitive and readable language.
So to ensure some user input contains a name and a valid email, it’s simply
const schema = Joi.object({
name: Joi.string()
   .min(3)
   .max(30)
   .required(),
email: Joi.string()
   .email({ minDomainSegments: 2, tlds: { allow: ['com', 'net'] } })
})

This code block validates an input to have a name property with a number of characters between 3 and 30, and an email with two domain parts (sample.com) and a top level domain (TLD) of either .com or .net.
B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Methmi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips: How to get last element of an array in javascipt]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devvsakib/tips-how-to-get-last-element-of-an-array-in-javascipt-3k2j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devvsakib/tips-how-to-get-last-element-of-an-array-in-javascipt-3k2j"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T03:56:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An array is a data structure, which can store a fixed-size collection of elements of the same data type
If you have worked with JavaScript arrays before, you might know that they can be destructured much like objects. This is most commonly used to extract the first value of an array or the values of an array with a known length.
But destructuring can go much further, as it allows you to extract the length property of an array. Add this to the fact that extracted variables can be used in the destructuring assignment itself and you can put together a one-liner to extract the last element of an array.
const arr = [1, 2, 3];
const { 0: first, length, [length - 1]: last } = arr;
first; // 1
last; // 3
length; // 3

While this technique is interesting, it has a couple of caveats. First off, you have to extract the length property, which creates an additional variable for it. And secondly, it doesn’t have any significant performance advantages over other options, such as using Array.prototype.slice(). 
Another way we can do is, first we need array length then subtract 1 to get the last element index.
Take a loot at code
const arr = [1, 2, 3];
const lastEle = arr[arr.length - 1]
lastEle; // 3

arr.length = 3
website DevvSakib.Me]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevvSakib</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luma Language — Learn French in seconds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/luma-language-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/luma-language-2"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T02:22:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[探索自我是一条漫长的路]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75858</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75858"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T02:15:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[在这个大众觉醒的时代，我们常常听到「我们需要探索自我，了解自己」。但是，假设我们很粗暴地把人分为三种：认为不需要寻找自我的人（或不知道「寻找自我」重要性的人）、正在寻找自我的人、以及找到了自我的人，第一类人是绝大多数，第二类是少数，第三类是少数中的少数。
这其实也对应了我们认识自我的三个阶段。
第一阶段是我们需要觉醒，意识到探索自我的重要性。
为什么探索自我对每个人都很重要？
人是需要意义驱动的动物，我们天生有实现自身价值的冲动。但每个人的价值、优势是不同的。我的性格是怎样的？我想做的事情是什么？对我来说，什么最重要？我未来的方向是什么？我想过上怎么样的生活？我的价值实现在哪？这些问题如果得不到解答，短短一生很容易忙忙碌碌、随着大流就这样过去了，实在可惜。
项飙在《把自己作为方法》中说：

（瓶颈的问题）是回到自己作为一个边缘者、回到我是谁的问题。想清楚究竟我能做什么，我跟世界的关系是什么。我认为世界上所有的人都有这个问题，都得搞清楚自己是谁，否则都会有这种危机，除非完全盲目地被主流裹挟进去。

当我们意识到探索自我的需求之后，我们还需要方法，这就来到了第二阶段——开始寻找自我。但我感觉，很多人对于探索自我的方法却没有什么头绪。
困难之处，在于「自我」是非常复杂的，我们之所以是今天这样，受到了童年经历、社交媒体、朋友亲人、国家文化等等各种因素的影响，这些影响之中大部分更是在日常不知不觉之中就成为了我们的一部分，所以无论是从横向（各种因素的复杂性）和纵向（性格和价值观形成过程的复杂性）看，自我都是极其复杂的。
但好在，这几年通过各种各样的渠道和自证，我积累了一些有用的、可执行的方法，想在这里分享给你。
再多读几本书
阅读有什么用呢？学习知识肯定是好处之一，可是看完可能就忘了；拓展眼界也是的，可是没去亲身经历还是差了一点。
那最大的用处是什么呢？我认为， 是读自己。
在《活下去…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Theia在路上</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[将你的 Python 脚本转换为命令行程序]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15061-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15061-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T01:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[使用 Python 中的 scaffold 和 click 库，你可以将一个简单的实用程序升级为一个成熟的命令行界面工具。




在我的职业生涯中，我写过、用过和看到过很多随意的脚本。一些人需要半自动化完成任务，于是它们诞生了。一段时间后，它们变得越来越大。它们在一生中可能转手很多次。我常常希望这些脚本提供更多的命令行工具式的感觉。但是，从一次性脚本到合适的工具，真正提高质量水平有多难呢？事实证明这在 Python 中并不难。

搭建骨架脚本

在本文中，我将从一小段 Python 代码开始。我将把它应用到 scaffold 模块中，并使用 click 库扩展它以接受命令行参数。

#!/usr/bin/python

from glob import glob
from os.path import join, basename
from shutil import move
from datetime import datetime
from os import link, unlink

LATEST = 'latest.txt'
ARCHIVE = '/Users/mark/archive'
INCOMING = '/Users/mark/incoming'
TPATTERN = '%Y-%m-%d'

def transmogrify_filename(fname):
    bname = basename(fname)
    ts = datetime.now().strftime(TPATTERN)
    return '-'.join([ts, bname])

def set_current_latest(file):
    latest = join(ARCHIVE, LATEST)
    …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[准备好迎接 AIOps 时代]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15060-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15060-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T00:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[随着技术的进步，企业，无论大小，都必须将自己转变为数字公司。转型不再是“选择”的问题；相反，它是关于“如何”推进过渡。这就是 AIOps 的用武之地。


将组织转变为数字公司会遇到很多挑战。缺乏专门的 IT 技能、组织变革管理、不断变化的客户需求和混合环境只是其中的一小部分。企业需要增强其 IT 运营（ITOps）以应对这些挑战并满足客户期望。

数字化转型：AIOps 之路

未来，ITOps 将结合算法和人工智能，使 IT 系统的性能变得透明，并帮助他们提供无缝体验。


“AIOps 对 IT 运营的长期影响将是变革性的。” —— Gartner


AIOps 对于成功的数字化转型至关重要，可以帮助系统以现代业务所需的速度运行。反过来，这将确定公司获得和保持市场领先地位的速度。

现代 AIOps 技术在本地、云端或混合环境中提供 IT 基础架构。它们的自动化使开发人员能够专注于设计下一代业务应用，而不必担心底层基础设施。

什么是 AIOps？

AIOps 结合人工智能和机器学习来分析 IT 运营的数据。这是将人工智能应用于 IT 运营的过程。它可以帮助组织主动检测错误，还可以帮助运营团队在问题影响最终用户之前预防问题。

传统的 IT 管理技术已经无法应对数字化业务转型。当 Gartner 创造 AIOps 一词时，该公司预测 IT 运营过程将发生重大变化，组织管理其 IT 生态系统的方式也会发生巨大变化。

AIOps 平台使用大数据。他们从各种 IT 运营和设备收集数据，以自动识别和实时响应问题，同时仍提供传统的历史分析。然后，AIOps 使用机器学习对组合的 IT 数据执行综合分析。

结果是自动化驱动的洞察力驱使持续改进和修复。AIOps 支持基本 IT 功能的持续集成和部署 （CI/CD）。

AIOps 的范围是什么？

开始使用 AIOps 最初似乎具有挑战性，因此最好采取循序渐进的方法。我们需要从识别和理解 IT 运营数据开始。 AIOps 的核心是数据驱动。因此，它需要访问所有相关的操作数据，包括非结构化数据、日志、指标、实时数据、API 输出和设备数据。还需要结构化的业务数据，例如数据库、社交活动和其他关系数据。 AIOps 平台处理的相关数据越多，他们的预测就越准确。

企业需要了解他们的数据如何帮助他们解决最大的问题，无论他们身处哪个行业。他们应该实施 AIOps 来回顾他们过去的失败，并确定哪些数据将帮助他们找到解决方案。

数据分析可用于查找中断或系统变慢的根源。然后 AIOps 平台可用于检测常见问题及其补救措施。企业可以使用收集到的结果来实施机器学习和 AI，以进行实时监控和自动响应。这整个过程帮助公司推动 AI 成熟，有效地修复错误，避免停机，提高效率。



为什么 2022 年需要 AIOps？

随着企业加快数字化转型，应用程序和系统架构变得非常先进。我们可以通过以下几种方式见证这种复杂性：


组织正在从传统的应用架构转移到云原生、灵活和基于微服务的容器化应用堆栈。

这些应用也部署在本地、混合、公共和私有云平台上。


随着应用和 IT 环境的扩展，它们会产生大量数据。 IT 运营团队因无法管理的数据而筋疲力尽。但是，人工智能可以处理大量数据。随着数据量的扩大，将人工智能纳入 IT 流程的机会要大得多。

异常检测、分类和预测都可以通过使用机器学习和深度学习模型来完成，这些模型擅长分析海量数据并提供分析。AIOps 的许多功能可帮助公司通过交互式仪表盘提供良好的用户体验。

实施 AIOps 的企业报告了诸如无缝体验、更低的运营费用、更快的客户服务、更短的平均解决时间和更少的停机时间等好处。 AIOps 通过基于预测分析做出坚定的决策来支持 IT 运营。

最后一点

AIOps 是 IT 运营分析（ITOA）的下一步。 人工智能、认知技能和 RPA（机器人流程自动化）用于在基础设施或 IT 运营问题成为问题之前自动修复它们。 自我修复系统是 AIOps 的最终目标。


via: https://www.opensourceforu.com/2022/09/get-ready-to-embrace-the-aiops-era/

作者：Amit Shingala 选题：lkxed 译者：geekpi 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s new adventure game takes a top-down trip through ancient Mesoamerica]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/9/22/23367413/google-arts-culture-educational-game-ancient-mesoamerica-descent-of-the-serpent</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/9/22/23367413/google-arts-culture-educational-game-ancient-mesoamerica-descent-of-the-serpent"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T00:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love the cute characters in the game. | Screenshot by Jay Peters / The Verge
    

  
Google’s Arts & Culture division has released a charming new educational game all about ancient Mesoamerica. The game, The Descent of the Serpent, is available to play right now in your browser or via the Google Arts & Culture iOS and Android apps. 
There’s a light plot to Descent of the Serpent, shown in a short video that plays at the beginning of the game. While exploring a museum, a large artifact is stolen by Tezcatlipoca, the Lord of the Smoking Mirror, and a living statue asks for your help to recover 20 icons included on the artifact to prevent floods from taking over the world. You, naturally, agree, and the statue says they’ll send you back in time to ancient Mesoamerica. 
You’ll be able to pick from one of four adorable animal...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Impressions: Shovel Knight Dig is my new roguelite gaming addiction]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883870</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883870"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T00:07:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The modern-retro goodness of Shovel Knight returns with a refreshing take on roguelites.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Machkovech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon is tightening its ebook return policy to thwart BookTok]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/9/22/23367699/amazon-ebook-kindle-return-policy-change-refunds</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/9/22/23367699/amazon-ebook-kindle-return-policy-change-refunds"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T23:47:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s Logo. | Illustration by Alex Castro / The Verge
    

  
Amazon plans to limit automatic ebook returns to cases where people have read no more than 10 percent of the book, according to the Authors Guild. The change, which follows complaints that Kindle buyers were returning titles they’d fully read to get a refund, is expected to take place by the end of the year.
The Authors Guild says it reached the deal after negotiating with Amazon executives. Individual authors raised concerns about an uptick in returns earlier this year, noting that Amazon would bill them for any royalties they earned from the books. Some pinned the practice’s rise on the book community of video platform TikTok, and in a press release, the guild blamed “BookTok influencers” for encouraging people to get “free” books by...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The case of the murdered mummies: “virtual autopsy” reveals fatal injuries]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1880352</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1880352"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T22:47:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One was struck on the head and stabbed; the other had massive cervical spine trauma.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fables.ink — Forget about PDF's while playing RPG]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/fables-ink</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/fables-ink"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T22:19:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USB-A adapter adds instant Wi-Fi 6E support to Windows 11 PCs]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883728</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883728"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T22:14:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[$90 adapter makes Wi-Fi 6E adoption slightly easier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scharon Harding</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After pushing AV1 codec, Google goes after Dolby with HDR and audio standards]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883817</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883817"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T21:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AV1's Alliance for Open Media wants more royalty-free standards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artist receives first known US copyright registration for generative AI art]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883867</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883867"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T21:38:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Registration of AI-assisted comic comes amid fierce online debate about AI art ethics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mailscribe — Keep your inbox clean]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/mailscribe</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/mailscribe"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T21:31:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I hope you'll join us in using Mailscribe to make your email life easier! 😍

---

🔥🔥 Spoiler Alert! 🔥🔥
Mailscribe Inbox is just one of the Mailscribe products. We're getting ready to publish our other products in a few weeks. To follow us, you can subscribe to our newsletter on our website.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackathon finds dozens of Ukrainian refugees trafficked online]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883832</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883832"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T20:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Europol also identified dozens of online users suspected of exploiting refugees.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Belanger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hunga Tonga eruption put over 50B kilograms of water into the stratosphere]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883835</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883835"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T20:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New study shows eruption plume circled the globe multiple times in the stratosphere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla issues recall for 1.1 million EVs due to power window problem]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883836</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883836"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T20:24:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A closing window could pinch someone thanks to problems with the reversal action.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Task Manager for ClickUp — Manage all your ClickUp tasks in one go.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/task-manager-for-clickup</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/task-manager-for-clickup"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T19:56:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Founder-Anonymous — Being a founder is hard. You are not alone.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/founder-anonymous</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/founder-anonymous"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T18:43:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hustlers — Stories of people making money while having a full-time job]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-hustlers</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-hustlers"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T18:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook users sue Meta for bypassing beefy Apple security to spy on millions]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883760</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883760"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T18:28:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A former Google engineer reported the risk, but Meta found no privacy concern.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Belanger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GetReadyWithMusic by Spotify — Get a playlist that matches your style]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/getreadywithmusic-by-spotify</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/getreadywithmusic-by-spotify"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T18:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Party Data EBook & Data Audit — How to use first-party data to grow your audience & sales]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/first-party-data-ebook-data-audit</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/first-party-data-ebook-data-audit"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T18:11:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Florida to Supreme Court: Let us regulate social networks as common carriers]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883762</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883762"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T18:01:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Florida law was blocked by lower courts that found it violates First Amendment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huddu — Accessible logging for everyone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/huddu</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/huddu"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T17:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Moore’s law actually dead this time? Nvidia seems to think so]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883729</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883729"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T17:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chips "going... down in price is a story of the past," CEO says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[nGrow.ai — AI-driven push notifications on top of your analytics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ngrow-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ngrow-ai"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T17:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ungodly Surveillance of Anti-Porn ‘Shameware’ Apps]]></title>
        <id>632a29ecc9bb1af7ef249865</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/covenant-eyes-anti-porn-accountability-monitoring-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Churches are using invasive phone-monitoring tech to discourage “sinful” behavior. Some software is seeing more than congregants realize.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruv Mehrotra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI model from OpenAI automatically recognizes speech and translates it to English]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883524</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883524"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T16:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Whisper" open source model may become a building block in future speech-to-text apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Lawmakers Push Tech Firms on Abortion Benefits for Gig Workers]]></title>
        <id>632c79038990652479ff398c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/lawmakers-pressure-tech-companies-over-abortion-benefits-for-gig-workers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T16:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren and Cori Bush led over two dozen congressional Democrats in urging Amazon, Lyft, Uber, and others to reclassify contractors as employees.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caitlin Harrington</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new Chromecast is official: It’s $30, runs Google TV, and has a remote]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883693</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883693"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T16:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The remote and dongle look identical to the 4K version.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linked Lists in Python – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-linked-lists-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-linked-lists-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T16:08:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Different programming languages offer different ways to store and access data. Some of the data structures you can use are collections such as arrays, lists, maps, sets, and so on.  These all do an awesome job storing and accessing data, but sometimes you might need something different. Another data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fakorede Damilola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alldone.app — All-in-one personal productivity app to level up your life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/alldone-app</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/alldone-app"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T16:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://medium.com/@karstenwysk/...
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Align Text in HTML – Text-align, Center, and Justified Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-align-text-in-html/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-align-text-in-html/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T16:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Text is essential on web pages, as it tells your users what your web page is all about. When you add text to your web page, it dictates the direction and feel of your web page based on your language. For example, by default, English moves from left to right]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mario + Rabbids: Sparks of Hope is a more dynamic take on tactical RPGs]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883664</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883664"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T16:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Preview: Gaming worlds collide in this oddly charming and confident action-RPG sequel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Contributors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Next Silicon Valley Will Be in the US Heartland]]></title>
        <id>62fd21627072d2c1f58788c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-next-silicon-valley-will-be-in-the-us-heartlands/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steve Case, founder of AOL, predicts the dominance of tech companies on the coasts will give way to a flourishing of startups from smaller cities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[某开源堡垒机历史漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11721</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11721"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T15:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[某开源堡垒机历史漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft plans October 12 event to address its very out-of-date Surface lineup]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883662</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883662"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T15:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's not a single Surface model with a current-gen processor in it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Hacking? The Hacker Methodology Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-hacking/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-hacking/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T15:21:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time to learn the basics of the splendid art of hacking 👨‍💻👩‍💻.  In this article, you will learn what the hacking process really looks like. And hopefully one day, you'll get to say those famous words: “I’m in”. Disclaimer: This is for educational purposes only. Please (with a cherry]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Iwugo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The pathway to 90% clean electricity is mostly clear. The last 10%, not so much]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883678</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883678"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T14:46:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six different approaches—with pros and cons—for getting to a 100% carbon-free grid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Inside Climate News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Linux Tool Aims to Guard Against Supply Chain Attacks]]></title>
        <id>632b295b00704d14b5ffb9a0</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/chainguard-wolfi-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T14:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security firm Chainguard has created a simple, open source way for organizations to defend the cloud against some of the most insidious attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intro to Algorithms with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/intro-to-algorithms-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/intro-to-algorithms-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T14:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding algorithms in an important skill for many computer science jobs. Algorithms help us solve problems efficiently. We just published an introduction to algorithms with Python course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. In this course, you'll work with algorithm basics like recursion then go all the way to working with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ironhack Podcast: Tech Careers — All of your tech career questions answered in one podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ironhack-podcast-tech-careers</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ironhack-podcast-tech-careers"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T14:33:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Power Up Anywhere With Our Favorite Portable Chargers]]></title>
        <id>60084ece15db9ef1886a34f6</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-portable-chargers-power-banks/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keep your phone, tablet, laptop, and other electronics running with these handheld power banks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gilbertson, Simon Hill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Made the Right Upgrades in the New AirPods Pro]]></title>
        <id>632b345720bc56769c4131b6</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/apple-airpods-pro-2nd-generation/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a good example of how you make already-great wireless earbuds even better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Parker Hall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There’s New Proof Crispr Can Edit Genes Inside Human Bodies]]></title>
        <id>632a125774ce5b82a68ef2f9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/theres-new-proof-crispr-can-edit-genes-inside-human-bodies/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The technique had largely been limited to editing patients’ cells in the lab. New research shows promise for treating diseases more directly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Mullin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sMiles — Earn Bitcoin for things you already do]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/smiles-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/smiles-2"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T12:56:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New tech can make your house a solar microgrid]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1874815</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1874815"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T12:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New version of support hardware can keep homes solar-powered during outages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US and EU are Teaming Up to Contain Big Tech]]></title>
        <id>6328f8e440fe1e8870aa3b4e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-us-and-eu-are-teaming-up-to-contain-big-tech/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The EU’s chief antitrust enforcer Margrethe Vestager says that US tech companies are changing their behavior as global regulators question their dominance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Conrad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peloton Row and the Future of At-Home Workouts]]></title>
        <id>632b6c05f2203b5586fabfe4</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/gadget-lab-podcast-567/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, we talk about Peloton’s growing product lineup, and whether our days of sweating along to streamed exercise classes at home are over.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which Apple Watch Is Best Right Now?]]></title>
        <id>5f7214734266579a211f5085</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-apple-watch/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that the Series 8 and Ultra sport watch are here, we can help you figure out which version to get (and which to avoid).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrienne So</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘Surveillance Solutionism’ of Putting Cameras in NYC Subways]]></title>
        <id>632b3054d884b4dcc941655d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-surveillance-solutionism-of-putting-cameras-in-nyc-subways/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When “if you see something, say something” becomes “we see everything,” everyone loses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Fox Cahn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawns Are Dumb. But Ripping Them Out May Come With a Catch]]></title>
        <id>6329fa9874ce5b82a68ef2f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/lawns-are-dumb-but-ripping-them-out-may-come-with-a-catch/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meticulous turf is environmentally terrible. Yet grass does have one charm: It “sweats,” helping cool the local area.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greenspace Golf  — Virtual Golf Clubhouse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/greenspace-golf</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/greenspace-golf"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T11:46:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[charlie@greenspacegolf.com
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Video Game Deals This September]]></title>
        <id>62476d5dedc71717de2ded88</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-video-game-deals/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Games for every console, plus DLC and freebies—all in one spot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louryn Strampe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe’s Heat Waves Offer a Grim Vision of the Future]]></title>
        <id>632b748b8990652479ff394a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/europe-heat-wave-limits/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Extreme temperatures are the direct result of climate change, which means more intense heat events, wildfires, and droughts to come.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Reese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Niftify PaaS — Start & run your NFT business in minutes.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/niftify-paas</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/niftify-paas"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T10:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion Icons Generator — Add icons to all your Notion pages based on their title]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/notion-icons-generator</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/notion-icons-generator"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T10:40:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://notaku.so) look much nicer and pretty 🤩

Let me know what you think in the comments! 😃
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trombone Champ — It's like Guitar Hero but for Trombone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/trombone-champ</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/trombone-champ"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T10:13:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Better Birth Is Possible]]></title>
        <id>631f7fcfd884b4dcc94164f3</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ruha-benjamin-pregnancy-black-maternal-mortality/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a young Black woman, I saw my pregnancy treated like a problem. So I ditched the doctors for home delivery and found an alternative model for health care.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ruha Benjamin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #767 史上最贵开发的游戏《星际公民》已筹集五亿美元]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15059-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15059-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T09:19:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[史上最贵开发的游戏《星际公民》已筹集五亿美元

《星际公民Star Citizen》游戏开发了十年，至今仍处于 Alpha 阶段，虽然现在也可以进行游戏了。它筹集的资金突破了五亿美元，是至今为止开发费用 最昂贵的游戏，远超其它开放世界 3A 游戏，如《赛博朋克 2077》等。它于 2012 年在 Kickstarter 上成功众筹，原计划 2014 年交付。但众筹结束后，该游戏以开发并销售游戏内虚拟物品的名义继续募资。2018 年它筹集到 2 亿美元，如今已突破 5 亿美元，


消息来源：RSI



老王点评：这莫非是一种“滚动式开发”的游戏？不过我看了图都觉得不错，有没有玩过的朋友来说说这游戏怎么样，值吗？




图片网站禁止上传 AI 生成的图像

过去几个月，自然语言图像生成模型如 DALL-E 产生了一批令人称奇的艺术图像，部分艺术家随后将这类 AI 图像上传到图像销售网站销售。但由于 AI 图像是在现有图像的基础上生成的，一些图片网站称，出于版权方面的担忧禁止了此类内容。Getty 图片社是最新一个做出类似决定的平台，而 Shutterstock 尚未禁止此类内容，但限制了对 AI 图像的搜索。


消息来源：Solidot



老王点评：我觉得更大的原因是，这类 AI 图片可能会断了这些图片销售网站的根吧。以后大家都用 AI 来生成，谁还买图片。这种阻挡只是螳臂当车，AI 图片肯定会迅速流行开。




微软将 systemd 引入 WSL

通过与 Canonical 深度合作，微软今日宣布了 Windows 中的 Linux 子系统 WSL2 的一项功能更新，它现可在兼容的 Linux 发行版（如 Ubuntu）中运行 systemd 来管理服务。为此，WSL2 做了若干重要修改，更改了 WSL 在启动时的行为方式，因此微软建议谨慎地将之应用于现有的 WSL 发行版。


消息来源：微软



老王点评：一直以来 systemd 没有进入 WSL，可以说既不意外，也有点意外。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[万彩特效大师(限时送会员) – 0基础轻松剪辑合成特效动画视频，不用AE也能制作特效大片]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43417</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/animiz09/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T09:10:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[万彩信息开发过很多款与制作动画相关的软件，如果是我的老粉，应该用过不少他们家的软件，比如万彩动画大师、Focusky动画演示大师、万彩微影，等等。这些软件，都有一个非常明显的特点，就是：简单高效，0基]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>开发者推荐账号</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EPUB Manga Creator – 把漫画图片打包成 EPUB 格式]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43416</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/epub-manga-creator/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T08:35:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EPUB Manga Creator 是一款可以把一堆漫画图片打包成 EPUB 格式的在线工具。虽然是在线版本，但内容在浏览器本地处理，无上传，所以可以速度很快，开源。@Appinn 故事是这样的，青]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[使用 Podman Desktop 在 Fedora Linux 上管理容器]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15058-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15058-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T07:53:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Podman Desktop 是一个开源 GUI 应用，用于在 Linux、macOS 和 Windows 上管理容器。


从历史上看，开发人员一直使用 Docker Desktop 对容器进行图形化管理。这适用于那些安装了 Docker Daemon 和 Docker CLI 的人。然而，对于那些使用无守护进程的 Podman 工具的人来说，虽然有一些 Podman 前端，如 Pods、Podman desktop companion 和 Cockpit，但没有官方应用。现在不是这种情况了。有了 Podman Desktop！

本文将讨论由红帽和其他开源贡献者开发的 Podman Desktop 的特性、安装和使用。

安装

要在 Fedora Linux 上安装 Podman Desktop，请访问 podman-desktop.io，然后单击 “Download for Linux” 按钮。你将看到两个选项：Flatpak 和 zip。在这个例子中，我们使用的是 Flatpak。单击 “Flatpak” 链接后，通过双击文件在 GNOME 软件中打开它（如果你使用的是 GNOME）。你也可以通过终端安装它：

flatpak install podman-desktop-X.X.X.flatpak


在上面的命令中，将 X.X.X 替换为你下载的特定版本。如果你下载了 zip 文件，那么解压缩存档，然后启动 Podman Desktop 应用的二进制文件。你还可以通过进入 GitHub 上项目的 发布 页找到预发布版本。

特性

Podman Desktop 仍处于早期阶段。然而，它支持许多常见的容器操作，如创建容器镜像、运行容器等。此外，你可以在 “首选项Preferences” 的 “扩展Extensions” 部分下找到 Podma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Speech-to-Speech — Use your voice to create realistic AI speech in real-time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/speech-to-speech</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/speech-to-speech"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T07:35:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Only Reminder — Reminder app that only reminds you what you need to do]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/only-reminder</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/only-reminder"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T07:31:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eyelet.io — Drive product adoption with onboarding guides & checklists.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/eyelet-io</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/eyelet-io"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T07:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leo AR for NFTs — See your NFTs come to life with AR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/leo-ar-for-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/leo-ar-for-nfts"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T07:03:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://youtu.be/NYUoZNHGkKU
🎥 https://youtu.be/4EY8lMT9ucw

Install Leo AR Now and let us what you think!
It’s an amazing and fun way to capture the reality you want to live in 🪄
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Git configurations I make on Linux]]></title>
        <id>70204 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/9/git-configuration-linux"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[5 Git configurations I make on Linux
Alan Formy-Duval
Thu, 09/22/2022 - 03:00

            
Setting up Git on Linux is simple, but here are the five things I do to get the perfect configuration:
Create global configuration
Set default name
Set default email address
Set default branch name
Set default editor
I manage my code, shell scripts, and documentation versioning using Git. This means that for each new project I start, the first step is to create a directory for its content and make it into a Git repository:
$ mkdir newproject
cd newproject
git init



            
More on Git
What is Git?
Git cheat sheet
Markdown cheat sheet
New Git articles
There are certain general settings that I always want. Not many, but enough that I don't want to have to repeat the configuration each time. I l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Formy-Duval</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eastway — Effortlessly hire the best startup developers worldwide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/eastway-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/eastway-2"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T06:53:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[日程管理 with Firstseed Calendar]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75709</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75709"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T05:26:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[个人日程管理的需求
在选择日程管理的形式或者app的时候，我的要求很简单：即先确定需求，再按照需求探索日程管理方式。我对日程管理的需求有几点：

任务与日程要在同一个页面；
尽可能随手拿起就能使用；
有较大的自由度，即可以根据个人需求添加备注等；
要能够自上而下地「俯视」整个日程管理过程；
随时可以逃离。

根据这几点需求，我开始了自己的日程管理尝试1。
日程管理尝试
1. 纸质日程本
本科时期，还在用着黑莓9790、z10等一些「非主流」手机，他们没办法与电脑形成一个良好的生态系统，所以没有习惯用他们来做日程管理，而是使用传统的纸质日程本。
当时，已经在用Moleskine的单行笔记本做日记本，对M家的本子很有好感，尤其是口袋本，非常便携。出于一种仪式感的传承，我开始尝试M家的周记本：本子摊开，左边是一周的日程记录，可以记录有确定时间的日程，也可以记录只固定日期的日程；右边是一整面的横线页面，可以写下一些备忘事项，例如可能需要本周或者下周要做的事情等，也可以记录本周的一些打卡事项。

后来尝试了M家特有的400页超厚日程本，一天一页，每一页都是当天从8点到22点的日程记录。本子非常厚，携带有点不方便；记录是方便许多，能写的位置也多了很多，但因为不是每天都有排满的日程，一些琐事写进去也没意思，最终本子留了许多空，总感觉有点浪费，尤其是年终总结的时候觉得似乎是虚度了时光一样。

后来也尝试过MUJI的月记本，但是总感觉没有周记本好用，我便回归Moleskine的周记本，直到我后来舍弃它。
2. 手机自带日程管理工具
舍弃纸质日程本的原因有两个：

设备和系统升级了，从「非主流」机升级到了带有安卓系统的Blackberry Keyone，自带的日历强大了很多；
当时正在读研究生，我们的课比谁都多，每天都被课程排满，而这些课程都写进纸质笔记本里不太可能，只把课程外的待办事项写进本…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hkoch24</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNOME “文件”引入最受欢迎的功能：“新建文件”菜单]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15057-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15057-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T04:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[这是 GNOME “文件”中的“新建文件”功能，它为你提供了一种创建文档和文件的新方法。让我们看一看。


无需在后端进行更多调整。通过“文件Files”（又名 Nautilus）中的上下文菜单创建新文档/新文件的最令人期待的功能终于到来了。

作为 谷歌编程之夏 2022 的一部分，（由 Ignacy Kuchciński 开发的）这个新功能最近经过审查并合并到 “文件” 的主分支中。

它看起来如何

当你右键单击文件时，上下文菜单有一个新选项“新建文件New File”。



GNOME “文件”中的“新建文件New File”选项启动一个操作窗口，如下图所示。



当它启动上述对话框时，会在后台发生一些事情。

你可能知道你可以在主目录中创建一个带有模板的 Template 文件夹，以便轻松访问常用的文档类型。因此，GNOME “文件” 会检查你是否有该目录。

如果当前存在一个带有模板的 Template 目录，你能通过那些文档类型的列表以创建新文档。



如果你没有任何模板（很可能），GNOME “文件”会扫描你的系统并根据系统中已安装的应用程序显示常见文件类型的列表。

例如，文本编辑器、LibreOffice 文档类型（电子表格、演示文稿）等。

这里还发生了一些其他事情。当你为新文档选择文件类型时，系统会选择默认的文件扩展名。这是文件名文本框中的受保护标签。

此外，如果你没有安装任何模板或任何应用程序，则根本不会显示“新建文件”菜单选项。

未来路线图

开发人员还提出了未来对该功能的增强，更大程度地扩展其功能。

当没有可用的模板时，对话框将如下所示。它将允许你通过选择应用程序来创建文件，包括空白文件。

此外，你可以直接启动软件来安装一些可以帮助你创建相应文件类型的应用程序。

由于这个功能比较复杂，可能会在以后开发。目前还没有时间表。

这在“文件” v43 中可用（通过 GNOME 43）吗？

但是，在我看来，这种变化需要一些额外的设计审查。我觉得它不完整。例如，当你有模板时，你无法创建标准文档类型（文本、LibreOffice 文档）—— 这两个对话框是互斥的。另外，我发现了一些小 BUG。

尽管该功能目前 已获得批准和合并，但由于日程冲突，它无法进入 GNOME 43候选版本。

希望在经过一轮良好的审查和测试后，你可以在明年的 GNOME 44 版本中获得此功能。

总结

总的来说，这是一个优雅的功能，我认为如今没有任何其他文件管理器具有这种先进的设计。一旦这个“文件”的“新建文件”功能被完全实现，它将会是其出色功能集的一个很好的补充。

那么，你喜欢这个新设计吗？请在评论框中告诉我。


via: https://www.debugpoint.com/gnome-files-new-file-document/

作者：Arindam 选题：lkxed 译者：littlebirdnest 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[这个基于 Flutter 的非官方软件中心可能会取代 Ubuntu 的官方应用]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15056-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15056-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T03:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canonical 是否计划用这个基于 Flutter 的应用程序取代 Ubuntu 软件中心？也许是，也许不是。




Ubuntu 通常被认为 是最适合初学者的发行版之一，但默认的软件中心（GNOME 软件中心Software Center）需要更多的打磨才能使其成为令人愉悦的体验。

为什么？嗯，它很慢而且占用资源很多，所以大多数用户不会费心使用它，或者使用感受很糟糕。

是的，多年来它可能有所改善，但仍远非良好的体验。

它看起来像是来自 Canonical 的贡献者，而其他人已经联手为 Ubuntu 软件中心开发一个轻量级、基于 Flutter 的替代方案！

等等，它 不是官方替代品。但是，我想知道它是否打算很快取代 Ubuntu 软件中心？🤔

🆕 使用 Flutter 制作的 “Ubuntu 软件”



这个使用 Flutter 实现的 “Ubuntu 软件Ubuntu Software”旨在实现轻量级、自适应和快速，提供比传统软件更好的用户体验。

但首要因素必须是可用性，对吧？因为最后，你只是为了安装软件。而且，你想快速完成，没有任何麻烦。

当我在我的系统上尝试它时，我注意到“我的应用程序”下有一个单独的 “Snaps” 和 “Deb 包”部分：



这应该便于处理单个应用程序中的不同包。毕竟，这是我一直想要的！

轻松安装/管理应用程序的统一体验，是不是要求太多了？ 🤷

但是应用信息和安装页面呢？好吧，它已经过重新设计，带有微妙的动画以增强体验。



自适应布局简直就是锦上添花。这有点类似于 elementary OS 7 为我们准备的：


elementary OS 7 准备添加响应式应用程序，并移植到 GTK 4


所以，它看起来像是对未来的一个深思熟虑的实现，对吧？



它会取代 Ubuntu 软件吗？

虽然项目贡献者将其标记为 Ubuntu 软件中心的非官方替代品，但我认为它更像是一个尝试作为替代品的实验。

考虑到负责 Ubuntu 上 Flutter 的高级工程师 @Canonical JP Nurmi 参与其中，这将是一件值得期待的事情。

我们现在唯一能做的就是“预测”。随着事情的发展，这似乎有更多的机会成为官方的。

想尝试这个基于 Flutter 的商店吗？

你可以前往它的 GitHub 页面 并按照构建说明让它运行。请注意，截至目前，它正在大力开发中。


下载 Ubuntu 软件


对于正在积极开发的东西来说，它的效果相当好。

💬 我希望当前的软件中心被取代。你怎么看？在下面的评论中让我知道你的想法！


via: https://news.itsfoss.com/unofficial-flutter-ubuntu-software/

作者：Sagar Sharma 选题：lkxed 译者：littlebirdnest 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Words On Words — A new dimension to the classic crossword game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/words-on-words</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/words-on-words"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T02:49:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unita — Discover, compare and review the best communities and groups]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/unita</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/unita"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T02:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andor first impressions: Star Wars inches toward the best of modern adult TV]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883626</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883626"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T23:26:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The darkest Star Wars series yet takes too long to establish positive momentum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Machkovech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use CSS Combinators to Select and Style Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-combinators-to-select-elements/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-combinators-to-select-elements/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T23:17:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Combinators allow you to combine multiple selectors to target specific elements in the DOM. In this article, I'll explain how four of these combinators with examples. In my previous post on CSS Selector Types [/news/how-to-select-elements-to-style-in-css/], I shared seven types of selectors for targetting elements that you want to style. If]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fearing copyright issues, Getty Images bans AI-generated artwork]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883513</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883513"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T22:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getty sidesteps potential legal problems from unresolved rights and ethics issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logitech builds Android-powered Steam Deck clone for portable cloud gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883453</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1883453"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T20:26:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is your local Wi-Fi infrastructure ready for a portable cloud gaming device?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating to Web3: A Cheat Sheet — Learn what Web3 is and how your business can migrate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/migrating-to-web3-a-cheat-sheet</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/migrating-to-web3-a-cheat-sheet"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T19:54:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Filebase, just released a nice ebook about how to migrate your infrastructure to web 3. If you want to be less dependent on centralized systems like AWS, it deserves checking out.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spriteley Voxcells — Build and evolve blocky life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/spriteley-voxcells</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/spriteley-voxcells"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T19:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://discord.gg/spriteley
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Remove Last Commit – How to Undo a Commit in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-remove-last-commit-how-to-undo-a-commit-in-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-remove-last-commit-how-to-undo-a-commit-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T17:42:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a powerful tool and the most popular version control system. It is how developers and technical teams collaborate and work together on projects. But what happens when you accidentally commit a file and realize that you shouldn't have done that because that file contains an error? There is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Super CMMS — Makes asset, work orders, & inventory management super easy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/super-cmms</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/super-cmms"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T17:41:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://supercmms.com/
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MakerBox Workbook — Marketing workbook with 100 actionable tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/makerbox-workbook</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/makerbox-workbook"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T17:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generic PNP Monitor – How to Fix Windows 10 PC Device Driver]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/generic-pnp-monitor-how-to-fix-windows-10-pc-device-driver/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/generic-pnp-monitor-how-to-fix-windows-10-pc-device-driver/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T16:18:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you acquired a new monitor only to find out it's not displaying anything from your computer? Or maybe the monitor suddenly stops working? On many occasions, this problem is caused by a faulty generic PNP monitor driver. Apart from driver issues, the monitor might not be working due to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Software Testing? A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/software-testing-beginners-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/software-testing-beginners-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T16:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software testing is essential to development. It saves you time and money in production mode.  But software testing is a complex topic and can be a bit difficult to understand. In this article, I'll explain the major topics in software testing and how this practice can help you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Iroegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[California Voted for Cheaper Uber Rides. It May Have Hurt Drivers]]></title>
        <id>6328b71020bc56769c413195</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/california-voted-for-cheaper-uber-rides-it-may-have-hurt-drivers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uber and Lyft spent millions promoting a controversial ballot measure. A new study suggests it has lowered driver wages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aarian Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-33980命令执行漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11723</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11723"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T15:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-33980命令执行漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[从前端代码审计挖掘未授权进入后台到文件上传拿下某色情网站]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11729</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11729"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T15:52:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[从前端代码审计挖掘未授权进入后台到文件上传拿下某色情网站]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dll劫持注入从原理到白加黑漏洞利用]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11711</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11711"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T15:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dll劫持注入从原理到白加黑漏洞利用]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp is Building a NEAR Curriculum]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/near-curriculum/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/near-curriculum/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T15:10:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past 9 months, several of our instructors have been hard at work on a comprehensive NEAR curriculum. This will focus on NEAR's blockchain protocol and the NEAR tool ecosystem. This curriculum is made possible by NEAR Foundation, who gave our charity a grant to 100% fund development of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Mondloch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp is Building a Solana Curriculum]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/solana-curriculum/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/solana-curriculum/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T15:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past 9 months, we've made considerable progress on our Solana curriculum. This will focus on Solana's blockchain protocol and the Solana tool ecosystem. This curriculum is made possible by The Solana Foundation, who gave our charity a grant to 100% fund development of this curriculum. What will this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Mondloch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Walnut Beyond Demos — Grow your revenue with unprecedented intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/walnut-beyond-demos</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/walnut-beyond-demos"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T13:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Car Phone Mounts and Chargers]]></title>
        <id>62ff5278f06d7dee6f53bb5f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-car-phone-mounts-chargers-and-accessories/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These mobile accessories will make your smartphone a better—and safer—road trip companion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simon Hill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MeltingSpot — Customizable community platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/meltingspot</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/meltingspot"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T12:35:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://meltingspot.io

Thibaud

PS: if you believe in communities, prove me right, share your feedback and let the PH community work its magic 💪
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remotelane 5.0 — Remote jobs for everyone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/remotelane-5-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/remotelane-5-0"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T12:15:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remoelane.com from scratch with a new tech stack and it's my seventh startup which is part of the 24 Startups in 24 Months Challenge. The versions of Remotelane.com before were developed together with @sonnypgs. The other seventh startup from @sonnypgs is EpicAhead.

Remotelane.com is known as a remote job aggregator which shows up to 15 new remote jobs per hour from all around the web which will stay 30 days on the page. The search works simple with executing the search after stop typing for 1s without the need to press a button. 

The job post cell includes now a description which you can expand/collapse per click, also you can filter by categories and tags. The "Post a Remote Job" Feature is as simple as possible, just provide the job title, company name, job description, the link to apply or email to apply, choose a category and add up to five optional tags. Also the newsletter is just a simple list like the website itself.

A more detailed blogpost can be found here https://24startups24months.com/posts/7-startup-remotelane-com

If you should have questions or feedback, let us know in the comments below :) All feedback is welcome.

Cheers!
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Dangerous Meme in US Politics Is Over a Century Old]]></title>
        <id>6328bee136c33c0247a2f0ab</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/america-first-meme-politics/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many associate the ‘America First’ movement with Trump, but its origins—and rebirth—are more complicated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED Ideas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #766 Rust 将进入 Linux 6.1]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15055-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15055-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T11:08:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rust 将进入 Linux 6.1

在 Linux 内核维护者峰会上，Linus Torvalds 表示除非有意外发生，Rust 将进入 Linux 6.1，但“只是核心基础设施（即还没有正经用例）”。目前正在开发的版本是 Linux 6.0，6.1 是下一个版本。西部数据的工程师们在 Linux Plumbers 大会上展示了使用 Rust 语言开发的 NVMe 驱动，它已经实现了与 C 语言版本相当的性能。内核开发者同意 Rust on Linux 已经准备就绪。


消息来源：ZDNet



老王点评：在前两天 Linus 的采访中，他还没有肯定地确认 Rust 将进入 Linux 6.1，现在看起来经过几天的会议，内核开发者们已经达成了共识。




LibreOffice 上架 Mac 应用商店，售价 9 欧元

文档基金会宣布在 Mac 应用商店发布 LibreOffice，以支持那些希望从苹果的专有销售渠道获得所有桌面软件的最终用户。Mac 应用商店上的版本是由 Collabora 发布的，并由其提供三年的支持服务，下载它需要付出 8.99 欧元的“便利费”，以支持该项目的开发。但 macOS 用户仍然可以从文档基金会下载免费版本，免费版本和 Mac 应用商店的版本都是采用相同源代码构建的，功能没有区别，甚至商店版本由于苹果的政策限制而需要另行下载依赖项 Java。


消息来源：文档基金会



老王点评：基金会专注于免费的社区版本，而将收费的空间留给生态伙伴，这是一种好的做法。




研究发现 YouTube 的反馈按钮几乎没有用

Mozilla 研究人员通过利用来自 2 万多名 YouTube 用户的视频推荐数据发现，“不感兴趣”、“不喜欢”、“停止推荐频道”和“从观看历史中删除”等按钮在防止类似内容被推荐方面基本上不起作用。报告发现，即使在最好的情况下，点击过这些按钮后，仍有一半以上相似的内容推荐。YouTube 称，这些行为是故意的，因为该平台并不试图阻止跟某个主题有关的所有内容，并批评该报告的“类似”的定义没有考虑到 YouTube 的推荐系统是如何工作的。


消息来源：福布斯



老王点评：合着这些按钮就是安抚用户情绪啊？我想，其它的视频或微博上的类似按钮是不是也如此呢？]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Time for Cities to Ditch Delivery Trucks—for Cargo Bikes]]></title>
        <id>632a4d3440fe1e8870aa3b57</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cargo-bikes-greener-quicker/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study shows that cycling packages the final few miles to their recipients isn’t just greener than using a van, but often quicker too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>William Ralston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Joy and Dread of AI Image Generators Without Limits]]></title>
        <id>6328ed95977791160bfcd2ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-joy-and-dread-of-ai-image-generators-without-limits/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artists are free to create fantasies or nightmares with unrestricted image generator Stable Diffusion, but some fear a flood of AI-made horrors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Joy and Dread of AI Image Generators Without Limits]]></title>
        <id>6328ed95977791160bfcd2ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-joy-and-dread-of-ai-image-generators-without-limits/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artists are free to create fantasies or nightmares with unrestricted image generator Stable Diffusion, but some fear a flood of AI-made horrors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Apple Watch Series 8 Wants to Be Your Lifeline]]></title>
        <id>63294359f1e5c40d2b1bc6ec</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/apple-watch-series-8-and-apple-watch-se/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Crash Detection and longer battery life in Low Power mode, the wearables seem to be designed for an increasingly terrifying world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrienne So</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Time for Cities to Ditch Delivery Trucks—for Cargo Bikes]]></title>
        <id>632a4d3440fe1e8870aa3b57</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cargo-bikes-greener-quicker/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study shows that cycling packages the final few miles to their recipients isn’t just greener than using a van, but often quicker too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>William Ralston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shadowy Russian Cell Phone Companies Are Cropping Up in Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>632a4347c4d3ebc9237bc61c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ukraine-war-mobile-networks-russia/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But as Ukrainians retake ground, some of the firms are erasing their online presence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FreeDOS 的 16 种颜色的由来]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15054-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15054-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T09:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[为什么文本只能使用这些有限的颜色显示，为什么 FreeDOS 使用这些颜色和阴影，而不是其他颜色？答案就像技术中的许多事情一样，历史原因。




如果你仔细了解过 FreeDOS，你可能已经注意到文本使用有限的颜色范围 —— 16 种文本颜色和 8 种背景颜色。这类似于 Linux 显示文本颜色的方式 —— 你或许能够在 Linux 终端中更改 文本颜色，但你仍然只能使用 16 种文本颜色和 8 种背景颜色。



DOS 文本有 16 种颜色和 8 种背景颜色（吉姆·霍尔，CC-BY SA 4.0）

为什么文本只能使用这些有限的颜色显示，为什么 FreeDOS 使用这些颜色和阴影，而不是其他颜色？

答案就像技术中的许多事情一样，历史原因。

PC 色彩的由来

为了解释为什么文本只有 16 种颜色，让我给你讲一个关于第一台 IBM 个人计算机的故事。这个故事的部分内容可能有些杜撰，但基本内容已经足够接近。

IBM 于 1981 年发布了个人计算机Personal Computer 5150（“IBM PC”）。该 PC 使用了一个简单的监视器屏幕，以绿色显示文本。由于此显示器仅适用于一种颜色，因此被称为 单色monochrome（“IBM 5151 单色显示器”，搭载 IBM 单色显示适配器Monochrome Display Adapter，即 MDA）。

同年，IBM 发布了 PC 的更新版本，带来了惊人的技术成就 —— 颜色！新的 IBM 5153 彩色显示器依赖于新的 IBM 彩色图形适配器Color Graphics Adapter（CGA）。正是由于这个原始的 CGA，所有的 DOS 文本都继承了它们的颜色。

但在我们讨论那一部分之前，我们首先需要了解一些关于颜色的东西。当我们谈论计算机屏幕上的颜色时，我们谈论的是混合 三原…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tab Wrangler – 倒计时，自动关闭不常用的标签页[Chrome/Firefox]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43409</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/tab-wrangler/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T09:02:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tab Wrangler 是一款专为不愿关闭浏览器标签页用户准备，帮你自动、定时关闭不常用的标签页，以让你的浏览器看起来正常一些，当然还可以节约内存、节省 CPU 资源。另外被关闭的标签页可以轻松找回]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Python interpreters to try in 2022]]></title>
        <id>70202 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/9/python-interpreters-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[6 Python interpreters to try in 2022
Stephan Avenwedde
Wed, 09/21/2022 - 03:00

            
Python, one of the most popular programming languages, requires an interpreter to execute the instructions defined by the Python code. In contrast to other languages, which compile directly into machine code, it’s up to the interpreter to read Python code and translate its instructions for the CPU performing the related actions. There are several interpreters out there, and in this article, I’ll take a look at a few of them.
Primer to interpreters
When talking about the Python interpreter, it’s usually the /usr/bin/python binary being referred to. That lets you execute a .py file.
Lexing - The human-made source code is converted into a sequence of logical entities, the so called lexical tokens.
Par…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephan Avenwedde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My favorite open source alternatives to Notion]]></title>
        <id>70201 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/9/open-source-alternatives-notion"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My favorite open source alternatives to Notion
Amar Gandhi
Wed, 09/21/2022 - 03:00

            
If you have notes to yourself scattered throughout your hard drive, you might need a notes application to collect and organize your personal reminders. A notes system can help you track ideas, important tasks, and works in progress. A popular application that isn't open source is Notion, but here are two options that respect your privacy and data.
Standard Notes
Standard Notes is an open source (AGPL 3.0 license) notes application featuring a password manager, a to-do list, and, of course, a great system for writing and storing notes.
One of the most important things about taking notes is finding them again, so organization is critical. Standard Notes uses an intuitive and natural tagging syste…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amar Gandhi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bg Eraser — Clean up and remove unwanted objects, background from images]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/bg-eraser</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/bg-eraser"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T05:48:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Image Enlarger was released three years ago, we have received quite a lot of emails, and users love using our AI tool to process their images. Now we have released a quite new tool of Bg Eraser that you can use for improving the productivity of the designing and creative works. 

🤓 What is Bg Eraser and How Does it Work?
We have integrated an AI Inpainting model that could recognize and remove the objects, guess and regenerate the content backward. If you want to remove unwanted objects, people, text, and even watermarks from an image, you can try this tool, as that is what Bg Eraser can do.

Bg Eraser also enables you to remove the background from an image and make it background transparent. After that, you can use the editing tool to change the background color or images. Quite easy to start.

All in all, Bg Eraser provides two great features for your creative and designing works. Increase your productivity and clean up your pictures easily.

1.	Magic Eraser: Remove unwanted objects and retouch images with reliable quality.
2.	Background Eraser: Remove background from images in seconds.

🔥 Why you should use BgEraser
Bg Eraser applies the latest and cut-edging technology that make your job easier.

Here are some features 
1. Remove objects from an image with the AI Inpainting technology
2. Remove background and create PNG images
3. 100 free to use and no account required
4. Unlimited access to the Magic Eraser tool
5. Reliable, fast and amazing.

🚀 Roadmap
- More accurate when inpainting
- Make the process faster

Just drop me an email at support@bgeraser.com or leave your comments if you have any ideas. I would like to hear from you!
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System Design: WhatsApp]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/system-design-whatsapp-fld</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/system-design-whatsapp-fld"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T05:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#distributedsystems #architecture #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karan Pratap Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[和设计师聊聊，exping 专属地图是如何设计？]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75841</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75841"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T04:36:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[上一篇《exping：一个地图创作工具是怎么诞生的？》 和大家分享了 exping 的诞生故事后。感谢大家的支持与建议，也感谢少数派的推荐，让更多的人认识了 exping ，其中也有投资人、媒体关注到了我们。这是意料之外的收获。时隔3个月，我们有了许多的变化与提升。在这段时间里，也有更多的机会去接触用户，进行深入的交流，从中也更清晰我们的产品定位，以及我们的使命。
「地图」就像一张画布，是另类的创作载体
从地图诞生以来，大家对地图的认识，更多是作为「导航指引」用途。其中涉及了不少的学科，如「地图学」、「地理学」、「测绘学」、「遥感技术」等等。根据地图的应用场景，结合这些学科专业，绘制不同的专用地图。
因此，地图创作对大家来说似乎需要有一定的专业要求。而 exping 的诞生始于让每个人可以轻松、容易地呈现自己的品味地图。地图就像一幅画的画布，一个另类的创作载体。（欢迎看看小编写的文章《emoji + 地图 = exping》）在此之上以标记「点」，绘制「路线」，表达基于地理位置上的故事。「地图」作为重要的画布，重点在于可塑性，如何帮助创作者对地点进行多样性的表达。那或许一般的地图不足以满足这些需求，借此，这次我们和设计师聊聊，exping 专属地图的一些设计心路历程。
 

作为 exping 的设计师，你怎么理解 exping？
当大家还在以图文的方式分享一个好地方的时候，exping 开始将地图作为主视角。 Explorer 可以方便快捷地添加去过、计划要去的地方以及设计路线，简单或隆重地补充对该地点的评价，上传相关照片。
通过这种更直接的方式，将你的数据传递给你的观众，大幅度减少了“这是哪里？”，“我也想去”，“环境怎么样？”等问答游戏。
在这之前，exping 的地图风格是怎样的？
在 exping v0.1~0.3 的地图风格从 Light （简约）到 Stree…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CLU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie 2.0 — AI content creation for everyone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/charlie-2-0-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/charlie-2-0-2"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T04:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iOS Ref – iOS 开发者一站式系统、硬件数据指南]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43404</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/ios-ref/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T03:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iOS Ref 是一个为 iOS 开发者提供一站式的硬件数据参考网站，比如历代 iPhone、iPad 屏幕分辨率、支持的最低系统、Swift 版本、内存与 CPU 等信息。@Appinn 事情是这样]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fungus That Killed Frogs—and Led to a Surge in Malaria]]></title>
        <id>6318fe21c4d3ebc9237bc511</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-fungus-that-killed-frogs-and-led-to-a-surge-in-malaria/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A global fungal pandemic wiped out amphibians, destroyed biodiversity, and ultimately increased human illness. Now a second similar pathogen is on the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maryn McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[对writeObject流程动点手脚]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11720</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11720"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T15:59:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[对writeObject流程动点手脚]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[关于"linux capability"的两个特殊案例]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11716</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11716"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T15:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[关于"linux capability"的两个特殊案例]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GenieACS CVE-2021-46704认证前RCE漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11722</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11722"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T15:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GenieACS CVE-2021-46704认证前RCE漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CubyText：一个正在开发中的快速的跨平台开源知识管理应用]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15053-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15053-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T15:42:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CubyText 是一个迷人的个人项目，你可以分叉或尝试作为一个知识管理应用。




有很多开源应用可以帮助你记下并组织你的想法、研究或知识。

如果你不记得它们，请允许我分享其中的几个：


Logseq

Obisidian


当然，你还可以探索一些最适合这项工作的笔记应用：


这里是我们为你找到的最好的 Linux 笔记应用


但是，我看到了 Vincent Chan 的个人项目，它提供了类似于 Notion 的外观，专注于成为一种快速且私密的选择。


💡 请注意，开发者并不打算将其作为任何商业项目的替代品。它是一个实验性的应用程序，以满足他的要求。不要指望它能取代你最喜欢的任何应用程序。


CubyText：实验性知识管理应用



CubyText 是一款自由开源的跨平台知识管理应用，还处于早期开发阶段。

📢 该项目的第一个版本于 9 月 12 日上线。所以，它是真的新啊。

你可以在 Linux、macOS 和 Windows 上试用它。 .deb 文件可用于 Linux。

该项目的有趣之处在于其类似于 Notion 的用户界面与块编辑器的概念。开发者为这个工具建立了一个 块编辑器，以便能够组织内容。



因此，你在此处添加的任何内容都是按块组织的。它支持带有 Markdown 标记的富文本，因此你可以轻松地增强你的笔记。

此外，你可以添加选项卡以快速创建更多笔记以及一目了然地了解信息。你还可以在上面的截图中注意到待办事项列表。

看起来很有趣，对吧？

如果你好奇，请前往它的 GitHub 页面 并为你的平台下载适当的包进行测试。


CubyText


💬 你如何看待 CubyText 这个个人项目？你想要这样的东西来代替你的笔记知识管理应用吗？


via: https://news.itsfoss.com/cubytext-experimental-project/

作者：Ankush Das 选题：lkxed 译者：geekpi 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U 盘启动盘创建工具 Rufus 在 Linux 上不能使用？这里有 6 个替代品]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15052-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15052-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T15:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rufus 一个用来创建启动盘的开源工具。它可以按照你的需求进行调整，用起来很简单。不仅用起来很方便，而且制作启动盘的速度也出奇的快。

遗憾的是，Rufus 不能在 Linux 上使用，它只能在 Windows 上使用。因此大多数在 Windows 上使用过 Rufus 的人，都会在 Linux 上寻找替代软件。

如果你也是这样，不用着急，我们有一些优秀的替代软件，可以满足不同的使用条件。

我们来看看一些关于 Rufus 的替代软件：

6 款最佳的 Linux 启动盘创建工具

列出的所有替代软件都是开源的，并且在 Linux 发行版运行很好。

注意： 下列软件无任何特定排序

1、balenaEtcher



balenaEtcher（或 Etcher）对于多平台（Windows、 MacOS）用户是一个很好的选择，也包括 Linux 用户。

此软件没有任何高级选项。因此十分容易使用。只需要选择 ISO（镜像文件），然后选中目标 U 盘进行写入即可。

它是完全开源的，并在写入完成后检验你的 U 盘。此外，它还自动选择你插入的 U 盘，以避免你不小心选择了硬盘进行格式化。

你可以参考这本 便捷手册 来在 Linux 上安装它。


balenaEtcher


2、Fedora Media Writer



Fedora Media Writer 是专门用来帮助用户创建 Fedora Linux 启动盘的软件。如果你还没有 ISO 文件，它还能为你下载 ISO。

当其它的 U 盘启动盘创建软件导致你不能格式化你的 U 盘时，它也是一个优秀的 U 盘启动盘修复程序。

不用担心，你也可以选择 Fedora Linux 之外的其他镜像来创建启动盘。

你可以在 Flathub 找到任何 Linux 发行版可用的最新的 Flatpak 软件包。如果你是新手请参考这篇 Flatpak 指导


Fedora Media Writer


3、Startup Disk Creator



如果你使用的是 Ubuntu 系统，在系统上已经预装了一个 U 盘启动盘制作软件，即 Startup Disk Creator。

你可以用它选择任何需要的 ISO 文件（最好是 Ubuntu 的任何版本），并选择 USB 设备进行下一步。

当你确认操作后，它就会写入数据来完成制作启动盘。

4、SUSE Studio Imagewriter



SUSE Studio Imagewriter 是一个简单的启动盘制作软件。

我没有在 Ubuntu 软件中心找到它，但是在 Manjaro 的社区仓库和 AUR 中可以找到。如果它可以适配你的 Linux 发行版，你可以试试它。


SUSE Studio Imagewriter


5、UNetbootin



UNetbootin 是一个支持 Linux、Windows 和 macOS 的 U 盘启动制作软件。有少量的几个可以调整的选项，比如你可以查看所有可用的驱动器，还可以选择一个发行版来自动下载 ISO 文件。

它与上面的软件不同，它并不是指定用在某些 Linux 发行版。因此，它支持各种各种各样的发行版和系统程序。


UNetbootin


6、Ventoy



Ventoy 是一个有趣的 USB 启动盘解决方案，你只需要复制粘贴镜像文件到 U 盘即可。

你仅仅需要在 U 盘上安装 Venoy，它会在其上建立两个分区。其中一个用来存储 ISO 镜像，你只需要将镜像文件粘贴到 U 盘即制作成功。

有趣的是你还可以使用它来 引导多个系统。

它可在 Windows 和 Linux 上使用。


Ventoy


总结

如果你需要在 U 盘上放多个 Linux 发行版而不是反复格式化它，Ventoy 似乎是上面所有选项中最好的选择。

为了简单起见，特定于发行版的工具是个很好的选择，例如：Ubuntu 的 Startup Disk Creator 和 Fedora 的 Fedora Media Writer。

SUSE Studio Imagewriter 也不错，但可不能不是最方便的。

如果你没有任何特定的偏好，balenaEtcher 应该是最直接的选择，UNetbootin 是它的一个合适的替代软件。

你最偏爱哪个 U 盘启动盘创建软件？在下面的评论区中让我了解你的想法。


via: https://itsfoss.com/live-usb-creator-linux/

作者：Ankush Das 选题：lkxed 译者：alfred-hong 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Has a Serious Doxing Problem]]></title>
        <id>6329c23beecde8c117e7f4ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/telegrams-doxing-problem/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T13:39:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The encrypted messaging app is a haven for politically motivated vitriol, but users are increasingly bringing threats to targets’ doorsteps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Guest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Has a Serious Doxing Problem]]></title>
        <id>6329c23beecde8c117e7f4ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/telegrams-doxing-problem/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T13:39:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The encrypted messaging app is a haven for politically motivated vitriol, but users are increasingly bringing threats to targets’ doorsteps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Guest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How My Daughter and I Learned to Speak the Same Language]]></title>
        <id>62f55d453787a50a7ae8c947</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/duolingo-language-learning-family-relationships/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Duolingo's gamification made Spanish lessons fun—and helped bridge the gap with my tween.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaclyn Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[25 Great Wireless Chargers to Refuel Your Phone (or Watch)]]></title>
        <id>5fd1ea6cefa5f68151a599d7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-wireless-chargers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stop fumbling for cables in the dark. These WIRED-tested stands and pads will take the hassle out of recharging your iPhone or Android phone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian Chokkattu, Simon Hill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best iPhone 13 Cases and Accessories]]></title>
        <id>6148d470eb28d4df0601baac</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-iphone-13-cases-and-accessories/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We tested MagSafe compatibility on everything from cases to wireless chargers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian Chokkattu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Games, Mysteries, and the Lure of QAnon]]></title>
        <id>63288cb640fe1e8870aa3b0e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/qanon-games-alternate-reality-conspiracy-theories/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What do puzzles, video games, and conspiracy theories have in common?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Hon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happens to Everything With Queen Elizabeth II’s Image?]]></title>
        <id>6328ff5574ce5b82a68ef2e9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/updating-british-royal-iconography/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From stamps and cash to passports and postboxes, the minting of the United Kingdom’s new royal iconography will take years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Baraniuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Unsend and Edit Messages in iOS 16]]></title>
        <id>6324a27562435d269fdbdb7c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-unsend-and-edit-messages-ios-16/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With one long press, you can finally unsend that ill-considered rant—as long as both you and your contact have iOS 16.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brenda Stolyar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peloton’s New Rowing Machine Is Here. Get Ready to Pay Up]]></title>
        <id>6328b5f2d884b4dcc941652e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/peloton-row/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peloton Row is the company’s latest high-priced piece of workout equipment—and a holdover from a previous Peloton era.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Goode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Is Measuring Extreme Heat Wrong]]></title>
        <id>63235caf20bc56769c4130f0</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-us-is-measuring-extreme-heat-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent studies have revealed flaws in the heat index. With rising temperatures and humidity, maybe it’s time for a more holistic approach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Barber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RoEx Automix — AI powered music production and distribution tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/roex-automix</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/roex-automix"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T08:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/playlist...)
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YouTube’s ‘Dislike’ Button Doesn’t Do What You Think]]></title>
        <id>6328fc0820bc56769c41319c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/youtube-dislike-button-mozilla-research/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users try to control the video platform’s algorithm by giving content a thumbs-down, but Mozilla researchers say it’s not so simple.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 ways to use the Linux inxi command]]></title>
        <id>70196 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/9/linux-inxi-command"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[3 ways to use the Linux inxi command
Don Watkins
Tue, 09/20/2022 - 03:00

            
I was looking for information about the health of my laptop battery when I stumbled upon inxi. It's a command line system information tool that provides a wealth of information about your Linux computer, whether it's a laptop, desktop, or server.
The inxi command is licensed with the GPLv3, and many Linux distributions include it. According to its Git repository: "inxi strives to support the widest range of operating systems and hardware, from the most simple consumer desktops, to the most advanced professional hardware and servers."
Documentation is robust, and the project maintains a complete man page online. Once installed, you can access the man page on your system with the man inxi command.

More Li…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Don Watkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security buzzwords to avoid and what to say instead]]></title>
        <id>70186 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/9/security-buzzword-alternatives"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security buzzwords to avoid and what to say instead
Seth Kenlon
Tue, 09/20/2022 - 03:00

            
Technology is a little famous for coming up with "buzzwords." Other industries do it, too, of course. "Story-driven" and "rules light" tabletop games are a big thing right now, "deconstructed" burgers and burritos are a big deal in fine dining. The problem with buzzwords in tech, though, is that they potentially actually affect your life. When somebody calls an application "secure," to influence you to use their product, there's an implicit promise being made. "Secure" must mean that something's secure. It's safe for you to use and trust. The problem is, the word "secure" can actually refer to any number of things, and the tech industry often uses it as such a general term that it becomes …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Kenlon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[《超市里的原始人》札记]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75833</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75833"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T06:03:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[阅读初衷
平时一无聊下来，偶尔会通过消费购物，来提起自己的生活兴致，买东西从挑选，到想象自身使用场景，再到下单盼望着快递，最后拆封这个过程，能在很长一段日子里给自己提供着生活的兴致。而有些时候，反省下觉得单纯是无聊想买买买，而不是使用需求强烈促使我去购物。自觉这种动机是不健康的，同时也很好奇为什么有这种心理，于是便在网络推荐下接触到了这本书——《超市里的原始人》，想借此机会，弄清楚什么是消费主义，对我这种自以为不健康的消费行为如何解剖。
从看到书名中的「原始人」开始，我就期待着书中内容将追根到底消费的欲望最原始的动机是什么。首先需要引用一下在生物学中对人作为社会性灵长类动物特点的描述：

人类在进化过程中形成了许多小范围的社会集体，身在其中，你的形象和地位就是至关重要的，这已经不仅仅是为了满足生存的需求，还是为了吸引伴侣、娱乐朋友和抚育后代。

消费这件事情之所以扯到这么遥远和深层的角度呢，是因为作者主张需要从进化心理学的角度才能透彻地了解消费主义的根源，消费者虽然会半自觉地设法炫耀出财富、地位和品味，但真正想要展现的是更深层次的心理特质（比如善良、智慧和创意）和生理特质（比如生育能力、强壮、美貌）。
《超市里的原始人》中的三个关键论点：

人试图展示自身特质的本能与消费主义关系紧密。
我们用于识别关键人类特质和情感的社交感知系统经过漫长的进化历程变得准确高效，能将所有能收集到的不同暗示聚集起来，察觉出一个人的身体、脸部、语言和行为。
消费主义在很大程度上就是一种画蛇添足的行为。我们得到了有惊人适应力的人类自我展示的能力，即语言、智慧、善良、创造力和美丽，然后却忘记了如何用它们来结交朋友、吸引配偶和获取声望。相反，我们却依赖通过教育、工作、消费获得的商品 和服务来向他人展示自己的个人特质。这些高成本信号大都是多余的或是误导性的， 所以别人通常都会对其视而不见。

消费主义中…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>一克</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KikoPlay – 播放本地视频，显示网络弹幕（ A 站、B 站、动画疯、Dandan、爱奇艺、腾讯视频、Tucao）[Windows]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43393</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/kikoplay/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T05:12:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KikoPlay 是一款全功能的弹幕播放器，开源。主要功能就是在播放本地视频的同时，显示网络弹幕，支持从 A 站、B 站、动画疯、Dandan、爱奇艺、腾讯视频、Tucao 获取弹幕。另外还能获取动画]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Marketplace — Single click add-ons for your web3 tooling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/quicknode-marketplace</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/quicknode-marketplace"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T04:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://www.quicknode.com/marketplace or if you have a QuickNode account already, just click "Developer" on the left nav bar.

We're looking for early feedback as we just launched this yesterday at Messari's Mainnet conference. Looking forward to hearing from you!
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[当 AI 能代替我们写作，我们还有什么？]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75803</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75803"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T03:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[你用过人工智能写作工具吗？前两个月，我看到了一些AI写作工具推出了文章续写功能。

只要你写上一篇文章的开头和结尾，智能系统就能自动生成一篇完整的文章。虽然现在技术还不成熟，积累的样本数据还不够完善，写出的内容还是会被挑剔，但是我总感觉排布好内容逻辑是迟早的事情。
在那个时候，AI就能代替我们写作吗？
作为内容创作者，我们还有活路吗？现在能帮人进行AI写作的工具有很多，从媒体报道、工作汇报这些角度看，人工智能会逐步替代人工写作。它只追求客观报道和逻辑推导，但无法完成偏主观价值判断的内容生产，因为AI不能代替的是我们对内容的「审美」。
人工智能与审美
前段时间AI绘画掀起了一阵火热，只要输入一些文字和句子，表达画的风格和内容，AI就能自动生产出一副艺术作品。有的画真的能与大神媲美，吊打国内外大部分艺术工作者。但是，这里的问题是，这个作品从「点子」到「作品」之间，完全忽略了过程。
怎么判断一个作品已经做到最好了？还能不能更好？这一笔触能不能再调一调？那一个色块能不能再深一些？如果单独抠几个细节，那是调整，如果从头开始就抠细节，那就是「创作」。
AI写作能根据你前面写的一个词、一段话，自动生成出后面的句子和篇章，但是它对于一个真正想表达的人来说，生产出的段落总会让人差强人意，甚至因为一个字的误用就导致表达结果与表达目的南辕北辙。
说到底，AI写作只能成为我们的工具，是基于创作者的审美的工具。倘若作者的审美和沉淀不够，反而会出现被工具主导，甚至被代替的困境。如同普通人去使用AI绘画一样，对绘画细节失控，除了标题能自己把控，后面的笔触、构图、用色等细节都和自己无关。如果我们本身就懂绘画，那么还可以去微调，但当我们什么都不懂的时候，剩下的只有无尽的赞叹。通过AI生产出了一个远超自己能力范畴的作品，或者说，它远远超出了我们对作品的审美极限。所以，无法对它进行细节的判定。
就如同我们在写作…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>猴猴说话</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[双链笔记是伪概念？聊聊双链的核心优势——知识管理]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75822</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75822"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T03:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[与其说双链是笔记软件，不如说他们是知识管理软件或思维工具。而这个认知上的错位便是导致目前双链饱受争议的原因之一。

双链是个伪概念？
双链笔记软件目前的争议不少，大家对其的批判也非常实际，可谓是针针见血：

双链的底层逻辑尚未普及，用户无所适从。链接有什么用？哪些应该链接？
notion、语雀、印象笔记都能一定程度上双向链接各种文章。虽然稍微简化了一些，但好像也能用啊。
界面太“硬核”了，不优雅，不美观，基本没有办法给别人看。
没有办法共享和协作。
导出十分麻烦，有时候还要靠插件。
各种命令、快捷键、插件，学习成本高。
代码程度较高，没有代码基础的人被劝退。
知识图谱功能基本只是用来装逼，东西一多基本没法看。

可以发现，当我们以“笔记软件”的角度来看待双链，它和目前各种成熟的笔记软件相比差太多了。看着甚至像尚未完成就拿出来给人用的Alpha版本软件，非常粗糙，体验极差。
但是，如果我们换一个视角，以“知识管理软件”和“思维工具”的角度来看待双链，结果可能会完全不同。而我认为这才是双链的核心优势。
双链的核心优势——知识管理和思维辅助工具
1、信息颗粒度更细，便于细化和延展
个人认为，信息粒度是双链笔记最核心的优势。比起印象笔记以"篇"为单位、notion以“块”为单位，双链笔记是以“点”为单位。这就以为着，我们可以将大块的知识细化为一个个相对独立的知识点。同时，在细化的过程中，我们逐渐把各个知识点从原有的语境中解放（抽象）出来，进而形成能够在长时间的考验下保留下来的知识。这样，当日后遇到新的情景的时候，我们也能迅速知识结构，以支持新的目标。

具体而言，以roam research为例，在使用过程中，你任何时候都可以用 [[]] 来关联另一个概念或者页面，或用 (()) 来关联一个句子或一个块。
2、记录成本低
大部分双链笔记都是基于大纲笔记的，即整体的框架类似于bull…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>人形睿</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Using .env Files Now!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gregorygaines/stop-using-env-files-now-kp0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gregorygaines/stop-using-env-files-now-kp0"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T21:04:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #node #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Gaines</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Favorite Xero Barefoot Shoes Are on Sale Right Now]]></title>
        <id>6328840740fe1e8870aa3b0d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/xero-z-trail-barefoot-shoes-sale-september-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Snag a pair of zero-drop, minimalist shoes and rediscover the ground beneath your feet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gilbertson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[写在 Xperia 5 IV 到手前，我的 Xperia 5 III 体验]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75828</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75828"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T16:31:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[在正式开始说体验前，先谈谈索尼在 9 月初正式发布的全新真·小屏旗舰——Xperia 5 IV，在设计上融合了 Xperia 1 系列的特点，总算是更换了硬朗的边框以及磨砂质感的后盖玻璃，可以说完全契合个人的审美爱好，更不用说破天荒加入了无线充电，我对 Xperia 5 III 最不满意的两点都解决了，还有什么理由不买呢？加上最近在各种视频网站看到关于 Xperia 1 IV、5 III 等机器的吐槽，于是就想在 5 IV 到手前，和大家分享一下我的使用体验。
为何购买 Xperia 5 III
说起来在今年入手 5 III 之前，我在用的是三星 Galaxy S22 Ultra，S22U 真的什么都好，拍照、系统啥的我都挺满意，而且外观更是延续了曾经最爱的 Xperia XZ Premium 的神韵，当时一发售就冲了。只是在实际使用时，总会觉得这机器实在是太大了，单手用太累，可我又不像当年用黑莓 Passport 那样充满喜爱，对其体积无下限容忍，于是乎就又考虑换台趁手的小屏旗舰机器。
然后说起现在的小屏机器，基本上没得选，iPhone 就只有 SE 和 12、13 mini，Android 这边能看上眼的就是魅族 18、Galaxy S22 和 Xperia 5 III。综合来看，12、13 mini 因为刘海直接 pass，SE 电量实在担忧，魅族 18 不防水也 pass，只能让 5 III PK S22。作为一个曾经的 Xperia 5 用户，对于 5 III 可以说是完全不担心，唯一的问题就是臭名昭著的火龙 888，但 S22 用的是 8 Gen1，这对卧龙凤雏就随便吧，毕竟我都能接受 S22U 的 8 Gen1 了。最后特意跑去三星官方店实际上手体验 S22 的感觉，由于 S22 70.6mm 的宽度握持时有点撑手不舒服，于是乎 68mm 宽度的 Xperia…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[goby指纹提取与yara逆向.md]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11701</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11701"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T15:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[goby指纹提取与yara逆向.md]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[记一次较为详细的某CMS代码审计]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11714</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11714"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T15:53:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[记一次较为详细的某CMS代码审计]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Affilisting — 10K+ affiliate programs across 500+ niches for $99]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/affilisting</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/affilisting"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T14:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://affilisting.com/#affiliate

You can get 20% off until 15 October 2022 with the code PH20OFF or by clicking on this link: 
https://gsouillard.gumroad.com/l...


If you have any questions, feel free to contact me on Twitter: https://twitter.com/affilisting
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Budget Phone Plans to Ditch the Big Carriers]]></title>
        <id>5f3ea5d786a7c014331d160f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/guide-to-mvno-phone-plans/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t overpay for Verizon, T-Mobile, or AT&T. It might make sense for you to go with one of these smaller providers instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Jancer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feel the Magic Touch With Our Favorite Touchscreen Laptops]]></title>
        <id>62ea930fbb7ad736f1d6a9c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-touchscreen-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These 2-in-1 and clamshell computers upgrade the norm with touch displays, 360-degree hinges, and detachable keyboards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Speight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In 2022, This Samsung Is the One TV to Rule Them All]]></title>
        <id>631a171036c33c0247a2f012</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/samsung-qn900b/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You won’t need all the pixels, but Samsung’s 8K flagship TV will be the prettiest screen in your neighborhood.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Parker Hall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To Understand Brain Disorders, Consider the Astrocyte]]></title>
        <id>631f6903c4d3ebc9237bc5b6</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/to-understand-brain-disorders-consider-the-astrocyte/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neurons get a lot of attention—but researchers think this star-shaped brain cell type could hold the key to treating some disorders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maggie Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pott'd — Air-dry pottery kit for fun date nights or time w/ friends]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/pott-d</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/pott-d"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T11:42:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Electric Vehicles Could Rescue the US Power Grid]]></title>
        <id>631fb2ab62435d269fdbdaf0</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/electric-vehicles-could-rescue-the-us-power-grid/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By 2035, the batteries in California’s zero-emission cars could power every home in the state for three days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aarian Marshall, Matt Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could Slack Finally Fix the 'Away' Status?]]></title>
        <id>6324a974977791160bfcd28e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/slack-status-updates-green-dot/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The workplace messaging platform is working on new ways of telling our coworkers that we’re really, really not available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Goode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acer Nitro 5 Is Our Top Pick for Laptop Gamers on a Budget]]></title>
        <id>631f0c0af2203b5586fabf0b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/acer-nitro-5-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finding a portable PC with enough gaming power at a reasonable price can be tough. This low-cost machine fits the bill.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Speight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Electric Vehicles Could Rescue the US Power Grid]]></title>
        <id>631fb2ab62435d269fdbdaf0</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/electric-vehicles-could-rescue-the-us-power-grid/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By 2035, the batteries in California’s zero-emission cars could power every home in the state for three days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aarian Marshall, Matt Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Deep Roots of Nigeria’s Cybersecurity Problem]]></title>
        <id>63238b91d884b4dcc941650e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/nigeria-cybersecurity-issues/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite having one of the strongest data-protection policies in Africa, the country’s enforcement and disclosure practices remain dangerously broken.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olatunji Olaigbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ArchiveWeb.page – 将浏览过的网页完整「录」下来，做网页的 “PDF” 格式。]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43382</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/archiveweb-page/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T08:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ArchiveWeb.page 是一款可以将浏览过的网页完整的录下来的 Chrome 扩展，可保存下高保真度的网页存档，包括外部资源，使用起来就像联网使用一样。@Appinn 青小蛙专门对比测试了一下]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making a fast website is SUPER EASY 😏]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/enterspeed/making-a-fast-website-is-super-easy-9lb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/enterspeed/making-a-fast-website-is-super-easy-9lb"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T07:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #performance #programming #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kasper Andreassen, Enterspeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I got my first pull request merged!]]></title>
        <id>70197 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/9/first-pull-request-merged"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I got my first pull request merged!
Oluwaseun
Mon, 09/19/2022 - 03:00

            

Words cannot express my joy when I got the notification about the merge below, and I owe it to my current engineering school, AltSchool Africa.
  


      
   
Image by: 
(Awosise Oluwaseun, CC BY-SA 4.0)
Before this, I had been introduced to open source many times, told about its importance in the tech space, and even attended open source conferences (e.g., OSCAFest). I had all the instant excitement to start, but imposter syndrome set in on opening GitHub to create something.
Fast forward to Monday, the 8th of August, 2022, when I watched Bolaji's video on contributing to open source. I felt pumped again, but I wanted to apply what I learned, so I noted some steps.
The steps:
I made up my mind I was goin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwaseun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyLint: The good, the bad, and the ugly]]></title>
        <id>70185 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/9/pylint-good-bad-ugly"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PyLint: The good, the bad, and the ugly
Moshe Zadka
Mon, 09/19/2022 - 03:00

            
Hot take: PyLint is actually good!
"PyLint can save your life" is an exaggeration, but not as much as you might think! PyLint can keep you from really really hard to find and complicated bugs. At worst, it can save you the time of a test run. At best, it can help you avoid complicated production mistakes.
The good
I'm embarrassed to say how common this can be. Naming tests is perpetually weird: Nothing cares about the name, and there's often not a natural name to be found. For instance, look at this code:
def test_add_small():
# Math, am I right?
assert 1 + 1 == 3
def test_add_large():
assert 5 + 6 == 11
def test_add_small():
assert 1 + 10 == 11

The test works:
collected 2 items                      …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moshe Zadka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[我是如何用工具组合养成运动习惯的]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75799</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75799"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T06:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐 
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

我是一个拥有七年工龄的年过三十的打工人，base 在北京。
工作的前五年，我任职于一家外企。凭借着年轻和朝九晚六，工作的大多数时候我都能轻松应付，并没有把运动当回事儿。工作五年后我跳槽到了互联网行业，工作强度和工作时长陡增，对体力和精力都有了新的考验，因此运动也不得不提上了日程。
但是运动这件事只有想法是没办法做成的，我花了一年多的时间断断续续走了很多弯路。三天打鱼两天晒网经常发生，一下子荒废半个月的情况也并不少见。而最终让我养成运动习惯的是我狠下心氪金，配齐了各种运动辅助工具，并在各种工具的综合作用下，让运动成为了我生活习惯。
此文写作时间为 2022 年 9 月 19 日，我刚刚收到了 Apple Watch 发送给我的「最坚持奖 - 22 天」的奖章。一个习惯的养成需要 21 天，这个奖章也让我动了念头，想把这个过程分享出来，于是就有了这篇文章。
2022 年 9 月 19 日 收到最坚持奖 22 天
我的典型一天：工作日运动
时间选择
工作日大家都疲于奔命，很难抽出大块时间来专门运动。所以选择适合自己的运动时间很重要。
我首先尝试的是下班后跟着 Keep App 来做一些运动。但是遇到了两个阻碍：一个是下班时间不固定，有时候到家已经九点多了，不方便再做剧烈运动，会直接影响睡眠质量；另一个是有时候晚饭吃了比较多的主食，所以整个人头昏脑胀的，大多数时候只想躺着刷剧，并没有意志力再爬起来。
然后我尝试了在中午的时间运动。我会早十五分钟锁定电脑屏幕赶去健身房，并点好一个定时派送的外卖（运动完后食堂已经关门）。这样实行了快半年时间…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Journey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stacks — Solving the lost bookmarks problem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/stacks-0c41d0d4-1c47-4f9f-a7d8-15a87df03db0</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/stacks-0c41d0d4-1c47-4f9f-a7d8-15a87df03db0"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T05:14:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surge 发布开源网络延迟测速工具：SGNetworkTest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43376</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/sgnetworktest/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T04:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SGNetworkTest 是一款由 Surge 发布的开源网络延迟测速工具，主要用来「评估 Surge 是否按预期正常工作，也可使用该工具与协议的官方客户端进行对比，确认 Surge 对代理协议的实]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[房屋适老化改造，为了那场终将到来的落幕]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75786</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75786"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T02:44:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[起初，我从未感受到我妈对于衰老的恐惧。直到大概五六年前我家重新装修房子的时候，我妈坚持要在他们卧室的厕所里装一个马桶，后来问了原因才知道，她大概是觉得以后自己老了，万一腿脚不方便了，用马桶会轻松很多。从那一刻起，我才猛然发觉这种隐秘的恐惧。
第七次全国人口普查的的数据显示，目前中国60岁及以上的人口数量已超2.6亿，这个人数占总人数的18.7%。这就意味着，有相当一部分老人正在经历着这种关于衰老的隐秘恐惧，还会有越来越多的人陷入这种关于衰老的恐惧。
为了回应这些恐惧，很多人可能最先想到的是“适老化改造”。当然，适老化改造是一个相当大的问题域，本文目前所要探讨的仅仅是房屋的适老化改造，特别是对现有的城镇房屋进行一些“修补性”的适老化改造。
为什么要进行房屋适老化改造？
我们需要先回答一个问题：为什么我们要率先对“房屋”这样一个区域进行适老化改造呢？这个问题的答案有很多。
首先是出于目前国内养老格局的考虑。国内养老事业呈现出一种所谓的“9073”的格局。也就是说，90%左右的老年人居家养老，大约7%的老年人需要依托社区进行养老，最后3%左右的老年人将入住养老院。这意味着大多数老人会在自己的家中度过大部分的晚年时光。这几乎是最适合老人，同时也是最经济的养老方式。
其次是出于老人活动范围的考虑。随着年龄的增长，老人的社会活动范围会逐渐缩小，老人对于居住空间的依赖程度也会越来越高。这意味着，居住环境成为老人晚年生活最重要的空间载体，居住条件的好坏将会直接影响老人的生活质量。[1]
再次是出于老年人人体工学的考虑。据老年人人体工学的研究，在衰老过程中人体的尺寸也会发生变化。医学研究资料显示：人在28-30岁时身高最高，35-40岁之后逐渐出现衰减，70岁时身高会比年轻时减少2.5%-3%。[2]这就意味着，随着居住者年龄的增长，房屋也应该发生一些改变。
所以，出于上述的种种原因，除了大…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>商隐商隐商商隐</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[小爱触屏音箱实现 Stream Deck 贫替]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75789</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75789"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T13:42:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[前几天看到时间线上 latter21 有晒 Elgato 的 Stream Deck，感觉很炫酷自定义程度也很高就想买一个。我一查价格居然要一千多一个，太贵了买不起。然后我又看到「爱运动的数码君」有将小爱触屏音箱安装 Macro Deck 的视频，这就是我想要的：一百多能实现 Stream Deck「贫替」。我折腾完用了几天感觉还不错，今天就写个教程和使用体验给大家分享下。
准备工作

小爱触屏音箱。
Windows 电脑
Micro USB 数据线
下载需要的文件（包含了驱动、刷机包、搞机工具箱、和安卓端的 App）

安装改版固件
小爱触屏音箱的官方系统是不能安装第三方 app 的，而是需要刷入改版固件才行。安装改版固件不影响小爱同学的正常功能， 也不影响保修。
安装驱动
安装驱动
将文章开头的工具包下载解压，打开 FlashTool - Driver 文件夹里的 Mediatek-Drivers-Install.bat（需要管理员权限），跟随提示完成驱动安装。
进行刷机
设置刷机
打开 FlashTool 文件夹里的 _SPFT.exe 刷机工具，如果弹出报错提示，直接确认忽略即可。

下载 DA 框选择：FlashTool 下 Hikaru_resign-Xiaomi 文件夹里的 DA_Mi_Hikaru-resign.bin
配置文件选择 Image 文件夹里的 MT8167_Android_scatter.txt
验证文件选择 FlashTool 下 Hikaru_resign-Xiaomi 文件夹里的 auth_sv5.auth

然后我们将下方的选框从下载改到固件升级。
刷机过程
点击下载按钮后，通过数据线连接小爱触屏音箱就会开始刷机。刷机的过程可能需要几分钟到十几分钟，在此期间小爱同学触屏音箱会始终处于黑屏状态，只要能在设备管理器中找到其 com 端口即连…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>酱紫表</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best MagSafe Accessories for Your New iPhone]]></title>
        <id>6184e74b41d2d21ecfcb0cff</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-magsafe-accessories/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Load up your iPhone 14, iPhone 13, or iPhone 12 with a magnetic bike mount, tripod, wallet, or power bank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian Chokkattu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Sex Toys for Every Body]]></title>
        <id>5ec58eed5bea2fa8333c4edd</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-sex-toys-and-tech/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are our favorite gender-inclusive vibrators, wand massagers, and sleeves to give you and your partner(s) a helping hand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaina Grey, Louryn Strampe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Epigenetic ‘Clocks’ Predict Animals’ True Biological Age]]></title>
        <id>631f681e036b54662b510484</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/epigenetic-clocks-predict-animals-true-biological-age/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A statistical analysis of chemical tags on DNA may help unify disparate theories of aging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ingrid Wickelgren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use DuckDuckGo’s Privacy-First Email Service]]></title>
        <id>6309107c567860ab6c66c64f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-use-duckduckgo-privacy-first-email/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tired of advertisers spying on your private communications? This beta promises to kick tracking technology to the curb.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Nield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Queen’s Funeral Sets Off the Biggest UK Police Operation Ever]]></title>
        <id>63250dc8f2203b5586fabfbb</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/queen-elizabeth-ii-funeral-details-security/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Snipers on buildings. Drone no-fly zones. Temporary CCTV. The security plan is even more complex than it was for the London 2012 Olympics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heartstring — Connect with people nearby & worldwide in short chats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/heartstring</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/heartstring"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T09:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Figma Alternatives For A Blazingly Fast Increase In Your Productivity.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wiseai/9-figma-alternatives-for-a-blazingly-fast-increase-in-your-productivity-3g40</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wiseai/9-figma-alternatives-for-a-blazingly-fast-increase-in-your-productivity-3g40"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T07:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#design #uiweekly #productivity #ux]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahmoud Harmouch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Best UI Component Libraries/Frameworks in 2022 for Frontend Developers🔥]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aviyel/top-9-best-ui-component-librariesframeworks-in-2022-for-frontend-developers-b48</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aviyel/top-9-best-ui-component-librariesframeworks-in-2022-for-frontend-developers-b48"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T07:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #css #tailwindcss #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pramit Marattha, Aviyel Inc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[图形方格纸 MyGraphPaper – 免费、可自定义的纸张模板、方格笔记本、打印纸]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43369</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/mygraphpaper/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T06:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[图形方格纸 MyGraphPaper 是一款自定义纸张模板的网页，主要用来制作各种大小的田字格/拼音、作业本、信纸、分镜表等模板，并用来打印。免费，高自定义（纸张大小、方向、边框、留白、标题、横线等等]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[如何免费用微信小程序中文 AI 绘画？]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75783</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75783"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T03:44:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[前些日子，我给你介绍了本地使用 Stable Diffusion 人工智能绘画工具的方法（如何在你的 M1/M2 Mac 本地运行 Stable Diffusion？）。不少小伙伴们反馈说玩儿得很开心。

不过也有不开心的，因为手头儿没有 M1/M2 的 Mac 电脑。

是不是因为设备限制，就只能眼巴巴看着别人体验新科技成果呢？
当然不是。人工智能技术的普及化，已经是科技发展的潮流趋势了。我今天给你介绍一个不需要安装任何应用的体验方式。而且，更好的消息是，你都不用把自己的想法翻译成英文了，直接输入中文就行。
这是个微信小程序，叫做「盗梦师」。开发者是西湖大学蓝振忠老师团队。
我这里给你做个演示。
今早我看到有人分享了一段视频，是喷气式背包的实验场景。很有意思。

于是我就在朋友圈发了一番感慨：

有了这玩意儿，上班堵车不是事儿了。

感慨之后，觉得光用文字表达不够形象，刚好就可以用「盗梦师」画出来。
于是我打开小程序，输入了这样一段话：

一个背着喷气式背包的中年人在交通拥堵的马路上轻松自在飞行

这里注意你可以选择绘画的类型。我选择的是「赛博朋克」，我觉得和主题很搭。

然后是选择画家风格。我对赛博朋克艺术家不了解，于是设置成为「不限定」。

下面还有一个选项，是画面的长宽比例。我觉得对于展示的画作来说， 16:9 感觉上比较好。
好了，做了这些设定后，就可以直接画了。

这里需要等上几秒钟即可，比本地 M1 Mac 运行起 Stable Diffusion 来快多了。画做好了，你感觉怎么样呢？

有了这样的形象画面，朋友圈里的评论一下子就丰富了起来，例如：

假发套得粘的紧一点

以及：

当姑娘们画好了妆，做好了头发，美美的在街上走着，然后突然被人用喷气背包的风吹乱的时候，你猜她们会不会捡石头把它打下来

我觉得，这些担心，都不无道理，值得背包开发商们认真记录和讨论。
如果你感兴趣的话，直接打开微信，搜索这个小程序试试看吧。上文图中也包含了二维码可以直达。目前阶段，每天有 5 次免费创作机会。然后每分享给一位好友，双方可以获得 20 次创作额度。
当然，我也尝试了一些其他的图画，例如中国风的「雪中山寺古钟」。

雪、山都齐全了，只是寺庙在哪里？找了半天没看到，哈哈。如果你玩儿过 Stable Diffusion ，应该知道很多时候你需要多画几张，从中选择更合适的图画。所以我准备等明天有了新的额度，再用同样的文本，多画几张对比看看。
欢迎把你的尝试结果和经验心得分享到留言区，咱们一起交流讨论。
祝人工智能绘画愉快！
如果你觉得本文有用，请充电。
如果本文可能对你的朋友有帮助，请转发给他们。
欢迎关注我的专栏「科研利器」，以便及时收到后续的更新内容。
  
 
延伸阅读

【知识星球精选】刻意练习区的辅助线
“没有灵魂” 的 AI 文本生成，有啥用？
可视化卡片笔记写作？我试了最近才开放的 Heptabase
大块的写作时间？这个时代，它是奢侈品
互联网上的时光机器]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>玉树芝兰</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[听播客也要收集精彩片段，哪个播客应用更适合？]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75736</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75736"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T02:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[播客的形式和内容日益丰富，其中不乏一些可以与文章、视频媲美的信息价值和密度。我们会通过剪藏、截图来收集文字和图像，然而对于声音为媒介的播客，是否你也产生了“要是能把这段单独截出来就好了”的想法？
作为半个播客爱好者，我目前一直在使用 Spotify，无论是设备进度同步，还是UI交互，播客的基础功能都算基本满足，唯一遗憾是当听到精彩的片段时，没有裁剪和收藏片段的功能。
因此开始在市面上寻找这样的应用，我的需求算比较清晰，首先必须要有片段截取功能；其次需要能创建公开链接，无论用于分享朋友还是收集； 最后软件的播客功能需要能过得去，如果能跨平台也是加分项；
在市面上找了一轮，大体能满足要求的找到了三款，下面就通过比较 Snipd、Airr 和 QlipCast 三个播客应用，给有类似需求的读者做参考。
💡 喜马拉雅也包含片段截取的“卡擦”功能，但由于广告泛滥和部分内容限制，我个人不纳入考虑，不介意的朋友可以尝试喜马拉雅，从功能齐全、多端同步、网络稳定上都是较优选择，注意敏感内容即可。
   
具体比较
1、整体设计风格
Snipd 整体风格和 Spotify 相近，大线条的图标以及深蓝渐变和绿色的色彩；
Airr 界面简洁干净，主要以黑白交错为主，首层只有两个模块：第一个主要是看自己和他人分享的一些片段，第二块包含关注或订阅的播客、听过的节目和创建过的片段。
QilpCast 作为最近更新已经是两年前的软件，UI 虽无法媲美前两者，也还算得差强人意。
左：Snipd；中：Airr；右：QlipCast
2、片段创建和分享功能
这部分的功能可以说是我的需求核心，功能对比也聚焦在主要的操作流上，即：裁剪与创建片段→ 管理与编辑片段 → 分享/导出
💡 截取的片段名称在各软件叫法各异，Snip（Snipd），Quote（Airr）和 Qlip（QlipCast），为阅读理解便利，以…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kinh_l</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop writing API functions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/saeedmosavat/stop-writing-api-functions-3693</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/saeedmosavat/stop-writing-api-functions-3693"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T23:22:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #codequality #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saeed Mosavat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Obsidian 综述 - 新 UI 新征程（v0.16 发布之际）]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75781</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75781"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T16:48:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[打算开一个新的系列「Obsidian 综述」，不同于「玩转 Obsidian」系列，「综述」更关注 Obsidian 的功能和插件的使用，而「玩转」系列更成体系，它们的区别：

综述系列重点在「介绍」，针对 Obsidian 近期的新功能、新插件、新主题进行体验。并在使用过一段时间之后，进行简单的介绍和归纳。
玩转系列重点在「方法论」，是在吃透了「综述」内容之后，结合自己的体验进行总结和提炼。

v0.16 重磅更新
最近 Obsidian 重磅发布了 v0.16 ，当然目前还属于「内部预览」版，只有付费支持的用户才能体验，不过大家也不用着急，通常「公开版」也不会等太久。
最大的升级是「重新设计了 Obsidian 的界面」带来了「标签组」等重磅功能，官方内部对这次新 UI 称为 Dragonglass（龙晶），从体验上看完全颠覆了从前我对 Obsidian 界面和易用性上的感知，贴几张个人使用的图大家感受一下：

这次 UI 升级是重头戏，本篇不会事无巨细的介绍所有升级点，我会挑选几条个人最满意的地方跟大家展开介绍，如果您想了解本次所有升级功能可以参考官方文档：

中文介绍
英文介绍

工作区支持「标签组」
本次升级引入了「标签组」概念，「标签组」简单理解，就像我们在「浏览器」上使用「标签组」一样，在 Obsidian 中通过多个「标签组」每个组多个「标签页」，可以较大限度的实现「平铺散列」的阅读方式，如图：
 

「标签组」的优势在于一方面我们可以通过快速切换「标签组」内的不同「标签页」，提高「信息摄入速度」；另一方面「标签组」也极大拓展了我们打开「笔记」的数量。这两点优势在「整理知识」和「创意输出」的时候非常有用。
在升级前我们只能采用「下图」中的方式打开多篇「笔记」，这种方式最大的问题是「最多同时可以看到 2篇笔记全貌」，如果想要看到更多需要将笔记拖拽到「中间区域」…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>闲者时间_王掌柜</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[试探索iOS微信文件存储机制]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75769</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75769"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T15:03:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[小众消息的冯大辉前两天推送了一篇很有意思的文章，大概是探讨一个B站视频对微信存储机制可能存在的误解。文中提出了一个实验方法，看到做了试验可能会有奖品，我眼睛一下放光，不如就趁此机会做几个试验，好好探讨一下微信在iOS上的文件存储机制，包括：

转发文件是否会占用额外的存储空间？
从同一人处多次接收同一份文件是否会占用额外的空间？
从不同人处多次接收同一份文件是否会占用额外的空间？
微信和WeChat在以上这些问题上是否存在差异？
同一台手机上的不同微信账号接收的同一文件是否占用额外存储空间？

试验的环境是iOS 14.8.1、iPhone 11、微信8.0.28。首先我们删除手机上的微信重新安装。登录一个WeChat小号（小号A）。此时微信占用的空间是少的可怜的752.2MB，其中数据占244.5MB。我提前准备好了一个Ubuntu的iso镜像（880MB）。将它发送给这个小号。下载后重启手机，可以看到，微信占用的空间变成了1.77GB，其中数据占1.26GB。多出来大约1GB的空间，可能是除了文件以外的缓存、其他需要的程序和资源文件。
接收文件前后的微信
接下来我们正式开始实验。我们讲接收到的文件转发给三个不同的小号。重启手机，可以看到，如冯大辉所料，微信所占用的存储空间并没有增加。依然是1.77GB（数据1.26GB)。微信显然做了最基本的文件存储去重。
所占空间没有变化
接下来，我从另一个微信号将刚刚发送的文件再次转发给小号三遍。当我点进新发送的文件时，看到需要接受文件，我有一种不详的预感。难道微信真会重新接收一遍文件？所幸，当我点击接收文件后，文件在一瞬间就接收完成了。显然，微信也伴有服务器端的去重，在服务器上的同一份文件，在本地并不会接收多次。重启手机也可以看到，微信占用的空间并无增加。
看似要重新接收，实际所占空间没有明显变化
按照这个逻辑，即使是不同的人转发给我的同一份文件，应该也不会需要重复下载，或是占用额外的空间。我试着用另外两个小号（小号B、小号C）将同一份文件转发给小号A。虽然也显示需要接收文件，但同刚才一样，一瞬间就完成了接收。再次重启手机，微信所占用的空间依旧没有变化。
不过，刚才验证的情况中，虽然是多个账号转发给一个小号，但是微信很容易在服务器端追溯到，这些文件的源头是同一个。那假如各个账号是各自上传的同一份文件，微信在服务器端是否也有去重能力呢？为此，我在另一台小米手机上登录小号B与小号C，各自发送同一份文件给小号Ａ。发送文件的时间较长。这似乎足以让人判断出，微信大概没有类似百度网盘的文件去重判断。
然而出人意料的是，小号A还是一瞬间就完成了文件的接收。重启手机后也可以看到，微信所占用的空间并没有明显增加（总计1.83GB，数据1.32GB）。这说明至少在服务器端，微信确实能够判断出一份文件是否曾经上传过。而缺少类似网盘的秒传功能，可能是微信本身没有相关功能，也可能是Android端微信需要优化。
实际所占空间依然只有一份文件大小
出于好奇，我又尝试从小号B发送一份内容相同，只有文件名不同的文件，看看微信的查重是否基于文件名，或是基于文件本身。经过等待漫长的发送，如我所料，接收只在一瞬间就完成了。由此可知，微信的文件去重基于内容，并不依赖名字。
不同文件名也不会多占用空间
上面测试的都是同一账号下的情况。那么，同一台手机上的不同账号间又是怎样呢？我尝试在刚刚登录小号A的手机上切换了一个微信账号B。可以看到，这次转发收到的相同文件，需要重新接收下载。重启手机也能看到微信的占用空间变为3.8G（数据3.29G）。不过在这一微信账号下，同一文件仍然只需要下载保存一份，再次收到就能秒存。同时利用这个微信账号简单试了一下，我发现以上WeChat的文件存储机制对微信也同样成立。
实打实地需要下载，所占空间也倍增了
到这里，我们可以基本得出结论，iOS的微信文件存储去重做得还是比较令人满意的。同一账号下的同一个文件，只要内容相同，就只会在本地留存一份。未来微信团队可以努力的方向是不同账号间的文件存储去重。
另外值得一提的是，微信大概是真的有在代码层面实现去重，而非依赖APFS的CoW特性。因为即使只占一份空间，iPhone在统计容量时也会重复计算一个文件的多次拷贝。通过多次复制粘贴同一份文件，你能很容易地复现苹果的这个Bug：
苹果什么时候出4T iPhone？
在我原本的设想中，我写出这篇文章后，与其拿到那500元钱，我更想获得一个与Fenng交流的机会，说服他微信是一个糟糕的产品。但转念一下，即使我做到了，也并不能改变得了微信这个产品本身，以及我们必须使用它的环境。更何况再一看那篇文章，是要证明微信没有去重才能拿到那笔钱。是我审题不细了😀

如果你觉得我的这篇文章不错，也欢迎你阅读我之前有关微信的两篇文章：虎头蛇尾的《微信戒断实验》与尝试减少微信占用空间的《微微微信怎么办》。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>雪伊莲梦璃</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Border Agents May Have a Copy of Your Text Messages]]></title>
        <id>6324bae4c9bb1af7ef2497d2</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cbp-phone-database-ai-instagram-surveillance/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: An AI artist exposes surveillance of Instagram users, the US charges Iranians over a ransomware campaign, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Couts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[💁‍♂️ Built a Dev.to replica with The MERN stack and more]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marodevv/built-a-devto-replica-with-the-mern-stack-and-more-fbd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marodevv/built-a-devto-replica-with-the-mern-stack-and-more-fbd"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T12:43:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#showdev #javascript #react #node]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marwan mostafa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Git Commands I Use Every Day]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wadecodez/the-git-commands-i-use-every-day-5g17</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wadecodez/the-git-commands-i-use-every-day-5g17"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T12:34:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#git #beginners #programming #javascript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wade Zimmerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Colorado River Is Dying. Can Its Aquatic Dinosaurs Be Saved?]]></title>
        <id>631f676474ce5b82a68ef1a9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-colorado-river-is-dying-can-its-aquatic-dinosaurs-be-saved/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The razorback sucker has survived in the river for more than 3 million years. Climate change could end that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Mencimer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why our websites are slow — Importance of bundle size]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shreyvijayvargiya/why-our-websites-are-slow-importance-of-bundle-size-1le4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shreyvijayvargiya/why-our-websites-are-slow-importance-of-bundle-size-1le4"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T11:31:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#programming #react #javascript #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>shrey vijayvargiya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Design the Perfect Queue, According to Crowd Science]]></title>
        <id>632522c740fe1e8870aa3b0a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/queen-elizabeth-ii-queue/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The line to see Queen Elizabeth II lying in state is snaking across central London. Could it have been done better?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is OpenRAN?]]></title>
        <id>70194 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/9/open-radio-access-networks"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is OpenRAN?
Stephan Avenwedde
Sat, 09/17/2022 - 03:00

            
If you own and use a smartphone capable of connecting to arbitrary computers all over the world, then you are a user of Radio Access Networks (RAN). A RAN is provided by your cellular provider, and it handles wireless connections between your smartphone and your communication provider.
While your smartphone may be running an open source operating system (Android) and the server you try to access is probably running Linux, there's a lot of proprietary technology in between to make the connection happen. While you may have a basic understanding of how networking works locally, this knowledge stops when you plug a SIM card into your smartphone in order to make a connection with a cell tower possible. In fact, the majorit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephan Avenwedde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[InPaper – 42 种布局，无限量壁纸，创造性的自动化壁纸应用[iPhone/iPad]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43358</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/inpaper-for-ios/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T04:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[InPaper 壁纸是一款不提供壁纸的 iPhone、iPad 壁纸类工具。通过拼图、文字、日历、地图等 42 种布局，配合颜色、照片、文字，来生成无限量的个性化壁纸，并可以通过快捷指令自动化更换壁纸]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Uber Hack’s Devastation Is Just Starting to Reveal Itself]]></title>
        <id>632496798990652479ff3877</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/uber-hack-mfa-phishing/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T21:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An alleged teen hacker claims to have gained deep access to the company’s systems, but the full picture of the breach is still coming into focus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Growth Scanner — Unlock your data insights to make better business decisions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/growth-scanner</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/growth-scanner"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T20:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Picssy — Shared photo albums within your friend groups]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/picssy</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/picssy"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T19:29:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Views by Airplane — Developer-centric approach to quickly building internal UIs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/views-by-airplane</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/views-by-airplane"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T15:23:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neal Stephenson Named the Metaverse. Now, He’s Building It]]></title>
        <id>632354efc4d3ebc9237bc605</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/plaintext-neal-stephenson-named-the-metaverse-now-hes-building-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: Depicting the nerd mindset; the best lettuce; and the future is flooding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Debug React Apps With VS Code - Boost Your Debugging Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/profydev/how-to-debug-react-apps-with-vs-code-boost-your-debugging-productivity-1k05</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/profydev/how-to-debug-react-apps-with-vs-code-boost-your-debugging-productivity-1k05"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T12:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #javascript #webdev #vscode]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Johannes Kettmann, Profy.dev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The World Has Reached Peak Attenborough]]></title>
        <id>6324633c977791160bfcd28c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/david-attenborough-documentaries/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T11:52:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The British documentarian is a national treasure. But soaring strings and stunning drone shots feel frozen in an earlier era of climate activism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banning Gas Cars Is Good, but It’ll Take More to Save the Planet]]></title>
        <id>63221ac5d884b4dcc9416509</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/banning-gas-cars-is-good-but-itll-take-more-to-save-the-planet/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People must both drive less and switch to electric vehicles to reduce carbon emissions enough to avoid the worst effects of climate change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aarian Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a ‘Living Drug’ Could Treat Autoimmune Disease]]></title>
        <id>632340c5c9bb1af7ef2497c9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-a-living-drug-could-treat-autoimmune-disease/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAR-T therapy has been successful at treating cancer. Now, it’s driven lupus into remission in a handful of patients.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Mullin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[跟着操作，50元创造属于你的智能家居]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/72429</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/72429"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T08:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[智能家居。我的理解是：智能的、易用的，能给生活提供极大便利的，才能称之为「智能家居」。
大家好，我是少数派新晋 Martix 作者，目前从事主要以政府项目为主的运营。作为我在少数派潜水多年后的第一篇内容，就是如何利用极低的成本打造属于你的智能家居。
内容背景

本文将以「Home Assistant」智能家居平台（简称 「Home Assistant」，下同），开展工作，并通过 iOS 的 HomeKit 及 Android 自身的设备管理器来控制智能家居配件。关于「Home Assistant」的详细介绍，如何部署及安装插件的教学，少数派已有前辈进行了详细说明，这里不再赘述。

需强调的是，笔者通过 Debian 10 进行部署，版本是 2022.3.8，预装插件与其他方法略有出入。
由于系统过于老旧，「Home Assistant」的 Home Assistant Supervisor 不再支持 Debian 10 ，但使用下来，似乎实际上没有影响。
重复造轮子？

既然前辈已经在少数派中发表了基于「Home Assistant」构建的「智能家居」内容，为何笔者仍然要以此作为在少数派的第一篇内容？不是前辈撰写的内容不好，只是内容方向不同，本文将基于 YAML 语言来定制属于自己的「智能家居」。
本文将尽可能使用通俗的语言，力求做到即使每一位读者未曾接触也不能理解 YAML 语言的情况下能码出自己想要的配置文件，但由于笔者对 YAML 语法也未能做到了然于胸，更多地是一边学习一边进行，涉及到变量的部分无可奉告。
自身情况及案例
自身情况

笔者家中由于入网设备较多，以及需要多网合并带宽等需求，传统路由器性能已无法达到笔者需求，因此家中有一台低功耗服务器作为软路由使用，部署在 VMware 虚拟机中。

所使用网络基于中国电信，配备有公网非固定 IP 和动态域名。
自身案例…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pendulumchirs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe 收购 Figma 之后会怎样]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75740</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75740"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T08:12:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[近日（2022/9/15）设计圈有个大新闻，Adobe 公布了收购 Figma 的消息：

Adobe 的官方公告
Figma 的官方公告
Figma CEO 的推特

Adobe 决定用 200 亿美元（一半股票，一半现金）收购 Figma，交易还需要获得监管部⻔的批准，预计将在 2023 年完成。
这对于设计界来说是一个爆炸性的新闻，虽然在此前也有征兆，早在去年（2021）Figma 的最早的两个联合创始人之一，与现任 Figma CEO 在大学时期一起创建 Figma 的前 CTO Evan Wallace 从 Figma 离职了，可能在那时就已经决定了 Figma 的命运。
对于这次收购，很多设计师对 Figma 非常的悲观，相比 Figma 而言 Adobe 更像是一个无情的资本机器，收购来的产品鲜有好下场的，上一个 Adobe 收购的界面设计工具 Macromedia Fireworks 已经死在 2013 年了。
Macromedia Fireworks 1.0
而 Adobe 的旧有产品缓慢又迟钝的更新，在设计师群体中形成了 Adobe 就是一头笨拙的大象的印象。在过去，设计师们既不满意又无法逃过 Adobe 的魔掌，Figma 的出现让设计师至少在 UI 设计领域上挣脱了 Adobe 的束缚，可惜即使 Figma 在 UI 设计领域战胜了 Adobe，又拓宽了设计与协作的领域，最终还是被 Adobe 花钱摆平了。
很多设计师对 Adobe 收购最有印象的是 2005 年收购 Macromedia，曾经风靡一时的 Macromedia 产品 Dreamweaver、Fireworks、Flash、 Authorware 几乎都死在了 Adobe 手上，其实 Adobe 的买买买从更早就开始了，Adobe 的代表产品 Photoshop 就是 1995 年收购…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>四喜茶茶</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App+1 | Android 上更加好看的 Spotify ：Jetispot]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75751</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75751"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T07:28:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spotify 可以说是少数派中无所不知的一款音乐软件，简洁克制的界面设计和无干扰的听歌体验吸引了不少听众。但是一直以来，Spotify 在 Android 上算不上有特别好的体验。尤其是一直没有修复的手势条沉浸问题，一条黑色的底边让人感到非常膈应。Spotify 似乎也没有做Light Mode 的打算，如果能有个亮色主题也会非常好看。
来源：@酱紫表
⚠️使用该 App 需要有 Spotify Premium
Introducing to New redesign Spotify: Jetispot

打开应用的第一个界面，我就已经被吸引到了。这些控件按钮都有十足的“原生”的味道
Welcome to Jetispot!
开始体验一下全新风格的 Spotify
登录后，可以看到主界面和Spotify的基本排布类似。Navigation Bar 上分为主页、搜索和资料库，右上角的三个小图标排布也相同。不过可以看到，作者还添加了两个分类标签：Music 和 Podcasts & Shows。我认为这是一个很实用的功能，毕竟谁也不想在公共场合打开后看到播客里显示一些很奇怪的东西 可惜这个App本身还未完成，这部分还不能正常使用。

随意探索一下
可以看到在搜索页面依然是大差不差。最明显的就是 Browse all 所有的卡片都用上了圆角。不过也能看到搜索栏功能还尚未实现。

现在，我们来选择一个专辑看看
可以看到在专辑页面中，背景色不再是原来的偏向于黑暗的页面。背景的渐变颜色是根据专辑封面来选取的，与 Spotify 相比感觉没有那么的压抑，整体显得很轻快明亮。

选择一首歌来听听
感觉加载速度和 Spotify 比起来没有很大的延迟，就是一个用起来不会因为加载不动而感到不舒适。不过这个音乐界面相对来说有一些简陋，上半部分很空旷。同时进度条也没有用上长得像蛇一样的波浪条👀

还可以做的更好

整体而言，我对 Android 上能有一个外观不错的 Spotify 第三方还是很满意了。
毕竟 Spotify 连个手势条沉浸都不管
Jetispot 可以说是很好看，但绝对算不上稳定优秀。
在我使用的过程中经常会偶尔遇到闪退和 Bug。而且这个软件很多功能尚未完成：搜索栏尚未支持，消息通知点无法使用，主页的筛选也无法使用，点赞的功能尚未实现，通知栏中的小图标也尚未适配。
小图标的位置只有空虚⚪
该 App 目前仍然在继续开发中。作者在 Telegram Channel 中还发布了正在制作歌词部分的预览。
以下是作者在 Github 上的规划

What's working:

sign in (login/pass only, no FB/Meta/whatsoever support, no Smart Lock either)
"browse", "home", album, premium plan, artist and genre screens (some of the blocks might be unsupported)
library: "liked songs" w/ tag&sort support, rootlist (liked playlists) + pins + artist/album support w/ nice animations, delta updates + pub/sub processing support
basic playback w/ Spotify Connect support (connect support is very WIP)
fairly optimized R8 rules, providing approx. 5-6 megabytes release APK size (with the playback and protobuf parts!)

What's in progress:

"Now Playing" improvements
better service (notification improvements)

希望可以能够长久的发展下去，RIP for Xpo Music🙏
你可以在 Github 或 Telegram Channel 免费下载使用 Jetispot。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krrrrrik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZoZo App — Increase your daily productivity with keyboard shortcuts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/zozo-app</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/zozo-app"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T03:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AjPicard25@icloud.com
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（四）高级篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11705</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11705"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T02:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（四）高级篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[利用ASP.NET Web API Help Page文件上传]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11697</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11697"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T02:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[利用ASP.NET Web API Help Page文件上传]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[基于netfilter的rootkit]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11673</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11673"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T02:33:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[基于netfilter的rootkit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A US Rail Strike Was Averted—but the Crisis Is Far From Over]]></title>
        <id>63223fe940fe1e8870aa3ad0</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/a-us-rail-strike-was-averted-but-the-crisis-is-far-from-over/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T21:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A preliminary agreement prevented a total shutdown, but many supply chains still face delays and disruption caused by staff shortages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caitlin Harrington</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA’s Perseverance Rover Digs Up Organic Molecules on Mars]]></title>
        <id>63235cf3036b54662b5104de</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/nasas-perseverance-rover-digs-up-organic-molecules-on-mars/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T20:34:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are tantalizing hints that microbes might have lived on Mars billions of years ago, but scientists need to study the rocks back on Earth to be sure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramin Skibba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Satellite Data Shows How Russia Has Destroyed Ukrainian Grain]]></title>
        <id>6320a9edc9bb1af7ef249735</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/satellites-ukraine-russia-grain/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T18:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Russian blockade and bombardments are cutting off thousands of tons of grain, threatening the food supply in countries that rely on wheat exports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vittoria Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Satellite Data Shows How Russia Has Destroyed Ukrainian Grain]]></title>
        <id>6320a9edc9bb1af7ef249735</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/satellites-ukraine-russia-grain/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T18:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Russian blockade and bombardments are cutting off thousands of tons of grain, threatening the food supply in countries that rely on wheat exports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vittoria Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monkeypox Cases in the US Are Falling. There's No One Reason Why]]></title>
        <id>630d2a44dec8aa69fd32238c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/monkeypox-cases-falling-united-states/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T16:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many people changed their behavior, the vaccines might be helping, and the virus might someday burn itself out—but there’s not enough data to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maryn McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[19 Practical ES6 Snippets to Solve Common JS Problems 🚀💯]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/madza/19-practical-es6-snippets-to-solve-common-js-problems-31o9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/madza/19-practical-es6-snippets-to-solve-common-js-problems-31o9"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T15:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #frontend #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Madza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[不常见的内存与流量取证 -- WMCTF 2022 1!5!]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11699</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11699"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T15:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[不常见的内存与流量取证 -- WMCTF 2022 1!5!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2020-8558-跨主机访问127.0.0.1]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11674</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11674"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T15:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2020-8558-跨主机访问127.0.0.1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[红日安全团队ATT&CK(二)实战系列靶场]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11676</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11676"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T15:40:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[红日安全团队ATT&CK(二)实战系列靶场]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“黑猫”又伸出恶魔之手？揭秘BlackCat病毒的三重勒索]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11656</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11656"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T15:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“黑猫”又伸出恶魔之手？揭秘BlackCat病毒的三重勒索]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Modern Humans Can Learn From Ancient Software]]></title>
        <id>630fa634333af8e1504c49a1</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/modern-humans-learn-ancient-software-retrocomputing/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retrocomputing is about more than nostalgic nerdery. It’s also a way to keep your tech in perspective.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Ford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Must Know JavaScript Tips & Tricks 🎈]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dcodeyt/7-must-know-javascript-tips-tricks-2m8f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dcodeyt/7-must-know-javascript-tips-tricks-2m8f"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T12:49:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #beginners #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dom (dcode)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching ‘Selfish’ Wind Turbines to Share Can Boost Productivity]]></title>
        <id>63227cb7036b54662b5104dd</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/wind-turbine-efficiency-algorithm/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A software update can help turbines become less disruptive to their neighbors and distribute the wind more efficiently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Perez Ortiz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Shaky Future of a Post-Roe Federal Privacy Law]]></title>
        <id>631b4210eecde8c117e7f368</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/adppa-roe-democrats-congress/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The American Data Privacy and Protection Act could protect people across the country. But first, it has to get past Nancy Pelosi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Laslo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[打工人如何让自己从「商品」变成「艺术品」？]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75685</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75685"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T09:44:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[如果你到了一个陌生的地方旅游，你会选择哪种方式？

方式一：去名胜古迹，或被证明过很好玩的地方打卡；
方式二：随机开车，走到哪儿就在哪儿玩。

我是属于比较保守的那类人，我会选择第一种，这样感觉更保险。但是我住在加拿大的姨娘选择的是第二种。下面这个是她的朋友圈：

随机点地图的出行方式让我心生艳羡，于是评论道「特别好」。
但我想很多人，包括我在内，都会觉得这种靠随机点地图就走的方式比较冒险，就像去到一家陌生的商场里，会先通过大众点评的评级进行一轮筛选，然后再去看对应店家下的评论，最后确定在了一家网红餐厅上。
这种由别人构建出的无形的价值系统，会让我们不自觉地去遵从，我把这种价值系统称作「体裁」。
拧巴、纠结、焦虑，都可能是因为你身处的体裁与你的内在目标产生了矛盾。我想通过这篇文章，疏通一下你的「自我拧巴」情绪。
一、体裁与规则
体裁原本指的是「一切艺术作品的种类和样式」。一个表现形式，只有在特定的场景中，才会发挥应该有的意义。
赵衡毅在《趣味符号学》里说1：

所有的符号文本，都从属于一定的体裁，体裁是一种符号发出者与接收者都接受的一个文化契约，在契约中，符号的发送者与接收者互相限制对方的自由，但是增加了效率。

比如，小说和说明书就是不同的体裁，两者都有对应的呈现形式。而对于读者而言，看小说可以不用当真，但是看说明书需要一板一眼地照着指示来改变现实。
在看一本书之前，先知道它属于什么体裁，就能提高你和作者的沟通效率。再比如谍战人员之间秘密传输的暗号，就需要严格按照对应的体裁规范，去生成信息和解析信息。
体裁如果延伸到我们的生活方式里，它就是某一个群体约定俗成的潜规则。这些规则会束缚着我们的思想和行为。群体有大有小，小到某一个兴趣社群，大到社会性别的约束。
20年前，一位陕西咸阳附近农村的家庭妇女，从小的家里教育就是要孝敬公婆、做好饭、做好衣服、照顾孩子。
她是大家眼里的好…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>猴猴说话</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一日一技｜六边形法迅速查找 Apple Watch 中的 app]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75719</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75719"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T06:56:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 0 引入
众所周知，Watch 有两种视图。第一个是「列表视图」，第二个则是「蜂窝视图」。我第一次用蜂窝视图的时候觉得这种交互模式非常炫酷，但是用了一段时间后的感受是 —— 「就像把杂货箱的东西全部倾倒出来，然后直到找着这一次需要的东西」。这无疑是一个非常糟糕的体验，因为每一次找 App 都要反复体验一下找杂物的难受感。所以这里触发了一个痛点是：「买完 Apple Watch 之后，我们应该如何快速找到并打开目标 app 呢？」
回忆一下小时候混乱的工具箱
本篇文章的前提 —— 在抛除了「Siri」、「程序坞」、「表盘上的快捷入口」三种检索方式的基础之上，再来探索有没有办法可以进一步提高效率，让我们的「应用菜单」也可以具备更强的检索性，做到井井有条。
Grid View（网格视图，我也喜欢称为蜂窝视图）
Part 1 思路总括
一开始我是换回了习惯的「列表视图」，依靠皇冠的转动来找到 App。但是列表视图有个问题是 —— 你无法调整 App 的显示顺序。就算你可以调整并分类 App，你也有可能需要在「单向」上线性地浏览众多的 App 之后才能找到目标，
List View（列表视图）
所以思路开始清晰起来 —— 如果我们把应用进行分类，并从中心延伸到几个不同的方向，就可以减少查找的时间和查找的路径长度。基于此，我们利用蜂窝的特性，从中心恰好可以切割出 6 条大方向，代表 6 个大类，然后把最主要的 App 直接放到 6 条线上。相当于至少提高检索速度 6 倍。
自制演示图
Part 2 和我一起来分类
现在，请大家停下 1 分钟，和我一起思考：我的 Apple Watch 上大致都有哪些 app 呢？对于我而言，我会分为以下 6 大类（逆时针），然后把最常用的放到线上：

健康
运动
音乐·声音
办公·社交·信息
支付
其他工具

Part 3 和我一起思考 6 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>莱森</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[微信，成为老大哥]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75731</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75731"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T04:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[大雾重重，时代喧哗造物忙。火光忷忷，指引盗寇入太行。
近期，微信因推出输入法再次冲上热搜，由于越使用占用空间越大，又一次激起了人们对微信「小而美」的调侃。
为什么微信越来越臃肿了？在过去十一年来，微信是如何一步一步成为一个超级 APP 的？为了了解背后的发展故事，我作了此文加以梳理。研究中国最大的社交软件的发展史，其实也是研究过去十几年来简中移动互联网的变迁过程。也是试图解答一个徘徊许久的疑问：这些在摇滚精神和改革开放理念下成长的一代人，简中世界互联网的掌门人，作为新中国历史以来最成功的阶级上升案例，又是如何一步一步，从勇者变成恶龙的。
本文亦有视频版本。
老大哥在看着你
在 1984 的开篇有这么一句话：无论你走往哪个方向，总有一双眼睛跟着你。Big Brother is watching you.

如今，无论身处何时何地，只要打开手机，也有一双眼睛在看着你。
船票：新大陆与旧秩序
今年是世界末日后的第十年。在今天，很多人可能并不了解或已经遗忘了 2012 的含义。但在十年前，桌面互联网发展的高峰之时，新兴媒体里关于世界末日的讨论贯穿了 2012 年始末。2012 贴吧也是那一年里最热门的百度贴吧之一。有人发帖说自己变卖了全部家产，准备在末日到来前玩个痛快。
风靡一时的 2012 贴吧
待到末日论调随新年钟响而息鼓偃旗，人们发现生活还要继续；曾以为世界将有很大的变化，然而现实来临时却总是似是而非，但未来的确将有所不同。
2011 年，采用三明治架构的、被视作时代经典的 iPhone 4 进入中国市场；同年，iPhone 4S 在乔布斯逝世前一天发布，被喻为乔布斯的遗作，引起了热烈的抢购和黄牛加价。「割肾换爱疯」的梗也从那时流传开来。十月份，《乔布斯传》中文版上市，成为当年排行第一的畅销书，销量甚至力压了当时常年霸占销冠、各有新书的韩寒和郭敬明。在一篇《萌芽》杂志对韩寒的…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>拐子狼</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Twitter Whistleblower’s Testimony Has Senators Out for Blood]]></title>
        <id>6320f8e900704d14b5ffb882</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/peiter-mudge-zatko-twitter-senate-judiciary-testimony/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T19:01:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peiter “Mudge” Zatko’s allegations about the social media platform renewed a sense of urgency for lawmakers to rein in Big Tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Laslo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Twitter Whistleblower’s Testimony Has Senators Out for Blood]]></title>
        <id>6320f8e900704d14b5ffb882</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/peiter-mudge-zatko-twitter-senate-judiciary-testimony/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T19:01:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peiter “Mudge” Zatko’s allegations about the social media platform renewed a sense of urgency for lawmakers to rein in Big Tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Laslo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-1292的分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11703</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11703"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T13:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-1292的分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gitlab常见漏洞复现及后利用]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11690</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11690"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T13:39:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gitlab常见漏洞复现及后利用]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The UN Wants to Curb Anti-Satellite Missile Tests]]></title>
        <id>631b932f40fe1e8870aa3a2e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-un-wants-to-curb-anti-satellite-missile-tests/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a high-profile meeting in Geneva, international negotiators are moving closer toward developing rules for space actors in low Earth orbit and beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramin Skibba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End of Roe Will Spark a Digital Civil War]]></title>
        <id>63208fea20bc56769c4130dc</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-end-of-roe-will-spark-a-digital-civil-war/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New privacy and expression laws that vary state to state will be a nightmare for platforms, and for users’ rights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Perault</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing APIs for humans: Error messages]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stripe/designing-apis-for-humans-error-messages-94p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stripe/designing-apis-for-humans-error-messages-94p"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T11:36:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#api #webdev #programming #stripe]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Asjes, Stripe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Gets to Build the Next Software Stack of Civilization?]]></title>
        <id>631a39e1f1e5c40d2b1bc5f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/who-gets-to-build-the-next-software-stack-of-civilization/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WIRED’s editor in chief considers Silicon Valley’s visions for the future of governance, plus more thoughts on this month’s headlines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gideon Lichfield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A GMO Purple Tomato Is Coming to Stores. Will the US Bite?]]></title>
        <id>631f8cd2f1e5c40d2b1bc637</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/a-gmo-purple-tomato-is-coming-to-grocery-aisles-will-the-us-bite/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most genetically engineered foods were developed to aid farmers. This one will try to sway over health-conscious produce shoppers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Mullin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Charles the ‘Activist King’ Means for the Climate]]></title>
        <id>632121cceecde8c117e7f3f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/king-charles-iii-climate-environmental-activist/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a long record of environmental campaigning as the Prince of Wales, how will King Charles III’s accession to the throne translate to public policies?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine’s Cyberwar Chief Sounds Like He’s Winning]]></title>
        <id>6320f08cd884b4dcc94164fe</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/yurii-shchyhol-urkaine-cyberwar-russia/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yurii Shchyhol gives WIRED a rare interview about running the country’s Derzhspetszviazok and the state of the online conflict with Russia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Vast Wasteland of Internet Television]]></title>
        <id>630fb1b9dbc9ebd1c95a7469</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/i-want-the-internet-tv-we-were-all-promised/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When TV came online in the aughts, it was exciting. Then Facebook took over.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Virginia Heffernan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[从mcms历史漏洞中捡漏]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11695</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11695"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T11:53:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[从mcms历史漏洞中捡漏]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 网鼎杯玄武组-you can find it 题解—Spring通用MemShell改造]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11688</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11688"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T11:52:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2022 网鼎杯玄武组-you can find it 题解—Spring通用MemShell改造]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Whistleblowers Navigate a Security Minefield]]></title>
        <id>631fc39f8990652479ff3848</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/whistleblower-safety-mudge-twitter-senate-hearing/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exposing wrongdoing is risky on the best of days. Whistleblower Aid cofounder John Tye explains the extensive steps needed to keep people safe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Whistleblowers Navigate a Security Minefield]]></title>
        <id>631fc39f8990652479ff3848</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/whistleblower-safety-mudge-twitter-senate-hearing/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exposing wrongdoing is risky on the best of days. Whistleblower Aid cofounder John Tye explains the extensive steps needed to keep people safe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When the Big One Hits Portland, Cargo Bikers Will Save You]]></title>
        <id>631b9e5a40fe1e8870aa3a2f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/when-the-big-one-hits-portland-cargo-bikers-will-save-you/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pacific Northwest is due for a massive quake. I trained to help rescue efforts in the aftermath—by racing around the city on an electric kid hauler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrienne So</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Fantastic Heroku Alternatives]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jainilprajapati/7-fantastic-heroku-alternatives-4jf8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jainilprajapati/7-fantastic-heroku-alternatives-4jf8"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T18:26:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#heroku #javascript #webdev #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jainil Prajapati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Undocumented Workers Protest Uber Eats Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>631f59fc40fe1e8870aa3a70</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/uber-eats-paris-protests/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T16:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In France, the gig economy platform welcomed thousands of immigrants during the pandemic, unions say. Now it’s deactivating them en masse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Morgan Meaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building an interactive screen-sharing app with Puppeteer and React 🤯]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/novu/building-an-interactive-screen-sharing-app-with-puppeteer-and-react-12h7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/novu/building-an-interactive-screen-sharing-app-with-puppeteer-and-react-12h7"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T15:05:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #webdev #javascript #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevo David, novu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The FTC Is Closing in on Runaway AI]]></title>
        <id>6315e68a44c07c3774c4cba0</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ftc-ai-regulation/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US regulator is eager to end unfair use of artificial intelligence and commercial surveillance, but experts remain skeptical.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khari Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The FTC Is Closing in on Runaway AI]]></title>
        <id>6315e68a44c07c3774c4cba0</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ftc-ai-regulation/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US regulator is eager to end unfair use of artificial intelligence and commercial surveillance, but experts remain skeptical.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khari Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iOS 16 Has 2 New Security Features for Worst-Case Scenarios]]></title>
        <id>631b90a1d884b4dcc94164be</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/apple-ios-16-safety-check-lockdown-mode/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Safety Check and Lockdown Mode give people in vulnerable situations ways to quarantine themselves from acute risks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding remote work in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/k_ivanow/finding-remote-work-in-2022-26j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/k_ivanow/finding-remote-work-in-2022-26j"/>
        <updated>2022-09-11T15:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#remote #interview #career #jobs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristian Ivanov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Making of A React Component Library]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aviavinav/the-making-of-a-react-component-librabry-cep</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aviavinav/the-making-of-a-react-component-librabry-cep"/>
        <updated>2022-09-11T12:09:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #react #webdev #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Avi Avinav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering these 7 Basics CSS Skills will make you a Frontend Wizard 🧙✨]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/mastering-these-7-basics-css-skills-will-make-you-a-frontend-wizard-2khn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/mastering-these-7-basics-css-skills-will-make-you-a-frontend-wizard-2khn"/>
        <updated>2022-09-11T06:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #programming #css #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapajyoti Bose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Full Stack Permanent Applications with Arweave, Smartweave, and Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dabit3/building-full-stack-applications-with-arweave-and-nextjs-28hg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dabit3/building-full-stack-applications-with-arweave-and-nextjs-28hg"/>
        <updated>2022-09-10T19:12:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #nextjs #web3]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nader Dabit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Target Los Angeles School District With Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>631bd10a8990652479ff3840</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/la-school-district-ransomware-albania-iran-security-roundup/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: Albania cuts ties with Iran, claims of a TikTok data breach that didn’t happen, and much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why are people developing inside containers?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/github/why-are-people-developing-inside-containers-38o6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/github/why-are-people-developing-inside-containers-38o6"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T20:49:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#github #beginners #cloud #docker]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rizèl Scarlett, GitHub</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[某后台管理系统的审计]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11669</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11669"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T15:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[某后台管理系统的审计]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Am I Wrong to Judge People for Talking to Me in Emoji?]]></title>
        <id>630f9ec45d32e4cad34d6f24</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/am-i-wrong-to-judge-talking-in-emoji/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WIRED’s spiritual advice columnist reassures a literary reader that it’s OK to communicate with images.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meghan O'Gieblyn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[30 PyTricks I've Learned By Joining the Real Python Mailing List.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wiseai/30-pytricks-ive-learned-by-joining-the-real-python-mailing-list-227i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wiseai/30-pytricks-ive-learned-by-joining-the-real-python-mailing-list-227i"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T20:16:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#python #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahmoud Harmouch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12 Modern UI Components to Inspire Your Future Designs 😍✨]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/madza/12-modern-ui-components-to-inspire-your-future-designs-4ni4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/madza/12-modern-ui-components-to-inspire-your-future-designs-4ni4"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T16:08:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #design #ui #inspiration]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Madza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[关于那WebSocket劫持的二三事]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11684</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11684"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T15:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[关于那WebSocket劫持的二三事]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Woman Who Became a Company Has Lessons for a Post-Roe World]]></title>
        <id>62fd1fe9b07577beee1be7f9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/art-data-property-roe/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jennifer Lyn Morone became a corporation in hopes of protecting her data privacy. Her experience shows the downfalls of treating data like property.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charlotte Kent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[50+ Awesome tools for Web Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/surajondev/50-awesome-tools-for-web-developers-5gan</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/surajondev/50-awesome-tools-for-web-developers-5gan"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T11:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #beginners #react]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Vishwakarma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Tips And Tricks Every Developer Should know 💯 🚀️]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devsyedmohsin/javascript-tips-and-tricks-you-need-to-know-1g2k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devsyedmohsin/javascript-tips-and-tricks-you-need-to-know-1g2k"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T11:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #programming #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Syed Mohsin Raza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Clever Anti-Censorship Tool Lets Russians Read Blocked News]]></title>
        <id>631939da8990652479ff376e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/russia-internet-censorship-samizdat-online/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samizdat Online syndicates banned news sites by hosting them on uncensored domains—allowing people to access independent reporting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Me & React: 5 years in 15 minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/valeriavg/me-react-5-years-in-15-minutes-58od</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/valeriavg/me-react-5-years-in-15-minutes-58od"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T07:10:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #beginners #javascript #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s Killing the Password. Here’s Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>6318d57feecde8c117e7f34a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/apple-passkeys-password-iphone-mac-ios16-ventura/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T18:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With iOS 16 and macOS Ventura, Apple is introducing passkeys—a more convenient and secure alternative to passwords.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（三）中级篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11682</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11682"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T15:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（三）中级篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Web Paint Application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/anshika_gautam_/build-a-web-paint-application-5f55</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/anshika_gautam_/build-a-web-paint-application-5f55"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T14:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #html #css #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshika</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banning Phones in Class? Not So Fast]]></title>
        <id>6303a03afd602ff2f11e6ffa</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cell-phone-bans-school/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tech dependence is following many students back to school—but waging a war against devices helps no one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erica Berry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detect When Users Switch Tabs using JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/j471n/detect-when-users-switch-tabs-using-javascript-3mi3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/j471n/detect-when-users-switch-tabs-using-javascript-3mi3"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T04:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #tutorial #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jatin Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[红队开发基础-基础免杀(四)]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11659</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11659"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[红队开发基础-基础免杀(四)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[揭开新型窃密软件的面纱：伪装成CDR画图应用安装包]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11653</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11653"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T15:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[揭开新型窃密软件的面纱：伪装成CDR画图应用安装包]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux提权基础分享和讨论]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11664</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11664"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T15:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux提权基础分享和讨论]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Complete List of Heroku Alternatives to Consider]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/zevir/the-complete-list-of-heroku-alternatives-to-consider-1l8o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/zevir/the-complete-list-of-heroku-alternatives-to-consider-1l8o"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T15:21:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#heroku #webdev #programming #devops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zevi Reinitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So, You Want Twitter to Stop Destroying Democracy]]></title>
        <id>6306003d1814a994d3a63460</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-democracy-harm-reduction/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telling people to quit the platform is less effective than stopping influential elites from using the site in harmful ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katherine Cross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Time to Get Real About TikTok’s Risks]]></title>
        <id>630f9a9a3dfe1372fb61110f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/tiktok-nationa-security-threat-why/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US lawmakers keep warning about the popular app. But until they can explain what makes it uniquely dangerous, it’s difficult to tailor a resolution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2020-28413 MantisBT SQL注入漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11671</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11671"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T15:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2020-28413 MantisBT SQL注入漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（二）进阶篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11681</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11681"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T15:54:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（二）进阶篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JAVA常用框架SQL注入审计]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11672</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11672"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T15:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JAVA常用框架SQL注入审计]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a live-event alert system with React, Socket.io, and Push Notifications 🚀]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/novu/building-a-live-event-alert-system-with-react-socketio-and-push-notifications-2jg5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/novu/building-a-live-event-alert-system-with-react-socketio-and-push-notifications-2jg5"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T14:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #react #programming #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevo David, novu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Abortion Pill ‘Reversal’ Really Accomplishes]]></title>
        <id>63122b60a4a22698f6d24aae</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/abortion-pill-reversal-essay/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s more than an unproven medical treatment—it’s a view into the antiabortion movement’s larger project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Knibbs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We measured the SSR performance of 6 JS frameworks - here's what we found]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/enterspeed/we-measured-the-ssr-performance-of-6-js-frameworks-heres-what-we-found-1ck0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/enterspeed/we-measured-the-ssr-performance-of-6-js-frameworks-heres-what-we-found-1ck0"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T06:35:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #react #performance #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kasper Andreassen, Enterspeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15+ Array Methods in Javascript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codewithtee/15-array-methods-in-javascript-1p1m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codewithtee/15-array-methods-in-javascript-1p1m"/>
        <updated>2022-09-04T18:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #beginners #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tabassum Khanum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 must-have Chrome Extensions for Web Developers 🚀🌐]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/6-must-have-chrome-extensions-for-web-developers-1ma2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/6-must-have-chrome-extensions-for-web-developers-1ma2"/>
        <updated>2022-09-04T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #productivity #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapajyoti Bose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Cheatsheet]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sarath_pm/git-cheatsheet-414e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sarath_pm/git-cheatsheet-414e"/>
        <updated>2022-09-03T13:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#git #programming #github #codenewbie]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarath P M</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Police Across US Bypass Warrants With Mass Location-Tracking Tool]]></title>
        <id>6311923d9fbbe8d3536bfa37</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/fog-reveal-police-montenegro-ransomware-ftc-lawsuit/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: An unsecured database exposed face recognition data in China, ‘Cuba’ ransomware knocks out Montenegro, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big O notation basics made dead simple]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/heyjtk/big-o-notation-basics-made-dead-simple-1c9m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/heyjtk/big-o-notation-basics-made-dead-simple-1c9m"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T19:06:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#softwareengineering #algorithms #coding]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JTK</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Versify — Engage and reward your customers with digital collectibles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/versify</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/versify"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T18:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Versify. We have worked extremely hard to make the process so easy that someone with zero technical knowledge can create and airdrop an NFT to their entire customer list in less than 5 minutes. Seriously, try it here.

Here's what you can expect from Versify:
🏎️ Frictionless. Not familiar with blockchain? Don't own a crypto wallet? No problem at all. Versify has the crypto newcomers in mind, so we abstracted away all technical intricacies.
😌 Convenient. Already store your customer list in another app like Salesforce or Mailchimp? Perfect! With our pre-built integrations, you can instantly connect your other tools and automatically airdrop an NFT to any or all of your customers.
💰 Cost-effective. Did we mention that Versify is entirely free for up to 25 mints?

🎲 SCAVENGER HUNT 🎲
In the spirit of some Product Hunt fun & creativity, we decided to create a mini scavenger hunt using Versify Mint Links. We have hidden three collectibles within this page and the Versify dashboard. Collect all 3 to redeem free premium access (up to 1,000 mints) to the platform for a month. We'll make the first one a freebie. Here it is.

We are so excited to build Versify with you and can't wait for you to try it. To get started, create your account here. We'd love to hear all feedback, suggestions, and questions.

Thank you all for your support and advice.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok Users Were Vulnerable to a Single-Click Attack]]></title>
        <id>63110e2a44c07c3774c4cb37</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/tiktok-android-app-deep-link-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft disclosed the flaw in the Android app’s deep link verification process, which has since been fixed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin, Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why DeepMind Is Sending AI Humanoids to Soccer Camp]]></title>
        <id>631134165d32e4cad34d6f3b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/alphabet-deepmind-ai-humanoids-soccer-camp/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Alphabet-backed AI firm is using virtual games to help its digital creations move more like humans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amit Katwala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Russian Spy in My Econ Class]]></title>
        <id>630629f0fd602ff2f11e70a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/national-security-spies-johns-hopkins/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Johns Hopkins' long history with student-spies suggests this most recent incident will not lead to much change—but maybe that's OK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Conrad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awesome GitHub Repositories for Web Developer - Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-github-repositories-for-web-developer-part-2-1h8b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-github-repositories-for-web-developer-part-2-1h8b"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T11:36:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#github #webdev #javascript #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Vishwakarma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trans Researchers Want Google Scholar to Stop Deadnaming Them]]></title>
        <id>630506f9cea7c0581e825d21</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/trans-researchers-want-google-scholar-to-stop-deadnaming-them/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The academic search engine’s policy on name changes is out of step with other search tools and publishers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khari Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's the difference between : and :: in CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/whitep4nth3r/whats-the-difference-between-and-in-css-23p4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/whitep4nth3r/whats-the-difference-between-and-in-css-23p4"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T09:41:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#css #webdev #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salma Alam-Naylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（一）基础篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11677</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11677"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T09:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（一）基础篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn Web3 (September 2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/francescoxx/how-to-learn-web3-september-2022-3h9h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/francescoxx/how-to-learn-web3-september-2022-3h9h"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T06:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#web3 #blockchain #beginners #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francesco Ciulla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[利用Nginx、Tyk Gateway API和CloudFlare防火墙隐藏C2设施]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11662</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11662"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T14:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[利用Nginx、Tyk Gateway API和CloudFlare防火墙隐藏C2设施]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[域内批量获取敏感文件]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11667</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11667"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T14:54:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[域内批量获取敏感文件]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Heroku Alternatives for free]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/meshvpatel18/top-heroku-alternatives-for-free-46g1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/meshvpatel18/top-heroku-alternatives-for-free-46g1"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T13:49:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#heroku #webdev #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meshv Patel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The FTC May (Finally) Protect Americans From Data Brokers]]></title>
        <id>630e23a9567860ab6c66c659</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-ftc-may-finally-protect-americans-from-data-brokers/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The agency’s lawsuit against Kochava should squash the industry’s core defense—and help keep sensitive info off the open market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Sherman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-31197 PostgreSQL JDBC SQL注入分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11660</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11660"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T15:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-31197 PostgreSQL JDBC SQL注入分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Pays for an Act of Cyberwar?]]></title>
        <id>62fb9c2216995ea7b1a92dd3</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/russia-ukraine-cyberwar-cyberinsurance/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyberinsurance doesn't cover acts of war. But even as cyberattacks mount, the definition of "warlike" actions remains blurry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josephine Wolff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building an aircraft radar system in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devdevcharlie/building-an-aircraft-radar-system-in-javascript-4ml8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devdevcharlie/building-an-aircraft-radar-system-in-javascript-4ml8"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T16:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webusb #rtlsdr]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charlie Gerard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ADCS攻击笔记]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11627</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11627"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ADCS攻击笔记]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Useful Articles Every New Developer Should Bookmark 👍💯]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ijsucceed/7-useful-articles-every-new-developer-should-bookmark-bpg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ijsucceed/7-useful-articles-every-new-developer-should-bookmark-bpg"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T13:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#codenewbie #webdev #beginners #javascript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeremy Ikwuje</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ThinkPHP 5.0.X代码审计]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11658</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11658"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T13:51:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ThinkPHP 5.0.X代码审计]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【云攻防系列】从攻击者视角聊聊K8S集群安全（上）]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11652</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11652"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T13:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[【云攻防系列】从攻击者视角聊聊K8S集群安全（上）]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[给木马带双眼睛]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11655</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11655"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T13:48:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[给木马带双眼睛]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[利用 PHP-FPM 做内存马的方法]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11651</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11651"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[利用 PHP-FPM 做内存马的方法]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Most Common useState Mistakes React Developers Often Make]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/refine/5-most-common-usestate-mistakes-react-developers-often-make-3aig</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/refine/5-most-common-usestate-mistakes-react-developers-often-make-3aig"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T09:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #webdev #programming #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Necati Özmen, refine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Three-City Problem of Modern Life]]></title>
        <id>62fd5532fd602ff2f11e6fbe</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/technology-philosophy-three-city-problem/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What does Athens have to do with Jerusalem—and what do either have to do with Silicon Valley?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Burgis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made all countries' flags using HTML & CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/j471n/i-made-all-countries-flags-using-html-css-4cnc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/j471n/i-made-all-countries-flags-using-html-css-4cnc"/>
        <updated>2022-08-28T09:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#css #webdev #html #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jatin Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 neat tricks for JS that you probably did not know]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/7-neat-tricks-for-js-that-you-probably-did-not-know-358d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/7-neat-tricks-for-js-that-you-probably-did-not-know-358d"/>
        <updated>2022-08-28T05:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #programming #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapajyoti Bose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Alternatives to Heroku]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/daveson217/free-alternatives-to-heroku-3jh9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/daveson217/free-alternatives-to-heroku-3jh9"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T10:28:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#help #heroku #webdev #python]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Babalola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[20 principles I learned from 10 years of developing software]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ondrejsevcik/20-principles-i-learned-from-10-years-of-developing-software-5354</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ondrejsevcik/20-principles-i-learned-from-10-years-of-developing-software-5354"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T17:38:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#beginners #programming #career]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ondrej Sevcik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing Is Protecting Child Influencers From Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>63053fed3a62afdd20ead128</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/child-influencers-exploitation-legal-protection/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social media accounts featuring kids are more popular than ever. But labor and privacy laws haven't been updated to safeguard the young stars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ellen Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I got my first job as a developer by making simple projects seem big]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yuridevat/how-i-got-my-first-job-as-a-developer-by-making-simple-projects-seem-big-48oi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yuridevat/how-i-got-my-first-job-as-a-developer-by-making-simple-projects-seem-big-48oi"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T12:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#codenewbie #career #motivation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>𝕁𝕦𝕝𝕚𝕒 👩🏻‍💻</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why your website should be under 14kb in size]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shadowfaxrodeo/why-your-website-should-be-under-14kb-in-size-398n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shadowfaxrodeo/why-your-website-should-be-under-14kb-in-size-398n"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T00:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#todayilearned #webperf #webdev #performance]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathaniel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>