<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-10-13T10:50:37.974Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-10-13T10:50:37.974Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox’s new service gives you a burner phone number to cut down on spam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/13/23402171/firefox-relay-phone-masking-service-privacy-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/13/23402171/firefox-relay-phone-masking-service-privacy-security"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T10:37:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image: Firefox
    

  
Firefox Relay, a Mozilla service designed to hide your “real” email address by giving you virtual ones to hand out, is expanding to offer virtual phone numbers. In a blog post Mozilla product manager Tony Amaral-Cinotto explains that the relay service generates a phone number for you to give out to companies if you suspect they might use it to send you spam messages in the future, or if you think they might share it with others who will.
The idea is that handing out this alternative phone number makes it easier to block spam phone calls or texts in the future. You can either block all calls or texts sent to your relay number, or just block specific contacts. Importantly it lets you keep your “real” phone number private, which is...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Search for a Pill That Can Help Dogs—and Humans—Live Longer]]></title>
        <id>633de7e0fe6027f6ad16e5bd</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-search-for-a-pill-for-dog-and-human-longevity/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People have been searching for a fountain of youth for thousands of years. Celine Halioua thinks she’s found one—for canines. Be patient, we’re next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Simonite</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s an early look at Android’s app archiving feature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/13/23402141/google-android-archive-app-feature-leak</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/13/23402141/google-android-archive-app-feature-leak"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T09:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The feature should display how much storage space you can save by archiving an application instead of having to completely uninstall it. | Image: Google / @AssembleDebug
    

  
While we’ve been waiting to hear more about Google’s upcoming tool that “archives” certain apps to help free up space on your device, @AssembleDebug has managed to activate the feature ahead of its release (via Android Police).
Google first announced archiving earlier this year, claiming it can help users free up around 60 percent of their device’s storage for apps without having to completely delete them. In the screenshots shared by AssembleDebug, it appears that the tool will be built into the Google Play Store, allowing users to select between two options when they attempt to uninstall an application. The standard uninstall option is still present alongside a new ‘Archive’ option, which will whisk the app away into a separate...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony and Honda plan to start selling their electric cars in the US in 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/13/23402157/sony-honda-electric-vehicles-evs-timeline-sales-2026</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/13/23402157/sony-honda-electric-vehicles-evs-timeline-sales-2026"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T08:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sony’s prototype Vision-S 02 SUV, unveiled at CES 2022 as a platform for developing Sony’s EV technology.  | Image: Sony
    

  
Sony and Honda have announced that they plan to start selling their jointly-developed electric vehicles in the US in early 2026. 
The US has been chosen as the first market because of its well-developed taste for EVs. The cars will then go on sale in Japan later the same year, and then, perhaps, in Europe. Preorders for the vehicles will open in 2025, with sales and vehicle customization pushed through online channels.
The two Japanese companies announced they would be working together on a new 50-50 venture earlier this year, with the company later named Sony Honda Mobility. The alliance is intended to unite Honda’s expertise in car manufacture with Sony’s prowess in the fields of sensors, software, and entertainment. The companies hope...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Office will become Microsoft 365 in major brand overhaul]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/13/23402155/microsoft-office-microsoft-365-rename-branding-changes</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/13/23402155/microsoft-office-microsoft-365-rename-branding-changes"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T08:35:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image: Microsoft
    

  
Microsoft is making a major change to its Microsoft Office branding. After more than 30 years, Microsoft Office is being renamed “Microsoft 365” to mark the software giant’s collection of growing productivity apps. While Office apps like Excel, Outlook, Word, and PowerPoint aren’t going away, Microsoft will now mostly refer to these apps as part of Microsoft 365 instead of Microsoft Office.
Microsoft has been pushing this new branding for years, after renaming Office 365 subscriptions to Microsoft 365 two years ago, but the changes go far deeper now. “In the coming months, Office.com, the Office mobile app, and the Office app for Windows will become the Microsoft 365 app, with a new icon, a new look, and even more features,” explains a F...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intro to Array in JavaScript.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jindalkeshav82/intro-to-array-in-javascript-3e75</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jindalkeshav82/intro-to-array-in-javascript-3e75"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T08:31:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. Introduction
Syntax
const variable_name= [//"data"];

2. Its importance
NOTE
3. Array length
const cars= ['BMW', 'Audi', 'Mercedes'];
console.log(cars.length)

Output for above example is:
const laptops = ['Lenovo', 'Dell', 'HP'];
console.log(laptops.length)

output:
4. Array Push
const fruits= ['Apple', 'Mango', 'Banana'];
fruits.push('Orange');
console.log(fruits)

Output:
["Apple", "Mango", "Banana", "Orange"]
In above example, an array named fruits was created and in statement 2, using push keyword, 'orange' was added in the list.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Jindal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create your first PR 🎉: Hacktoberfest 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sadeedpv/create-your-first-pr-hacktoberfest-2022-34pi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sadeedpv/create-your-first-pr-hacktoberfest-2022-34pi"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T08:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a beginner who is looking to contribute to open-source? Are you confused about where to start?
Open-Source-for-All is a GitHub repo where you could learn to contribute to open-source projects through a step-by-step tutorial.
https://github.com/Sadeedpv/Open-Source-for-All
Open-Source-for-All


Using this repository, you will have a comprehensive guide on how to contribute to open-source projects on GitHub. If you have any doubts, you can always raise a question in discussion.
101-Programming-resources is a GitHub repo where you can get 101 completely free programming resources that could potentially enhance your coding skills. Feel free to add your own resources to the list by forking the repository.


  
  
  Thanks for your time and I hope you found this helpful and would consider contributing to the project 🎉🎊]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sadeedpv</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting a web3 job as a developer]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thenuelgeek/getting-a-web3-job-as-a-developer-5436</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thenuelgeek/getting-a-web3-job-as-a-developer-5436"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T08:07:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By the start of 2020, the ledger size had surpassed 200 GB.
The web3 ecosystem has seen a rise in talent scouting in recent years, and as a result, many individuals with expertise in industries such as health, finance, cyber, government, etc. have entered the blockchain industry. 
This article will mostly discuss and relate to the context of developers, although the knowledge and information learned from it may be used in a variety of professions in web3. 
I decided to transition from being a graphic designer (Brand Identity Designer) to a blockchain developer around this time in 2021. There have been several stages, from managing a lot of information to learning the basics of programming, which has nothing to do with visual design, but that's a gist for another day. Obtaining a full-time …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nuel geek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steampunk Spotter — Assisted Automation Writing tool for your Ansible Playbooks.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/steampunk-spotter</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/steampunk-spotter"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T07:28:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set up Facebook Conversion API on Shopify]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gloriamaldonado/how-to-set-up-facebook-conversion-api-on-shopify-20cd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gloriamaldonado/how-to-set-up-facebook-conversion-api-on-shopify-20cd"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T07:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having accuracy problems tracking data through Facebook Pixel? Hold on: It’s time to sing the Facebook Conversion API’s praises as it will help you secure much better results in no time. 
Your browser-based, vintage Facebook Pixel fails to deliver accurate and consistent data due to ad-blockers, cookie blockers, etc. because it works on the browser side. On top of all that, the latest iOS updates put you in a tight spot when it comes to tracking & monitoring data through Facebook Pixel. 
The Facebook Conversion API comes to the rescue, though. It works on the server side and gets all your purchase data in the back end, providing much better results at the end of the day. 
Here, I’ll help you to set it up on your Shopify store - with no additional apps required. 
There are a couple of thing…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloria W. Maldonado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moni Alpha Report — Daily web3 report with fresh and early alpha projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/moni-alpha-report</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/moni-alpha-report"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T07:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://alpha.getmoni.io/?promoc... (for the first 25 subscribers).

Come to the Discord Smart Party – https://discord.gg/getmoni
Subscribe to the Alpha Report – https://alpha.getmoni.io/
Want to say Hi? garri@getmoni.io
🫡
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What you need to know about compiling code]]></title>
        <id>70247 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/compiling-code"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What you need to know about compiling code
Alan Smithee
Thu, 10/13/2022 - 03:00

            
Source code must be compiled in order to run, and in open source software everyone has access to source code. Whether you've written code yourself and you want to compile and run it, or whether you've downloaded somebody's project to try it out, it's useful to know how to process source code through a compiler, and also what exactly a compiler does with all that code.
Build a better mousetrap
We don't usually think of a mousetrap as a computer, but believe it or not, it does share some similarities with the CPU running the device you're reading this article on. The classic (non-cat) mousetrap has two states: it's either set or released. You might consider that on (the kill bar is set and stores po…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Smithee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asynchronous programming in Rust]]></title>
        <id>70228 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/asynchronous-programming-rust"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asynchronous programming in Rust
Stephan Avenwedde
Thu, 10/13/2022 - 03:00

            
Asynchronous programming: Incredibly useful but difficult to learn. You can't avoid async programming to create a fast and reactive application. Applications with a high amount of file or network I/O or with a GUI that should always be reactive benefit tremendously from async programming. Tasks can be executed in the background while the user still makes inputs. Async programming is possible in many languages, each with different styles and syntax. Rust is no exception. In Rust, this feature is called async-await.
While async-await has been an integral part of Rust since version 1.39.0, most applications depend on community crates. In Rust, except for a larger binary, async-await comes with zero costs.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephan Avenwedde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beautiful LinkedIn Carousel Generator — Create beautiful LinkedIn carousels easily and for free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/beautiful-linkedin-carousel-generator</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/beautiful-linkedin-carousel-generator"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T06:44:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://www.linkedin.com/in/anki...
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burnims Drive — Simple & Powerful Drive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/burnims-drive</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/burnims-drive"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T06:42:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Idea Validation by Adstra — Otherworldly personalized tips on idea validation, biweekly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/idea-validation-by-adstra</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/idea-validation-by-adstra"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T06:38:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mouseflow — Behavior analytics for optimal website UX]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/mouseflow-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/mouseflow-2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T06:38:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plaid Identity Verification — Verify users globally in as little as 10 seconds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/plaid-identity-verification</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/plaid-identity-verification"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T06:28:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一日一技 | 怎样将 iPhone 备份保存到 Mac 的外部存储设备]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76016</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76016"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T06:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

一、问题描述
前段时间碰到一个问题，我 iPhone 背板碎了，需要走 AppleCare 交给苹果返厂维修，而我的 iPhone 是 512GB 的，在备份数据时候麻烦了，我笔记本本身就是 512GB 空间的，肯定不够用呀。
而备份 iPhone 默认的存储位置是在本机的硬盘上，我有个 14T 的硬盘，那么如何将默认的备份位置改到外部存储设备上呢。

二、如何设置备份位置到外部存储器
默认的备份位置在下面这个目录
~/Library/Application Support/MobileSync/Backup
其目录是这样的，Backup 里面就是你的每个设备每次的备份记录

我们要做的就是将这个位置映射到你的移动硬盘上去。
1. 确定你的移动硬盘位置
你需要知道自己硬盘的完整文件路径：

打开终端，
输入 cd 然后将你的硬盘图标拖到终端中，就会看到它的路径了
回车进入到移动硬盘目录下，指令 ls -al 能看到硬盘中的所有文件（图片中的 ll 是我自定义的一个指令）
我的就是 /Volumes/Kyle 14TB/ （在终端的路径需要转义空格，所以能看到终端中名字空格前面有个 \）

2. 移动硬盘中新建一个备份文件夹
在你的移动硬盘中新建一个备份文件夹，用于存储接下来的手机备份文件。
mkdir Backup
此时能看到目录中多出一个名为 Backup 的文件夹
 

进入这个文件夹并展示它的绝对路径
cd Backup
pwd
能看到我的这个文件夹的绝对路径是 /Volumes/Kyle 14TB/Backup，这个会在下…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青枫</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Wallpaper Does Not Exist — AI generated wallpapers and background images.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/this-wallpaper-does-not-exist</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/this-wallpaper-does-not-exist"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T06:13:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Styling the recent posts - part 6]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dailydevtips1/styling-the-recent-posts-part-6-637</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dailydevtips1/styling-the-recent-posts-part-6-637"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T06:12:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that we have the intro header styled let's look at the rest of the homepage.
There are two sections left here: the recent posts and the featured work section.
There are some things to note here:
The section header is a recurring element
The recent posts section has a different background
With that said, let's get started on the first one.
Let's start by adding a new component to keep things organized.
recentPosts.js file in my components structure.
Let's bootstrap the main elements.
export default function RecentPosts() {
  return (
    <section className='bg-blue-100'>
      <div className='max-w-4xl mx-auto py-12'>header</div>
    </section>
  );
}

This will already render the blue section with a smaller container inside.
It already looks like the image below:

As mentioned, the sec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bongers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whispering Dubverse, Powered by OpenAI — Generate English Subtitles for videos in any language!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/whispering-dubverse-powered-by-openai</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/whispering-dubverse-powered-by-openai"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T05:39:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy containerized workloads with Amazon Lightsail]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/deploy-containerized-workloads-with-amazon-lightsail-m05</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/deploy-containerized-workloads-with-amazon-lightsail-m05"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T04:38:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Amazon Lightsail


Amazon Lightsail is an easy-to-use cloud platform that provides everything you need to build an app or website with an affordable monthly fee.

Lightsail Containers, announced at re:Invent 2020 , aims to make it easy for you to build container-based apps and websites. To deploy containers in Lightsail, you create a container service that only specifies a few parameters, its performance, and its scope.
AWS manages the compute, network, and traffic management for you. You can deploy up to ten containers in a container service, and one of them can be chosen as the public endpoint. Lightsail provides a secure, load-balanced HTTPS endpoint to access the public endpoint.
You can create a website or app with just a few clicks. 
Automatically configure your netwo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MakendranG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best deals of Amazon’s fall Prime Day event]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/23400318/amazon-prime-deals-best-sale-tech-tablets-tvs-earbuds-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/23400318/amazon-prime-deals-best-sale-tech-tablets-tvs-earbuds-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T04:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nicholas Barclay / The Verge
    

  
Amazon’s Prime Early Access Sale, its second Prime Day event of 2022, is drawing to a close. That means it’s the last chance to take advantage of many of these deals. Our entire team is continuing to scour Amazon’s catalog high and low to find the best tech deals for you, including the great ones, and even some of the “hey, that ain’t bad” variety.
While it’s possible some of these deals may linger a little longer than the official end date, most of them are set to expire in less than a few hours, and may not return until Black Friday and Cyber Monday come around next month. So, get a head start on your holiday shopping, pick up that big-ticket item you’ve been patiently waiting for, or jump on a fun impulse purchase (we won’t tell...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GestureSign – 开源鼠标手势工具，支持触摸版、触摸屏、触控笔、鼠标[Windows]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43604</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/gesturesign/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T03:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GestureSign 是一款开源的 Windows 电脑鼠标手势工具，同时支持触控板、触摸屏、触控笔、鼠标，自定义度很高，支持全局手势、指定应用手势，可以发送指令、快捷键、运行程序等。@Appinn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MetMate — MetMate is an AI-powered collaboration meeting platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/metmate</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/metmate"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T02:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best tablet and phone deals from Amazon’s October Prime Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/23398415/amazon-prime-deals-best-tablet-phone-early-access-sale-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/23398415/amazon-prime-deals-best-tablet-phone-early-access-sale-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T02:35:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It doesn’t get much better than the Pixel 6A selling for $329. | Photo by Vjeran Pavic / The Verge
    

  
You don’t want to sleep on Amazon’s Prime Early Access Sale if you’re looking for deals on tech products, particularly phones or tablets. Now through the remainder of today, October 12th, you’ll be able to save a good amount of cash on some unlocked Pixel phones, a few of Apple’s latest iPads, and a bevy of Amazon-branded Fire tablets. It’s not a total who’s who of a deal event like Black Friday and Cyber Monday — there aren’t really any iPhone deals — but there are more than enough deals to make it worth putting together this post.
If you’re looking for our main post on Prime Early Access Sale deals, we’ve got you covered here. And if you want to see all of our coverage, including posts on individual products we think are worth your...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gatekeep.xyz — Firewall for Crypto Wallets.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/gatekeep-xyz</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/gatekeep-xyz"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T02:32:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://gatekeep.xyz
Twitter: https://twitter.com/gatekeepxyz
Github: https://github.com/gatekeepxyz
Methodology Article: https://gatekeepxyz.medium.com/t...
White Paper & Documentation: https://docs.gatekeep.xyz
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Community Catalog by Community Hunt — Discover 1500+ great communities across 20+ domains]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-community-catalog-by-community-hunt</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-community-catalog-by-community-hunt"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T02:31:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Book Worm — Build better reading habits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-book-worm</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-book-worm"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T02:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best Amazon Prime Day deals under $25]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/23392608/amazon-prime-best-cheap-deals-under-25-early-access-sale-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/23392608/amazon-prime-best-cheap-deals-under-25-early-access-sale-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T02:19:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s premium Fire Stick 4K Max and mid-range Fire Stick 4K streaming dongles look identical, though the latter is currently discounted to just $24.99. | Photo by Chris Welch / The Verge
    

  
Day two of Amazon’s Prime Early Access sale is under way, and while all the attention may be on big-ticket items like TVs, laptops, or wearables, we know not everyone can throw money around on that kind of stuff on a whim. There are also deals going on that can appeal to any tech fiend on a tight budget, so we’re pooling together all the best deals under $25 that we can find.
But you’d be remiss to think of these deals as just “cheap stuff.” We carefully comb through the myriad sales to find budget-friendly items that are worth your time and dollars, even at these lower-stakes prices: like a 4K-capable Fire TV Stick or a small and lightweight wireless earbuds. Frankly, sometimes it’s these inexpensive buys that can be some of the...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best TV deals from Amazon’s fall Prime Day event]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/23391507/amazon-prime-early-access-sale-best-tv-deals-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/23391507/amazon-prime-early-access-sale-best-tv-deals-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T02:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LG’s C2 OLED is one of the many TVs available at a discount during Amazon’s Prime Early Access Sale. | Photo by Chris Welch / The Verge
    

  
Amazon’s Prime Early Access Sale is providing yet another opportunity to get a fantastic discount on a 4K TV. If you’ve been scouting for deals in the lead-up to Black Friday, this is a week when you’ll want to be paying attention. Right now, we’re seeing some big price cuts on all sorts of smart TV models, ranging in size, streaming platform, and display (QLED, OLED, etc.). This roundup includes deals that are exclusive to Prime members as well as some that are available from Best Buy, Walmart, Target, and wherever else we find good discounts.


The best Prime Day TV deals



LG’s 48-inch A1 OLED is a stellar value if you want an OLED, but don’t need the high-end features that can cause the price to soar. While it costs $946.99 for...

  
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best gaming deals from fall Prime Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/23393295/amazon-prime-deals-best-game-gaming-console-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/23393295/amazon-prime-deals-best-game-gaming-console-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T02:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best deals on gaming accessories you can find during Prime Day Early Access | Photo by Cameron Faulkner / The Verge
    

  
Amazon’s Prime Day Early Access Sale is here for another day, so let's scope out some sweet deals on gaming headsets, keyboards, and other cool accessories. Whether you’re gaming on a console or PC, there are plenty of awesome odds and ends to round out your setup at home. For a better view of what’s currently on sale make sure to check out our best deals from Amazon’s Prime Early Access sale. 
We’re not holding our breath for discounts on next-gen consoles like the PlayStation 5 or Xbox Series X, but we’re already finding great deals on gaming keyboards from Razer, HyperX headsets, and Bluetooth controllers from 8BitDo. Of course, we’ll be looking out for deals on anything that can make your gaming experience just a little more awesome....
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Beginner’s Guide to Big O Notation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jstats/a-complete-beginners-guide-to-big-o-notation-56lh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jstats/a-complete-beginners-guide-to-big-o-notation-56lh"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T01:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since in programing there can be thousands of ways to solve a problem, how do you tell which one is the 'best' or let say that there is a function that is implanted in two different ways one with loops the other way by recursion which one of those ways should be the use in the function? That is where Big O comes in it a system of find out which algorithm would take longer to run and understand. The algorithm that takes less amount of time and less complex to understand is going to win.
Big O uses numbers to tell which algorithm is excellent and which ones need to be though again.
The reason for even using Big O is not only for job interviews but also when there are bigger datasets as performance matters at that point. Since there are a lot of data, the algorithms that take an hour to sort …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Stathopulos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sign In with Solana - Authenticate Users with their Phantom Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thirdweb/sign-in-with-solana-authenticate-users-with-their-phantom-wallet-4b21</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thirdweb/sign-in-with-solana-authenticate-users-with-their-phantom-wallet-4b21"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T01:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


In this guide, we are going to use thirdweb auth to add sign in with Solana to our Dapps!
Before we get started, below are some helpful resources where you can learn more about the tools we will use in this guide.
View project source code
Solana SDK
Getting Started with Solana
Let's get started!
Sign-in with Solana allows you to securely log in using a wallet and verify the wallet on the backend! We are going to use Thirdweb Auth which uses the very popular JWT standard! JSON Web Token (JWT) is an open standard that defines a compact and self-contained way for securely transmitting information between parties as a JSON object.
I am going to use the Next typescript solana starter template for this guide.
If you are following along with the guide, you can create a project with…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Avneesh Agarwal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should we hire junior developer advocates?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/blackgirlbytes/should-we-hire-junior-developer-advocates-13m2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/blackgirlbytes/should-we-hire-junior-developer-advocates-13m2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T01:08:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A common debate in Developer Relations is whether or not we should hire junior developer advocates. While many may adamantly say no to hiring junior developer advocates, my answer is yes.  YES – and instead of questioning whether or not we should hire them, we should strategize how to hire and support them. 
However, the concerns are valid. Often underestimated, Developer Relations and Developer Advocacy work requires effort and high-level skills. People in these departments are often responsible for business strategy, sharing technical knowledge, maintaining empathy, managing community, educating, and creating content. With all of these responsibilities in mind, many organizations lean toward hiring experienced developer advocates because they’re nervous to hire someone who doesn’t have a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rizèl Scarlett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[19 Best Deals From Best Buy’s Flash Sale (2022): Headphones, TVs, Apple Devices]]></title>
        <id>6345d9710b299b05896f7c21</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-buy-flash-sale-prime-day-rival-sale-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T00:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon isn’t the only one in a prime position to unleash killer discounts on smart TVs, headphones, and Apple devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Jancer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[37 Best Prime Day Deals Under $50 (2022): Cheap Tablets, Streaming Devices, and iPhone Cases]]></title>
        <id>62bc601330b57f91eba20c7c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-amazon-prime-day-deals-under-50-2022-6/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T00:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are the best bargains to scratch your shopping itch without breaking the bank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Medea Giordano, Gear Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tackle long running tasks with Java threads]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/smuhammed/handle-long-running-tasks-with-java-threads-4ekl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/smuhammed/handle-long-running-tasks-with-java-threads-4ekl"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T00:04:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Long running tasks need a special way of handling which user have not to wait until these tasks finished, our get benefit of CPU power and parallel processing long running tasks to finished faster.
A thread is a path of program execution, and JVM allows that multiple paths/threads to work concurrently and not interfere each other.

As we said before a thread is a path of exaction, and any piece of logic have to run as part of thread as below image.

The Main thread is responsible for executing logic inside main method and execution have to go through line by line and not to move to next until finishing current one. As above image there is a long running task there, and if Main thread is responsible for executing this logic the result will not be shown until this method finis…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sameh Muhammed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[84 Absolute Best Prime Day Deals (2022): Prime Early Access Sale]]></title>
        <id>62bef56c06a26f633de99ff8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-prime-day-deals-2022-9/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T23:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Prime Early Access Sale is here. From Alexa-powered Echo Dots to laptops, here are all the greatest discounts we’ve found.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gear Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The HTML 5 <Dialog /> Tag: The easiest way to create modal.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/frantchessico/the-html-5-tag-the-easiest-way-to-do-modal-8na</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/frantchessico/the-html-5-tag-the-easiest-way-to-do-modal-8na"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T23:25:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HTML5 dialog tag is the easiest way to create a modal. All you need to do is add the tag to your page and you're done. You can then style the dialog with CSS and add behaviors to it with JavaScript.
A dialog tag in HTML is used to create a pop-up dialog box on a web page.
dialog tag defines a dialog box or window. This element can be used to display an alert message, a confirmation message, or anything that requires the user to respond.
First let's create 3 files: index.html, main.js and style.css.


In index.html write this code:




<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en">
<head>
    <meta charset="UTF-8">
    <meta http-equiv="X-UA-Compatible" content="IE=edge">
    <meta name="viewport" content="width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0">
    <meta name="author" content="Francisco Inoque">
   …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco  Inoque</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beginner Bank — Product design financing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/beginner-bank</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/beginner-bank"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T23:22:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://BeginnerBank.com. 

If you're a developer or founder, you may have design talent on your team already or you don't. We're here for those who don't and know they need it for product-led growth. 

You can find design everywhere. And there are countless design tools anyone can use. But you can't always find good designers, especially a team of principal product designers who are:
1) available, and
2) affordable

So you end up shipping something people need but don't quite want because you have't dialed in its desirability. And to get that, you may just need principal product design.

We can help. But first, a little background:

In January, 2022, Ethos acquired the Tomorrow app I co-founded. Since then, I've been working with Joshua Martens (Tomorrow's design lead) to test this hypoth…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collection.xyz — #1 NFT liquidity incentive protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/collection-xyz</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/collection-xyz"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T23:16:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rank Tracker — The most affordable rank checking software for SEO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/rank-tracker-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/rank-tracker-2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T23:05:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create useful noise patterns with Academy award winning Ken Perlin 🏆🎲]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thormeier/create-useful-noise-patterns-with-academy-award-winning-ken-perlin-3fc6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thormeier/create-useful-noise-patterns-with-academy-award-winning-ken-perlin-3fc6"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T23:04:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Randomness is weird. Apart from the fact that true randomness on computers can only be achieved with either really complex devices or fish tanks, it just doesn't look appealing, either.
Consider this piece of code:
<canvas id="c" width="640" height="360" />

<script>
const canvas = document.querySelector('#c')

const paintGreyPixel = (canvas, x, y, grayScale) => {
  const context = canvas.getContext('2d')
  context.fillStyle = `rgba(0, 0, 0, ${grayScale})`
  context.fillRect(x, y, 1, 1)
}

for (let x = 0; x < 640; x++) {
  for (let y = 0; y < 360; y++) {
    paintGreyPixel(canvas, x, y, Math.random())
  }
}
</script>

What it does, is to paint every single pixel in a random grey scale. Math.random() combined with rgba and a black color results in a random shade of grey. And that's the resu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pascal Thormeier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[27 Best Prime Day Deals on Amazon Devices (2022): Early Access Sale]]></title>
        <id>62bdc4a0042ab1ffde99c523</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-amazon-device-deals-prime-day-2022-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T22:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Echo smart displays and speakers to Kindles and Fire tablets, snag the retailer’s own hardware on sale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brenda Stolyar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Machine Learning Model in Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-machine-learning-model-in-rust/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-machine-learning-model-in-rust/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T22:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning is a really interesting concept in computer programming. It involves using data to train a computer program to carry out tasks.  During the process, the program learns from data by discovering patterns. This reduces the need for programmers to hard code rules in some applications. Languages like]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chigozie Oduah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Email Alias – How to Set Up a Professional Email for Free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/email-alias-set-up-a-professional-email-for-free/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/email-alias-set-up-a-professional-email-for-free/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T22:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I needed to log in to AWS. But my main email address was rejected. Apparently I'd done this in the past and the account had been irreversibly deleted.  No reset option – just a message saying the account was permanently deleted: There are about a million ways to get]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[54 Best Prime Day Kitchen and Home Deals (2022): Vacuums, Mattresses, Cookware]]></title>
        <id>62bf1f687c12fa62407fc2ca</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-amazon-prime-day-smart-home-kitchen-deals-2022-5/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrade your digs with Amazon price cuts on cooking gadgets, TVs, vacuums, and air purifiers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haley Sprankle, Gear Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[21 Best Prime Day Apple Deals (2022): Amazon Prime Early Access Sale]]></title>
        <id>62cec9aec3b9c7c6435ad287</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/apple-devices-prime-day-deals-2022-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T21:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From MacBooks to iPads to MagSafe accessories, we’ve rounded up the best discounts on the company’s finest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brenda Stolyar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100,000 Humans That Don't Exist — Full-body model photos for your projects. Free & worry-free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/100-000-humans-that-don-t-exist</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/100-000-humans-that-don-t-exist"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T21:16:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet 100,000 AI-born people!

• Super realistic yet synthetic humans
• Diverse skin tones, various poses and looks
• 100% worry-free
• Compliant with GDPR, CCPA, and similar regulations
• No likeness rights
• No model releases required

Full-body photos can do much more than just faces. Use them wherever you want: in mockups, ads, games, or other projects. Tell us how you can use them and what you need, and we'll put the most wanted features on our roadmap.

What’s inside? 100,000 generated humans as a pack of JPEG pictures with white backgrounds. If you need high-res images with transparent backgrounds or need something special, drop us a message.

Is it really free? Yes. Totally free for non-commercial use as long as you include link attribution back to https://generated.photos/, so that more people can find generated humans. 

What’s next? Different ages, body types, custom clothes and more. So, follow us on Twitter for updates.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[22 Best Deals From Walmart's Rollbacks & More Rival Prime Day Sale (2022)]]></title>
        <id>63445f2cf93a1584dc57f363</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/walmart-deals-prime-day-2022-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T21:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Score major deals on big-screen TVs, wireless earbuds, and more as the retailer tries to steal Amazon's thunder.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Jancer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carmack: “There’s a bunch that I’m grumpy about” in virtual reality]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889582</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889582"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T21:07:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lonely lecture as a VR avatar is a far cry from last year's "thousands of people" goal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[68 Best Prime Day Laptop, Phone, TV, and Tech Deals (2022): Prime Early Access Sale]]></title>
        <id>633d87847e8d589e28665ad0</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-amazon-prime-day-laptop-tv-phones-tech-deals-2022-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a ton of gadgetry on sale for Amazon’s Early Access sale. These are all the top offers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Speight, Parker Hall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Apple services and apps are rolling out on Windows 11 and Xbox]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889516</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889516"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T20:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Music for Xbox is here now; Music and TV for Windows will come later.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft fights to save Activision merger, says Sony protest is “self-serving”]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889553</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889553"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T19:42:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft says UK relied on Sony's "exaggerated" claims about Call of Duty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok wants to be Amazon, plans US fullfillment centers and poaches staff]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889530</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889530"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T18:33:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok to launch live shopping in the US over the holidays.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Belanger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kids 5-11 can now get the bivalent, BA.5-targeting COVID booster]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889533</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889533"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T18:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Federal officials urge Americans to get their boost by Halloween.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Visualization Tools – 2022 Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-visualization-tools-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-visualization-tools-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T17:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data visualization is the process of interpreting or representing data graphically. Generally, it is the graphical or visual representation of data using charts, tables, histograms, and other info-graphics.  Data plays a major role in any type of organization. Data visualization helps us understand certain trends and insights, and make]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Death to passwords: Beta passkey support comes to Chrome and Android [Updated]]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889431</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889431"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T17:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big Tech's cross-platform password replacement arrives in the Google ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nasal COVID vaccine blows clinical trial, flinging researchers back to the lab]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889484</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889484"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T17:17:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The trial used the same vaccine formula as the AstraZeneca vaccine given intramuscularly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webb captures truly strange set of rings built by massive stars]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889489</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889489"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T17:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past 120 years, stellar winds have built concentric circles of dust.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pixel 7 and Pixel 7 Pro Review: Even Better Value]]></title>
        <id>633f9b397e8d589e28665b11</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/google-pixel-7-pixel-7-pro/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These phones remain unbeatable when it comes to sheer value.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian Chokkattu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discovery Phase Checklist 2.0 — Your assistant in the world of software discovery phase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/discovery-phase-checklist-2-0-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/discovery-phase-checklist-2-0-2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T17:03:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pixel Watch review: Beautiful, fast, and way too expensive]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1887656</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1887656"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T17:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It could be better, but it might be good enough for a wearables-starved ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Polestar 3 SUV will cost $83,900 “loaded,” goes on sale Q4 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889421</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889421"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T17:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Production of the new EV starts in China in 2023, then South Carolina in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pixel Watch Review (2022): Better Late Than Never]]></title>
        <id>633f9b3892468d5a8855ae03</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/google-pixel-watch/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fitbit-enabled smartwatch lacks SpO2 and auto workout tracking, but its accuracy, elegance, and comfort more than make up for those oversights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian Chokkattu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zurau — Open Source analytics web app to visualize key Kafka metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/zurau</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/zurau"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T16:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://github.com/oslabs-beta/z...
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden gambles with global chip supply by halting US firms’ operations in China]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889454</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889454"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T16:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Power of US export curbs could diminish quickly without other nations joining.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Belanger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altogic — Backend as a service platform to develop apps in minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/altogic</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/altogic"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T16:49:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://altogic.com
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA says the Artemis I mission will be ready to launch in one month]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889450</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889450"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T16:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Set your alarm for 7 minutes after midnight on November 14.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[如何在 Brave 浏览器中使用画中画模式]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15137-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15137-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brave 是一款出色的类似于 Chrome，但可 替代 Chrome 的网络浏览器。


Firefox 和 Brave 是我喜欢在 Linux 系统上使用的两种浏览器。两者都有不同的优势。

Firefox 比 Brave 做得更好的一件事就是画中画（PIP）模式，它适用于 YouTube、Netflix 和大多数流媒体网站。

Brave 也有画中画模式，但它是如此隐藏，以至于你觉得它根本没有 PIP 支持。

内置画中画适用于某些网站（如 YouTube），但可能不适用于其他网站（如 Prime Video）。不用担心！你可以为此使用专用扩展。

让我在本教程中展示这两种方法。

方法 1：在视频上双击右键

技巧是依次单击两次右键，你应该会看到画中画模式选项。

让我通过一个例子来说明这一点。在 Brave 中播放 YouTube 视频。现在右键单击视频。



再次右键单击。它应该在视频上，但不在上一个上下文菜单上，而在视频的其他地方。

现在你应该看到另一个带有画中画选项的上下文菜单。



选择画中画，视频将从窗口中弹出。你可以将其移动到浏览器中的任何位置。



当你使用其他应用时，你还可以让它在屏幕上的任何位置播放。



在最近的 Brave 版本中，你可以根据自己的喜好调整弹出窗口的大小。

我不明白为什么 Brave 把它隐藏成这样。为什么不突出它？

无论如何，这适用于 YouTube 等网站，但可能不适用于 Prime 视频。如果你愿意，你可以安装一个扩展。

方法 2：使用画中画扩展

谷歌提供了一个官方插件，可让你在谷歌 Chrome 中获得画中画功能。由于 Brave 基于 Chromium，你可以在 Brave 中使用相同的扩展。


画中画扩展


进入扩展页面并点击 “添加到 BraveAdd to Brave” 按钮。



当你单击它时，它会提示添加扩展的选项。



添加扩展后，你应该会在浏览器的右上角看到它。



播放视频时，单击该扩展图标，视频应该会弹出。

你能在 Brave 中启用 PIP 模式吗？

画中画模式已成为休闲流媒体消费的必备功能。我觉得奇怪的是，Brave 和其他浏览器没有足够重视它。 Firefox 处理得很好。

我希望这个快速的小技巧可以帮助你在 Brave 浏览器中获得 PIP 体验。你更喜欢这两种方法中的哪一种？右键单击还是扩展？


via: https://itsfoss.com/picture-in-picture-brave/

作者：Abhishek Prakash 选题：lkxed 译者：geekpi 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Formsort — Low code form builder helping startups increase conversion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/formsort</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/formsort"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T16:19:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[使用 Linux 的优势和劣势]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15136-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15136-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T16:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 是一个流行词，你到处都能听到与 Linux 相关的内容。人们在技术论坛上讨论它、Linux 是课程中的一部分；你最喜欢的 YouTube 技术主播在兴奋地展示构建他们的 Linux 内核；你在 Twitter 上关注的 10 倍效率开发者10x developers都是 Linux 粉丝。

基本上，Linux 无处不在，每个人都在谈论它，因此你可能会不自主地陷入到对错失了 “学习 Linux” 的不安中。

所以，你想知道 Linux 的优势是什么，以及它是否值得去学习。

在这篇文章中，我总结了很多 Linux 的优势和劣势。

如果你在选择 Linux 还是你喜欢的操作系统上犹豫不决，我们愿意为你提供一些帮助。


在开始之前，我们要指出的是，“Linux” 本身并不是一个操作系统，它的操作系统被称为 Linux 发行版，而且 Linux 的发行版有数百种。为简单起见，我将其称为 Linux 操作系统，而不是某个特定的 Linux 发行版。可以参考 这篇文章，来更好地理解这些东西。


使用 Linux 的优势

如果你想使用 Linux 替代现在的操作系统，那么只有当你了解 Linux 的优势，才会有意义。

如果 Linux 在你想要它做的事情上表现出色，你将永远都不会后悔你的决定。

不用购买许可证



你需要拥有苹果公司的设备，才能使用 macOS 作为日常使用；你需要拥有 Windows 许可证，才能使用微软的 Windows。

因此，你需要对这些东西进行一定的投资。但是，对于 Linux 呢？它是完全免费的！

与 Windows 和 macOS 相比，不仅仅是操作系统上的不同，Linux 上还有许多免费的软件包。

你无需支付许可证费用，就可以使用所有主流的 Linux 发行版。当然，你可以选择捐赠来支持该…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: “Thousands” of Intel layoffs planned as PC demand slows and revenues fall]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889397</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889397"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T15:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sales of consumer and server CPUs are down as pandemic-era demand slows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All the Best Prime Day Deals still running for Amazon’s Early Access sale [Updated]]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1888606</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1888606"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T15:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've sorted through Amazon's pre-holiday sale to find the stuff that's worth your time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Gaskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RTX 4090 review: Spend at least $1,599 for Nvidia’s biggest bargain in years]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1888249</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1888249"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T15:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our review also dives deeply into DLSS 3—and how it may affect future Nvidia GPUs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Machkovech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lab-Grown Human Brain Tissue Works in Rats]]></title>
        <id>63446d8054f8c6faa9d67d25</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/lab-grown-human-brain-tissue-works-in-rats/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tiny cell clusters called organoids integrated with the animals’ own tissue, a step toward developing sophisticated mini-models of the brain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Mullin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Docker and Kubernetes – Free Hands-On Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-docker-and-kubernetes-hands-on-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-docker-and-kubernetes-hands-on-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker and Kubernetes are important technologies that can help you scale your applications. Docker is a platform for packaging, deploying, and running applications in containers. Kubernetes is a system for managing containerized applications across a cluster of nodes. It provides basic mechanisms for deployment, maintenance, and scaling of applications. We]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Designer — Create stunning designs in a flash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/microsoft-designer</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/microsoft-designer"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:18:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://designer.microsoft.com/ and we'll let you know when you've got access. 😊 

Happy designing! 

If you have any questions about Designer, drop them below. We're excited to hear your thoughts. 🙌
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft takes AI image generation mainstream, strolling into ethics minefield]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1888780</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1888780"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:16:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft sidesteps AI-powered art debate, embraces image generation as a tool for creatives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement a Whitelist in Smart Contracts (ERC-721 NFT, ERC-1155, and others)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-whitelist-in-smartcontracts-erc-721-nft-erc-1155-and-others/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-whitelist-in-smartcontracts-erc-721-nft-erc-1155-and-others/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I will show you three ways you can create a whitelist in a smart contract. Here's what we'll discuss:  * On-chain whitelists  * Digital signatures  * Merkle trees All methods are available in the repo here [https://github.com/gapon2401/smartcontract-whitelist]. A whitelist is useful if you want]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Igor Gaponov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LeadQuest by DropFriends — No Bullshit. Just Leads.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/leadquest-by-dropfriends</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/leadquest-by-dropfriends"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:11:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Web Storage Works – Local vs Session Storage Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-web-storage-works/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-web-storage-works/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone who works with the web needs to store data for a later use. Backend developers have some powerful databases in their toolkit. But if you are a frontend developer, you can still store and process data using web storage. In this article, you'll learn what is a web storage,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tooba Jamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft’s Audio Dock adds ports, a woofer, & tweeters to your setup for $250]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1888972</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1888972"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[USB-C docking station opts for video conferencing features over a vast port selection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scharon Harding</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft whiffs a desperately needed internal refresh for the Surface Studio desktop]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1887744</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1887744"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A generation-old quad-core processor is doing this $4,300 desktop no favors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surface Laptop 5 gets a boost from new Intel CPUs, but AMD option is going away]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1887997</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1887997"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft refreshes its 13.5- and 15-inch laptops without reinventing them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surface Pro 9 comes in both Intel and Arm flavors, absorbing the Surface Pro X]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1888085</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1888085"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For this refresh, Microsoft works up the courage to remove the headphone jack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Surface Event October 2022: Surface Pro Laptop 5, Surface Pro 9, Surface Studio 2 Plus]]></title>
        <id>633f03f44bb7933eb61831d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/everything-microsoft-announced-surface-october-event-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Say hello to next-gen Surface laptops and a new app called Microsoft Designer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brenda Stolyar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Database Management Systems and SQL – Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dbms-and-sql-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dbms-and-sql-basics/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Database Management Systems and SQL are two of the most important and widely used tools on the internet today.  You use a Database Management System (DBMS) to store the data you collect from various sources, and SQL to manipulate and access the particular data you want in an efficient]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bikash Daga (Jain)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your Personal Brand as a Freelance Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/branding-for-developer-freelancers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/branding-for-developer-freelancers/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You probably didn’t get into freelance development to become a marketer.  You got into freelancing so you could work when you want, make more money, and control your life. But, if you haven’t realized it yet, building a career as a freelancer requires you to embrace more than just]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Cruz Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Webshop with Angular, Node.js, TypeScript, & Stripe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-webshop-with-angular-node-js-typescript-stripe/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-webshop-with-angular-node-js-typescript-stripe/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to build a webshop from scratch! We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build a webshop or e-commerce store using Angular/TypeScript, Express.js, and Stripe.  You will learn how to use Angular material and Tailwind to structure the UI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roku's Smart Camera Lets You Keep an Eye on Your Yard]]></title>
        <id>63445f3ef93a1584dc57f364</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/roku-smart-home-news-october-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The manufacturer of well-priced TV streaming devices has partnered with Wyze to release affordable cameras, smart plugs, and smart lights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Medea Giordano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What It Means to ‘Feel Normal’ Online]]></title>
        <id>632ae3b036c33c0247a2f0b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/psychology-data-surveillance-normality-personality/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A personalized, authentic experience is an unquestioned building block of digital infrastructure. But what does that really involve?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tung-Hui Hu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Symphony — You can't get any closer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/symphony-4</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/symphony-4"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T12:43:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://symphony.live/

🚧 For your benefit, make sure you check our Product Roadmap via http://feedback.symphony.live to know what is in store for Symhony.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[vitrina — Commercial real estate exchange for instant transactions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/vitrina</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/vitrina"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T12:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Packshot Maker by Instashot — Free product visuals using virtual shooting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/packshot-maker-by-instashot</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/packshot-maker-by-instashot"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T12:09:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MonitUp - Freelancer — Productivity measurement tool for freelancers.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/monitup-freelancer</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/monitup-freelancer"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T11:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@farukdurak is super excited to hear you :)
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CV Maker — Mobile application for resume creation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/cv-maker-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/cv-maker-2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T11:31:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一二三四，打开心智]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76149</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76149"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T11:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[现今社会高速发展，充满了不确定性。我们置身于时代的洪流中，被裹挟着不知冲向何处。诚然，时代给了我们更多的选择，同时也让我们更加迷茫，仿佛处在一个有无数岔路的迷宫里，不知道自己将走向何方。
「如何在不确定的风浪里，实现确定性的成长？」这应该是现今大多人所关注的问题吧。
关于成长，市面上有很多方法论，但它往往都不讲背后的原理。不知道大家是否也和我一样，看到一些方法或者教程，经常会收藏起来，跟练一段时间，但大多都是半途而废，坚持一阵子后又打回原形了。
为什么会这样呢？因为每个人的情况不同，适用的方法也不同。如果只是知其然不知其所以然，那只有不断地尝试各种方法，不断地去磨合，才能找到适合自身的。这个尝试的过程，其实就是通过外界的方法，来获得自身的反馈，从而更了解自己。
但如果我们换个角度，一开始就从了解自己出发，再剖析方法背后的原理，那是不是更容易找到适合自己的方法呢？所以我认为，知其然又知其所以然，反倒是一条捷径。
要了解自己，就得先知道我们的心智是怎么运作的。所谓「心智」，就像是大脑里一个可以不断升级的系统，包含了我们对外部世界的所有认知，也包括因此所造就的思维方式。我们的认知和感觉，其实也只是心智对外部世界的投射而已。
前不久出版的一本新书——《打开心智》，正是围绕「心智」这个概念展开的。兵书有云，「知己知彼，百战不殆」。书中先是阐述了大脑的四个基本原理，帮助我们了解心智是怎么运作的，此为「知己」；然后又围绕情绪、习惯、动力、学习、思考和创造等方面，剖析背后的原理，此为「知彼」。不仅如此，它还提供一套行之有效的方法，让我们能更好地实现自己的目标。所以，这是一本帮助我们认识自我、突破自我的书籍，知己知彼，我们才能更有效实现自我成长，去应对时代的不确定性。
书籍作者是李睿秋（Lachel），一名深度思考践行者，常年专注于心理学、认知科学与心智研究，同时也是虎嗅年度十大作者、36氪…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>1A君</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plushcap — Content analyzer for developer focused GTM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/plushcap</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/plushcap"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T11:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@mattmakai  on creating a very helpful repository for folks like us who are figuring out the GTM in the deep-tech space for developers.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prospectss 2.0 — 40+ Tools for Growth Marketing, LeadGen, Outreach & Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/prospectss-2-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/prospectss-2-0"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T11:23:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Chip Sanctions ‘Kneecap’ China’s Tech Industry]]></title>
        <id>63444b96136a8fc35853e3e7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/us-chip-sanctions-kneecap-chinas-tech-industry/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The toughest export restrictions yet cut off AI hardware and chip-making tools crucial to China’s commercial and military ambitions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Chip Sanctions ‘Kneecap’ China’s Tech Industry]]></title>
        <id>63444b96136a8fc35853e3e7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/us-chip-sanctions-kneecap-chinas-tech-industry/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The toughest export restrictions yet cut off AI hardware and chip-making tools crucial to China’s commercial and military ambitions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gas Drilling Is Disrupting Animal Migration]]></title>
        <id>6344484d7b75d692a43c0054</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/gas-drilling-is-disrupting-animal-migration/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists are investigating why large animals like the mule deer of Wyoming go where they go—and how humans can get out of their way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Barber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pet Symptom Checker — Answer any urgent questions related to your pet's health]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/pet-symptom-checker</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/pet-symptom-checker"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T10:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mindyjs React Icons — Popular remixicons library to use as React Component]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/mindyjs-react-icons</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/mindyjs-react-icons"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T10:22:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VocalRemover – 强大的在线音频处理工具：人声分离、变调、剪辑、合并、录音、卡拉OK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43598</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/vocalremover/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T10:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VocalRemover 是一款拥有中文界面的在线音频处理工具，主要用来进行人声分离，也支持变调、剪辑、合并、录音、卡拉OK 等功能。@appinn 感谢 @noshit 同学的推荐：https://]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Airbabble — Share your voice with the world with one tap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/airbabble</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/airbabble"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T09:33:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Talent Service — Automated recruitment platform that disrupts hiring agencies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/talent-service</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/talent-service"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T09:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #787 微软与 Meta 合作，将 Teams、Office、Windows 和 Xbox 带到 VR]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15135-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15135-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T08:46:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[微软与 Meta 合作，将 Teams、Office、Windows 和 Xbox 带到 VR

在今天的 Meta Connect 会议上，微软 CEO 萨提亚·纳德拉表示，该公司正在与 Meta 合作，将其最大的服务，Teams、Office、Windows，甚至 Xbox 云游戏，带到 Meta 的 Quest VR 头盔上。人们将能够直接从 Meta 的 Horizon 工作间加入 Teams 会议，也可以在 Quest VR 头盔里面使用 Windows 365，获得 Windows 的完整体验，包括所有个性化的应用程序、内容和设置。此外，微软还通过 PWA 技术将 Office 应用的 2D 版本带到 Quest VR 头盔。甚至，Xbox 云游戏也将进入 Quest VR 头盔，虽然不会像 Xbox 原生 VR 体验那样令人沉浸，但你将能够拿起 Xbox 控制器，在头盔内的巨大屏幕上玩这些游戏。


消息来源：The Verge



老王点评：微软的这一合作，对 Meta 的元宇宙愿景来说可谓一剂强心针。




美国能源科学网络 ESnet6 带宽升至 46Tbps

成立于 1986 年的美国能源科学网络 ESnet，旨在帮助美国能源部的科学家们打通旗下各个实验室，使之能够快速共享大量原始数据。它由横跨全美的 2.4 万公里的专用光缆组成。随着该网络完成 ESnet6 更新，美国最快的互联网带宽也飙升到了 46 Tbps。2021 年的时候，通过 ESnet 网络传输的数据量，就已经达到了惊人的 1.1 EB。不过，在实验性网络中的最高传输速度的记录是日本创造的 1 Pbps，即 1000 Tbps。


消息来源：伯克利实验室



老王点评：这要是传个小电影得多快啊~




新西兰计划对农场动物打嗝、撒尿征税

据央视新闻，新西兰政府 11 日提议对农场动物打嗝、撒尿排放的温室气体征税，以应对气候变化。新西兰政府表示，该项税收是世界首创，将从 2025 年开始征收，税价未定。新西兰约一半的温室气体排放来自农场，包括牛打嗝产生的甲烷和尿液中所含的一氧化二氮。此前，新西兰政府 2003 年提出征收农场动物的“放屁税”计划，遭到农场主反对，最终告吹。


消息来源：每经报



老王点评：不是没有道理，但是为什么我觉得这么搞笑。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Timeclock.Kiwi — A cloud time clock system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/timeclock-kiwi</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/timeclock-kiwi"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T07:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[使用 Topgrade 一次升级 Linux 中的各种软件包]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15134-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15134-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T07:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[更新 Linux 系统并没有那么复杂，不是吗？毕竟，要更新 Ubuntu 之类的发行版，你只需要使用 apt update 和 apt upgrade 就行。

如果所有的包都是通过一个包管理器安装的，就会是这样。

但现在情况不再如此。你有经典的 apt/dnf/pacman，还有 Snap、Flatpak、Appimages。不止于此，你还可以使用 PIP（用于 Python）和 Cargo（用于 Rust）安装应用。

使用 Node？ NPM 包需要单独更新。Oh My Zsh？需要单独更新。Vim 中的插件、Atom 等也可能不被 apt/dnf/pacman 覆盖。

你现在看到问题了吗？这就是名为 Topgrade 的新工具旨在解决的问题。

Topgrade：处理各种更新的单一程序

Topgrade 是一个 CLI 程序，它会检测你使用的工具，然后运行适当的命令来更新它们。



除了通常的 Linux 包管理器，它还可以检测和更新 Brew、Cargo、PIP、Pihole、Vim 和 Emacs 插件、R 软件包等。你可以在 维基页面 上查看支持的包列表。

Topgrade 的主要特点：


能够更新来自不同的包管理器的软件包，包括固件！

你可以如何控制更新包。

高度可定制。

甚至能够在更新包之前进行概览。


所以不要浪费任何时间，让我们跳到安装。

使用 Cargo 在 Linux 中安装 Topgrade

安装过程非常简单，因为我将使用 Cargo 包管理器。

我们已经有了 详细指南，其中包含设置 Cargo 包管理器的多种方法。所以我将在我的示例中使用 Ubuntu 来快速完成。

因此，让我们以最少方式安装依赖项以及 Cargo：

sudo apt install cargo libssl-dev pkg-config


安装 Cargo 后，使用给定的命令安装 Topgrade：

cargo install topgrade


它会抛出一个警告：



你只需添加 cargo 路径即可运行二进制文件。这可以通过给定的命令来完成，你需要使用你的用户名替换 sagar：

echo 'export PATH=$PATH:/home/sagar/.cargo/bin' >> /home/sagar/.bashrc


现在，重启系统，Topgrade 就可以使用了。但是等等，我们需要安装另一个包来更新 Cargo 以获取最新的包。

cargo install cargo-update


这样我们完成了安装。

使用 Topgrade

使用 Topgrade 非常简单。使用一个命令，就是这样：

topgrade





但这不会给你除了系统包之外的任何控制，但正如我所提到的，你可以将不想更新的仓库列入黑名单。

从 Topgrade 中排除包管理器和仓库

假设我想排除 Snap 和从默认包管理器下载的包，所以我的命令是：

topgrade --disable snap system




要进行永久更改，你必须在其配置文件中进行一些更改，这些更改可以通过给定的命令访问：

topgrade --edit-config


对于此示例，我排除了 Snap 和默认系统仓库：



试运行 Topgrade

评估将要更新的过时软件包总是一个好主意，我从 Topgrade 的整个目录中找到了这个最有用的选项。

你只需使用带有 -n 选项的 topgrade 命令，它就会生成过期软件包的摘要。

topgrade -n




检查需要更新的软件包的一种简洁方法。

总结

在使用 Topgrade 几周后，它成为了我的 Linux 武器库中不可或缺的一部分。 像大多数其他 Linux 用户一样，我只是通过我的默认包管理器更新包。 Python 和 Rust 包被完全忽略了。 感谢 Topgrade，我的系统现在完全更新了。

我知道这不是每个人都想使用的工具。那你呢？愿意试一试吗？


via: https://itsfoss.com/topgrade/

作者：Sagar Sharma 选题：lkxed 译者：geekpi 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy applications using Foreman ACD]]></title>
        <id>70215 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/deploy-applications-foreman-acd"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy applications using Foreman ACD
Maximilian Kolb
Wed, 10/12/2022 - 03:00

            
When you manage your IT infrastructure using Foreman and Katello, the smallest unit to operate on is generally a host. You can provision hosts, deliver versioned content, and set configurations. Using Foreman ACD, you can use your Foreman instance to deploy applications consisting of multiple services spanning multiple hosts. This blog post briefly introduces the Foreman ACD plugin and explains how it can help you deploy a Prometheus and Grafana stack. If you want to know more about deploying an ELK stack consisting of an Elasticsearch cluster and Kibana, look at Deploying an ELK Cluster with Application Centric Deployment.
Introduction to Foreman and Katello
You can use Foreman and Katello to manag…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maximilian Kolb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[了解开放组织的新途径]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15133-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15133-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T06:34:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[通过参与两个令人兴奋的新项目来庆祝开放组织社区的六周年。




2021 年 6 月 2 日，开放组织Open Organization社区庆祝其成立六周年。这是六年来（上百篇的）文章、（一系列的）书籍、（具有启发性的）对话、（我们所 喜欢的）教学和学习。我们非常自豪地成为一个充满活力的开放专家和领导者的社区，致力于将 开放原则 带到大大小小的组织。事实上，许多 开放组织大使Open Organization Ambassadors 以帮助他人变得更加开放为职业，我们的社区仍然致力于帮助各行业的领导者以开放的心态和行为融入他们的社区和环境中。

去年 是开放组织项目的一个 成长 和 发展 时期。今年，我们将在这一势头的基础上继续努力。今天，我们很自豪地介绍两项新的倡议——当然，也邀请你的参加。

开启，调整，开放

首先，我们很高兴地宣布：我们社区的工作有了一个全新的场所。OpenOrgTV。这不仅仅是一个新的平台。它也是另一种媒介的实验：视频。

在我们的频道上，我们将举办各种对话 —— 从深层次的书评到社区圆桌会议。首先，请查看“开放领导力对话Open Leadership Conversations”系列，其中包括对某些富有洞察力的领导者的采访，提供他们对根据开放原则进行领导的意义的观点。或者观看我们的 Q&A 式写作节目 “问大使Ask the Ambassadors”，由社区专家回答你关于组织文化和设计的问题。也想参与这个节目吗？在我们的 新的专门的论坛 中向社区成员提交你的问题。

整个月，我们都会介绍 开放组织大使Open Organization Ambassadors，让你终于可以看到他们的面孔，并听到你多年来阅读的故事、案例研究和采访背后的声音。

定义开放领导力

自从我们几年前发布它以来，开放组织定义Open Organizat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eclypse — ultimate translation tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/eclypse</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/eclypse"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T04:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CleverPDF – 44 个免费的 PDF 在线工具集：PDF 转 Word、提取图片、加密/解密、拆分、合并等]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43591</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/cleverpdf/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T04:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CleverPDF 是一款免费的在线 PDF 工具集，拥有 PDF 转文档、PDF 转图片、文档转 PDF、解密 PDF、拆分、合并等共计 44 个功能。@Appinn 感谢 @Sin.Yor. 同学]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Modern Health — Wellbeing Side by Side]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-modern-health</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-modern-health"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T03:18:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://www.themodernhealth.com....
(We are most optimised for Google Business Suite and Google personal accounts and recommend a Google Sign Up)

Videos:

https://youtu.be/rzmZHM-uD3M

Please send us your feedback on kanika@themodernhealth.com.au.

With love, 
Kanika
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Article2Image — Turn your article into a cover image with Stable Diffusion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/article2image</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/article2image"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T03:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's really simple:
1️⃣ Paste your article.
2️⃣ Our AI will summarize it.
3️⃣ Another AI will capture it.
✅ A cover image comes out that matches your article!

You can try it out for free 🥳

I do apologies for asking you to create an account. My previous launch was full of spam and cost me a lot of $$$. Hopefully, this will protect it hehe.

Let me know what you think!
❤️ Danny.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[使用 PostgreSQL 建立你的数据库]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15132-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15132-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T02:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PostgreSQL 是最灵活的数据库之一，并且它是开源的。


数据库是以一种有组织且灵活的方式存储信息的工具。电子表格在本质上就是一个数据库，但是图形化应用程序这一限制使得大多数的电子表格应用程序对程序员毫无用处。随着 边缘计算 和物联网设备成为重要的平台，开发者们需要更有效且轻量级的方法，来存储、处理、查询大量的数据。我最爱的一种组合是使用 Lua 连接 ostgreSQL 数据库。无论你使用什么编程语言，PostgreSQL 一定是数据库的绝佳选择，但是在使用 PostgreSQL 之前，首先你需要知道一些基本的东西。

安装 PostgreSQL

在 Linux 上安装 PostgreSQL，要使用你的软件库。在 Fedora，CentOS，Megeia 等类似的 Linux 版本上使用命令：

$ sudo dnf install postgresql postgresql-server


在 Debian， Linux Mint， Elementary 等类似的 Linux 版本上使用命令：

$ sudo apt install postgresql postgresql-contrib


在 macOs 和 Windows 上，可以从官网 postgresql.org 下载安装包。

配置 PostgreSQL

大多数发行版安装 PostgreSQL 数据库时没有启动它，但是为你提供了一个脚本或 systemd 服务，能够可靠地启动 PostgreSQL。但是，在启动 PostgreSQL 之前，必须创建一个数据库集群。

Fedora

在 Fedora，CentOS 等类似的版本上，PostgreSQL 安装包中提供了一个 PostgreSQL 配置脚本。运行这个脚本，可以进行简单地配置：

$ sudo /usr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Side-Venture Toolbox — Toolbox & Community for building side-income]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/side-venture-toolbox</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/side-venture-toolbox"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T01:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://www.thekevinjon.com/side...
My YouTube channel I referenced: https://www.youtube.com/channel/...
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Recognize a Phishing Email – And What to Do When You Get One]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-recognize-phishing-email/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-recognize-phishing-email/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T00:52:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know the drill: you open your email client and there is it an email saying that you will be in trouble if you do not follow certain instructions in short time, no questions asked. All it takes is a single click, and you're in trouble. This kind of email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Pixel 7 and Pixel 7 Pro Pack New Android VPN and Tensor G2, Titan M2 Chips]]></title>
        <id>634592230b299b05896f7c1c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/google-pixel-7-pixel-7-pro-tensor-g2-android-vpn/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T19:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company says it hardened the security of its new flagship phones—and plans to release a built-in Android VPN.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Success! NASA Says DART Really Clocked That Asteroid]]></title>
        <id>6340a75cf93a1584dc57f351</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/success-nasa-dart-dimorphos-asteroid/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T18:52:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two weeks after the spacecraft collided with Dimorphos, researchers determined that it knocked the space rock 32 minutes off its old orbit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramin Skibba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[List of 85+ Notion Templates — The best templates from your favorite creators]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/list-of-85-notion-templates</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/list-of-85-notion-templates"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T18:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@IAmPascio)
2. iNotion (@iNotionHQ)
3. Atul Anand (@AtulACleaver)
4. Easlo (@heyeaslo)
5. Dave (@_heydave)

You mark certain templates as favorites and easily organize them into categories via tags.

Get started with Notion today by grabbing the best templates!
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AISEO ART —  Turn your imagination into amazing art]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/aiseo-art</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/aiseo-art"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T17:43:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Quest Pro VR Headset: Price, Specs, Details]]></title>
        <id>63444013d01ed05afa60f92a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/meta-quest-pro-vr-headset/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T17:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new device is more technologically advanced than ever. It still doesn’t make a great case for VR.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Goode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iOS 翻译体验优化（欧路词典 + Shortcuts + Back Tap）]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76131</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76131"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T15:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[前言
本教程源于 @yetone 的一篇 推文 ，和 @Jack Huang 讨论后稍作修改。
苹果自带的翻译功能在几次版本更新之后已很好用，但需要多个步骤，对专业词汇的支持也没有欧陆词典好（欧陆词典可自行扩充词库）。本教程基于 iOS 自带的 Back Tap 功能，快速启动翻译软件，并支持截图 OCR 翻译。
前期准备
下载软件： 欧路词典 (Eudic) 和快捷指令 (Shortcuts)
「欧路词典」，是一款经典的翻译软件，可自行扩充词库，专业版需付费。
「快捷指令」是苹果官方的软件，前身是 Workflow Gallery，可以理解成一个无代码开发平台（No-Code Development Platform），不需要编程知识，就能完成很多自动化功能的实现。如果对这方面感兴趣，可访问 Shortcuts Gallery 。
安装 Shortcuts
在 Safari 中打开以下两个链接，点击「获取捷径」，再点击「添加快捷方式」。
Clipboard Translate: https://www.icloud.com/shortcuts/b643ecb89dbd4468b8679cd4888b13d9
Image Translate: https://www.icloud.com/shortcuts/02bf2bb484a54f50897b8a3f315d48fd
设置快捷方式
点击「设置」- 辅助功能 – 触控 – 轻点背面（Back Tap）- 设置如图所示：

使用
Clipboard Translate：轻点手机背面两次，自动读取「剪切板」中的文本，并跳转欧路词典翻译。
Image Translate: 轻点手机背面三次，自动截屏，并识别图片中的文本，跳转欧路词典翻译。
扩展：

上文是通过 Back Tap 实现的，日常使用中偶尔会有误触的可能，也可以通过「辅助触控」，俗称「小白点」实现。
macOS 上的全文翻译可参考这篇文章：一种几乎永不失效的网页中英对照翻译方案]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Another_Dayu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Ada Lovelace Day! Here are our favorite tech books for kids]]></title>
        <id>70245 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/ada-lovelace-day-tech-books-kids"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Ada Lovelace Day! Here are our favorite tech books for kids
Lauren Pritchett
Tue, 10/11/2022 - 11:00

            
Tech is everywhere! And it's important to remember, everyone is a beginner once. The industry is continually growing, looking for new folks to add valuable perspectives. How do we inspire our next batch of tech contributors?
In honor of Ada Lovelace Day, we asked our community of writers if they had any resources or books they recommend for young programmers or enthusiasts. Here's what they had to share.
Start from Scratch
I recommend Coding Games in Scratch: A Step-by-Step Visual Guide to Building Your Own Computer Games by Jon Woodcock and Code Your Own Games!: 20 Games to Create with Scratch by Max Wainewright. Being a LEGO family, all of my kids have spent time with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Pritchett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stampix — Photo printing in a fast, easy & ecological way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/stampix</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/stampix"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T14:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Signal for Help I Created Went Viral. Now It Could Be Misused]]></title>
        <id>633ada06e0fe4cc825d3a56c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/domestic-violence-artificial-intelligence-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well-meaning efforts to integrate the hand signal with digital technology could expose vulnerable people to detection and escalated violence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrea Gunraj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robots Are Helping Immunocompromised Kids 'Go to School']]></title>
        <id>633dca06669c7202654d7d3d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/robots-education-sick-kids/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sure, my telepresence robot had some issues—but for students like me who can’t make it to campus because of disability or illness, these tools open new doors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gillian Okimoto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Signal for Help I Created Went Viral. Now It Could Be Misused]]></title>
        <id>633ada06e0fe4cc825d3a56c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/domestic-violence-artificial-intelligence-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well-meaning efforts to integrate the hand signal with digital technology could expose vulnerable people to detection and escalated violence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrea Gunraj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robots Are Helping Immunocompromised Kids 'Go to School']]></title>
        <id>633dca06669c7202654d7d3d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/robots-education-sick-kids/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sure, my telepresence robot had some issues—but for students like me who can’t make it to campus because of disability or illness, these tools open new doors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gillian Okimoto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advice for Junior Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jeroendedauw/advice-for-junior-developers-30am</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jeroendedauw/advice-for-junior-developers-30am"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T12:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#beginners #productivity #codenewbie #learning]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeroen De Dauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pixel Watch Has Landed. What Does That Mean for Wear OS?]]></title>
        <id>6344246beb69b9d725e55af4</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/google-wear-os-3-pixel-watch-software/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s everything you need to know about where Google’s smartwatch platform stands now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian Chokkattu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Sci-Fi Visions for Interstellar Travel Just Might Work]]></title>
        <id>633f4ebe058264dd3ee9304c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/travelers-guide-to-the-stars-interstellar-travel/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Les Johnson, author of the new book A Traveler’s Guide to the Stars, talked to WIRED about solar sails and more ways to get farther into the final frontier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramin Skibba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #786 ISC DHCP 服务器停止维护]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15131-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15131-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T10:29:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ISC DHCP 服务器停止维护

上周，ISC 发布了其 DHCP 服务器（dhcpd）的最后的维护版本，并宣布该服务器项目将在今年年底结束。除非发现非常严重的安全漏洞，ISC 没有计划继续发布更新，也同时停止了其代码的维护。发布于 1997 年的 ISC DHCP 是一个动态主机设置协议（DHCP）的服务器程序。ISC 结束这个项目是因为它不是为可测试性设计的，修改代码的风险性非常高，因此过去几年已经很少修改代码了。ISC 也发布了新的名为 Kea 的 DHCP 服务器作为替代。


消息来源：ISC



老王点评：除了 dhcpd，我从未注意过任何其它 DHCP 服务器，这么流行的一个默认级的开源软件就停止维护了，感觉还是很可惜。另外一个 ISC 的知名软件就是 DNS 服务器 BIND 了，不知道以后的下场如何。




VirtualBox 7.0 正式发布

甲骨文今天推出了 VirtualBox 7.0 版本，引入了诸多改进。最值得关注的改进是支持虚拟机完全加密运行，包括加密配置文件以及已保存的状态。不过加密仅支持通过命令行界面解开。此外还支持管理云端虚拟机；支持 DirectX 11 3D 加速；支持安全启动，等等。上一个大版本 VirtualBox 6.0 是 2018 年推出的。


消息来源：VirtualBox



老王点评：我觉得甲骨文还值得称道的开源贡献之一就是 VirtualBox 了，还好还在继续推出大版本更新。




超过四成的电脑仍然无法升级到 Windows 11

资产管理供应商 Lansweeper 称，在其测试的 6 万个组织的约 2700 万台 PC 中，有 42.76% 未能通过 CPU 测试，有 71.5% 没有通过内存测试，14.66% 没有通过 TPM 测试。研究还发现，Windows 11 采用率正在提高，在 1.44% 的计算机上运行，而在 1 月份只有 0.52%。另外，在被调查的商业设备中，约有 4.82% 的设备运行的是没有完整支持的操作系统，0.91% 的服务器已经报废。


消息来源：The Register



老王点评：不如把这些不能升级的电脑装上 Linux 吧~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building THE MOST practical Todolist with React and Websockets 🪄✨]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/novu/building-the-most-practical-todolist-with-react-and-websockets-18hd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/novu/building-the-most-practical-todolist-with-react-and-websockets-18hd"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T10:07:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #javascript #webdev #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevo David, novu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[我在 Linux 中使用的 5 个 Git 配置]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15130-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15130-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T08:23:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[这份简要指南能够帮助你快速开始使用 Git，以及配置一些选项。




在 Linux 中设置 Git 十分简单，但为了获得完美的配置，我做了以下五件事：


创建全局配置

设置默认名称

设置默认邮箱地址

设置默认分支名称

设置默认编辑器


我使用 Git 管理我的代码、命令行脚本以及文档版本。这意味着每次我开始一项新的任务，首先我需要创建一个文件目录并将其添加到 Git 库中：

$ mkdir newproject
$ cd newproject
$ git init


有一些我一直想要的常规设置。不多，但可以避免我每次都进行配置。我喜欢利用 Git 的 全局 配置功能。

Git 提供了进行手动配置的 git config 命令，但这有一些注意事项。例如，通常你会设置邮箱地址。你可以通过运行 git config user.email 你的邮件地址 命令进行设置。然而，这只会在你当前所在的 Git 目录下起作用。

$ git config user.email alan@opensource.com
fatal: not in a git directory


此外，当这个命令在 Git 仓库中运行时，它只会配置特定的一个仓库。在新的仓库中，你不得不重复这个步骤。我可以通过全局配置来避免重复。选项 --global 会指示 Git 将邮箱地址写入全局配置 ~/.gitconfig 文件中，甚至在必要时会创建它：


请记住，波浪线（~）代表你的主文件夹。在我的电脑中它是 /home/alan。


$ git config --global user.email alan@opensource.com
$ cat ~/.gitconfig
[user]
        email = alan@o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[用这个开源工具从任何网站获取变化提醒]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15129-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15129-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T07:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[使用 changedetection.io 在网站发生变化或更新时获得提醒。




那一年是 2020 年，关于大流行病的消息迅速涌来，每个人都感到完全被类似的新闻文章所淹没，提供了不同程度的更新。

但我需要知道的是，我们的官方准则何时改变。最后，这就是对我来说最重要的事情。

无论关注的是大流行病还是最新的科技新闻，提前了解网站内容的变化都至关重要。

changedetection.io 项目为网站变更检测和通知提供了一个简单但强大的开源解决方案。它很容易设置，而且可以通知 70 多个（还在不断增加）不同的通知系统，如 Matrix、Mattermost、Nextcloud、Signal、Zulip、Home Assistant、电子邮件等等。它还能通知专有应用，如 Discord、Office365、Reddit、Telegram 和许多其他应用。

但 changedetection.io 并不只是局限于观察网页内容。你也可以监视 XML 和 JSON 源，它将建立一个 RSS 馈送，记录变化的网站。

由于其内置的 JSON 简单存储系统，不需要设置复杂的数据库来接收和存储信息。你可以 使用 Docker 镜像运行 或用 pip 安装它。该项目有一个 全面的维基帮助页，大多数常见的问题都有涵盖。

对于使用复杂 JavaScript 的网站，你可以用内置的 Playwright 内容获取器 将你的 changedetection.io 连接到 Chromium 或 Chrome 浏览器。

运行后，在你的浏览器（默认情况下是 http://localhost:5000）中访问该应用。如果你的电脑可以从外部网络访问，你可以在 设置Settings中设置一个密码。



提交你想监控的页面的 URL。有几个与如何过滤该网页有关的设置。例如，…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[免费虚拟机软件 VirtualBox 7.0 发布，距离上一个大版本发布已相隔 4 年]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43585</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/virtualbox-7-0/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T07:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VirtualBox 是一款著名的跨平台虚拟机软件，昨日（2022-10-10）正式发布 VirtualBox 7.0 版本，距离上一个大版本 6.0 发布已相隔 4 年。新版本带来了完全加密的虚拟机]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[用另一种方式执行「断舍离」]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76120</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76120"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T07:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[当我第一次接触「断舍离」这个概念的时候，不仅对它描绘的图景所震撼，而且深切认为这就是我想要的生活。于是我在家里翻箱倒柜的搜索可以丢弃物品，从没用的数据线到大件的废纸箱，只要是能扔的我都直接从家中扔了出去。
也许是一次性丢弃的东西过多，还没等到我开始审视剩下的东西要不要留下，家中有些东西就已经告急了，无奈又开始了买买买的旅程。当我检查购物订单，发现其中含有已经丢弃的物品，我才意识到出现了问题。例如有一次，我需要同时充电多个设备，需要多根数据线，但为了实现「断舍离」，只保留了一根。那时我发现，很多我所丢弃的东西不是不需要的，而是在扔东西那一刻我认为不需要。
仔细想想，这种丢完东西后，又重新买的行为不正是商家所乐意看到的吗？把这种观念作为生活的准则似乎是从另一个方面掉入了消费主义的陷阱。为此我重新审视、省察了「断舍离」这个概念和我所想象的生活，并重新制定了一套可行、节俭的规则。
谨慎购买物品
谨慎购买物品应该是我认为最能体现「断舍离」后生活的方法了。毕竟，我希望看到的是一个没有过多杂物和没用物品的家。既然我无法将所有东西都丢弃，那么就控制新增物品的数量。先对已有物品尽可能收纳，让空间看起来不那么杂乱，再对每个想买的东西进行衡量，如果不是必须的，那就对它说不。
当然，谨慎购买物品也要购买物品。例如：平时生活需要用的牙膏、毛巾等必需品直接买就可以了，买时尽可能货比三家，选择合适的价格和种类。真正应该谨慎购买的是那些看起来有大用，但实际到手可能不会使用的东西。
这里可以分享几个我自己的衡量方法作为参考：
谨慎购买「美好生活」
例如，当我在网上看到了一个洗碗机的广告，它不断的宣传购买洗碗机后解放双手的美好。如果按照宣传所描述的，我是可以购买后有更多的时间去干其他的事情。然而，我回顾日常生活后发现我平时并没有洗大量碗的需求，也就是说，在没看到这个广告前我是不会想象到它所描绘的「美好生活」，…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vuhe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Groovy vs Java: Connecting a PostgreSQL database with JDBC]]></title>
        <id>70221 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/groovy-vs-java-sql"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Groovy vs Java: Connecting a PostgreSQL database with JDBC
Chris Hermansen
Tue, 10/11/2022 - 03:00

            
Lately, I've been looking at how Groovy streamlines the slight clunkiness of Java. This article examines some differences between connecting to a PostgreSQL database using JDBC in Java versus Groovy.
Install Java and Groovy
Groovy is based on Java and requires a Java installation. Both a recent/decent version of Java and Groovy might be in your Linux distribution's repositories, or you can install Groovy by following these instructions. A nice alternative for Linux users is SDKMan, which provides multiple versions of Java, Groovy, and many other related tools. For this article, I'm using SDK's releases of:
Java version 11.0.12-open of OpenJDK 11
Groovy version 3.0.8
Back to the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hermansen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[因突发情况被困外地，怎样尽可能坐上正常航班离开？]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76106</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76106"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T06:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

设想这样一个情况吧：
你带着愉快的心情到了一个地方度假，结果在度假期间遭遇新毒株的新冠疫情爆发，全城宣布静默，城市道路、公共交通和出港港口全部封闭或停运。在配合社区每天的核酸检测和居家不出门同时，你也在仔细留意当地发布的相关信息 —— 十分幸运的是，尽管此刻的疫情还很严重，但当地已经宣布恢复机场运行，你似乎看到了一丝曙光，决定购买机票离开。
然而，事情似乎并没有你想象的这么简单。从恢复机场的商业化运行之后，到你真正坐上飞机离开这里的时间，却过去了一个月。那么这一个月里，到底发生了什么？
偶遇三亚疫情，与「幽灵航班」斗智斗勇
我和朋友在今年的 7 月 16 日回到三亚，开始为期一个月的旅居生活。然而半个月后，一起从崖州区爆发的境外输入疫情在短短几天内就席卷了整个三亚，然后迅速波及了整个海南岛内。受到疫情的影响，我和朋友只能决定提前结束旅居，在 8 月 5 日的晚上购买了 8 月 9 日从海口回广州的火车票，并决定在 8 月 6 日一早坐环岛高铁前往海口。
但计划总是赶不上变化。就在 8 月 6 日的凌晨 3 点 52 分，三亚发布发出通知，宣布全域进入静默状态。

自 2022 年 8 月 6 日凌晨 6 时起，全市实行临时性全域静态管理，除保障社会基本运行服务、疫情防控和紧急特殊情况外，全市范围限制人员流动，暂停城市公共交通。恢复时间另行通告。
原本 7 月最后一个周末还因为办音乐节而人流爆满的三亚后海主街，短短一周就变得萧条异常
好在 8 月 15 日之后，三亚宣布有序恢复凤凰国际机场国内客运航班商业化运行。这意味着，只要是符合…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>宛潼</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LESLIE NOTE / 桌面便签 – 本地笔记软件，支持 WebDAV 同步[Windows]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43579</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/leslie-note/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T04:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LESLIE NOTE 是一款 Windows 下的本地笔记软件，自带一个桌面便签，数据保存在本地，开发者强调「你的笔记只属于你自己」。@Appinn 来自发现频道，开发者自荐： LESLIE NOT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[学习工作流的构建思路]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76113</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76113"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T03:35:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[平时工作中往往会遇到新的知识点，这个时候需要我们快速学习并且进行最佳实践。往往是在真正学习了一段时间之后，才会发现有哪些地方可以优化，这样磨合出来的工作流才是最适合自己的。经过两年工作之余的学习后，我磨合出了以下学习工作流：

底层核心逻辑
一开始我学习新知识时会参考一些博客或者是视频，当我开始敲代码实践时往往会出现一些纰漏和错误，我开始意识到我参考的信息可能是错误的，毕竟发博客的门槛低，因此文章的可信度可能不高，于是我开始查阅一些相关的中文书籍。
中文书籍的确是比较全面且系统地讲解了知识点，但众所周知，技术更迭很迅速，又因为老美在 CS 方面一直都是灯塔，所以一般中文书籍里的内容会滞后于当前最新的知识，导致我跟着中文书籍实践会出现软件版本差异的问题。这时我开始意识到一手信息的重要性，有些中文书籍是翻译英文书籍的，一般翻译一本书也要一两年，这会导致信息传递的延迟，还有就是翻译的过程中信息会有损失。如果一本中文书籍不是翻译的呢，那么它肯定也是参考其他书籍的，参考的过程会带有对英文原著中语言和语义理解的偏差。
于是我就顺其自然地开始翻阅英文书籍。不得不说，整体英文书籍内容的质量是比中文书籍高的，一个原因是写英文书籍的作者更会写作，他们会用自己的话很详尽地解释一个知识点，而不是像一些中文书籍那样罗列知识点并且理所当然地以为读者能读懂而忽略一些细节的描述，还有一个原因就是知识很注重时效性，英文书籍的内容往往更新一点。后来随着学习的层层深入，以知识的时效性和完整性出发，我发现 源代码 > 官方文档 > 英文书籍 > 英文博客，最后我得出了一张 信息损失图

虽然一手信息很重要，但后面的 N 手信息并非一无是处，往往这 N 手资料里写了作者对源知识的转化——作者对知识基于某种逻辑的梳理（流程图、思维导图等）以及自己的一些理解（对源知识的抽象、类比、延伸到其他知识点），这些转化可以帮助我…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vacodwave</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[谷歌 AI 推出新的数组存储开源库]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15128-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15128-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T02:19:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[谷歌 AI 引入了一个用于数组存储的高性能开源库 TensorStore。


谷歌开发的开源 C++ 和 Python 框架 TensorStore 旨在加速大型多维数组的读写设计。覆盖单一大型坐标系的多维数据集通常用于当代计算机科学和机器学习应用程序中。使用这些数据集具有挑战性，因为客户经常希望进行涉及多个工作站并行操作的调查，并且可能会以不可预测的间隔和不同的规模接收和输出数据。

谷歌研究院开发了 TensorStore，该库为用户提供了一个可以管理巨大数据集的 API，而无需复杂的硬件，以解决数据存储和操作问题。该库支持许多存储系统，包括本地和网络文件系统、谷歌云存储等。

为了加载和处理大量数据，TensorStore 提供了一个简单的 Python API。任何任意大小的基础数据集都可以加载和更新，而无需将数据集完整存储在内存中，因为在需要精确切片之前不需要在内存中读取或保存实际数据。

这是通过索引和操作语法实现的，它与 NumPy 操作的语法非常相似。除了虚拟视图、广播、对齐和其他复杂的索引功能，TensorStore 还支持如数据类型转换、降低取样和随意创建的数组这些功能。

此外，TensorStore 包含一个异步 API，可以并发进行读取或写入操作。在执行其他工作时，软件可以进行内存缓存处理（可配置），从而减少在访问常用数据时处理较慢存储系统的需要。

大型数值数据集需要大量的处理能力来检查和分析。实现这一点的常用方法是在分散在许多设备上的大量 CPU 或加速器内核之间并行化任务。在保持出色速度的同时并行分析单个数据集的能力一直是 TensorStore 的关键目标。 PaLM、脑图和其他复杂的大规模机器学习模型是 TensorStore 应用案例的一些例子。


via: https://www.opensourceforu.com/2022/10/google-ai-unveils-a-new-open-source-library-for-array-storage/

作者：Laveesh Kocher 选题：lkxed 译者：KevinZonda 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[微信陪伴的九年间，我都用它做了什么？]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76096</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76096"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T02:03:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[如果说苹果发布会是每年一度的春晚，微信的间歇性更新就像不期而至的假期。在过去的十一年间，微信逐步从最初的简单样子一步步变迁为现在承载了许多功能和期待的国民软件。
而我作为一个非极客普通用户，在翻看朋友圈时蓦然发现这款软件自己也已经不知不觉得用了九年，发布了无数朋友圈内容和加入了许许多多的群聊。自己也从一个微信聊天使用者变成了公众号重度用户和创作者。不妨总结下过去这些年我是如何一步步从抗拒到全面使用微信的以及它带给了我日常生活哪些改变。
面朝屏幕的对话
毫无疑问，所有微信用户使用频率最高的一定是微信的基本功能：聊天。一对一或一对多，文字或语音。每个人都习惯了面对着屏幕表达自己。
加个微信
随着微信的普及，几乎没有朋友没有微信，以至于“加个微信”变成一个礼貌性和建立连接的标准动作。
我一开始并不理解为何微信会拿下偌大的市场，但过年回到老家后看到那么多中老年非QQ用户拿着微信发语音消息时，我才意识到它极大得拓宽了用户群体：“按住说话，松开发送” 简洁而易用。即便是我自己并不喜欢对面突如其来的数个60秒语音（希望微信语音能像子弹短信那样实现可以自动转为文字或者暂停播放的语音管理），但毕竟使用门槛大大降低了，而且简洁爽气的操作界面远远超过了当时花里胡哨的QQ。
所以几乎国内智能手机用户人均一个微信号时，加个微信，犹如一个登门入户的邀请，使得物理分离开之后，依旧保持了进一步交流的可能性，既有的情感更容易维系或加深。
当我们都拥有了一个便宜而高清的通讯渠道时，高昂的运营商资费带来的束缚瞬间被打破，许多亲人和朋友的联系变得频繁。当某个中秋和朋友们打着微信视频“云喝酒”，一起庆祝花好月圆夜时突然觉得科技的进步真好。如果哪一天能够启用Callkit（即像接听电话一样接听），微信电话或视频的体验应该会更好。
遇见陌生人
刚刚开始使用微信时的的朋友大多是熟人，群聊大多是家庭群，工作群，同学群。之后…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James_Tu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teuko Lunchbox Challenges — Be inspired and motivated when packing your kids’ lunches!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/teuko-lunchbox-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/teuko-lunchbox-challenges"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T01:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://www.teuko.com/user/Jessica - yes, I’m a mom of 2 and pack my kids' lunches every day! :) )
 
At Teuko, we hope that boosting inspiration and motivation in a fun way will fulfill our mission to make lunch packing a better experience! You can now see Teuko as the "Strava for Lunchbox Packers" - it offers lunchbox inspiration AND motivation, one lunchbox at a time (meal prepping and packing lunches every day in our kitchen is somehow a daily sport! :) )

🎉 We'd love to hear your thoughts, so try out Teuko.com and enjoy lunch packing! And thanks for the upvote.

Jessica
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[17 Best Early Amazon Prime Day Deals (2022): Echo Devices, Phones, and TVs]]></title>
        <id>633de512058264dd3ee92ffd</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-early-amazon-prime-day-deals-access-sale-2022-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T22:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Prime Early Access Sale runs on October 11 and 12, but the discounts have already started—including on the Apple Watch Series 8.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louryn Strampe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ruleset — Decision-As-A-Service for Lenders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ruleset</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ruleset"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T18:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 7 Best Touchscreen Gloves (2022): Heated, Waterproof, Knitted]]></title>
        <id>61af6ef8d184762c75e0040d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-touchscreen-gloves/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We braved the cold to answer the modern dilemma: Can you keep your hands warm and use a smartphone at the same time?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simon Hill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Physics of Smashing a Spacecraft Into an Asteroid]]></title>
        <id>633db9013099da4d4e0dd650</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-physics-of-smashing-a-spacecraft-into-an-asteroid/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NASA will soon release the results of its DART mission to find out whether crashing a probe into a space rock can deflect it. Here’s how they'll do the math.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhett Allain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 Now Offers Automatic Phishing Protection]]></title>
        <id>63374abad90aafbd66b0c6cb</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/windows-11-automatic-phishing-protection/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’re safer than ever—here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Nield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Best Game Controllers (2022): PC, Switch, PS5, Xbox, Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>5d83cd2ad0c3a500091b0606</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-game-controllers/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A great gamepad instantly levels up your play. These are our top picks for Switch, Xbox, PlayStation, and PC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaina Grey, Simon Hill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[25 Best Cat Toys and Supplies (2022): Scratchers, Window Perches, Modern Furniture, Etc]]></title>
        <id>5f74c5cba85f9b2341236869</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-cat-toys-and-supplies/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Between litter boxes, beds, scratchers, and trees, felines need a lot of stuff. Here’s what the cats of WIRED have tested and loved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Medea Giordano, Louryn Strampe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cities Need More Native Bees—Lots and Lots of Them]]></title>
        <id>633cbd4147233f8cddd753c7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cities-need-more-native-bees-lots-and-lots-of-adorable-bees/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These pollinators can help urban gardens grow. That will be critical for cooling cities as the planet warms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #785 Linux 之父的 PC 挂了，恐影响 Linux 6.1 发布]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15127-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15127-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 之父的 PC 挂了，恐影响 Linux 6.1 发布

两年前我们 报道 过，Linus Torvalds 攒了一台新电脑，一晃两年半过去了，如今，这台电脑的内存条坏了，频繁出现机器不稳定甚至编译器损坏的情况。当时，Torvalds 本来想买 ECC 内存，但是又嫌太贵，于是买了 4 条便宜的 16GB DDR4-2666 的内存。目前，Torvalds 使用他外出携带的 MacBook Pro 工作，但是拖慢了他的工作进度。他说，“我正在我的笔记本电脑上进行合并（非常缓慢），同时在等待新的 ECC 内存条的到来。”。


消息来源：The Register



老王点评：谁能想到，整个 Linux 世界的进步瓶颈就卡在几条内存上。🤣




龙架构已初步支持开源鸿蒙操作系统

龙芯中科宣布，开源鸿蒙（OpenHarmony）操作系统与龙芯 2K0500 开发板完成适配验证，龙架构（LoongArch）平台对于开源鸿蒙已形成初步支持。龙芯 2K0500 是基于 64 位 LA264 处理器核设计的高集成度处理器芯片，该芯片主要面向工控互联网应用、打印终端、BMC 等应用场景。


消息来源：龙芯中科



老王点评：这对于龙芯和鸿蒙都是一小步，但是或许会带来更多想象空间。




英特尔确认 Alder Lake BIOS 源代码被泄露

英特尔 Alder Lake BIOS 源代码被泄露到 4chan 和 Github，这个 6GB 的文件包含用于构建和优化 BIOS/UEFI 镜像的工具和代码。但英特尔“不认为这暴露了任何新的安全漏洞”，英特尔称，“这段代码属于我们的‘断路器项目’中的漏洞赏金计划，我们鼓励任何可能发现潜在漏洞的研究人员通过该计划告知我们。”


消息来源：Tom's Hardware



老王点评：这件事或许没有英特尔说的那么轻描淡写，如果真的无关紧要，何不开源呢？]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Remote Tech Workers Secretly Juggle Multiple Jobs]]></title>
        <id>6340bd5b7683076f6363ecac</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/remote-tech-workers-secret-multiple-jobs/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working from home makes it easier to take on several full-time posts. The extra cash is nice—but simultaneous Zoom meetings can be tricky.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Carnegie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Yourself If Your School Uses Surveillance Tech]]></title>
        <id>633c99e6f9498791684f713b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-protect-yourself-school-surveillance-tech-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colleges and K-12 campuses increasingly monitor student emails, social media, and more. Here’s how to secure your (or your child’s) privacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pia Ceres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hurricane Ian Destroyed Their Homes. Algorithms Sent Them Money]]></title>
        <id>6340bf58eb69b9d725e55ae2</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hurricane-ian-destroyed-homes-google-algorithms-sent-money/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's AI scanned satellite imagery to identify the worst-hit neighborhoods—helping direct aid to residents' phones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hurricane Ian Destroyed Their Homes. Algorithms Sent Them Money]]></title>
        <id>6340bf58eb69b9d725e55ae2</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hurricane-ian-destroyed-homes-google-algorithms-sent-money/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's AI scanned satellite imagery to identify the worst-hit neighborhoods—helping direct aid to residents' phones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildfire Smoke May Carry Deadly Fungi Long Distances]]></title>
        <id>633dc511058264dd3ee92ff8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/wildfire-smoke-may-carry-deadly-fungi-long-distances/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pathogens in soil are a danger to firefighters, but smoke may transport spores that cause valley fever and other infections into cities too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maryn McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Yourself If Your School Uses Surveillance Tech]]></title>
        <id>633c99e6f9498791684f713b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-protect-yourself-school-surveillance-tech-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colleges and K-12 campuses increasingly monitor student emails, social media, and more. Here’s how to secure your (or your child’s) privacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pia Ceres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[无门槛群晖 NAS 搭建指南]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/72672</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/72672"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T10:43:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[前段时间清理电脑，发现「坚果云」在电脑上缓存了 50GB 平时用不上的文件。在与技术人员沟通后，被告知自从 M1 芯片发布以来，「云桥模式」的接口就无法使用，缓存只能手动清理。于是萌生了自己搭建一个 NAS 服务器的想法。
什么是NAS

NAS (Network Attached Storage：网络附属存储) 是一种连接您家中或办公室网路的智慧储存装置。您可以将家人或同事的重要文件、珍贵的相片、影音收藏等档案储存于 NAS，仅需透过网页浏览器或手机应用程式，即可轻松存取档案并享有 NAS 提供的丰富服务。

NAS 也可以简单理解为：「不限速的个性化本地网盘」。
不知道你在日常生活中是否遇到过以下的情形：

电脑的储存空间不够用，想要使用文件，但不想把所有文件存在本地；
存在百度云盘的文件或视频，下载速度仅有 69KB/s；
急需从 OneDrive 下载一个文件，却发现 OneDrive 无法打开；
迅雷下载影片，进度超过 98% 之后下载速度只有 5KB/s；
无处安放的照片存在云相册，画质受到不可逆损伤；
MAC 内建备份功能「时间机器」无处备份个人数据；
无法忍受互联网大厂的隐私乱象；
团队协作交互讨论、修改、审批效率太低，大文件传输困难；

如果你在生活中遇到过以上痛点，这篇文章或许会给你提供一个解决思路。
如何选购 NAS
目前的 NAS 市场基本被群晖和威联通垄断，即便是采用 DIY 方案，也还是要使用黑群晖或黑威联通的系统（即破解版系统）。本文以本土化更好些的群晖NAS（Synology NAS）为例，介绍如何选购家用 NAS。
群晖桌上型较高阶NAS选型指南
「盘位」代表可以安装的硬盘数量，部分型号可以通过购买扩充装置的方法进行盘位扩展。
「双核和四核」表示可以同时运行的程序数量。
「2GB内存」代表程序运行的速度，部分型号可以进行扩展。但要注意，部分…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>白夜</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[:where :is CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mustapha/where-is-css-20nk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mustapha/where-is-css-20nk"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T08:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#css #webdev #beginners #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mustapha Aouas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[如何让特斯拉拥有 CarPlay？]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76097</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76097"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T07:38:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

我是特斯拉 Model 3 的用户，个人觉得特斯拉在大陆的导航和娱乐系统确实不太好用，当然可能也和我日常喜欢用高德导航、Spotify 听歌这些比较多有关系。相信很多特斯拉的用户也和我一样，非常希望能用上苹果的 CarPlay，但特斯拉的车机系统其实是 Linux 并且非常封闭，目前也不太存在破解和安装软件这种捷径的可能。
特斯拉 CarPlay
不过波兰的开发者 Michał Gapiński 前段时间给出了一个用树莓派的解决方法，实现了在特斯拉上使用 CarPlay。因为之前一直需要的两块树莓派的开发板，直到最近简化到了一个并且也简单稳定了不少，我也就做个教程和大家分享下。
准备工作
需要说一下，树莓派 4B 目前的价格依然比较高，整个过程也稍微有点麻烦，折腾的乐趣大于实际使用的意义，不太建议特意为这个去买树莓派，也不太建议不熟悉刷机的朋友尝试。
为了实现在特斯拉上使用 CarPlay 的效果，你需要准备：

树莓派 4B 开发板（需包含 SD 卡和读卡器）
HDMI 转 CSI-2 转接板
Micro HDMI to HDMI 连接线
车连易的 CarPlay 盒子
USB Type-C 数据线（用于刷机以及连接车供电）
一台电脑（用于给树莓派安装系统 Win Mac 都可以）
下载好系统 （版本：2022.38.1)

当然有些是可选的：比如树莓派的外壳和散热风扇，推荐选择塑料的外壳，因为金属的可能会屏蔽树莓派的 Wi-Fi 信号；如果想让特斯拉连接到树莓派的 Wi-Fi 的时候还能使用网络，则需要再购买一个 USB 4G…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>酱紫表</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sakura Photo Viewer – 占用小、速度快、界面好看的 Windows 图片浏览器[Windows]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43573</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/sakura-photo-viewer/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T07:23:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sakura Photo Viewer 是一款占用小、速度快、界面好看的 Windows 图片浏览器。@Appinn 感谢来自频道群组的 @S 同学推荐：就是占用小、速度快、界面好看，尤其打开速度，非]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defining an open source AI for the greater good]]></title>
        <id>70232 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/defining-open-source-ai"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defining an open source AI for the greater good
Stefano Maffulli
Mon, 10/10/2022 - 03:00

            
Artificial intelligence (AI) has become more prevalent in our daily lives. While AI systems may intend to offer users convenience, there have been numerous examples of automated tools getting it wrong, resulting in serious consequences. What's happening in the AI system that leads to erroneous and harmful conclusions? Probably a dramatic combo of bad AI combined with a lack of human oversight. How do we as a society prevent AI ethics fails?
The open source community has had, for well over 20 years, clear processes for dealing with errors ("bugs") in software. The Open Source Definition firmly establishes the rights of developers and the rights of users. There are frameworks, licenses, and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefano Maffulli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polytomic — The one platform to sync any data anywhere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/polytomic</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/polytomic"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T06:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[不是你的怀旧助手：多亲 F22 Pro 两周体验]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76092</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76092"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T03:36:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[我的第一部手机是在去外地上初中时，从我妈那里淘汰下来的诺基亚 3100，之后是高中时用的诺基亚 5320XM。读中学时移动互联网才初露头角，5320XM 用 100 MB 流量的 EDGE 网套餐承载了我躲在宿舍床上的摸鱼时光，按键的漆也在一条条聊天短信里被磨掉。当时我的所有朋友都在用全拼打字，而我为了提高速度，把手指挪动更少的笔划输入法练得飞快。

后来我换了 Android 机器，在还有不少想去把玩的手机没试过时，迎来了 Symbian 与诺基亚的衰落，送走了滑盖、旋盖、全键盘。移动互联网改变了我们使用手机的习惯，也同样改变手机的形态——所以当我发现还有厂商在出实体数字键盘的智能机时，就一直想找个机会试试。赶上多亲 F22 Pro 新品发布，我付了款，等过了两周的疫情，终于把它拿到了手。
这份喜悦在到手的一小时内烟消云散。

青涩但合格的硬件设计
多亲 F22 Pro 的设计和前代的 F21 Pro 其实有很多不同。
除了处理器从 MT6761 / 虎贲 T310 一下跃升到 MTK G85 以外（虽然还是挺弱的），比较显眼的就是尺寸变化。屏幕从此前的 2.8 英寸 480*640 升级到了 3.5 英寸 640*960，这样的参数现在看来可能并不出色，但它和 iPhone 4 的那块 Retina 细腻程度其实一致，文字显示效果不错。而且由于用了几天只有三英寸的 Jelly 2，这块屏幕甚至让我有种换上大屏手机的错觉。

机身和之前的多亲手机一致，依然是与功能机一样的瘦长手感，再加上与 iPhone 4 一样的屏幕和圆形的导航键，整个手机颇有一种当年 iPhone 配上 Typo 键盘壳的感觉。手机的宽度也因为屏幕增大从 53 mm 扩展到 58 mm，和现在流行的尺寸相比，仍然很容易上手。
按键方面，F22 Pro 抛弃了上代采用的孤岛式按键，转向了一体式的按键设计…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>北鸮</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inity — Stay on top of your finances with Inity.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/inity</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/inity"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T02:17:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emailify for Figma — Design and export production-ready HTML emails from Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/emailify-for-figma</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/emailify-for-figma"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T00:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12 Best Wireless Gaming Headsets (2021): PS5, Switch, PC, Xbox Series X/S, PS4, Xbox One]]></title>
        <id>5ae8e8c1f55bd701fb684f85</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-wireless-gaming-headsets/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These WIRED-tested, battery-powered headphones will serve you well whether you’re chatting with teammates in Fortnite or coworkers in Zoom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Ravenscraft, Gear Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turn around your Git mistakes in 17 ways]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/smitterhane/turn-around-your-git-mistakes-in-17-ways-2mn1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/smitterhane/turn-around-your-git-mistakes-in-17-ways-2mn1"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T12:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#git #productivity #github #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Smitter hane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why It’s the Age of the Investor-Entrepreneur]]></title>
        <id>633f414181222da12cb0d9f1</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/investor-entrepreneur/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plural's Taavet Hinrikus says early-stage VC funds need to set a founder to catch a founder.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Armstrong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe’s Plan to Beat Silicon Valley at Its Own Game]]></title>
        <id>633f415585e7a4cc2f80227b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/europe-beat-silicon-valley-startups/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WIRED spoke with Skype cofounder Niklas Zennström about why the burgeoning European startup scene is poised to lead the technological revolution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Armstrong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DocsReminder — Set reminders on documents to avoid missing any deadlines.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/docsreminder</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/docsreminder"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T08:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[即时工具 – 241 款在线小工具集合，无需注册直接使用：图片处理、文档转换、单位换算、文本提取等]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43565</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/67tool-com/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T08:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[即时工具是一款集合了 241 款在线工具的在线工具，主要有视频工具、音频工具、图片工具、文档处理、文档转换、文本工具、单位转换等小工具。@appinn 来自发现频道，开发者自荐：耗时半年开发工具箱,体]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2年半海外居家远程办公体验报告]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76026</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76026"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T03:22:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[我在硅谷科技大厂工作，自20年初疫情爆发至今居家办公已有2年半。在此期间，为应对远程办公而打造的软件、平台、工具雨后春笋般涌现而发展壮大，工作中的沟通协同方式乃至绩效考核机制也随之发生了深刻的改变。相信如此大规模且持续的远程办公潮流在人类工业发展史上都是头一次，而这种趋势还将继续延续下去。
这股远程办公的潮流和趋势，对于身处其间的打工仔而言又有怎样的影响呢？首先要强调的是，远程办公也许并不适用于所有行业(至少在现阶段)，居家远程办公也未必适合所有人。
以我个人的经历而言，我的小孩在此期间出生现都已2岁有余，除此之外我还经历了买房升职。似乎远程办公的工作形式并没有对我的人生重要节点造成什么特别的影响。然而回过头来看又不能不承认，我的生活作息、社交活动与工作方式都已发生积极正面的改变。
居家办公始末
20年初，随着疫情的爆发和公司对于员工健康的关注，硅谷的科技公司陆续允许员工在家远程办公。除去极少数公司在初期就允诺疫情结束之后员工可以继续远程工作，绝大多数的公司还是给出了一个返回办公室的预定时间目标。不过由于漂亮国防疫政策的拉垮，这个预定时间不断地被推迟。直到疫苗的大规模铺开，最终在今年的5月前后，各大公司开始号召员工返回办公室。
2年多的远程办公已经深刻地改变了人们的生活方式：有人已经离开房价高企的硅谷或大都市搬迁到物价更低的偏远地区，有人因为家中有高危人群（老人或小孩）而不愿意回到办公司暴露在潜在的感染风险之中，有人单纯习惯了不用上下班通勤的生活而不再愿意花费时间去办公室。把四散各地的员工“驱赶”回办公室并非可一蹴而就。有感于此，大多数“开明”的公司都发布了混合办公的政策，即一周可以有若干个工作日在家办公（其余工作日仍然需要回到办公室）；又或者开放了永久远程办公的申请，为铁了心不回办公室的员工打开一个通道。某种程度而言，全员远程办公这件事情，已经在今年夏天结束。
我的情况稍…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>浮沉之主</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🤖️ 如何逐步关闭 MIUI 无处不在的广告]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76076</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76076"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T02:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[如果你喜欢我的文章，希望点赞👍 收藏 📁 评论 💬 三连支持一下，谢谢你，这对我真的很重要！

最近需要给长辈置换一下手机，在有限的预算内，经过多次比较发现还是小米的硬件配置更好一些，最后也是下单了小米。
在 2022 年，Android 系统对手机权限的进一步限制，一些过往的卡顿问题都得到了一定的解决。但是在国内的定制版 Android 机上，和原生 Android 系统还是多了一些特色的东西：

无处不在的系统级广告，诱导用户点击/误触，从而去跳转/下载 APP
“不小心下载” 的 APP，占用宝贵的内存/硬盘资源，拖慢手机速度
国内特色的航母级 APP，一个 APP 占几个 G 的硬盘，有些小而美的应用甚至几十个 G

上面的三个问题中，前两个可以通过一定的努力解决大部分，第三个大家都没得选只能硬抗。本文就是聚焦于「关闭 MIUI 无处不在的广告」这个话题的。

虽然 MIUI 一直有 ADUI 的称呼，但是个人身处这个行业也能表示理解：
小米把硬件上的利润压到了最低，赚不到钱就要从其他路子上想办法，只能不停的“加点儿广告怎么了”

废话不多说，我们直接开始。

本文成文于 2022.09，使用的是 MIUI 13.0.4 版本，随着时间的推移，其它版本 MIUI 可能有操作不一致的情况，这点需要读者注意。

一、通过常规手段关闭广告推送
1.1 关闭系统广告
MIUI 的许多内置应用（例如 天气、万年历、音乐）和系统级页面（例如桌面文件夹）上都会推送一些贴片广告，诱导用户观看和点击。
可能用户反馈过于激烈，2019 年年末某个版本更新中，新增了「一键关闭系统广告」的功能。这个开关也很好找，我们直接进入「设置」，然后在搜索框里输入「系统广告」，然后点击进入新页面，把「系统工具广告」这个开关关上即可。
我们可以通过「查看涉及应用列表」查看涉及的 APP，然后去相关…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>卤蛋实验室</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[通过Tweetdeck打造属于自己的内容时间线]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76019</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76019"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T02:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[相信对于很多小伙伴来说，Twitter并非单纯是一个“社交”平台，而是“信息获取”平台。通过追踪各类名人、机构的账号来了解所关注领域的最新动向。比如最近火热的NFT、Web3.0社区中就有大量的意见领袖在Twitter发声。
然而从获取信息效率的视角来看，常规Twitter浏览界面并不是特别友好，时间线上有着各类广告，同时经常用着用着就发现自己迷失在几十个选项卡和搜索结果页中。如果你遇到过类似问题，并希望提高在Twitter获取信息的效率，我会强烈推荐Tweetdeck这个功能。
Tweetdeck是Twitter官方提供的在线工具，有模块化，高度自定义化的浏览界面，不仅适合专业的Twitter运营人员工作使用，也非常适合个人用户来改造优化自己的信息时间线。通过对比图片，可以很清楚的看到两种模式的差异。Tweetdeck可以在设置中选择 黑/白 两种显示模式，我个人更喜欢黑暗模式，看起来更轻松。
4K显示器下的twitter常规界面，大量留白非常浪费空间4K显示器下的tweetdeck界面
 
基础介绍
Tweetdeck和常规界面相比最重要的功能主要是3点：自动刷新、多列显示和自定义模块。自动刷新不需要过多解释，节省频繁刷新的操作和时间。自定义模块可以定制每一列种显示的内容，例如：

我想单独查看Elon Musk的所有推特或者他直发的内容。 - 单用户模式
我希望把多个账号归为一个主题，单独浏览，如：NBA球星们、实时股市新闻、NFT相关资讯。 - 清单模式
我想追踪网友对正在发生的热点事件的评论，如：WWDC大会、俄乌冲突事件等 - 搜索模式

多列显示则大幅度提升了屏幕利用率，让我们可以同时间追踪上述这些不同的主题。

上图是我最近使用Tweetdeck的截图，我通过Vivaldi浏览器“垂直平铺”功能在右边放置了Tesla AI Day的视频直播，在左边放置了Tweetdeck，并添加了：“tesla ai day”搜索结果列、“tesla bot”搜索结果列、Elon的个人内容列，和常用的市场资讯列。
 
模块选择
在Tweetdeck中，可以选择添加多种不同的模块，其中包含，
内容类模块：单用户模式、搜索模式、清单模式、正在流行内容等
功能类模块：通知、站内信、@我的、已预约内容等
我并没有做账户运营的需求，因此最常使用的还是：搜索结果、单个用户、多用户清单这几个内容类模块。
可添加模块截图
 
搜索模式：
显示关键词搜索结果配合自动刷新功能，达成“直播”的效果。并且可以通过设置条件对搜索结果进一步筛选，可设置条件包含：

按推文类型过滤：例如包含图片、视频、GIF等的推文；或者是否显示“转发”内容。
筛选内容的发布时间范围，最小单位可以精确到半个小时。
按照推文语言类型筛选，例如：中文、英文、日语等。
筛选推文发布者：选择特定的单个用户或者一组用户的搜索结果。
内容互动情况：显示至少有多少点赞、转发或评论的内容。

 
单用户模式 & 多用户清单：
这2个模式本质差别就是关注用户的多少，选定关注范围后的筛选条件选项完全一致。在这2个模块中，同样可以通过设置筛选条件，包含：

按推文类型过滤：例如包含图片、视频、GIF等的推文；或者是否显示“转发”内容。
关键词过滤：显示或排除包含指定关键词的内容。
用户筛选：由指定用户发布的内容 或 @特定用户的内容。

在Tweetdeck追踪的，不管是单用户还是清单，并不要求是关注的账户。这点非常贴心，也帮助我区分不同使用场景，我把大量“新闻资讯”类账号从关注列表中去除，放在Tweetdeck清单中，日常在手机上浏览就不会被刷屏，而更关注轻松的内容，坐在电脑前则可以追踪查看这些庞杂的资讯。
在Tweetdeck创建的清单可以选择设置为公开或者私有列表，同时这个列表也会同步到常规界面左侧的列表按钮中。

 
模块设置：
这几个内容模块中都可以单独设置“媒体展示尺寸大小”，可以大体理解为模块中每一条内容的高度。以及是否通过“声音”或者“桌面通知”的形式发送通知，提示关注的内容有更新。

Tweetdeck是简单，但又很强大的工具，给我带来了很多的便利，也希望分享给大家，打造适合自己的内容模块。
 
PS：
Tweetdeck访问地址：https://tweetdeck.twitter.com
今年Twitter官方下架了Tweetdeck的桌面客户端软件，仅提供网页版本，如果想在电脑上安装独立客户端可以使用Tweeten，有Windows和Mac版本，并且基于Tweetdeck提供了更多的功能。
Tweeten部分功能展示
题图源自：Brett Jordan on Unsplash
更多内容欢迎访问我的个人博客：「假设检验」]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>johnbens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made 1,000x faster TypeScript Validator Library]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/samchon/typescript-json-is-10-1000x-times-faster-than-zod-and-io-ts-8n6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/samchon/typescript-json-is-10-1000x-times-faster-than-zod-and-io-ts-8n6"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T16:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #typescript #opensource #benchmark]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeongho Nam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paranoia Threatens to Upend Professional Chess]]></title>
        <id>633f2a90058264dd3ee9304a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/magnus-carlsen-hans-niemann-cheating-chess-fide/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Magnus Carlsen–Hans Niemann cheating scandal points to abuses and suspicion at the highest levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg Keener</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Hackers Minted $569M in Crypto—Then It Got Complicated]]></title>
        <id>634019df81222da12cb0da05</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/binance-hackers-minted-569-million/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: The US warns of a mysterious military contractor breach, a "poisoned" version of the Tor Browser is tracking Chinese users, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman, Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why ‘Carbon Emissions’ Are Now ‘Climate Pollution’]]></title>
        <id>633b185ffe6f3e53574722ab</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/why-carbon-emissions-are-now-climate-pollution/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[California activists fought to frame climate change as an air quality problem. Now it’s federal law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in Tel Aviv]]></title>
        <id>633dee8185e7a4cc2f802274</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-in-tel-aviv-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Home to Silicon Wadi and a long-running streak of mega-money exits, the Tel Aviv tech scene leads with innovative applications of robotics, AI and medtech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Armstrong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in Amsterdam]]></title>
        <id>633def4820105ba57106995f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-amsterdam-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amsterdam continues to punch well above its weight, combining tech powerhouse status with being one of the most livable cities on the continent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gian M. Volpicelli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in Helsinki]]></title>
        <id>633ded7447233f8cddd753e7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-in-helsinki-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a small city, but investment in its startups is growing apace, thanks to an international mindset and a sturdy support system for local founders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in Dublin]]></title>
        <id>633debe681222da12cb0d9a1</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-in-dublin-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The city is celebrating more local talent than ever, as being the only English-speaking country in Europe tempts new founders and drives outside investment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Makes a Champagne Vintage Great? Ask a Deep Learning Model]]></title>
        <id>6340b2c1d01ed05afa60f88b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/what-makes-a-champagne-vintage-great-ask-a-deep-learning-model/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bollinger is data mining its meticulous records to predict vintage years and weather the challenges of climate change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Barber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LiveHosts – 在浏览器中实时添加 主机/IP 映射，无需修改 hosts 文件[Chrome/Firefox]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43560</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/livehosts/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T09:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LiveHosts 是一款可以在 Chrome、Firefox 浏览器中实时添加 主机/IP 映射，无需修改 hosts 文件的开发者工具，纯跳转方式，方便进行网络测试。@Appinn 感谢 lof]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[我在英国留学摄影之——如何理解「摄影」？]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76044</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76044"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T08:02:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

在不久之前，我写了一篇文章，大概讲了一下我认为出国留学「摄影」这件事对我而言的几个较有价值的部分，其中有一点是获得了「从学术的角度出发理解摄影」的一个方法。今天我就打算展开讲讲我从英国这个摄影的「发源地」学到的方法论之——如何理解摄影，希望和大家一同探讨。
需要提醒的是，这篇文章里有一些学术概念，我已经用了尽量简单易懂的方式表述，但出于对「信息传递更精准」的目的，我依然保留了一些可能不好理解的名词，建议大家收藏本文，慢慢看。
首先，我想先对「理解摄影」这个话题加上一个更具体的语境，即——如何用一种具有创造性的方式理解摄影，而这也是我们上个学年在讨论的一个核心议题：「The central question will be how to read photographic images in an innovative manner. 」。
正如上面提到的，「用创造性的方式解读摄影」，这个表述背后事实上是默认了在「创造性 」的解读照片的方式背后还有一种「非创造性」的方式解读照片。那么所谓的「非创造性」和「创造性」指的是什么呢？让我们先从「非创造性」开始说起。
「非创造性」——摄影的本质
首先，要从沃克·埃文斯（Walker Evans）在 1931 年写的一篇名为《摄影的重生》（The Reappearance of Photography）的文章说起。这篇文章里提到了尤金·阿杰特（Eugene Atget）、史泰钦（Edward Steichen）、阿尔伯特·伦格-帕茨（Renger Patzsch）等多位摄影师的作品，并对他们有…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>啦苏LASU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QNAP 威联通 AList 插件，支持挂载阿里云盘、百度网盘、PikPak、夸克网盘等到本地]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43555</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/alist-webdav-for-qnap/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T04:21:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[多云盘挂载集成工具 for QNAP（Alist webdav for QNAP）是 @bbis 同学基于 AList 发布的 QNAP 威联通 AList 插件，可以很方便的将阿里云盘、百度云盘、P]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Knock Sources — Power your product notifications with Segment and Hightouch.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/knock-sources</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/knock-sources"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T20:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Uber Data Breach Conviction Shows Security Execs What Not to Do]]></title>
        <id>633ee35881222da12cb0d9a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/uber-joe-sullivan-conviction/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T19:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Uber security chief Joe Sullivan’s conviction is a rare criminal consequence for an executive’s handling of a hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden’s Privacy Order Slaps a Band-Aid on the EU-US Data Crisis]]></title>
        <id>634078763099da4d4e0dd65d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/biden-eu-us-data-privacy-executive-order/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T19:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new executive order tries to reassure Europeans that their data is safe on US soil, despite government surveillance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Morgan Meaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Deepfake Bruce Willis Doing in My Metaverse?]]></title>
        <id>633f03e57e8d589e28665ae3</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/plaintext-bruce-willis-deepfake-metaverse/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: The future as seen from 1991, Google fights Apple for your wrist, and nuclear war.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Deepfake Bruce Willis Doing in My Metaverse?]]></title>
        <id>633f03e57e8d589e28665ae3</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/plaintext-bruce-willis-deepfake-metaverse/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: The future as seen from 1991, Google fights Apple for your wrist, and nuclear war.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Far Would You Have to Tunnel Underground to Lose 20 Pounds?]]></title>
        <id>632869f7c9bb1af7ef249857</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-far-would-you-have-to-tunnel-underground-to-lose-20-pounds/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In What If? 2, Randall Munroe explains that evading gravity can reduce your weight—but let’s do the math to see how far you have to go.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhett Allain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Async & Await]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maximization/understanding-async-await-22o6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maximization/understanding-async-await-22o6"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T12:28:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #beginners #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maxim Orlov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Says It Has Busted More Than 400 Login-Stealing Apps This Year]]></title>
        <id>633dce494bb7933eb618317d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/meta-facebook-login-stealing-android-ios-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company plans to alert 1 million Facebook users that their account credentials may have been compromised by malicious software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in Barcelona]]></title>
        <id>633de9fd47233f8cddd753e5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-in-barcelona-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The city is a global hub for investors, startups, and larger companies seeking sunnier climes and a business-friendly atmosphere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Armstrong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in Stockholm]]></title>
        <id>633dea4b92468d5a8855add5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-in-stockholm-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A city famed for friendliness also has a booming startup scene—and that network of founders supporting founders has led to a slew of firms taking the lead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Christian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in Lisbon]]></title>
        <id>633dea32f9498791684f71d8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-in-lisbon-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The reinvention of the Portuguese capital is picking up speed, as a slew of government incentives is making it an attractive base for new arrivals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joao Medeiros</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Time to Treat Housing Insecurity as a Health Risk]]></title>
        <id>633faa5d81222da12cb0d9ff</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cancer-housing-deprivation/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study shows that cancer patients in precarious living situations are twice as likely to die from their illness, underscoring the harms of unstable housing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kasra Zarei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fight to Cut Off the Crypto Fueling Russia's Ukraine Invasion]]></title>
        <id>633d947e4bb7933eb6183179</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/russia-ukraine-cryptocurrency-funding/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain investigators have uncovered at least $4 million—and counting—in cryptocurrency donations to Russia’s violent militia groups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 GitHub Repositories to Contribute for Hacktoberfest 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/atapas/15-github-repositories-to-contribute-for-hacktoberfest-2022-215d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/atapas/15-github-repositories-to-contribute-for-hacktoberfest-2022-215d"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T09:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#opensource #hacktoberfest #webdev #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapas Adhikary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix WebCam – 黑客帝国式的虚拟摄像头]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43551</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/matrix-webcam/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T08:43:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix WebCam 是一款开源的虚拟摄像头工具，基于 Python，可以提供一个黑客帝国式的虚拟摄像头工具，让你在远程视频、视频会议中独具一格。@Appinn 注意，obs-studio 自]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn programming at Open Jam 2022]]></title>
        <id>70214 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/open-jam-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn programming at Open Jam 2022
Seth Kenlon
Fri, 10/07/2022 - 03:00

            
Open Jam game jam is happening from October 28 to November 9 this year. Every year for the past several years, programmers from around the globe build open source video games, and then play and rate one another's games. Just for fun.
Open Jam is a "game jam," which is a casual way to inspire programmers of all skill levels to focus on a just-for-fun project for a concentrated period of time. It promotes open source games as well as open source game creation tools. While participants aren't required to use open source tools to create their game, the games themselves must bear an open license, and you literally get extra points during the scoring round for using open source tools.
Another important aspect of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Kenlon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Rethinks the Philosophy of the Facebook Feed]]></title>
        <id>633e13295ec45110c69a14b5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/meta-rethinks-facebook-news-feed/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WIRED spoke with the head of Facebook about competition from TikTok and his theory that algorithms can enhance our personal relationships.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are You Sure You Know What Revenge Porn Is?]]></title>
        <id>633ca4055a49457c993f5331</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/revenge-porn-platforms-grindr-queerness/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forty-eight states have passed protections against revenge porn—but their narrow definition of such content leaves many people exposed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Gilden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Can’t You Tickle Yourself? Neuroscientists Unravel the Mystery]]></title>
        <id>6332304b00704d14b5ffba02</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/neuroscientists-unravel-the-mystery-of-why-you-cant-tickle-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Playfulness and tickling aren’t always considered “serious” subjects, but a new study shows how they can address key questions about the brain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max G. Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awesome tools for Open Source Contribution]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-tools-for-open-source-contribution-36cm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-tools-for-open-source-contribution-36cm"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T11:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#opensource #beginners #javascript #react]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Vishwakarma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are the 100 Hottest Startups in Europe in 2022]]></title>
        <id>633de90f669c7202654d7d43</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/100-hottest-startups-europe-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Entrepreneurs across the continent are embracing new ways of working—and there’s a perceptible shift in what startups choose to focus on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in London]]></title>
        <id>633de7e981222da12cb0d99e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-in-london-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fallout from Brexit isn’t in the rearview mirror just yet, but the UK capital is forging ahead regardless.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joao Medeiros</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in Berlin]]></title>
        <id>633de7d7669c7202654d7d42</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-in-berlin-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Look out, London—Berlin is fast catching up in all areas, from sheer volume of funding by startups to its rapid transition into a center for deeptech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Carnegie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in Paris]]></title>
        <id>633de92a1cda20e3228c79f3</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-in-paris-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Business incubator Station F has supercharged the Paris tech scene, but it’s far from the only show in town.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Morgan Meaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Is Totally Wrong About Population Collapse]]></title>
        <id>633e0b514bb7933eb618318b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-population-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla’s outspoken CEO thinks the biggest threat facing the planet is people not having enough babies. Demographers disagree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swatted: A Shooting Hoax Spree Is Terrorizing Schools Across the US]]></title>
        <id>633da05620105ba571069956</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/swatting-schools-us-september-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sixteen states collectively suffered more than 90 false reports of school shooters during three weeks in September—and many appear to be connected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruv Mehrotra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Election-Swinging, Facebook-Fueled, Get-Out-the-Vote Machine]]></title>
        <id>633c7c7b058264dd3ee92fe8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-election-swinging-facebook-fueled-get-out-the-vote-machine/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Democratic operative Tara McGowan is sinking millions into Meta’s ad network to build Courier Newsroom, a media powerhouse for the left.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nancy Scola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamically update TLS certificates in a Golang server without downtime]]></title>
        <id>70217 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/9/dynamically-update-tls-certificates-golang-server-no-downtime"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamically update TLS certificates in a Golang server without downtime
Savita Ashture
Thu, 10/06/2022 - 03:00

            
Transport Layer Security (TLS) is a cryptographic protocol based on SSLv3 designed to encrypt and decrypt traffic between two sites. In other words, TLS ensures that you're visiting the site you meant to visit and prevents anyone between you and the website from seeing the data being passed back and forth. This is achieved through the mutual exchange of digital certificates: a private one that exists on the web server, and a public one typically distributed with web browsers.
In production environments, all servers run securely, but server certificates may expire after some period. It is then the server's responsibility to validate, regenerate, and reuse newly genera…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Savita Ashture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[新玩意 122｜少数派的作者们最近买了啥？]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76045</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76045"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T06:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[关于栏目
为了满足读者们对于《新玩意》栏目加更的需求，机器人特地邀请了 Matrix 作者们也来聊聊自己近期购买的新奇产品。喜欢本栏目的话，欢迎充电或评论文章来表达自己的喜爱，你的每一次真心夸赞或建议，都是作者前进的动力。
所有内容均遵循 原创、首发、非商务 原则，投稿细则可查看文末。

@甜食：神藤毛巾内毛圈浴巾

入手渠道：淘宝
入手价格：370 元

最近因为搬家，许多生活用品需要重新购买，其中自然也包括各类卫浴洗漱用品这种又占空间、单价又便宜，导致搬走不如买新的的物件。在物色新浴巾的时候，我发现了神藤毛巾这个品牌。神藤毛巾是日本大阪的毛巾品牌，有别于传统的毛圈表面的毛巾，他们的产品以棉纱材质的毛巾见长。
传统毛巾的毛圈材质表面积更大，用来清洁自然是效率更高的，不过生活在南方的读者应该多少都会有潮湿天气下毛巾连日难以风干，甚至产生异味的经验，神藤的毛巾采用了多层纱布的织法，既保证了良好的吸水性，疏松的质地也让毛巾更加速干，同时比较平滑的表面也提供了更清爽的触感。
我最终购买的这款产品叫作 Inner Pile，算是神藤毛巾比较创新的一款产品（和很多刻板印象中的日本作坊式品牌一样，他们总共只有三款产品 —— 另外两款是多层棉纱毛巾「2.5-PLY GAUZE」和传统的毛圈毛巾「YUKINE」，具体用途只通过尺寸来区分），由外层的两层纱布夹着中间的一层毛圈构成。由于中间的毛圈层，这款毛巾的吸水性比纯纱布的毛巾更胜一筹，整体也更蓬松，摸起来甚至有点冬天棉衣的蓬松感，但又非常轻。外层的纱布又保证了清爽的触感，格外适合作为浴巾使用。
毛巾的近距离状态，可以看到多层疏松透光的结构毛巾的标签，我到手之后直接把标签拆了，没有拍到新品缝在毛巾上的样子
我这些年的一个经验是，从所谓改善生活质量的角度出发，买更多更好更贵的大件（如电子产品）带来的幸福感往往远不如买一些高品质的小件生活用品。…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matrix机器人</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockamp — YouTube for Web3 - watch what is being minted live on-chain!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/blockamp</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/blockamp"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T19:05:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Needs to Recognize Intimate Privacy as a Civil Right]]></title>
        <id>6317a57979f10149f7bb9f4a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/privacy-intimacy-civil-rights-danielle-citron/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital privacy invasion isn’t just a consumer protection issue. It’s inextricably linked to equality, with urgent implications for women and minorities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danielle Keats Citron</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Change your old methods for writing a JavaScript Code - Shorthand's for JavaScript Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devsimc/change-your-old-methods-for-writing-a-javascript-code-shorthands-for-javascript-code-54hp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devsimc/change-your-old-methods-for-writing-a-javascript-code-shorthands-for-javascript-code-54hp"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T12:51:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #beginners #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>simc dev CSM®</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The FCC's Rules on Space Junk Just Got Stricter]]></title>
        <id>633764fba546819a4885f46f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-fccs-rules-on-space-junk-just-got-stricter/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new and contentious five-year limit for getting rid of dead satellites could slow the growing orbital litter problem—if people actually abide by it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramin Skibba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bold Effort to Cure HIV—Using Crispr]]></title>
        <id>63374d5faf6115289c0e5fec</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/a-bold-effort-to-cure-hiv-using-crispr/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An experiment tests whether the gene-editing technology can stop the virus from replicating, which would ultimately wipe out the infection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Mullin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use OCI containers to run WebAssembly workloads]]></title>
        <id>70224 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/wasm-containers"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use OCI containers to run WebAssembly workloads
Aditya R
Wed, 10/05/2022 - 03:00

            
WebAssembly (also referred to as Wasm) has gained popularity as a portable binary instruction format with an embeddable and isolated execution environment for client and server applications. Think of WebAssembly as a small, fast, efficient, and very secure stack-based virtual machine designed to execute portable bytecode that doesn't care what CPU or operating system it runs on. WebAssembly was initially designed for web browsers to be a lightweight, fast, safe, and polyglot container for functions, but it's no longer limited to the web.
On the web, WebAssembly uses the existing APIs provided by browsers. WebAssembly System Interface (WASI) was created to fill the void between WebAssembly and sys…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditya R</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn this before React]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jps27cse/learn-this-before-react-4hpl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jps27cse/learn-this-before-react-4hpl"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T04:47:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #javascript #webdev #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Pritom Soren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Created a File Sharing Website using Simple JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/varshithvhegde/how-i-created-a-file-sharing-website-using-simple-javascript-355g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/varshithvhegde/how-i-created-a-file-sharing-website-using-simple-javascript-355g"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T04:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#html #javascript #css #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Varshith V Hegde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16 Libraries You Should Know as a React Developer 💯🔥]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/madza/16-libraries-you-should-know-as-a-react-developer-4f1k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/madza/16-libraries-you-should-know-as-a-react-developer-4f1k"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T15:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #coding #react #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Madza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamers Use Playlists to Control the Music Industry]]></title>
        <id>6320aa3940fe1e8870aa3a85</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/spotify-streaming-playlists-music/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recorded music market is regaining its former hourglass shape—this time with platforms like Spotify at the center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Giblin, Cory Doctorow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opendoor’s iBuyer Model Is a Canary in the Economic Coal Mine]]></title>
        <id>633b79b8b1070500c040c678</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/opendoor-ibuyers-housing-market/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company is losing huge sums of money on cookie-cutter homes—suggesting a fundamental weakness in the US housing market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden's AI Bill of Rights Is Toothless Against Big Tech]]></title>
        <id>6335f8bac554667379f2da78</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/bidens-ai-bill-of-rights-is-toothless-against-big-tech/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The draft's tenets include allowing citizens to opt out of algorithmic decisionmaking, which could reshape federal government—but not the private sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khari Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists Have Discovered a New Set of Blood Groups]]></title>
        <id>633b72b6dc2b0a44046db8a2</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/new-blood-types/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘Er’ grouping could help doctors identify and treat some rare cases of blood incompatibility, including between pregnant mothers and fetuses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Baraniuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mediterranean Sea Is So Hot, It’s Forming Carbonate Crystals]]></title>
        <id>6335f490c554667379f2da77</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-mediterranean-sea-is-so-hot-its-forming-carbonate-crystals/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the rapidly warming Eastern Mediterranean, water stratifies into layers, like a cake. That’s allowing carbon-spewing crystals to form.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the OSI model in 5 minutes]]></title>
        <id>70227 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/osi-model-network-communications"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the OSI model in 5 minutes
Anamika
Tue, 10/04/2022 - 03:00

            
The Open Systems Interconnection (OSI) model is a standard for how computers, servers, and people communicate within a system. It was the first standard model for network communications and was adopted in the early 1980s by all major computer and telecommunications companies.
The OSI model provides a universal language for describing networks and thinking about them in discrete chunks, or layers.
Layers of the OSI model
The model describes the seven layers through which computer systems communicate over a network.
Application layer
Presentation layer
Session layer
Transport layer
Network layer
Data link layer
Physical layer
Each of these layers has its own way of working, with its own set of protocols that disti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anamika</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing a secure API]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vaultree/designing-a-secure-api-4059</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vaultree/designing-a-secure-api-4059"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T04:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#beginners #api #design #security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Aravena, Vaultree</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s Half-Baked Robot Is a Clunky First Step]]></title>
        <id>633b0db69149b25103844a45</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musks-half-baked-robot-is-a-clunky-first-step/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T20:56:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla’s Optimus robot did not dazzle robotics experts and can’t yet walk. But if the project delivers, it could give the company an edge in manufacturing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[赛博朋克风再起时，香港霓虹正在消失]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76030</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76030"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T11:59:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[本文首发于CITYLAB公众号]
今年，赛博朋克的风又刮了起来。一部《赛博朋克：边缘行者》的热播动画，不仅让游戏《赛博朋克2077》的玩家数量暴涨近400%，也让赛博朋克风再度成为亚文化讨论焦点。而说起赛博朋克美学，则绕不开一座城——香港。
香港街头琳琅满目的霓虹灯招牌，曾是赛博朋克视觉想象的灵感之源，但时至今日，这些霓虹魅影正在被拆除、消亡、遗忘。
01.赛博朋克的视觉语言
「Cyberpunk」一词源自1983年美国作家Bruce Bethke创作的短篇小说，是「Cybernetics」与「Punk」的结合词。「Cybernetics」是一种「关于在动物和机器中控制和通信」的科学研究，又称模控学，「Punk」则是由1960年代摇滚乐流派延伸出来的词，指涉那些对主流社会充满反叛精神的边缘人群。
《赛博朋克：边缘行者》中的主角出身贫民阶层
赛博朋克作品一般设定在科技高度发达的近未来，模控化的义体人或仿生人被大量应用，同时，这样的社会又往往被极权政府、跨国财团或秘密组织所掌控，导致贫富差距严重，恶劣的生存环境刺激底层punk们进行反叛。因此，高科技、低生活的反乌托邦景象成为赛博朋克作品的鲜明特征。
而赛博朋克的视觉化构建，是早于这个词诞生的。
1982年的电影《银翼杀手》，可以说是奠定了赛博朋克视觉美学的基础。片中总是雨水潮湿的街道、鱼龙混杂的路边摊、荧光闪烁的立面装饰、英文与亚洲文字混杂的霓虹灯招牌……成为众多观众心目中对于赛博朋克的经典印象，导演雷德利·斯科特曾经表示，这些布景的感觉是参考了「天气很差时的香港街道」。
电影《银翼杀手》中的街道
1995年的动画电影《攻壳机动队》则将香港与赛博朋克更紧密地联系在一起。导演押井守认为21世纪的亚洲将主导未来世界的发展，而香港是当时其他城市效仿的对象，于是他选择了香港作为片中未来大都会「新港市」的想象蓝本。
经过押井守多次到香…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>老直啊</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Cities Are Recycling Trees and Poop to Make Compost]]></title>
        <id>63376c44d90aafbd66b0c6d7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/crowdsourced-compost-tree-waste-poop/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wood and biosolids from water treatment plants can be used to improve the soil—and keep remaining trees healthy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryn Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Huge New Data Set Pushes the Limits of Neuroscience]]></title>
        <id>63334e06f1e5c40d2b1bc768</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/a-huge-new-data-set-pushes-the-limits-of-neuroscience/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Allen Institute’s release includes recordings from a whopping 300,000 mouse neurons. Now the challenge is figuring out what to do with all that data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grace Huckins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The High Cost of Living Your Life Online]]></title>
        <id>6336feb9a546819a4885f45d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/privacy-psychology-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Constantly posting content on social media can erode your privacy—and sense of self.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thor Benson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tremor - Free React Library for Dashboards]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sm0ke/tremor-free-react-library-for-dashboards-3gm9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sm0ke/tremor-free-react-library-for-dashboards-3gm9"/>
        <updated>2022-10-02T17:42:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #opensource #dashboards]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sm0ke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Self-Taught AI May Have a Lot in Common With the Human Brain]]></title>
        <id>6331e992995b6da54b57f049</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/self-taught-ai-may-have-a-lot-in-common-with-the-human-brain/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neural networks can use self-supervised learning to figure out what matters. This process might be what helps humans do the same.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anil Ananthaswamy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[趁着换季，给衣柜来一次断舍离]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75973</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75973"/>
        <updated>2022-10-02T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一阵秋雨过后，忽然就意识到气温的变化，于是给衣橱换季也不得不提上了日程。
从收拾夏日衣物并分批洗涤，到把冬衣填进衣柜、不再穿的衣服送去衣物回收，一共用了三四天的时间。其中大部分时间都用在洗涤和晾晒，专门用来收拾布局的只有不到一天的时间。
之前的每次换季都不可避免地会撞上搬家，所以正儿八经的衣橱换季还是第一次。以下就是我这次整理衣橱的心得，另有对消费和断舍离的反思，希望对你有所帮助。
第一步：辞旧
此处的「旧衣服」指的是夏季的衣物，还有一些不打算再穿的衣服。
夏季出汗多，为了防止汗渍沉积，因此需要在收纳前清洗干净。如果是年初的冬夏换季，需要注意的是不能烘干的毛衣等需要更长的时间手洗、晾干，可能需要提前预留更多时间。
第一步就是把所有冬天不准备再穿的衣服都拿出来，掏干净口袋后分门别类放进不同的洗衣袋里。我的分类依据主要是洗涤方式：只可机洗不能烘干的，以及可机洗可烘干，深浅分开，一共四筐。另外还有一个纸箱，专门用来放不准备再穿的衣物。
 
洗涤先从至少需要过夜晾干的娇贵衣服开始，然后是可烘干的那些。中间我留了足够的时间，以确保大部分的衣服都能在差不多的时间内足够干爽，可以安心放进储藏室而不用担心发霉。
接下来，就是把所有衣服，按照洗涤方式分类放入收纳箱。家里的教诲是「把娇贵的衣服放在最上层才不容易被压坏」，但以我对自己的了解，天气热起来的时候肯定直接从最上层拿衣服，所以在上层放好洗的普通衣物总没错；同理，冬装收纳的最上层也是轻薄的毛衣。
这个过程中，我没有把所有洗干净的衣服都放进收纳箱，而是专门留下了许多不打算再穿的衣服。关于我的「断舍离」，会在后面有一节详细讲述。
而收起来准备明年再穿的衣服，都和一小块檀香皂放进可密封的袋子里，明年拿出来再穿的时候，衣服上就自然染上好闻的香气了！除了檀香皂，还可以尝试樟木球、香挂，以及切成小段、放进纸袋里的线香，都是可以持续散发香气、且味道不会…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>鸿苓</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Cool HTML Elements Nobody Uses]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/7-cool-html-elements-nobody-uses-330c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/7-cool-html-elements-nobody-uses-330c"/>
        <updated>2022-10-02T04:44:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #html #javascript #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapajyoti Bose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 个视频，3 万粉丝，少数派作者是怎么运营 B 站的？]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75780</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75780"/>
        <updated>2022-10-02T03:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

前言
开始的时候我就决定了，未来哪天必定要写这样的一篇阶段性总结文章，只不过那时设想的时间点远在第十个视频之后，而这天的到来比我所预期的要早很多，因为很幸运地提前完成了一个年初定下的小目标，全网 5 万关注达成了。
也因为我的账号起源与少数派这个网站有莫大关系，所以选择将这篇长文首发于此，希望能帮到对运营 B 站有想法、以及对视频剪辑工具有需求的同学。
大家好，这里是 二一的笔记，一个硬核测评笔记软件和效率工具的 UP 主。

文章简介
本文非常长，有 1.5 万字。
前半部分讲的是我会做 B 站账号的契机、以及我对如何做 B 站视频的理解；视频制作工具的推荐在后半部分，各位可以根据右侧目录有选择性地观看。看完后也许就能大致明白，运营一个 B 站账号可能会需要哪些基础知识。
以下是文章的关键内容概述：

频道定位
我是谁，这是个什么样的频道，我是如何起步的，我取得了哪些成绩？
我为什么做这个频道，我看到了哪些问题，发现了什么痛点？
我打算怎么做好这个频道，我所坚持的理念是什么？
我现在的收入如何，我打算如何变现？

我的方法
我是怎么写脚本的，我用到了哪些技巧，例如要怎么「骗弹幕」？
我是怎么学习剪视频的，我看了什么教程，关注了哪些频道？
我是怎么剪视频的，我用到了哪些工具、软件、或者插件？

我的问题
我的能力都有哪些不足？
我的频道运营有哪些瓶颈？
我该如何面对、以及如何解决这些问题？


频道的诞生
频道定位
注：此处仅为账号运营前 1~2 年的短期规划。

账号定位：硬核测评笔记软件和效率工具，折腾与分享精进生产力的经验与…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>二一的笔记</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktoberfest is here — and this is the lowdown]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devteam/hacktoberfest-is-here-and-this-is-the-lowdown-3d76</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devteam/hacktoberfest-is-here-and-this-is-the-lowdown-3d76"/>
        <updated>2022-10-01T15:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#hacktoberfest #meta #opensource #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Halpern, The DEV Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made an admin dashboard for React using Typescript! Use it for free!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fredy/i-made-an-admin-dashboard-for-react-using-typescript-use-it-for-free-49fh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fredy/i-made-an-admin-dashboard-for-react-using-typescript-use-it-for-free-49fh"/>
        <updated>2022-10-01T13:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#showdev #typescript #webdev #react]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fredy Andrei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Exchange Server Has a Zero-Day Problem]]></title>
        <id>63373e41d90aafbd66b0c6ca</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/microsoft-exchange-zero-day-cia-spies-security-roundup/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: CIA failures allegedly got US informants killed, a former NSA worker is charged under the Espionage Act, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman, Dhruv Mehrotra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Problem With Mental Health Bots]]></title>
        <id>632e515220bc56769c4131ee</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/mental-health-chatbots/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With human therapists in short supply, AI chatbots are trying to plug the gap—but it’s not clear how well they work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grace Browne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一日一技｜Obsidian Command 进阶用法三则]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75847</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75847"/>
        <updated>2022-10-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

数字文具盒征文活动 中看到许多将 Obsidian 纳入日常学习工作流的好文章，想必使用过程中或多或少都与命令（command）打过交道。所谓命令，其实就是在 Obsidian 执行的各种操作：新建文档、星标文档、打开大纲面板等常规操作，以及所有与插件的交互、使用快捷键执行的操作……这些都是命令。
和许多文本编辑器一样，Obsidian 内建了一个命令面板（Command Palette），用于快速搜索并执行命令。默认的快捷键 ⌘+P 唤起方便是方便，只不过这个内建的命令面板还是略显简陋了：只能搜索，顶多在设置中将常用命令置顶，就没了。它没办法记忆最近使用的项目，每次都要重新查找；并且文本编辑、核心插件、社区插件的命令一股脑儿混在一起，很多 几乎永远用不到的命令，由于首字母的关系，排名却很靠前。
尽管 Obsidian 一直在更新，也已经增加了许多呼声颇高的内容（比如 窗口多开），但还是没有往命令面板上做文章。你可能会说，常用的命令，用用快捷键就好了呀。不过我的系统全局快捷键已经很多了，所以除了极为常用的诸如加粗（⌘+B）这种命令，我还是倾向用快捷键以外的方式去执行命令。
那么本文将介绍三款优秀的社区插件，让 Obsidian 的命令更为好用。

写在前面：

本文若涉及快捷键，那么 modifier key 将会使用 Mac 标准的 ⌘、⌥、⇧ 等，Windows 系统请相应替换。
随着 Obsidian 的更新，许多插件已不再适配或是迁移、合并至新的版本。本文推荐的插件都是写作时点（2022-09-20）能够使用的。

你应该…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bakamio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[城市漫步指南 | 四日三晚浅品江南的秋]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75929</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75929"/>
        <updated>2022-10-01T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[前言
为了在上班前再抓紧时间享受一下旅行的快乐，我和女朋友一起去了一趟杭州和绍兴。十年前，我和父母曾经去过一次杭州和苏州，但那时正值盛夏，酷暑难耐，我的父亲出行时又是出了名的紧张和暴躁，导致少了不少游玩的乐趣，杭州在我心目中也并没有留下什么深刻的印象。在一位杭州「土著」同学的怂恿下，为了帮助杭州洗刷这个对她并不公平的心理评价，我决定再来一次杭州。
按照这位同学说，我们这一次来得正是时候，赶上了杭州为期两周的秋天，早来了太热，晚来了太冷。
她是没错的。九月底的杭州真的是——好舒服啊！
除了正午那几个小时，杭州的天气这几天一直稳定在很适宜的温度，在室内和室外几乎没有温差。哪怕是上午快十二点，大晴天走在大街上也只是有丝丝暖意，如果这时候有几阵微风从西湖吹来，送上岸边荷叶清新的香气和清凉，我就会情不自禁地把手臂张开，闭上眼睛，好好感受这让人舒服得跺脚的惬意。
因为我们这一次以休闲游为主，并没有安排很满的行程，这几天都是睡到自然醒，吃完饭中午才出门，所以行程上也安排得不是很有效率。作为一个旅行攻略太过勉强，但也确确实实享受到了放空身心的那种悠闲和惬意。
灵隐寺
食
很惭愧，这一次是摆烂的行程。因为不想时间太紧张，所以并没有专门搜一些当地人才会去的苍蝇馆子，吃的都是比较常见的连锁餐厅，外婆家、新白鹿、绿茶。我这个外地人尝不出地不地道，但坐着挺舒适，味道也挺好的。我特别喜欢西湖天地那家外婆家，旁边就是西湖，吃完饭去消消食也是一流的。
第一天晚上杭州的同学带我们去银泰附近吃了一家名为杭州酒家的餐厅。据说已经有一百年历史了。叫花鸡被一层壳包裹，需要客人颇具仪式感地亲自敲几下，而后师傅再帮忙敲开，鸡肉已经酥软无比，香味甚至渗进了骨头；熏鱼比我想象中的多汁，带着一种甜甜的味道；藕粉样子很好看，但感觉味道稍淡了些，响铃沾了不同的酱料味道很丰富。
叫化鸡响铃
住
这次我们选择了在湖滨步行街附近的一家…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hermanchannn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Challenge of Cracking Iran’s Internet Blockade]]></title>
        <id>633715a5010e2be68af5d47e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/subvert-iran-internet-blackout/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T21:16:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People around the world are rallying to subvert Iran's internet shutdown, but actually pulling it off is proving difficult and risky.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go Update iOS, Chrome, and HP Computers to Fix Serious Flaws]]></title>
        <id>63363df7af6115289c0e5f70</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ios-chrome-hp-whatsapp-critical-update-september/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: WhatsApp plugs holes that could be used for remote execution attacks, Microsoft patches a zero-day vulnerability, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate O'Flaherty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Matrix Update Patches Serious End-to-End Encryption Flaws]]></title>
        <id>63349aecc554667379f2d9f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/matrix-patches-vulnerabilities-that-completely-subvert-e2ee-guarantees/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The messenger protocol had gained popularity for its robust security, but vulnerabilities allowed attackers to decrypt messages and impersonate users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin, Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tech communities you should join! (online and in person)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/juliafmorgado/tech-communities-you-should-join-online-and-in-person-4nba</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/juliafmorgado/tech-communities-you-should-join-online-and-in-person-4nba"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T14:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#techtalks #webdev #community #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julia Furst Morgado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are You a Victim of Crypto Crime? Good Luck Getting Help]]></title>
        <id>632b64c600704d14b5ffb9a3</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cryptocurrency-cybercrime-law-enforcement/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Local law enforcement isn’t ready to deal with this new type of fraud, even with shady scams on the rise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Rizzo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mystery Hackers Are ‘Hyperjacking’ Targets for Insidious Spying]]></title>
        <id>633458ef995b6da54b57f057</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hyperjacking-vmware-mandiant/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For decades, security researchers warned about techniques for hijacking virtualization software. Now one group has put them into practice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How trigger browser to make a PDF from HTML using window.print()]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/climentea/simple-way-to-generate-pdf-from-html-21mh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/climentea/simple-way-to-generate-pdf-from-html-21mh"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T11:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alin Climente</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are your git aliases?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/imjoseangel/what-are-your-git-aliases-43om</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/imjoseangel/what-are-your-git-aliases-43om"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T20:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#git #beginners #tutorial #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Angel Munoz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Race to Find the Nord Stream Saboteurs]]></title>
        <id>6334a719dd4bc612fd8df151</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/nord-stream-pipeline-sabotage-explosion-russia-gas/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T20:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Damage to the pipeline that runs between Russia and Germany is being treated as deliberate. Finding out what happened may not be straightforward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Takes a Stab at a Captcha That Doesn’t Suck]]></title>
        <id>63332e18eecde8c117e7f622</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cloudflare-captcha-turnstile/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T13:05:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The internet infrastructure company has an alternative tool to check whether you’re human—and it doesn’t force you to pick out buses in tiny boxes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let me understand how JavaScript works under the hood]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/inancakduvan/let-me-understand-how-javascript-works-under-the-hood-3ibf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/inancakduvan/let-me-understand-how-javascript-works-under-the-hood-3ibf"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T12:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>İnanç Akduvan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tech Companies Are Reconsidering an Old Enemy]]></title>
        <id>632db7bff2203b5586fac00d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/friction-social-media-moderation/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody likes being asked to wait, but recent political history has shown that a completely frictionless internet has its own dangers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yasmin Green</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Love Twitter Bots and I Cannot Lie]]></title>
        <id>632aefbdc9bb1af7ef249866</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/bots-twitter-art-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t judge a bot by the troll farms—some make the internet a weirder and more wonderful place.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caroline Sinders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Kanban board with Node.js, React and Websockets 📝 ✨]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/novu/building-a-beautiful-kanban-board-with-nodejs-react-and-websockets-39dk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/novu/building-a-beautiful-kanban-board-with-nodejs-react-and-websockets-39dk"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T10:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #webdev #javascript #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevo David, novu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[0ctf2022 hessian-only-jdk writeup jdk原生链]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11732</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11732"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T08:51:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[0ctf2022 hessian-only-jdk writeup jdk原生链]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[警惕破解软件！APS 窃密木马已感染万余台设备]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11740</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11740"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[警惕破解软件！APS 窃密木马已感染万余台设备]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API安全漏洞靶场crapi的基本介绍与解题思路]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11734</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11734"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T08:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[API安全漏洞靶场crapi的基本介绍与解题思路]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Chatbot Aims to Steer People Away From Child Abuse Material]]></title>
        <id>63338f1d62435d269fdbdc3d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/pornhub-search-child-abuse-chatbot/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pornhub is trialing a new automated tool that pushes CSAM-searchers to seek help for their online behavior. Will it work?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Faster Programmer]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marcinwosinek/how-to-become-a-faster-programmer-hp9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marcinwosinek/how-to-become-a-faster-programmer-hp9"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T05:46:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcin Wosinek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Unlikely Cure for Burnout? A Second Job]]></title>
        <id>63221a4d036b54662b5104d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/overemployment-work/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Overemployment” sounds like more of the same old grind, but its underlying philosophy is critical of work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fadeke Adegbuyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Advocate for Data Privacy and Users' Rights]]></title>
        <id>6323876af1e5c40d2b1bc653</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-advocate-your-tech-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to speak up against Big Tech, unjust data collection, and surveillance? Here's how to be an activist in your community and beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omar L. Gallaga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dire Warnings in the Lapsus$ Hacker Joyride]]></title>
        <id>632a09f320bc56769c4131aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/lapsusdollar-uber-rockstar-breach-multifactor-authentication-weaknesses/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fun-loving cybercriminals blamed for breaches of Uber and Rockstar are exposing weaknesses in ways others aren't.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[某json 1.2.80 漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11727</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11727"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T08:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[某json 1.2.80 漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[关于HTTP Request Smuggling（HTTP请求夹带）的二三事]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11728</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11728"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T06:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[关于HTTP Request Smuggling（HTTP请求夹带）的二三事]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Things to Consider When Working On a Personal Project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maxr96/7-things-to-consider-when-working-on-a-personal-project-78d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maxr96/7-things-to-consider-when-working-on-a-personal-project-78d"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T22:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#beginners #programming #career #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Dev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Dear Unicorn Friend is Going on Vacation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devteam/our-dear-unicorn-friend-is-going-on-vacation-idm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devteam/our-dear-unicorn-friend-is-going-on-vacation-idm"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T19:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#meta #design #ux]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Halpern, The DEV Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web workers cheatsheet & 4 other webdev tips you may want to know 🚀]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mustapha/5-webdev-tips-you-may-want-to-know-2-41e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mustapha/5-webdev-tips-you-may-want-to-know-2-41e"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T13:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #css #html #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mustapha Aouas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Therapy Is Broken]]></title>
        <id>6328a9f4d884b4dcc941652d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/therapy-broken-mental-health-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone is telling one another to “get help,” but few acknowledge that the practice is often flawed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eleanor Cummins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Growing Old Online]]></title>
        <id>632a559feecde8c117e7f4f0</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/growing-old-online/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Millennials, the first generation to be online as kids, are starting to feel like we’ve aged out. Is there a way to age gracefully on the internet?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helena Fitzgerald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 HTML Tags for SEO🔍]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sampadsarker/10-html-tags-for-seo-9ib</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sampadsarker/10-html-tags-for-seo-9ib"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T06:46:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#html #seo #searchengine #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sampad Sarker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continue Using .env Files As Usual.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wiseai/continue-using-env-files-as-usual-2am5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wiseai/continue-using-env-files-as-usual-2am5"/>
        <updated>2022-09-24T13:46:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #node]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahmoud Harmouch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Local Storage Explained!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dboatengx/javascript-local-storage-explained-1di6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dboatengx/javascript-local-storage-explained-1di6"/>
        <updated>2022-09-24T09:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #beginners #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boateng Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[某开源堡垒机历史漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11721</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11721"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T15:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[某开源堡垒机历史漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘Surveillance Solutionism’ of Putting Cameras in NYC Subways]]></title>
        <id>632b3054d884b4dcc941655d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-surveillance-solutionism-of-putting-cameras-in-nyc-subways/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When “if you see something, say something” becomes “we see everything,” everyone loses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Fox Cahn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Awesome Notion Templates for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/surajondev/free-awesome-notion-templates-for-developers-43mh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/surajondev/free-awesome-notion-templates-for-developers-43mh"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T11:34:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #beginners #react]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Vishwakarma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Database GUIs in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/janproch/database-guis-in-javascript-2dpb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/janproch/database-guis-in-javascript-2dpb"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T10:27:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#database #sql #node #javascript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jan Prochazka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Your Productivity: Best Software For Dev Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jamieswift90/boost-your-productivity-best-software-for-dev-teams-476g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jamieswift90/boost-your-productivity-best-software-for-dev-teams-476g"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T08:24:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #programming #productivity #devops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Swift</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System Design: Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/system-design-netflix-3d9g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/system-design-netflix-3d9g"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T02:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#distributedsystems #architecture #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karan Pratap Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System Design: Twitter]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/system-design-twitter-865</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/system-design-twitter-865"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T02:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#distributedsystems #architecture #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karan Pratap Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-33980命令执行漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11723</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11723"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T15:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-33980命令执行漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[从前端代码审计挖掘未授权进入后台到文件上传拿下某色情网站]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11729</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11729"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T15:52:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[从前端代码审计挖掘未授权进入后台到文件上传拿下某色情网站]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dll劫持注入从原理到白加黑漏洞利用]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11711</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11711"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T15:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dll劫持注入从原理到白加黑漏洞利用]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Dangerous Meme in US Politics Is Over a Century Old]]></title>
        <id>6328bee136c33c0247a2f0ab</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/america-first-meme-politics/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many associate the “America First” movement with Trump, but its origins—and rebirth—are more complicated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED Ideas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System Design: WhatsApp]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/system-design-whatsapp-fld</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/system-design-whatsapp-fld"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T05:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#distributedsystems #architecture #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karan Pratap Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I'll teach you 7 Array methods. (with animations!)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fredysandoval/ill-teach-you-7-array-methods-with-animations-549c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fredysandoval/ill-teach-you-7-array-methods-with-animations-549c"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T21:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #array #beginners #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fredy Sandoval</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[对writeObject流程动点手脚]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11720</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11720"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T15:59:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[对writeObject流程动点手脚]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[关于"linux capability"的两个特殊案例]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11716</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11716"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T15:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[关于"linux capability"的两个特殊案例]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GenieACS CVE-2021-46704认证前RCE漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11722</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11722"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T15:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GenieACS CVE-2021-46704认证前RCE漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Games, Mysteries, and the Lure of QAnon]]></title>
        <id>63288cb640fe1e8870aa3b0e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/qanon-games-alternate-reality-conspiracy-theories/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What do puzzles, video games, and conspiracy theories have in common?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Hon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Every Blogger Should Save These 10 Insanely Useful Websites 👇]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hr21don/every-blogger-should-save-these-10-insanely-useful-websites-44ad</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hr21don/every-blogger-should-save-these-10-insanely-useful-websites-44ad"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T09:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#productivity #programming #webdev #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helitha Rupasinghe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Using .env Files Now!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gregorygaines/stop-using-env-files-now-kp0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gregorygaines/stop-using-env-files-now-kp0"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T21:04:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #node #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Gaines</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[goby指纹提取与yara逆向.md]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11701</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11701"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T15:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[goby指纹提取与yara逆向.md]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[记一次较为详细的某CMS代码审计]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11714</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11714"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T15:53:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[记一次较为详细的某CMS代码审计]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making a fast website is SUPER EASY 😏]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/enterspeed/making-a-fast-website-is-super-easy-9lb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/enterspeed/making-a-fast-website-is-super-easy-9lb"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T07:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #performance #programming #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kasper Andreassen, Enterspeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Figma Alternatives For A Blazingly Fast Increase In Your Productivity.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wiseai/9-figma-alternatives-for-a-blazingly-fast-increase-in-your-productivity-3g40</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wiseai/9-figma-alternatives-for-a-blazingly-fast-increase-in-your-productivity-3g40"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T07:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#design #uiweekly #productivity #ux]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahmoud Harmouch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Best UI Component Libraries/Frameworks in 2022 for Frontend Developers🔥]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aviyel/top-9-best-ui-component-librariesframeworks-in-2022-for-frontend-developers-b48</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aviyel/top-9-best-ui-component-librariesframeworks-in-2022-for-frontend-developers-b48"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T07:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #css #tailwindcss #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pramit Marattha, Aviyel Inc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop writing API functions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/saeedmosavat/stop-writing-api-functions-3693</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/saeedmosavat/stop-writing-api-functions-3693"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T23:22:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #codequality #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saeed Mosavat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[💁‍♂️ Built a Dev.to replica with The MERN stack and more]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marodevv/built-a-devto-replica-with-the-mern-stack-and-more-fbd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marodevv/built-a-devto-replica-with-the-mern-stack-and-more-fbd"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T12:43:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#showdev #javascript #react #node]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marwan mostafa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Git Commands I Use Every Day]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wadecodez/the-git-commands-i-use-every-day-5g17</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wadecodez/the-git-commands-i-use-every-day-5g17"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T12:34:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#git #beginners #programming #javascript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wade Zimmerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why our websites are slow — Importance of bundle size]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shreyvijayvargiya/why-our-websites-are-slow-importance-of-bundle-size-1le4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shreyvijayvargiya/why-our-websites-are-slow-importance-of-bundle-size-1le4"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T11:31:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#programming #react #javascript #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>shrey vijayvargiya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Debug React Apps With VS Code - Boost Your Debugging Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/profydev/how-to-debug-react-apps-with-vs-code-boost-your-debugging-productivity-1k05</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/profydev/how-to-debug-react-apps-with-vs-code-boost-your-debugging-productivity-1k05"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T12:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #javascript #webdev #vscode]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Johannes Kettmann, Profy.dev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（四）高级篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11705</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11705"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T02:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（四）高级篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[利用ASP.NET Web API Help Page文件上传]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11697</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11697"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T02:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[利用ASP.NET Web API Help Page文件上传]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[基于netfilter的rootkit]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11673</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11673"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T02:33:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[基于netfilter的rootkit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[19 Practical ES6 Snippets to Solve Common JS Problems 🚀💯]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/madza/19-practical-es6-snippets-to-solve-common-js-problems-31o9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/madza/19-practical-es6-snippets-to-solve-common-js-problems-31o9"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T15:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #frontend #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Madza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[不常见的内存与流量取证 -- WMCTF 2022 1!5!]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11699</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11699"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T15:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[不常见的内存与流量取证 -- WMCTF 2022 1!5!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2020-8558-跨主机访问127.0.0.1]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11674</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11674"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T15:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2020-8558-跨主机访问127.0.0.1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[红日安全团队ATT&CK(二)实战系列靶场]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11676</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11676"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T15:40:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[红日安全团队ATT&CK(二)实战系列靶场]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“黑猫”又伸出恶魔之手？揭秘BlackCat病毒的三重勒索]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11656</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11656"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T15:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“黑猫”又伸出恶魔之手？揭秘BlackCat病毒的三重勒索]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Modern Humans Can Learn From Ancient Software]]></title>
        <id>630fa634333af8e1504c49a1</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/modern-humans-learn-ancient-software-retrocomputing/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retrocomputing is about more than nostalgic nerdery. It’s also a way to keep your tech in perspective.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Ford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Must Know JavaScript Tips & Tricks 🎈]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dcodeyt/7-must-know-javascript-tips-tricks-2m8f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dcodeyt/7-must-know-javascript-tips-tricks-2m8f"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T12:49:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #beginners #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dom (dcode)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Free GumRoad products for Web Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/surajondev/10-free-gumroad-products-for-web-developers-1p6g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/surajondev/10-free-gumroad-products-for-web-developers-1p6g"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T11:38:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #react #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Vishwakarma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-1292的分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11703</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11703"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T13:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-1292的分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gitlab常见漏洞复现及后利用]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11690</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11690"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T13:39:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gitlab常见漏洞复现及后利用]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End of Roe Will Spark a Digital Civil War]]></title>
        <id>63208fea20bc56769c4130dc</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-end-of-roe-will-spark-a-digital-civil-war/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New privacy and expression laws that vary state to state will be a nightmare for platforms, and for users’ rights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Perault</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing APIs for humans: Error messages]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stripe/designing-apis-for-humans-error-messages-94p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stripe/designing-apis-for-humans-error-messages-94p"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T11:36:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#api #webdev #programming #stripe]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Asjes, Stripe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>