<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-10-26T10:44:53.988Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-10-26T10:44:53.988Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remove Letter To Equalize Frequency]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/salahelhossiny/remove-letter-to-equalize-frequency-1nh8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/salahelhossiny/remove-letter-to-equalize-frequency-1nh8"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T10:14:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You are given a 0-indexed string word, consisting of lowercase English letters. You need to select one index and remove the letter at that index from word so that the frequency of every letter present in word is equal.
Return true if it is possible to remove one letter so that the frequency of all letters in word are equal, and false otherwise.
Note:
The frequency of a letter x is the number of times it occurs in the string.

class Solution:
    def equalFrequency(self, word: str) -> bool:
        n = len(word)
        for i in range(n):
            if len(set(Counter(word[0:i] + word[i+1:]).values())) == 1:
                return True
        return False]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SalahElhossiny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need Web App and Mobile App Development Company?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maheenriaz/need-web-app-and-mobile-app-development-company-4joe</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maheenriaz/need-web-app-and-mobile-app-development-company-4joe"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T09:56:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zenkoders provide client-centric services that are user-friendly and aesthetic at the same time. We’ve collaborated with some fantastic companies and organizations to provide them with our exceptional services all across the globe including, Ecommerce App Development Services, Food Delivery App Development Services, HealthCare App Development Services, NFT App Development Services, and Real Estate App Development Services to help them construct their ideal digital products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>maheenriaz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s when your Samsung phone or tablet might get Android 13]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/26/23424170/android-13-update-samsung-release-schedule</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/26/23424170/android-13-update-samsung-release-schedule"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T09:41:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Samsung Galaxy S22 family is expected to recieve the update by the end of October 2022, with additional Samsung devices to follow. | Photo by Chris Welch / The Verge
    

  
A One UI 5.0 release schedule has reportedly appeared on the Korean-language version of Samsung’s Members App. It gives us a good indication of when the stable version of the Android 13-based update could arrive for Samsung’s lineup of Galaxy phones and tablets in South Korea and, eventually, the US and Europe.
As reported by Sammobile, the One UI 5.0 update will be landing on most high-end Samsung phones and tablets by November 2022. Mid-range Galaxy devices and some older flagship models will soon follow, getting the update in either December 2022 or January 2023. It’s expected that additional eligible Samsung devices will get the update around Q1 and Q2 of 2023.
Some of Samsung’s latest flagships have already received the update,...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In One Minute : JSON]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rakeshkr2/in-one-minute-json-1abn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rakeshkr2/in-one-minute-json-1abn"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T09:39:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JSON (JavaScript Object Notation) is an open standard file format and data interchange format that uses human-readable text to store and transmit data objects consisting of attribute–value pairs and arrays (or other serializable values).
It is a common data format with diverse uses in electronic data interchange, including that of web applications with servers.
It was derived from JavaScript, but many modern programming languages include code to generate and parse JSON-format data.




Douglas Crockford originally specified the JSON format in the early 2000s. He and Chip Morningstar sent the first JSON message in April 2001.
Official website :- https://json.org/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rakesh KR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu Budgie 22.10 的新变化]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15179-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15179-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T09:13:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu Budgie 22.10 是一个有趣的版本，它删除了几个 GNOME 应用程序，以及一些其他改进。




Ubuntu Budgie 是 Ubuntu 的官方版本，因其传统的桌面界面和最小的软件膨胀而广受欢迎。

Ubuntu Budgie 22.10 的发布带来了一些关键的调整和补充。

🆕 Ubuntu Budgie 22.10 有什么新变化



基于 Ubuntu 22.10 “充满活力的捻角羚Kinetic Kudu”，Ubuntu Budgie 22.10 带来了 Budgie 桌面 10.6.4 和许多其他改进。

一些值得注意的亮点包括:


增强型 Budgie 控制中心Control Center

更新了 Budgie 的“欢迎Welcome”应用

替换各种基于 GNOME 的应用程序

对翻译进行了更新


Budgie 桌面和控制中心



Budgie 桌面以及更新到 V10.6.4, 它添加了一个新的全局选项来控制小程序之间的间距，并对工作区和时钟小程序进行了各种改进。



Budgie 控制中心Control Center也得到了一堆调整，例如重新设计的显示颜色配置文件支持，修改了对屏幕分享的支持，如 RDP 和 VNC，用于显示缩放的选项，等等。

升级了欢迎应用



Ubuntu Budgie 22.10 特别升级了 Budgie 的欢迎应用，改善了翻译以及一些其他改进。

默认的应用的变化

Ubuntu Budgie 的开发人员已经开始替换和删除基于 GNOME 的应用程序，转而使用基于 MATE 的应用程序和其他替代品。

他们决定这样做是因为基于 GNOME 的应用程序在 Budgie 中的外观与其他具有圆角边缘的应用程序的外观不一致。

这些不一致是由于 GNOME 根据其样式和主题需求而转到 Libadwaita 库造成的。

Libadwaita 库是 GNOME 的一个有争议的补充，没有多少用户喜欢，你可以通过我们的报道来了解更多信息。


你对在 Linux 世界中 GNOME 的 Libadwaita 库怎么看？


以下是一些已删除或替换的应用程序：


GNOME 计算器被 MATE 计算器取代。

删除了 GNOME 日历。

GNOME 系统监视器已由 MATE 系统监视器取代。

删除了 GNOME 截图。

字体管理器 替代了 GNOME 字体查看器。


🛠️ 其他改变

其他改变包括以下：


重新开发的内置主题

移除 PulseAudio，并支持 PipeWire

原生的截图功能

支持 WebP 图像

能够查看显示器的刷新率


你可以通过 发行说明 了解更多。

📥 下载 Ubuntu Budgie 22.10

你可以在 Ubuntu 中央镜像仓库 或者它的 官方网站 下载最新的 ISO。

其官方网站可能需要一段时间才能提供 ISO。


下载 Ubuntu Budgie 22.10



💡 Ubuntu Budgie 22.10 将支持 9 个月直到 2023 年 6 月。如果你想使用稳定的功能，更应该选择 LTS 版本。


💬 你如何看待这个非 LTS 版本？愿意尝试一下吗？


via: https://news.itsfoss.com/ubuntu-budgie-22-10-release/

作者：Sourav Rudra 选题：lkxed 译者：littlebirdnest 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[M2E Cloud — Multichannel listing, inventory & order management platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/m2e-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/m2e-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T08:59:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[support@m2ecloud.com 

Drop us a line if you would like just to chat too!
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hinge plans to add video verification feature as ‘romance scams’ soar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/26/23424169/hinge-video-verification-feature-romance-scams-catfishing</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/26/23424169/hinge-video-verification-feature-romance-scams-catfishing"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T08:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A spread of Hinge’s existing profile features. | Image: Hinge
    

  
Match Group dating app Hinge is rolling out a new verification feature next month that will allow users to prove who they say they are by filming a short video selfie, Wired reports. The optional feature will prompt users to record a short clip, which Match Group will then compare against the photos posted on their profiles using a combination of machine learning tools and human moderation. If a user passes the test, their profile gets a “Verified” badge, providing an additional assurance to would-be daters. 
The launch of the feature comes as the amount of money lost as part of so-called “romance scams” is soaring. In February, the FTC reported that people lost a record $547 million to these scams in 2021, an increase of 80 percent...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Login System using Redux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/danielonugha0/building-a-login-system-using-redux-5ce3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/danielonugha0/building-a-login-system-using-redux-5ce3"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T08:38:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A login is a set of credentials used to authenticate a user. Most often, these consist of a username and password. However, a login may include other information, such as a PIN number, passcode, or passphrase. React Redux is the official React binding for Redux. It allows React components to read data from a Redux Store, and dispatch Actions to the Store to update data. Redux helps apps to scale by providing a sensible way to manage state through a unidirectional data flow model. React Redux is conceptually simple.
Goal
Table of Content
Introduction
Creating our React App
Creating our Login  Application
Login Value Inputs
Implementing Redux 
Final Outputs
Conclusion
Installing and Setting up React
npx create-react-app Login System
We have successfully installed our react application.
Creat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Onugha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webasyst Teamwork — Easy-to-use task tracker for teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/webasyst-teamwork</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/webasyst-teamwork"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T08:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dark mode pictures & 4 other webdev tips you may want to know 🚀]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mustapha/dark-mode-pictures-4-other-webdev-tips-you-may-want-to-know-2od</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mustapha/dark-mode-pictures-4-other-webdev-tips-you-may-want-to-know-2od"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T08:12:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. Dark mode pictures


This is how you can display different pictures in dark mode:

More on this topic on the article below:
Responsive images for better performance: Start using srcset and picture
Mustapha Aouas ・ Nov 8 '21 ・ 5 min read
#html
        #performance
        #webdev
        #tutorial
      
 


  
  
  2. HTML lang attribute


In HTML, the lang attribute specifies the language in which a content is written in and it can be used to help search engines index your site:

 


  
  
  3. CSS :lang


You can use the :lang pseudo-class to target elements based on the language they are determined to be in. Here is an example:

 




Hi there! I'm Mustapha, a technical writer, speaker and a passionate JS / TS developer. Follow me on Twitter for daily tech tips 🚀
 


  
  
  4. No script


Use the <noscript> element to provide alternative content for browsers that do not support scripting, or in which javascript has been disabled:

 


  
  
  5. Devtools tip: Last evaluated expression


You can access the most recently evaluated expression by typing $_ in the console:

 
 
That's all for now. I hope you found this useful! 
Until next time, have a nice week!
 

  
  
  What to read next?




  
    
A deep dive into ES6 Classes
Mustapha Aouas ・ Oct 26 '21 ・ 7 min read
#javascript
        #webdev
        #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mustapha Aouas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mailcoach Cloud — Let's make  email marketing easy and affordable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/mailcoach-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/mailcoach-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T08:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://freek.dev/2363-mailcoach...
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Have you tried React classnames?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dailydevtips1/have-you-tried-react-classnames-2845</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dailydevtips1/have-you-tried-react-classnames-2845"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T07:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regarding classes in React, we get a lot of power out of the box.
We can leverage the classnames package, which has been in the React ecosystem since 2015.
If all you do is write static classes like this:
<div className='static-class'></div>

This article might not be for you. Not to disrespect you, but in that case, keep doing what you are doing.
React classnames rock when it comes to dynamic classes or combined classes.
A combined class, for instance, if we allow the className to be passed from a parent component like this.
<div className={`existing-class ${className}`}>

Or even classes that render conditionally.
<div className={`existing-class ${success && 'bg-green'}`}>

Let's see how this would like with React classnames, but before we dive into that, we have to install it first.
npm install classnames

I tend to import it differently, so I never get confused with the default className by doing this.
import classnames from 'classnames';

And now we can use it like this.
<div className={classnames('foo', 'bar')}></div>

Or, in the more advanced examples, we can do stuff like this:
<div className={classNames('existing-class', className)}>

<div className={classNames('existing-class', 'bg-green': success)}>

And this is where it shines. It's a great way to abstract, difficult class conditions to be more readable.
For the result of your output code, it doesn't matter which way you go. It will be the same.
If you are an avid React user and use conditional classes, I would like you to try classnames.
Thank you for reading my blog. Feel free to subscribe to my email newsletter and connect on Facebook or Twitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bongers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tab Notes — Make notes on the browser new tab like articles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tab-notes</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tab-notes"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T07:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Setup Jenkins On Docker Container Using Ansible (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mmphego/how-i-setup-jenkins-on-docker-container-using-ansible-part-1-49po</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mmphego/how-i-setup-jenkins-on-docker-container-using-ansible-part-1-49po"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Story


Recently, my team found themselves in a situation where they needed to have a staging or development Jenkins environment. The motivation behind the need for a new environment was that we needed a backup Jenkins environment and a place where new Jenkins users could get their hands dirty with Jenkins without having to worry about changes to the production environment and most importantly we needed to ensure that our Jenkins environment is stored as code and could be easily replicated.
For this task, I decided to pair with my padawan/mentee (@AneleMakhaba) as he was a good fit for the task (and I wanted to disseminate the knowledge as well) which had been in the backlog for a while.
I thought this meme was relevant to the task.

Our initial approach to the task was to:
Create a Do…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mpho Mphego</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Django eCommerce - Use Products from Stripe]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sm0ke/free-django-ecommerce-dw-products-from-stripe-3792</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sm0ke/free-django-ecommerce-dw-products-from-stripe-3792"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T07:43:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello coders!
This article presents an open-source Django & Stripe Mini eCommerce starter that builds product pages using the information saved in Stripe Dashboard. Once the Stripe Secrets are provided in the .env file, the superusers are able to pull the products from Stripe and edit the information via a simple UI. The sources, released under the MIT License, can be used in commercial projects and eLearning activities. Thanks for reading!
👉 Django & Stripe eCommerce - source code

🚀 Free support via Email & Discord (just in case)








  
  
  ✨ How it works


The sources come with a default product, saved in the local filesystem. If the user initiates the purchase, the application warns that the Stripe Secrets are not provided and the flow cannot continue. The steps, as explained in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sm0ke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-41852 Apache Commons Jxpath 漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11769</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11769"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T07:29:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-41852 Apache Commons Jxpath 漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trillion — AR powered try-on of jewellery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/trillion</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/trillion"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T07:19:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[优化 Kubernetes 中的 Java 无服务器函数]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15178-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15178-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T07:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[在 Kubernetes 中运行无服务器函数时，实现更快的启动速度和更小的内存占用。




由于运行上千个应用程序容器荚Pod所耗费的资源多，令它实现较少工作节点和资源占用所需成本也较高，所以在使用 Kubernetes 时，快速启动和较少的内存占用是至关重要的。在 Kubernetes 平台运行容器化微服务时，内存占用是比吞吐量更重要的考量因素，这是因为：


由于需要持续运行，所以耗费资源更多（不同于 CPU 占用）

微服务令开销成本成倍增加

一个单体应用程序变为若干个微服务的情况（例如 20 个微服务占用的存储空间约有 20GB）


这些情况极大影响了无服务器函数的发展和 Java 部署模型。到目前为止，许多企业开发人员选择 Go、Python 或 Node.js 这些替代方案来解决性能瓶颈，直到出现了 Quarkus 这种基于 kubernetes 的原生 Java 堆栈，才有所改观。本文介绍如何在使用了 Quarkus 的 kubernetes 平台上进行性能优化，以便运行无服务器函数。

容器优先的设计理念

由于 Java 生态系统中传统的框架都要进行框架的初始化，包括配置文件的处理、classpath 的扫描、类加载、注解的处理以及构建元模型，这些过程都是必不可少的，所以它们都比较耗费资源。如果使用了几种不同的框架，所耗费的资源也是成倍增加。

Quarkus 通过“左移shifting left”，把所有的资源开销大的操作都转移到构建阶段，解决了这些 Java 性能问题。在构建阶段进行代码和框架分析、字节码转换和动态元模型生成，而且只有一次，结果是：运行时可执行文件经过高度优化，启动非常快，不需要经过那些传统的启动过程，全过程只在构建阶段执行一次。



更重要的是：Quarkus 支持构建原生可执行文件，它具有良好性能…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doing 64-bit math on a 16-bit system]]></title>
        <id>70264 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/64-bit-math"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doing 64-bit math on a 16-bit system
Jerome Shidel
Wed, 10/26/2022 - 03:00

            
A few years ago, I wrote a command-line math program for FreeDOS called VMATH. It was capable of performing only extremely simple mathematical operations on very small unsigned integers. With some recent interest in basic math in the FreeDOS community, I improved VMATH to provide basic math support on signed 64-bit integers.
The process of manipulating big numbers using only 16-bit 8086 compatible assembly instructions is not straightforward. I would like to share some samples of the techniques used by VMATH. Some of the methods used are fairly easy to grasp. Meanwhile, others can seem a little strange. You may even learn an entirely new way of performing some basic math.
The techniques explained here …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerome Shidel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips for using the Linux test command]]></title>
        <id>70258 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/test-command-linux"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tips for using the Linux test command
Seth Kenlon
Wed, 10/26/2022 - 03:00

            
The [ command, often called a "test," is a command from the GNU Core Utils package, and initiates a conditional statement in Bash. Its function is exactly the same as the test command. When you want to execute a command only when something is either true or false, use the [ or the test command. However, there's a significant difference between [ or test and [[, and there's a technical difference between those commands and your shell's versions of them.
[ vs test commands in Linux
The [ and the test commands, installed by the GNU Core Utils package, perform the same function using a slightly different syntax. (You might find it difficult to search for documentation using the single left-square bracket ch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Kenlon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【拾键杂谈】键盘圈不平凡的一年，我的所见所闻和所感。]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76367</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76367"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T06:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

2022 年，对我来说是不平凡的一年，键圈的兴亡成败在这一年格外明显。也是这一年我开始从一个消费者转变成一个创作者，遇到了更多的人，也想了了更多过去不会思考的问题。下面来讲讲我这一年的所思所想和所感，以及今后的一些打算。虽然都是些浅短的认识，但是分享出来也算是一种体验，非常感谢大家的观看和意见。欢迎评论区友好讨论。
键盘圈的大趋势
现代社会人与人的交流不再局限于过去话语和书信的形式，而更多倾向于快捷的网络输入交流。快捷频繁的信息互通使得输入工具成为生活工作长时间高频率接触的日常用品。2020 年的疫情提早将线上办公大规模地带入人们的生活之中，人们也重新开始审视自己的办公桌搭，机械键盘市场在疫情之下，不降反增。
机械键盘热度上涨这件事，无论是从日常生活中关于机械键盘话题讨论度愈发增高，还是从近些年来机械键盘品牌数急剧增加都可以得到一定程度的论证。
数据来源：什么值得买
近些年来，在机械键盘领域我能明显感知到的就是选择越来越多了，无论是量产还是客制化，无论是轴体、键帽、套件。国内机械键盘在「物质」水平上，毫无疑问的成长了。
在轴体领域，国产轴体自 2010-2012 开始萌芽，在 2019 年这个关键节点打出了名声，国内轴体市场也从 Cherry 的独角戏演变成现在的百家争鸣。
佳达隆的产品时间线 2012—2020
在键帽领域，过去的客制化玩家大多只能选择 GMK、SP 等海外品牌，如今有国产老牌客制化键帽 JTK、2019 年出现的 Domikey 和 2022 年入场的 PBTfans 以及各种各样的键帽代工厂，包括量产领域也出…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>车不能快</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[pypa has started to monitor workflows and tests]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kantarci/pypa-has-started-to-monitor-workflows-and-tests-2mi7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kantarci/pypa-has-started-to-monitor-workflows-and-tests-2mi7"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T06:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World famous packaging and virtual env management tool pypa has started to monitor their GitHub Actions and see the results:
https://pypa.app.runforesight.com/repositories/github/pypa/pipenv/workflow-run/180087c7-e109-37be-8402-236691c00948/9092458891/tests
They have almost 20 jobs on their main workflow. It looks very complex and windows tests looks a bit problematic 🤔]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Burak Kantarcı</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“文章助手”小程序已半残]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15177-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15177-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T06:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[前天，我收到了腾讯官方发来的一个警告：


“因用户投诉并经平台审核，你的小程序涉嫌滥用小程序接口能力，影响用户体验行为。”


惊讶之下，我发现是我们几年前为了解决公众号文章内不能放置链接而开发的“文章助手”小程序被警告了。

众所周知，一般情况下，微信文章不能像网页一样放入链接的。对于一般的文字性内容，这其实并无大碍，但是对于我们这种技术类文章，常常会有一些链接，以便读者可以深入了解相关内容。因此，这种限制对我们来说是一种缺陷，为了解决这种问题，我们陆续想过几种方法，比如利用文末的“阅读原文”、在文章内注明完整链接等。最后，我们在 2019 年想到可以开发一个小程序来 辅助提供 这个链接。

通过一些 简单的方式，可以在你的微信文章中需要放置链接的地方嵌入这个“文章助手”小程序。用户只需要点击该小程序链接，即可显示该链接，并自动复制链接到剪贴板，然后只需要打开浏览器粘贴访问即可。

我自己对这种委曲求全的解决方案感觉比较满意。

现在，这个有两年没有继续添加新功能的小程序被警告了。于是我仔细查看了警告内容，在腾讯官方提供的《微信小程序平台运营规范》中是这样说的：


5.15.4 滥用操作剪切板接口

在用户使用剪切板功能进行复制操作后，恶意、强行中断小程序内功能服务或业务的完整流程，要求用户跳转或使用其他方式才可完整体验业务流程，影响用户体验。

用户未进行任何操作情况下，小程序默认读取用户剪切板信息。


考虑到申诉基本上不会得到解决（事实上我申诉了，也被驳回了），我只能修改相关代码，将以下行为做了调整：


不检测剪贴板内容长度（原本是为了避免当剪贴板内有较多内容而被覆盖）

不自动复制链接到剪贴板，而需要用户手动点击一下才复制


以我的估计，这样就不算滥用了吧？……

然而，新版本提交之后，紧接着，“文章助手”小程序就被封了剪贴板能力：


因用户投诉并经平台审核，发现帐号已发布的服务涉嫌滥用小程序接口能力，影响用户体验

已封禁服务的“操作剪贴板”能力


哑然。

无奈之下再次发起无用的申诉（已被驳回），并寻求客服解答。经过漫长的等待，客服给出了如下答复：


审核部门排查发现你的小程序内活动通过文本口令引导跳转其他渠道体验或进行，属于滥用剪切板能力 请开发者对小程序进行全面排查以及整改，将涉及违规的内容移除(包括但不仅限于内容展示、代码、路径等)，如有隐藏内容、路径、代码等，也需一并移除


呵，合着是不让用户粘贴链接到浏览器啊！

原本“文章助手”小程序内会提示用户“链接已复制，请在浏览器内粘贴打开”，看来这是摸了老虎屁股了。

而没有剪贴板能力的“文章助手”小程序，可以说是已经失去了一半用处。

那现在我有两个选择：


放弃这个小程序（这样我也不用每个月支付云开发的 20 元费用，需要说明的是，这个小程序是完全免费，没有任何广告和赞助，公益提供给任何人使用的）；

看看是否还有抢救的机会。


考虑到这个小程序已经累计有了 16 万用户，并为近 50 万个链接提供过服务，如果就此关闭，是对既往用户的不负责。因此，经过我灵机一动，我考虑可以完整地显示链接，让用户自己复制，至于复制后干什么，我不说，我也不知道，我也不想知道。

所以，你看的 0.4.7 版的“文章助手”就是这样了。

至于这样是否还会触犯腾讯的禁忌，我就不知道了，只能说，大家且行且珍惜吧。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 handy PyCharm Plugins and 10 Hotkeys for Beginner]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vadimkolobanov/5-handy-pycharm-plugins-and-10-hotkeys-for-beginner-4gpd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vadimkolobanov/5-handy-pycharm-plugins-and-10-hotkeys-for-beginner-4gpd"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T06:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From author


You can find many interesting articles on my website, please visit it Happy Python Website
Automatic translation in the browser will help you to study everything conveniently. 
If the material is useful, I will try to translate all my articles for you
I think all developers, after choosing a programming language for themselves, thought about the question: "Where to write code?" I, as a developer in the Python programming language, turned to the Internet, where many answers were found.
For different languages — there are correspondingly different solutions. In fact, the development environment is just a programmer's "comfort zone" and it will not suit everyone. This applies not only to Python, but also to other languages.
After reading a few articles, I settled on the PyCharm …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vadim Kolobanov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Controlling Services and Daemons]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/elisamp12/controlling-services-and-daemons-1jo5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/elisamp12/controlling-services-and-daemons-1jo5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T06:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apa itu "DAEMON"
Menjelaskan Unit Layanan
Unit layanan memiliki service dan mewakili layanan sistem, digunakan untuk memulai daemon yang sering diakses, seperti server web.
Unit soket memiliki ekstensi .Jika klien terhubung ke soket, systemd akan memulai daemon dan meneruskan koneksi ke sana, digunakan untuk menunda dimulainya layanan pada saat boot dan untuk memulai layanan yang lebih jarang digunakan sesuai permintaan.
Unit jalur memiliki path digunakan untuk menunda aktivasi layanan hingga terjadi perubahan sistem file tertentu, digunakan untuk layanan yang menggunakan direktori spool seperti sistem pencetakan.
Melihat Status Layanan
1.Masuk ke ssh 

2.Perintah berikut ini untuk Perintah systemctl yang berfungsi memverifikasi status layanan tertentu. 

3.Perintah berikut ini "systemctl"…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elisamp12</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The OM-5 is the first leftover Olympus camera to be branded OM System, and I get sad looking at it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/26/23423252/omsystem-om5-mirrorless-camera-rip-olympus-announcement-price-specs</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/26/23423252/omsystem-om5-mirrorless-camera-rip-olympus-announcement-price-specs"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new OM-5 is a small body, weighing 366 grams, designed to size up with the Zuiko line of f/4 zooms and compact prime lenses. | Image: OM System
    

  
When Olympus sold its camera division and reformed as OM System, it hyped up a push toward computational photography with its new mirrorless cameras — this is not that camera. Today, OM System is announcing the new OM-5, a $1,199.99 mirrorless camera that launches late next month and looks like a zombified husk of Olympus. I’m sure it will be a fine camera, but I can’t help feeling depressed when I look at it.
Sure, the OM-1 was technically OM System’s first camera release, but it was still branded Olympus. Now, with the OM-5, it’s proudly wearing the OM System name on its forehead, something that’s sure to only please a handful of people in a marketing meeting somewhere.
Image: OM System
      We’ll have to get used to...
  
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Enterprise Linux, Open Sourse dan Close Source, Distribusi Linux, Virtualisasi vs Container vs BareMetal Service]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ainunrfy/red-hat-enterprise-linux-opensourse-dan-closesourcedistribusi-linuxvirtualisasi-vs-container-vs-baremetal-service-21h9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ainunrfy/red-hat-enterprise-linux-opensourse-dan-closesourcedistribusi-linuxvirtualisasi-vs-container-vs-baremetal-service-21h9"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T05:50:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Memulai dengan Red Hat Enterprise Linux serta pengenalan tentang OpenSourse dan Close Source, Distribusi Linux, Virtualisasi vs Container vs BareMetal Service.
1. Pengertian Linux
Linux adalah sistem operasi open source yang paling terkenal dan bebas dikembangkan siapapun sehingga banyak digunakan oleh para profesional TI. 
Lebih hemat biaya karena Linux bisa diperoleh secara gratis
Cenderung lebih aman karena untuk menjalankan aplikasi di Linux membutuhkan otorisasi dengan memasukkan kata sandi.
Linux dapat berjalan di hampir semua perangkat dengan lancar karena Linux tidak terlalu membutuhkan sumber daya RAM, CPU, dan Hard Drive yang besar.
Linux menyediakan akses mudah ke command-line interface (CLI) yang kuat.
Linux adalah sistem operasi modular yang memungkinkan Anda dapat mengganti a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ainunrfy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightcast — Just a simple podcast player, no recommendation algorithm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/lightcast</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/lightcast"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T05:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TikrBuddy — The fastest way to value any stock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tikrbuddy</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tikrbuddy"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T04:42:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dimensional — The social, personality testing platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/dimensional-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/dimensional-2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T04:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Valideate — Validate ideas before spending time & money on it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/valideate</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/valideate"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T04:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple confirms the iPhone is getting USB-C, but isn’t happy about the reason why]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/26/23423977/iphone-usb-c-eu-law-joswiak-confirms-compliance-lightning</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/26/23423977/iphone-usb-c-eu-law-joswiak-confirms-compliance-lightning"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T04:11:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Amelia Holowaty Krales / The Verge
    

  
Apple has given its most direct confirmation yet that a USB-C-equipped iPhone will happen, now that the European Union is mandating that all phones sold in its member countries use the connector if they have a physical charger. When asked by The Wall Street Journal’s Joanna Stern if the company would replace Lightning, Apple’s senior vp of worldwide marketing, Greg Joswiak, answered by saying: “Obviously, we’ll have to comply; we have no choice.”
Stern brought the law up during a talk with Joswiak and software VP Craig Federighi at the WSJ’s Tech Live conference and followed up by asking when we can expect to see USB-C on an iPhone. Joswiak replied, “the Europeans are the ones dictating timing for European customers.” Currently, the law...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast Search Page — All your podcast episodes, searchable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/podcast-search-page</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/podcast-search-page"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T03:57:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://podsearch.page to give podcasters a home page for their podcast where they can promote their channels, search content and share favorite moments.

Simply provide the link to your podcast (RSS, Apple Podcasts, etc.), and we create a page for you. Out of the box all of your episodes will be searchable, linking to the exact moment you’re looking for.  Remember that time Lex’s guest talked about whether “AI will kill us all”? Or want to find when you had that “person that works on RNA stuff”? Now you can. Once you’ve found that favorite moment, copy the link and share it with your listeners, or that person on Twitter you think it might be useful for. Your page updates automatically when new episodes are posted.

A year ago building something like this would have required a PhD and writing a ton of machine learning code. We think that building search that understands opaque content like audio should be simple as making a couple API calls. We’re building a search platform that enables these user experiences, and it’s what powering the site you see here (blog post on how to use it coming soon!). If you have audio or other content you’d like to make searchable we’d love to help you, please get in touch - https://airtable.com/shr3ukDZGRv....
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一键保存全文到 Obsidian 以及本地快照、自动标注，适合新用户的简悦 Obsidian 配置库]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43719</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/simpread-obsidian/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T03:23:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Obsidian 是一款强大的可扩展的知识库软件，它可以帮你管理本地的 .md 文件，并让这些文件以链接的方式互相连接起来，被誉为你永远的第二个大脑。 简悦则是一款适配了很多很多网站的开源沉浸式阅读扩]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>开发者推荐账号</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPhone 相机进化之路：单摄时代的功能演变（07 - 15）]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76395</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76395"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T02:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[最近我在抽屉里翻出来一台尘封已久的 iPhone 5s，它刚刚在 20 年才从我手中退役，一眨眼它就快发布十年了。在用它的时候我其实对手机了解很少，也不懂摄影，就只是拿来刷网页。于是趁着这个由头，重头开始了解一下 iPhone 的一些变化。首先想写的是 iPhone 相机的一些内容，暂时先写单摄时代的 13 款机型。照例先给出我全文的脉络，供各位参考。
太不巧整理，截自我的 Notion 页面
iPhone + iPhone OS 1 / iPhone 3G + iPhone OS 2
2007 年 1 月 9 日，乔布斯在初代 iPhone 的发布会上只用了一句话介绍其搭载的相机

看后面，最显眼的就是内置的 2 百万像素摄像头。
iPhone 发布会
 
关于相机方面大量的篇幅其实是在介绍照片软件，搭配 3.5 寸的可触摸屏幕，可以向左滑动或向右滑动查看照片，捏合放大缩小，横置手机的同时照片也跟着变换方向等。

第三个我想要展示给大家看的手机功能是照片。你知道的，我之前说过，在iPhone里内置有一台二百万像素的相机，我们也有着最酷的照片管理软件，它在移动设备中是最好的。但是我认为它在所有的平台中也都堪称最棒。这是我们的照片，我正在进入照片库，这就是照片库，在这里我可以用我的手指来滑动浏览照片，相当酷。让我们看看相册，我要选择意大利，让我们从第一张开始，我可以通过滑动手机来浏览这些照片。我可以翻看照片库，大家看这是一张风景照片，现在我调转了我的手机方向，然后它就变成了这个样子，酷吗？怎么样？当我在看这张风景照片的时候我也可以滑动它。怎么样？是不是看上去还不错？我还可以把一些照片放大，我能用我的手指来对它进行缩放。我可以让手指分开来让图片变大，酷不酷？我还能移动照片，怎么样，酷吗？还可以把照片设置为手机壁纸，这样就能设置成为壁纸。当我回到主页，然后锁屏，当我解锁之后，我设…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>太不巧</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The feds’ new open-access policy: Who’s gonna pay for it?]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892918</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892918"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T00:08:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Currently, researchers often have to choose between publishing and science.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad’s bringing back the early 2000s with a transparent charging brick]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/25/23423691/nomad-transparent-30w-charger</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/25/23423691/nomad-transparent-30w-charger"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T00:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad Transparent 30W USB-C charger | Image: Nomad
    

  
Nomad, known for its sleek accessories made from leather and metal, is playing around with a new material: transparent plastic. The company has announced a limited edition version of its 30W USB-C charger with a frosty-grey case that gives you a peek at the intricate electronics inside.
As with a lot of modern electronics, there’s not actually a ton to see. Sure, it uses GaN components to achieve its small size, but that’s not really obvious just by looking at it. To the untrained eye, it mostly seems like a neat collection of capacitors, solder joints, and various other components.
Luckily for Nomad, that makes for an incredibly cool aesthetic (at least in my opinion), especially for people like me who can appreciate electrical...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starlink satellite internet for moving vehicles launches in December]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/25/23423755/spacex-starlink-for-rvs-moving-vehicles-flat-high-performance</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/25/23423755/spacex-starlink-for-rvs-moving-vehicles-flat-high-performance"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T23:32:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image: SpaceX
    

  
SpaceX has announced that its Starlink for RVs satellite internet service will be available for moving vehicles starting in December 2022. While you’ve been able to mount one of the satellite dishes onto or outside of a stationary vehicle for a while now, it was intended for use only while parked, like at a campsite or remote cabin (though there were those that tried to make it work on the go). Soon, you won’t have to sacrifice connectivity when you pack up and hit the road, but that ability won’t come cheap.
While the standard Starlink for RV service uses SpaceX’s $599 satellite dish, using it in motion requires a Flat High Performance dish, which will cost a whopping $2,500. (When I visited the order screen, there was also a $50...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UIHUT Figma Plugin — Access 21000+ resources by copy paste from Figma plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/uihut-figma-plugin</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/uihut-figma-plugin"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T23:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[www.uihut.com
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s new App Store tax on ads is a direct shot at Meta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/25/23423637/apple-app-store-tax-boosted-social-media-posts</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/25/23423637/apple-app-store-tax-boosted-social-media-posts"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T23:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Illustration by Alex Castro
    

  
Just when I thought the relationship between Apple and Meta couldn’t get more hostile, here we are.
On Monday, Apple quietly updated its App Store rules to require that iOS developers use in-app purchases — and thereby give Apple 30 percent — on “sales of ‘boosts’ for posts in a social media app.” This primarily affects Facebook and Instagram, which let people pay to boost the reach of their posts. It’s the first time Apple has directly taxed advertising in iOS apps.
Meta, of course, isn’t happy. Company spokesperson Tom Channick sent The Verge the following statement: “Apple continues to evolve its policies to grow their own business while undercutting others in the digital economy. Apple previously said it didn’t take a share of...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reality Tasks — Kanban board & to-do list in the same modern app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/reality-tasks-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/reality-tasks-2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T22:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With shots and infections, the most common COVID symptoms have shifted]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892816</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892816"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T21:28:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beware of unexplained sneezing, which is becoming a more common COVID symptom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Python Lambda Function Works – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-lambda-function-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-lambda-function-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T20:37:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the beautiful things about Python is that it is generally one of the most intuitive programming languages out there. Still, certain concepts can be difficult to grasp and comprehend. The lambda function is one of them.  I've been there. When I first started learning Python, I skipped]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ibrahim Abayomi Ogunbiyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple releases patch for iPhone and iPad 0-day reported by anonymous source]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892801</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892801"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T20:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Freshly released iOS 16.1 and iPadOS 16 also fix 19 other vulnerabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SocialJuice — Collect and share video testimonials with no-code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/socialjuice</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/socialjuice"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T20:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My FAQ Page — Create a beautiful FAQ page in under 5 minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/my-faq-page</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/my-faq-page"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T19:43:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[insiderviz — insider trading made visual and understandable for everyone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/insiderviz</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/insiderviz"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T19:06:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://osu.az1.qualtrics.com/jf...
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aha! Create — The digital notebook for product builders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/aha-create</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/aha-create"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T18:47:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keyword Research by Pagecloud & Semrush — Boost your site traffic & search rank with keyword research]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/keyword-research-by-pagecloud-semrush</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/keyword-research-by-pagecloud-semrush"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T18:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js 13 — Build powerful & dynamic web applications – without limits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/next-js-13</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/next-js-13"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T18:44:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@next/font (beta): Automatic self-hosted fonts with zero layout shift
◆ Improved next/link: Simplified API with automatic 
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fire - Web3 Chrome Extension — Don’t treat smart contracts like terms & conditions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/fire-web3-chrome-extension</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/fire-web3-chrome-extension"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T18:23:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://www.joinfire.xyz/privacy...

The Fire extension can’t control any of your funds since we do not have access to your seed phrase (and we will never ask for it).

We’re so excited to open Fire up to everybody!

Be sure to check our minting game for everybody to see the power of Fire. Download the extension and mint the Fire NFT!
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RNC sues Google over spam filter, complains Gmail is “modern Western Union”]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892720</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892720"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T18:11:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RNC lawsuit says Gmail sends nearly all its end-of-month emails to spam folders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US public’s trust in science shows growing partisan gap]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892727</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892727"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T17:52:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trust in scientists remains high, but Republicans want them out of policy decisions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shutterstock partners with OpenAI to sell AI-generated artwork, compensate artists]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892577</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892577"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T17:24:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As DALL-E synthesis comes to Shutterstock, Getty Images makes countermoves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The outrageous electric Audi S1 Hoonitron stars in new Ken Block video]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892686</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892686"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T17:04:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Group B-inspired EV uses Formula E motors to turn its tires into smoke.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia RTX 4090’s power draw may be too much for its power connector to handle]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892574</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892574"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T16:42:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New GPU's monstrous performance is matched by monstrous power draw.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Production Ready eCommerce Website with ReactJS, TailwindCSS, PlanetScale and Stripe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-ecommerce-website-using-next-js-and-planetscale/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-ecommerce-website-using-next-js-and-planetscale/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T16:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, welcome to this tutorial. Today we're going to build a production-ready eCommerce website using ReactJS, TailwindCSS, PlanetScale, and Stripe. Before we begin, you should be familiar with the basics of React.js and Next.js to get the most out of this guide. If you're not and need to brush up,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharvin Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Friday Checklist — Squeeze every dollar out of the upcoming Black Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/black-friday-checklist</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/black-friday-checklist"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T16:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Galaxy S22 gets Android 13, Samsung posts timeline for older devices]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892600</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892600"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T16:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A two-month wait is fast for Samsung. Plus, more flagships get updated in November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ramp for iOS — Cards, reimbursements, and receipt uploads, now on mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ramp-for-ios</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ramp-for-ios"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T15:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bayonetta 3 review: An updated, over-the-top spectacle]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892583</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892583"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T15:36:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New weapons add much-needed variety, but 2D spy sections feel forced.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oinkoin - Money Manager — Oinkoin makes managing personal finances easy and secure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/oinkoin-money-manager</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/oinkoin-money-manager"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T15:13:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podurama — Free cross-platform podcast player - mobile, web and desktop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/podurama</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/podurama"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T14:18:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://podurama.com along with the mobile and desktop apps).

Some of the main features include:
- Organize podcasts by genres and custom tags.
- Search both shows & episodes, and filter by genre, language etc.
- See popular episodes in every show page.
- Take notes for podcast episodes and also bookmark within episodes.
- Create multiple playlists and Auto playlists.
- Create collaborative playlists with friends or public playlists for your followers.
- Sort your favourite podcast episodes into tiers (1-5).
- Ability to listen offline, custom rss feeds 
and many more.

Please let us know your thoughts. We would appreciate any feedback :)

Thanks!
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RankTracker — Track up to 500 keyword rankings on Google for free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ranktracker</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ranktracker"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T14:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[bookmarks.email — A daily digest of your Twitter bookmarks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/bookmarks-email</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/bookmarks-email"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T14:12:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@mention accounts on tweets, just use the native bookmarking feature!
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s app review fix fails to placate developers]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892587</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892587"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T14:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creators say projects still get blocked for no good reason.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hinge Will Try to Thwart Scammers With Video Verification]]></title>
        <id>6356e6b3a8552c961517a850</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hinge-selfie-verification-scammers-bots/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T14:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To combat the scourge of bots and fake accounts, the dating site will ask users to prove their humanity by capturing a video selfie.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Goode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hinge Will Try to Thwart Scammers With Video Verification]]></title>
        <id>6356e6b3a8552c961517a850</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hinge-selfie-verification-scammers-bots/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T14:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To combat the scourge of bots and fake accounts, the dating site will ask users to prove their humanity by capturing a video selfie.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Goode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp Turns 8 Years Old: Data Science Courses + University Degrees Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-math-computer-science-degree-update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-math-computer-science-degree-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T13:52:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the global freeCodeCamp community. 8 years ago, we started this grass-roots community of learners. Back then, freeCodeCamp sounded like an improbable dream. But we all rolled up our sleeves and got to work making it a reality. Today, more than a million people use freeCodeCamp each day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ISS has had to maneuver yet again from Russian satellite debris]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892562</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892562"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T13:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This fragment was one of more than 1,500 pieces of debris from Cosmos 1408.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys—Microsoft, Apple, and Google’s password killer—are finally here]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892537</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892537"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T13:25:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It only took 50 years, but there's finally a replacement that's safer and easier to use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[19 Best Camera Bags, Straps, Inserts, and Backpacks (2022)]]></title>
        <id>5f70d2ef608f734c52f1fc52</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-camera-bags-backpacks-straps-inserts/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tote your photo and video gear around in style. We tested more than 60 packs and rounded up our favorites.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian Chokkattu, Gear Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Headstart UI — The complete application wireframe kit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/headstart-ui</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/headstart-ui"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T12:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Best Laptop Deals Right Now (2022): Cheap Laptops, MacBooks, Accessories]]></title>
        <id>624d544c022170b3101f0a65</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-laptop-deals/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’re looking for an all-arounder, a gaming powerhouse, or a wallet-friendly machine, we’ve found discounts from trusted retailers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Speight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compar.ai — AI Powered Content Analyses - Find out what Sticks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/compar-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/compar-ai"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T11:57:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #800 Python 3.11 发布：性能大幅提升]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15176-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15176-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T11:29:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.11 发布：性能大幅提升

得益于 Faster CPython 项目，Python 3.11 在性能方面提升巨大。在 Ubuntu Linux 上使用 Pyperformance 基准测试套件和 GCC 编译时，CPython 3.11 比 CPython 3.10 平均快 25%。根据你的工作负载，速度可能会提高 10-60%。


消息来源：Python



老王点评：之前 Guido 曾经希望能速度翻倍，但是看起来距离目标大打折扣啊。




欧洲理事会正式批准统一 USB-C 法案

10 月初，欧洲议会通过一项法案：自 2024 年起部分消费电子产品必须提供单一的 USB-C 充电接口。这项法案经欧洲议会主席和理事会主席签署生效后，将在 24 个月后开始实施。新规定将适用于广泛的便携式设备，而生效的 40 个月后，所有笔记本电脑的充电接口也将被规定使用 USB-C 接口。据数据，此前充电器每年产生约 11000 吨电子垃圾。


消息来源：MacRumors



老王点评：不管苹果乐意不乐意，它都得接受了。




Linux 考虑淘汰对英特尔 i486 CPU 的支持

Linux 内核在十年前移除对 i386 的支持后，i486 是内核主线对 x86 架构支持的最低版本，Linus Torvalds 认为应该让 x86-32 架构支持的最低版本提高到奔腾及更高版本。他指出 i486 已经被视为可以在博物馆里展示的展品，不如让它们运行博物馆版本的内核。


消息来源：Phoronix



老王点评：嗯，确实，我在 1995 年买的第一台计算机就是 486DX266 的，这都快三十年了。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Petivity Smart Litterbox Monitor Review: Helpful Health Alerts]]></title>
        <id>63349096eecde8c117e7f632</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/petivity-smart-litterbox-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keep tabs on your cat's bathroom habits—and catch potential health issues early—with this scale and app developed by Purina.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Medea Giordano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pandemic Uncovered Ways to Speed Up Science]]></title>
        <id>6346eb34f93a1584dc57f38b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/covid-19-open-science-public-health-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There doesn't have to be a trade-off between good research and fast research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saloni Dattani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sustainable Farming Has an Unlikely Ally: Satellites]]></title>
        <id>63571bb5e53b9bdcb463c5f0</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/perennial-carbon-capture-satellite/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Growers are using images taken from space to quantify how much carbon is stored in their soil and validate the credits they’re selling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben James</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hunt for the Kingpin Behind AlphaBay, Part 1: The Shadow]]></title>
        <id>633de8395ec45110c69a14b2</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/alphabay-series-part-1-the-shadow/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AlphaBay was the largest online drug bazaar in history, run by a technological mastermind who seemed untouchable—until his tech was turned against him.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artifact | Explore Feature — Create your customers’ favorite experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/artifact-explore-feature</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/artifact-explore-feature"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T09:36:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Try Artifact for free 👈🏻

++++++++++++++++++++++++++++
Other Awesome Artifact Features
++++++++++++++++++++++++++++

❓Answers: Answers allows our users to ask important questions about the contents of their qualitative data and receive accurately synthesized answers back. 

Ask a question like, “What have customers said about resetting their passwords in Zendesk in the last 40 days?” and you’ll get an accurate summarized answer back. 

👀 Stream: Stream reads and summarizes the key distinct aspects of what happened in each customer interaction so you can quickly know what’s been discussed.

📈Inspect: Inspect constantly monitors and spots trends and anomalies in your qualitative data. It then alerts you to those changes with simple, easy-to-understand data stories and visualizations. 

🔌 Data integrations: Dozens, and dozens of qualitative data integrations (pretty much anything you want, and if we don't have it— then tell us and we'll build it).

💬See every customer interaction: No matter what feature you’re using, you can easily get to the original source. You can see every customer verbatim that backs up insights to give you confidence and additional context.

🎉🎉See what Artifact surfaces in your data with a two week free trial🎉🎉
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CloudTempo — Fast & smart command bar for AWS console]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/cloudtempo</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/cloudtempo"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T09:31:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YaoYao 灵动岛/实时活动/Apple Watch Ultra 适配更新]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76417</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76417"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T09:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[伴随 iOS 16.1 的发布，YaoYao 也适配了 iOS 16.1 相关功能
 
 
灵动岛
当你在手表上开始运动后，再打开手机App，你将发现YaoYao 的灵动岛功能。
灵动岛在 iPhone 14 Pro 上可以使用，你可以把灵动岛理解成一个indicator。

具体有多大用，实际我也没太明白，再就是要看这个功能提供后，各路厂商的想象力，以我自己的判断，Apple 可能也没太明白，这个应该会在后面继续迭代。
实时活动（Live Activity）
这个实时活动和灵动岛是一起的，绑定的，这也是我不太能理解的地方。它不需要iPhone 14 Pro，其他手机也会显示，你可以把它理解成一个特殊的通知.
它能实时显示新跳绳的运动数据，在 iPhone 14 Pro常亮屏的加持下更加好用，个人认为常亮屏是 iPhone 14 Pro 最大的亮点，就像 Apple Watch 自从有了常亮显示，体验大大提高一样。
Live Activity
Apple Watch Ultra 操作按钮（Action Button)
为了适配 Apple Watch Ultra 这个特殊的自定义键（Action Button，手表左侧这个黄色键），我特意买了一个 Ultra，现在在系统里配置该键后，你就可以：
 
 
1. 一键启动YaoYao
2. 按下该键暂停运动
3. 再按下恢复运动（或和右边的侧边键同时按下）
因为不用看屏幕可以直接按，减少了心智负担，实际使用非常好用！变成了我最喜欢 Ultra的功能。之前感觉佳明表全是按键操作，不能触控，拿到手完全不会用，感觉很傻，看来也有一定道理，哈哈。
Action Button 按键配置方法
Action Button 配置
请将App 更新到最新版，尝鲜以上功能。
如有其他问题或需求，欢迎随时找反馈~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>中年程序猿汪二</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Private Detector by Bumble — Open source version of Bumble's anti flashing A.I]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/private-detector-by-bumble</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/private-detector-by-bumble"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T08:13:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dazzle UI Icon library - 1,680+  FREE — Beautifully crafted UI icons, ready for your next project.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/dazzle-ui-icon-library-1-680-free</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/dazzle-ui-icon-library-1-680-free"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T08:07:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer files and folders from Windows to Linux with PSCP]]></title>
        <id>70265 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/transfer-files-windows-linux-pscp"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer files and folders from Windows to Linux with PSCP
Paul
Tue, 10/25/2022 - 03:00

            
Are you looking for a way to quickly transfer files from your Windows computer to your Linux computer and back again? The open source PSCP utility makes it easy to transfer files and folders, and of course it's open source.
Setting your PATH in Windows
Knowing how to set your command path in Windows makes it easier to use a handy utility like PSCP. If you're unfamiliar with that process, read how to set a PATH on Windows.
Using PSCP
PSCP (PuTTY Secure Copy Protocol) is a command-line tool for transferring files and folders from a Windows computer to a Linux computer.

Download pscp.exe from its website.
Move pscp.exe to a folder in your PATH (for example, Desktop\App if you followed the PA…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How innovative Open Organization charts work in practice]]></title>
        <id>70251 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/innovative-open-organization-chart-works"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How innovative Open Organization charts work in practice
Ron McFarland
Tue, 10/25/2022 - 03:00

            
In the first part of this series, I illustrated what an Open Organization chart looks like based on the book Team of Teams, by Stanley McChrystal. In this second and final part, I explore concerns about the information flow using this chart and give some examples of how it might work and (possibly unknowingly) has worked in the past.
Building team-to-team adaptability, collaboration, and transparency
Sometimes activities fit exactly with a single specialty and group responsibility. Other times these responsibilities overlap, with one party having primary responsibility and another playing a more minor but important, supportive role. Both must know each other's actions to be successf…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron McFarland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[秀展网 – 在线制作MG动画/宣传动画视频制作平台 [VIP激活码免费送]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43729</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/xiuzhan365/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T06:28:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[在生活中，大部分人是没有动画制作基础的，想要深入学习却没时间。所以有时候真正需要自己动手做动画的时候，往往无从下手，希望能有一个神器，能直接上手，不用学就会用。 这次就给大家带来一个神器——秀展网（w]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Four - Powerful Lock Screen Widgets — Toggle HomeKit devices, run shortcuts, open apps and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/top-four-powerful-lock-screen-widgets</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/top-four-powerful-lock-screen-widgets"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T06:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[me@topfourapp.com.

Thanks!
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dashworks — The search engine for your company’s knowledge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/dashworks-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/dashworks-2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T05:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Literal — Multiplayer app analytics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/literal</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/literal"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T05:38:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[literal screens in your mobile app is... genius. And the layering on multi-player analytics? C'mon! More people need to discover this!
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[incident.io — End-to-end incident management, right from within Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/incident-io</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/incident-io"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T03:34:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assembly | One-on-One Workflow — Have structured one-on-ones that build stronger teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/assembly-one-on-one-workflow</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/assembly-one-on-one-workflow"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T03:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[macOS Ventura 13.0 发布，看看你的 Mac 电脑是否可以升级]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43720</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/macos-ventura-is-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T02:45:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[macOS Ventura 13.0 正式发布，带来了包括连续互通相机、台前调度、Safari 浏览器引入通行密钥、邮件与信息等 app 重大更新等内容，现在就可以更新了。 哪些设备可以更新 macO]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[在 Ubuntu 中配置 SSH 的完整指南]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15175-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15175-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T02:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[如今 SSH 已成为了登录远程服务器的默认方式。


SSH 的全称是 “安全的 ShellSecure Shell”，它功能强大、效率高，这个主流的网络协议用于在两个远程终端之间建立连接。让我们不要忘记它名称的“安全”部分，SSH 会加密所有的通信流量，以防止如劫持、窃听等攻击，同时提供不同的身份认证方式和无数个配置选项。

在这份新手指南中，你会学到：


SSH 的基本概念

设置 SSH 服务器（在你想要远程登录的系统上）

从客户端（你的电脑）通过 SSH 连接远程服务器


SSH 的基本概念

在学习配置过程前，让我们先了解一下 SSH 的全部基础概念。

SSH 协议基于客户端-服务器server-client（CS）架构。“服务器Server”允许“客户端Client”通过通信通道进行连接。该信道是经过加密的，信息交换通过 SSH 公私钥进行管理。



OpenSSH 是在 Linux、BSD 和 Windows 系统上提供 SSH 功能的最流行的开源工具之一。

想要成功配置 SSH，你需要：


在作为服务器的机器上部署 SSH 服务器组件，它由 openssh-server 包提供。

在你远程访问服务器的客户端机器上部署 SSH 客户端组件，它由 openssh-client 包提供，大多数 Linux 和 BSD 发行版都已经预装好了。


区分服务器和客户端是十分重要的事情。或许你不想要你的 PC 作为 SSH 服务器，除非你有充分理由希望其他人通过 SSH 连接你的系统。

通常来说，你有一个专用的服务器系统。例如，一个 运行 Ubuntu 的树莓派。你可以 启用树莓派的 SSH 服务，这样你可以在你 PC 中的终端中，通过 SSH 控制并管理该设备。

有了这些信息，让我们看看如何在 Ubuntu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Timestone — Create alerts to track Stock and Crypto Markets in real time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/timestone</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/timestone"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T23:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Children’s hospitals fill up amid early surge in respiratory infections]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892525</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892525"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T22:56:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now is the time to get flu shots as well as COVID boosters, experts advise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Payment Request API in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/payment-request-api-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/payment-request-api-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T22:40:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Payment Request API provides a cross-browser standard that lets you collect payments, addresses, and contact information from your customers. You can then use this info to process their order. It also facilitates the exchange of this information between the browser and the website. The fundamental idea behind this is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atta ✨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Best Deals From Samsung Week: Galaxy Phones, Tablets, Soundbars, and TVs]]></title>
        <id>6356e9263d83d1af9973abd5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/samsung-week-deals-october-24/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T22:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company is celebrating its 53rd anniversary with a deals bonanza that runs through November 1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haley Sprankle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[18 Great Deals From Best Buy's Early Black Friday Sale (2022)]]></title>
        <id>6356b7c0a398fb738c4b9197</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-buy-deals-black-friday-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T22:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get cameras, headphones, and smart home gadgets before Halloween even arrives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Ravenscraft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circl — Meet your brain, live smarter.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/circl-ba0cf8dc-c0a6-48b3-9476-b25c8480cc19</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/circl-ba0cf8dc-c0a6-48b3-9476-b25c8480cc19"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T21:58:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merge — Launch hundreds of integrations in days for free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/merge-5</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/merge-5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T21:52:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Free are you talking?
Pretty free. We don’t charge you until you’ve integrated your first 5 customers.  

Startups can prove product-market fit with integrations, and larger SMBs and enterprises can proof-of-concept new integration-powered products and features. It includes:
🆓 Unlimited data usage (no limits on API requests or data models)
⚡Real-time data with webhooks
↔️ Full bi-directional capabilities (Read and Write)

What is Merge?
Merge is the easiest way to add over 150+ customer-facing integrations across multiple categories to your SaaS app. We offer integrations for:
- HR 
- Payroll 
- Directory 
- ATS/recruiting 
- Accounting 
- CRM 
- Project Management
- Help Desk
 
We started Merge in 2020 after seeing first-hand how expensive integrations were for B2B companies; to not lose out on deals, developers have to spend thousands of hours building and maintaining integrations. 

Since we came out of stealth, we’ve been fortunate enough to serve over 3,000+ organizations. Iconic companies like Ramp, Drata, TripActions, Ripplematch, and AngelList trust us to power their integrations.

After we announced our Series B on Monday, we knew stopping by PH was the next step to help even more companies with critical, customer-facing integrations! 

How do I get started?
If you want to start using Merge on our Free plan, you can sign up today at merge.dev/signup.

If you want to start exploring what our API can offer, check out our Get Started guide.

Super excited to hear your feedback and answer any questions! Our whole team is here to help you succeed.

Looking forward,
Shensi
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dropbox Capture — All-in-one visual communication tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/dropbox-capture-3</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/dropbox-capture-3"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T21:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://www.dropbox.com/capture?...
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Contribute to Open Source – a Guide for Technical Writers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-contribute-to-open-source-for-technical-writers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-contribute-to-open-source-for-technical-writers/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T21:20:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Contributing to open source can be a daunting prospect, especially if you haven't done so before, or if you're used to working on documentation rather than code. This guide will help technical writers get started contributing to open-source projects, and outline some of the common pitfalls you might encounter when]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Swift Handbook – Learn Swift for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-swift-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-swift-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T21:04:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Swift The Swift programming language was created by Apple in 2014. It's the official language that works with the whole Apple Operating Systems lineup: iOS, iPadOS, watchOS, macOS, and tvOS. Swift is an open source, general purpose, compiled programming language that's statically typed. Every value has a type]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flavio Copes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We were not wowed by our first Meta Quest Pro experience]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892497</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892497"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T21:04:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Best Buy demo doesn't put Meta's best foot forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Niche Site Metrics — Find profitable niches + SEO keywords with low competition!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/niche-site-metrics</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/niche-site-metrics"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T20:24:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slow Roads offers a chill, endless driving experience in your browser]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892326</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892326"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T19:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Free, meditative driving game with no strings attached might help you escape the grind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comcast’s new higher upload speeds require $25-per-month xFi Complete add-on]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892437</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892437"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T19:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[10Mbps uploads become 100Mbps—but only with xFi Complete hardware rental plan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AutoPredict — An AI tool that predicts how long your car will last]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/autopredict</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/autopredict"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T19:33:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marvel drops official trailer for Ant-Man and the Wasp: Quantumania]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892377</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892377"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T19:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kang the Conqueror makes his MCU debut as next big cross-movie villain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On eve of first launch, Relativity Space seeks to join SpaceX as “disruptor”]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892255</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892255"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T18:57:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Almost from the beginning of the company, I wanted to build a Falcon 9 competitor."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wide Angle Analytics — Lightweight, powerful and privacy-focused web analytics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/wide-angle-analytics</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/wide-angle-analytics"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T18:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GDPR compliance that's not just a fancy website badge.
Uncover insights with easy-to-read dashboards.
Go cookieless and avoid the dreaded Cookie Banner.
Improve reliability and circumvent unfair ad blockers without being forced to sell your visitor data.
Capture consent and leverage it for additional Personal Data insights.

Entirely made in and operated from the European Union, on a European cloud, with zero compromises.

I created a special offer for the Product Hunt community! 20% OFF on any annual plan.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Select – Statement and Query Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-select-statement-and-query-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-select-statement-and-query-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T18:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Structured Query Language (SQL) is a programming language that you use to manage data in relational databases. You can use SQL to create, read, update, and delete (CRUD) data in a relational database. You can write SQL queries to insert data with INSERT, read data with SELECT, update with UPDATE,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple releases OS updates for basically everything, including iPadOS and macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892379</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1892379"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T17:48:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything from the iPhone to the HomePod gets a software update today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pixel 6A, Pixel Buds Pro, and Other Google Devices Are on Sale Right Now]]></title>
        <id>6356b1680d79c592e1a4c431</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/google-pixel-6a-and-pixel-buds-pro-on-sale-october-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T17:37:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pixel 6A is just $299—its lowest price ever—but you can also pick up the Pixel Buds Pro and Nest Audio at a discount.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gilbertson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[flat.social — Fun virtual spaces for online meetings & remote socials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/flat-social</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/flat-social"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T17:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick note - we will be hanging out in the flat.social demo space - click here to visit the live demo and say hi! 

🤔 Back in 2021, I was a tech lead of a product team at an old-school FTSE 100 company. Like many other teams worldwide, we moved to a full-remote operation rather suddenly and without much preparation. While I was happy to see how productive we got in the new setting, the spirit and social aspects of our daily work were hurt. We had communication tools to keep us productive but using them in attempts to connect better as humans wasn't the most playful way to go.

💡 So I thought - what if I make a video meeting app that puts playfulness above productivity and focuses on creating connections between online guests instead of trying to turn them into digital worker bees? Serend…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Top New Features in MacOS Ventura (2022): Compatiblity, How to Install MacOS 13]]></title>
        <id>629e1d20bb966dfe6e2d39b4</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/apple-ventura-macos-13/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T17:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple has officially released MacOS 13. Here’s how to download the latest desktop operating system on your Mac.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brenda Stolyar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple iOS 16 and iPadOS 16 (2022): How to Download, New Features, Supported Devices]]></title>
        <id>629e135a83c980195cb99f16</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/apple-iphone-ios-16-ipados-16-new-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest versions for iPhones and iPads are now available, complete with a revamped lock screen, editable Messages, and Safety Check.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian Chokkattu, Brenda Stolyar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu MATE 22.10 的新变化]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15174-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15174-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T16:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu MATE 22.10 已经发布，其中有一些细微而有用的变化。来看看吧！




Ubuntu MATE 是 Ubuntu 官方版本 之一，每次升级都会增加有趣的改进。

它的目标用户是那些既珍惜传统桌面的外观和感觉，又渴望现代操作系统的功能的用户。

Ubuntu MATE 22.10 版本增加了许多改进和功能，让我们来看看这些。

Ubuntu MATE 22.10 的新变化



基于非 LTS 版本的 Ubuntu 22.10 ，Ubuntu MATE 22.10 带来了多项更新，一些关键的亮点包括：


对 MATE 桌面的改进。

新的 AI 墙纸。

PipeWire 是默认的音频服务器。

新的 MATE 用户管理器。

Firefox 105 更新。

LibreOffice 7.4。



💡 注意，Ubuntu MATE 的升级通常包括更多的功能补充。但这一次，Martin Wimpress 一直致力于为 Debian MATE 版带来类似的体验。你可以在我们之前的报道中阅读更多细节。



准备好在 Debian Linux 上获得 Ubuntu MATE 体验吧！


MATE 桌面升级



MATE 桌面收到了各种错误修复和对 Ayatana 指示器、MATE 面板的更新。

现在，你可以将小程序居中对齐，与通常的左右对齐选项一起。

这项功能将在 MATE 桌面 1.28 版中正式出现，但 Ubuntu MATE 团队在 MATE 桌面 1.27 版的基础上将其与这个版本一起推出。

MATE 用户管理器



MATE 用户管理器是该发行版的一个新的补充，允许你添加、修改、删除用户账户。

有了它，你可以选择哪些用户可以成为管理员、设置自动登录、设置个人资料图片，以及管理组成员资格。对于有多个用户的计算机来说，这是一个相当方便和急需的功能。

新的 AI 壁纸



这个版本的另一大亮点是增加了新的 AI 生成的壁纸。

这些看起来很美 😍

鉴于人工智能生成的壁纸现在正大行其道，Ubuntu MATE 团队在 Ubuntu MATE 22.10 中加入了一批新的壁纸。

它是由 Simon Butcher 使用扩散模型创建的，用来描画 “捻角羚”。

Linux 内核 5.19

Ubuntu MATE 22.10 得益于 Linux 内核 5.19 带来的改进，对各种 ARM SoC、Arc Alchemist GPU 等提供了增强支持。

你可以阅读我们的相关报道以了解更多。

🛠️ 其他变化和改进

与其他新版本一样，Ubuntu MATE 22.10 用 PipeWire 取代了 PulseAudio，以获得更好的音频处理，并加入了额外的蓝牙编解码器，如 AAC、LDAC、aptX 和 aptX HD。

其他值得注意的变化包括：


更新的应用程序包括：Firefox 105、LibreOffice 7.4、Celluloid 0.20 和 Evolution 3.46。

Ubuntu MATE HUD 支持 MATE、XFCE 和 Budgie，具有更多的配置能力。


如果你感到好奇，你可以查看 Ubuntu MATE 22.10 官方发布说明。

下载 Ubuntu MATE 22.10

你可以从 Ubuntu 的中央镜像库 或其 官方网站 下载最新的 ISO。

它的官方网站/仓库可能需要一段时间来提供 ISO。


💡 Ubuntu MATE 22.10 将被支持九个月，直到 2023 年 7 月 。如果你想要稳定而不是功能，你应该更喜欢使用 LTS 版本。



下载 Ubuntu MATE 22.10


💬 有兴趣尝试 Ubuntu MATE 22.10 吗？请在评论中告诉我你的想法。


via: https://news.itsfoss.com/ubuntu-mate-22-10-release/

作者：Sourav Rudra 选题：lkxed 译者：wxy 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Monetize Your Website with Microtransactions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-monetize-your-website/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-monetize-your-website/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T15:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web Monetization means that you can get money for every person that visits your website. Sounds good right? But how does it work?  We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to monetize your website using microtransactions and the Interledger Protocol.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubuntu 22.10 的新变化]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15173-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15173-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T15:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubuntu 22.10 可能不是最令人兴奋的升级。但是，它包括了一些有用的变化。




Kubuntu 是 Ubuntu 的一个官方版本，它在一个精致的 KDE 驱动的软件包中提供了很多功能。

Kubuntu 22.10 的发布带来了各种改进和一个 KDE Plasma 的更新版本。

让我们来看看这个版本的亮点。

Kubuntu 22.10 有什么新变化？



Kubuntu 22.10 带来了很多更新，其中一些重要的更新包括：


KDE Plasma 5.25

Linux 内核 5.19

PipeWire

Firefox 104

Qt 5.15.6



💡 Kubuntu 22.10 将被支持九个月，直到 2023 年 7 月。如果你想要稳定而不是功能，你应该更喜欢使用 LTS 版本。


KDE Plasma 5.25



尽管最近 KDE Plasma 5.26 已经发布了，但 Kubuntu 22.10 还是搭载了 KDE Plasma 5.25。

然而，KDE Plasma 5.25 与 5.24 相比仍然是一个重大的更新，它包含了很多改进，例如，加强了对触摸板/触摸屏的支持，升级了用户界面等等。

你可以阅读我们对 KDE Plasma 5.25 的报道来了解更多。


KDE Plasma 5.25：颜色、主题和其他改进


另外，你可以期待 KDE Plasma 5.26 作为一个小版本发布，而不是作为 Kubuntu 22.10 发布的一部分。

默认采用 PipeWire

像大多数基于 Ubuntu 22.10 的发行版一样，PipeWire 是这个版本的 Kubuntu 的默认音频/视频处理器。

它取代了 PulseAudio，众所周知，它与 Ubuntu 22.10 不兼容。

Linux 内核 5.19



Kubuntu 22.10 采用了最新的 Linux 内核 5.19，这应该会带来对 ARM SoC 和 Arc Alchemist GPU 的支持、Btrfs 的各种改进、对 AMD RDNA3 图形的初步支持等等。

测试用的 Wayland 会话



Kubuntu 22.10 具有对 Plasma Wayland 会话的初步支持，但它仅用于测试目的，并不是一个完整的集成。



其他升级

其他一些更新包括：


自定义桌面重点颜色

默认浏览器是 Firefox 104 Snap

Qt 5.15.6

LibreOffice 7.4

改进的应用程序商店


要探索更多关于该版本的信息，请参考 官方发布说明。

下载 Kubuntu 22.10

你可以从 Ubuntu 的中央镜像库 或其 官方网站 下载最新的 ISO。


Kubuntu 22.10


它的官方网站可能需要一段时间来提供 ISO。

💬 你对这个版本感到兴奋吗？


via: https://news.itsfoss.com/kubuntu-22-10-release/

作者：Sourav Rudra 选题：lkxed 译者：wxy 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Cloud Firestore in a React App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-firebase-database-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-firebase-database-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T15:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firebase provides some great services like NoSQL databases, authentication, cloud storage, and much more. In this tutorial, we will learn how to use your React application to read and add data to your Firebase database.  To demonstrate this, we will learn how to build a Todo app using React]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Best Projectors (2022): Short Throw, Portable, Low Latency]]></title>
        <id>5e5fd7420f6c98000810ccc5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-projectors/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you want a backyard presenter or a theater-quality behemoth, our picks will help you upgrade your at-home movie nights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Parker Hall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gradient Descent – Machine Learning Algorithm Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gradient-descent-machine-learning-algorithm-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gradient-descent-machine-learning-algorithm-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T13:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Gradient Descent Algorithm? Gradient descent is probably the most popular machine learning algorithm. At its core, the algorithm exists to minimize errors as much as possible.  The aim of gradient descent as an algorithm is to minimize the cost function of a model. We can tell]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salim Oyinlola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple iPad (10th Gen, 2022) Review: Just a Pretty Face With USB-C]]></title>
        <id>63515940e87d0914ff599043</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/apple-ipad-10th-gen-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What was once a basic and affordable entry-level tablet now feels anything but.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brenda Stolyar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Halloween 3D illustrations (2.0) — 3d pack for digital designers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/free-halloween-3d-illustrations-2-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/free-halloween-3d-illustrations-2-0"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T12:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Notion-like system with Socket.io And React 😍]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/novu/building-a-notion-like-system-with-socketio-and-react-1hjg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/novu/building-a-notion-like-system-with-socketio-and-react-1hjg"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T12:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #react #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevo David, novu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12 Best Office Chairs (2022): Budget, Luxe, Cushions, Casters, and Mats]]></title>
        <id>607895413c4558580f4abffa</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-office-chairs/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sitting at a desk for hours? Upgrade your WFH setup and work in style with these WIRED-tested comfy seats.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian Chokkattu, Gear Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s App Review Fix Fails to Placate Developers]]></title>
        <id>6352d0dc4893eeeb8da41701</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/apples-app-store-review-fix-fails-placate-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After bad press about its App Store rules, Apple added a way to challenge app rejections. Creators say projects still get blocked for no good reason.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubham Agarwal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worried About Nuclear War? Consider the Micromorts]]></title>
        <id>63530245695aea2cfb89ed06</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/micromorts-nuclear-war/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calculating the likelihood of dying in a nuclear conflict sounds like an impossible task, but it could give us a whole new way to think about the risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rats Are Invasive Menaces. These Cameras Spy on Them]]></title>
        <id>635028275f4eb0d9a7e18946</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/rats-are-invasive-menaces-these-cameras-spy-on-them/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping rodents off Santa Cruz Island is an exhausting task. But now, conservationists are getting an assist from an AI-powered surveillance system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hot on the Trail of a Mass-School-Shooting Hoaxer]]></title>
        <id>63518918e87d0914ff599048</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/school-swatting-textnow-ethiopia/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For months, an anonymous caller has terrorized communities around the US by reporting false shooting threats. We know how they did it. The question is, why?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruv Mehrotra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LVLUP — Elevate your personal training and online coaching business]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/lvlup-38a249c2-d797-4468-8446-12dbac95bcef</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/lvlup-38a249c2-d797-4468-8446-12dbac95bcef"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T10:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Purchase Checklist — A simple checklist app for home buyers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/home-purchase-checklist</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/home-purchase-checklist"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T09:10:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #799 一个单行补丁提升 Linux 隧道千倍性能]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15172-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15172-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T07:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一个单行补丁提升 Linux 隧道千倍性能

Linux 的通用 TUN 驱动为用户空间的程序提供数据包接收和传输，该驱动长期以来一直在 Linux 内核中使用，可用于 VPN、Open vSwitch 等用途。将近二十年前，Linux TUN 驱动设置了一个 10Mbps 链接的标称速度，这在当时足够了。但是现在，Linux 网络堆栈和硬件都有了很大的进步。开发者提出了一个补丁，将该设定值提升一千倍到 10Gbps，并建议干脆取消该限制，而让应用程序/用户自己决定一个正确的值。


消息来源：Phoronix



老王点评：这就和千年虫一样，当时对日后发展考虑不足。




GitHub 准备推出细粒度的个人访问令牌

GitHub 在 2020 年提供了 OAuth 认证，再之后，GitHub.com 所有认证的 Git 操作都需要基于令牌的认证，而不再接受账户密码。但 GitHub 的个人访问令牌只能被赋予有限的权限，也不是按仓库分配的，而且只有几个宽泛的类别。新的正在测试中的令牌是细粒度的，每个仓库有 25 种权限，其中大部分权限可以设置为只读、读写或不访问，另外有 14 种权限与账户管理有关。


消息来源：Devclass



老王点评：确实这是必要的，只是我原本以为这种细粒度的设置应该更早来到。




Gartner 发布十大战略技术趋势

著名的技术研究和咨询公司 Gartner 发布了 2023 年的十大战略技术趋势：数字免疫系统、应用可观察性、AI 信任/风险和安全管理、行业云平台、平台工程、无线价值实现、超级应用、自适应 AI、元宇宙、可持续技术。


消息来源：福布斯



老王点评：看了一下，感觉不明觉厉。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to display commits created on a specific day with the git log command]]></title>
        <id>70271 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/git-log-command"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to display commits created on a specific day with the git log command
Agil Antony
Mon, 10/24/2022 - 03:00

            
The git log command offers many opportunities to learn more about the commits made by contributors. One way you might consume such information is by date. To view commits in a Git repository created on a specific date or range of dates, use the git log command with the options --since or --until, or both.

More on Git
What is Git?
Git cheat sheet
Markdown cheat sheet
New Git articles
First, checkout the branch you want to inspect (for example, main):
$ git checkout main
Next, display the commits for the current date (today):
$ git log --oneline --since="yesterday"
Display commits for the current date by a specific author only (for example, Agil):
$ git log --oneline --since="yesterday" --author="Agil"
You can also display results for a range of dates. Display commits between any two dates (for example, 22 April 2022 and 24 April 2022):
$ git log --oneline --since="2022-04-22" --until="2022-04-24"
In this example, the output displays all the commits between 22 April 2022 and 24 April 2022, which excludes the commits done on 22 April 2022. If you want to include the commits done on 22 April 2022, replace 2022-04-22 with 2022-04-21.
Run the following command to display commits between any two dates by a specific author only (for example, Agil):
$ git log --oneline --since="2022-04-22" \
--until="2022-04-24" --author="Agil"

Reporting
Git has many advantages, and one of them is the way it enables you to gather data about your project. The git log command is an important reporting tool and yet another reason to use Git!
The git log command is an important reporting tool and yet another reason to use Git.

  
Image by: 
by Dafne Cholet. CC BY-SA 2.0.
 


  
Git
What to read next

        This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-Share Alike 4.0 International License.

                  
Register or Login to post a comment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Agil Antony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A PWA is the web browser]]></title>
        <id>70263 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/pwa-web-browser"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A PWA is the web browser
Alex Borsody
Mon, 10/24/2022 - 03:00

            
A progressive web app (PWA) is a web application that uses modern web technologies to deliver a user experience equal to any mobile app. An active open source community, in conjunction with tech leaders like Google and Microsoft, pushes the PWA agenda forward in an effort to "bridge the app gap."
Basically, a PWA runs your app in a web browser. Because there's essentially a two-party system of the Play and App stores, the focus is on two browsers: Google Chrome and Apple Safari (built on top of the open source Chromium and WebKit, respectively).
I won't be covering creating desktop apps. For more information on that topic, look into Electron.
PWAs are built the same way as any website or web app. They use the lates…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Borsody</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remixing Linux for blind and visually impaired users]]></title>
        <id>70189 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/9/linux-visually-impaired-users"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remixing Linux for blind and visually impaired users
Vojtech Polasek
Mon, 10/24/2022 - 03:00

            
When I was around 5 years old, my father brought home our first computer. From that moment on, I knew I wanted to pursue a career in computers. I haven't stopped hanging around them since. During high school, when considering which specific area I wanted to focus on, I started experimenting with hacking, and that was the moment I decided to pursue a career as a security engineer.
I'm now a software engineer on the security compliance team. I've been at Red Hat for over two years, and I work remotely in the Czech Republic. I've used Linux for about 12 years, mainly Arch Linux and Fedora, but I've also administered Debian, Gentoo, and Ubuntu in the past.
  
Image by: 
(Vojtech Polasek, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vojtech Polasek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[在忙碌的生活中坚持阅读：我的得到阅读器三年使用体验]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76372</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76372"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T06:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

为何是阅读器
大学毕业后，我告别了拥有海量藏书的图书馆，开始了漫长的阅读工具体验之旅。
起初，惯性思维让我从当当、京东等大平台买书来读。我喜欢撕掉新书塑封时的期待心情，也慢慢攒起来了自己的第一批库存。新书的开销几乎成为刚毕业的我除吃饭和租房外的第三大支出项。
后来，多抓鱼开始了他们的创业，我也成为了他们的最早一批用户。我在他们的小程序上养成了买二手书的习惯，也尝试着卖掉了一些看完的书。我喜欢这种循环与分享的理念，有时收到他人批注过的书页，时有共鸣，像是在和一名未曾谋面的老友会心一笑。
然而北漂不易，在这样试运行了快三年后，寸土寸金的租房空间已经难以下脚。再加上数次搬家几乎成了北漂的必修课，因此「纸质书」在我这里已经逐渐和「奢侈品」画了等号。我开始把目光转向电子书。
彼时「蜗牛阅读」早于「微信阅读」兴起，我用手机读完每天免费的一小时，眼睛已经感觉酸涩。后来我尝试了 iPad 版本，视觉的疲劳感依然没有好转。于是像每一个热爱阅读或者感觉自己热爱阅读的人一样，我下单了人生的第一台 Kindle，开始了我的阅读器泡面之旅。
Kindle 的小屏幕让我非常不适应。由于阅读惯性使然，为了尽可能获得和纸质书的一页近似的信息量，我需要把字体调整到很小，然而字体变小又让阅读本身变得吃力。加上 Kindle Unlimited 并不优质的资源和第三方网站的不稳定，我发现 Kindle 在我这里并没有代替纸质书的地位，反而是新鲜感过后，逐渐落入吃灰的境地。
再后来，得到 app 开始推出了电子书的业务，上线初期是 148元/年。我这个得到重度用户试用了…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Journey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[终于把右键新建菜单搞整齐了，强迫症患者福音：Windows 10 右键新建菜单重命名]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43712</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/context-menu-change-name-win10/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T05:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[来自 @LambertCrofts 同学的帖子：终于把右键新建菜单搞整齐了。 对于强迫症患者来说，看到上图左侧的样式，真不能忍，为什么 PPT 全称那么长？就不能短一些么？ 可以的。但需要…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPad与外接键盘，这样设置可以更好用]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76300</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76300"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T02:48:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[引言
iPad中关于键盘的设置与鼠标一样 —— 非常混乱。例如，iPad键盘的设置也是出现在「通用 | 键盘」、「辅助功能 | 键盘」以及「辅助功能 | 触控 — 辅助触控」中。
其中，「辅助功能 | 触控 — 辅助触控」其实就是上一篇文章中的「鼠标键」，具体可以参考《鼠标搭配 iPadOS，如何设置才能更好用？》
「通用 | 键盘 — 实体键盘」
键位调节
在实体键盘中，你可以根据iPad已有的输入法进行键位调节。例如我们常用的是QWERTY键盘，而你可以在这里改成AZERTY等。

 
下面的几项设置中，大家基本都能理解，而且也无关痛痒。笔者认为比较重要的是下面两个：
按下🌐显示表情符号
首先，这个🌐符号在妙控键盘里就是左下角的fn。
显示表情符号这个按钮，比较适合常用emoji😄的场景。例如‼️，一般写小🍠的朋友都需要用较多的emoji来分1️⃣2️⃣3️⃣等小标题，那么打开这个功能就会非常方便啦✨。
实际上，就算打开了这个功能，也不会影响我们切换输入法，因为使用control+空格也能轻松切换输入法，与我们使用Mac的习惯一样。

使用大写锁定键切换语言
第二个功能也是Mac中特有的功能。从Windows换到Mac的用户很不爽的一点是：想按Caplock键来输入大写字母，结果只能切换输入法，非得长按才行。
实际上这个功能是可以开关的，iPad上也一样。打开后，我们可以自由地在当前输入法和英文输入法之间切换（如果当前是简体中文输入法，那么就是中——英；如果是俄语输入法，那么便是俄——英），如果在键盘语言中把英文输入法删除的话，这个功能即使打开也不能使用了。关闭后，我们按下Caplock键就能切换为全大写输入。macOS中也一样，删除自带的中文输入法（英文输入法不能删除），就不能实现这个功能。

「辅助功能 | 键盘」

辅助功能中的键盘设置分为两个部分，一个是…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hkoch24</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu 22.10 的新变化]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15171-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15171-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T02:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu 22.10 是一个令人印象深刻的版本，它拥有新的快速切换功能、应用程序散布，以及更多。




Ubuntu 22.10 “充满活力的捻角羚Kinetic Kudu”来了。它带来了许多重大的改进，特别是 Linux 内核 5.19 和 GNOME 43 的体验。

当然，这是一个经过定制的 GNOME 体验，现有的 Ubuntu 用户会很熟悉。

那么，Ubuntu 22.10 都有哪些新变化呢？让我们一起来看看。

Ubuntu 22.10 的新变化



除了 GNOME 43 之外，Ubuntu 22.10 还包括：


一个改进的 设置Settings 应用程序。

经典的 Unity 应用程序散布模式Spread Mode的复活。

一些著名的应用程序被移植到 GTK4 和 Libadwaita。

全系统支持 WebP。

PipeWire 采样管默认的音频服务器。

Linux 内核 5.19。



💡 Ubuntu 22.10 将被支持九个月，直到 2023 年 7 月。如果你想要稳定而不是功能，你应该更愿意使用 LTS 版本。


🎨 视觉改进

当第一次测试一个新版本时，视觉上的变化总是最先被注意到的。在 Ubuntu 22.10 中尤其如此，这要归功于 GNOME 43 所带来的重大改进。



首先，我们有全新的快速设置菜单，它取代了旧的、相当笨拙的系统菜单。与安卓、iOS 和 Windows 11 中的菜单类似，这个新增的菜单允许你打开和关闭 Wi-Fi 和蓝牙，所有这些都无需进入设置Settings应用程序。

当然，在这个版本中我们还得到了全新的壁纸。



对于这个变化，我除了喜欢并希望从社区中看到更多这样的设计之外，没有什么别的可说的。

此外，更多的应用程序被移植到…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[开源 DevOps 工具的平台化未来]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15170-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15170-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T01:27:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[当商业 DevOps 工具市场着眼于平台时，是时候让开源 DevOps 工具重新定义它们的未来了。


DevOps 的开源根基是无法动摇的，即便有预言称全球的 DevOps 市场将在 2026 年之前达到 178 亿美元。不断变化的工作环境、安全和合规性问题，以及风险投资公司等等因素正在将市场推向 DevOps 平台，开发团队可以在云中获得完整的端到端 DevOps 工具链。

开源 DevOps 工具现状

我们要搞清楚一件事：开源工具不可能从 DevOps 世界中消失。现在，在开源和供应商提供的 DevOps 工具之间存在着一种平衡，开发人员会在两者间选择适合他们的工具。事实上，很多情况下，一个开发团队起初会为他们的 DevOps 流水线选择一个开源工具，后来又升级到商业版本。

三种开源 DevOps 工具实例

下面我们介绍一些开源 DevOps 工具的例子，每种工具都已经有了围绕其建立的商业化生态。

Git

源代码管理工具 Git 作为源代码库，可能是 DevOps 工具链的主要基础之一。

Git 的两个最佳商业案例是 GitLab 和 GitHub。GitLab 接受开发者对其贡献开源项目。GitHub 也在着手努力成为一个 DevOps 平台，推出了人工智能版的结对编程 GitHub Copilot，在推出后受到了一些开源团体的褒贬不一的评价。

Jenkins

作为一个开源的自动化服务，Jenkins 因其易于安装、配置和可扩展性而受到推崇。

CloudBees 提供了 JenkinsX，JenkinsX 是一套开源的解决方案，可以为 Kubernetes 上的云原生应用提供自动化持续集成和持续交付（CI/CD）以及自动化测试工具。他们还为JenkinsX 提供商业支持，包括：


访问 CloudBees 的专业技术…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Best Budget Gaming Laptops (2022): 16-Inch Screens, RTX 3060, and More]]></title>
        <id>62ea961dd0ad4d5c1833c0b2</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-budget-gaming-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming PC? That’s so 2020. Save some cash on a good, travel-friendly rig with these WIRED-tested picks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Speight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Best Chef’s Knives for Your Kitchen (2022): Affordable, Japanese, Carbon Steel]]></title>
        <id>5ecd3923469722286c4434eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-chef-knives/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the indispensable multi-tool of the kitchen. We sliced and diced our way through meats and veggies to find today’s best blades.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gilbertson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New Math of Wrinkling Patterns]]></title>
        <id>634d91d07fa81ffa8c2b011a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-new-math-of-wrinkling-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A comprehensive mathematical framework treats these crinkles as elegant solutions to geometric problems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Ornes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Quiet Insurrection the January 6 Committee Missed]]></title>
        <id>63502848470620c1e69a254e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/january-6-trump-digital-insurrection-politics/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A former congressman who helped the House select committee investigate the Capitol attack says the US is losing sight of the big picture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Laslo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Extract the Text From Any Image]]></title>
        <id>6326021af2203b5586fabfbf</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-extract-text-from-any-image/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether it’s for accessibility or research purposes, you have lots of tools to work with here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Nield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Quiet Insurrection the January 6 Committee Missed]]></title>
        <id>63502848470620c1e69a254e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/january-6-trump-digital-insurrection-politics/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A former congressman who helped the House select committee investigate the Capitol attack says the US is losing sight of the big picture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Laslo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swift Backup – 备份 Android 手机重要数据，包括短信、通信记录、壁纸、旧版应用等]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43704</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/swift-backup-for-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T05:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swift Backup 是一款用来备份 Android 手机重要数据的应用，可以备份应用、短信、通话记录、壁纸，甚至可以保留应用更新后的旧版本应用，以便将来降级安装。另外在 root 之后将获得更多]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[第一次 CrossFit 训练之前，你需要知道的几件小事]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76376</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76376"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T04:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[你好，我是马上要上第 700 节 CrossFit 团课的克莱尔。（但今天是我的休息日。所以我来写稿了。
如果你想减脂增肌，或者厌倦了在普通健身房对着满屋子器械不知从何下手，CrossFit 训练也许是一个最简单粗暴的健身方案。

融合有氧器械、哑铃壶铃、药球、奥林匹克举重与单杠和吊环体操动作， CrossFit 以社区感、团课、每天不重样的训练内容闻名。对，我们每天练的项目都不一样，它要求你什么都懂（一点），对心肺、力量、柔韧性等各方面都有要求。
换句话说， CrossFit 花样丰富，有趣，强度大，但作为一个相对小众的运动，准入门槛也不低。如果你在一二线城市，找到好馆子的可能性会比较大。如果你经常出差—— CrossFit 就像健身界的星巴克，无论到哪个城市，都能找到以相似模式运行的 Box ，能结识不同的朋友。
全球 CF 馆分布
今年是我练 CF 的第三年。根据三年的观察，许多来 CF 新客体验的人常被这项运动的强度或者“对新人不友好”震慑，觉得这是一馆子又壮又爱拼命的疯子。但其实 CF 并没有想象中这么吓人。在进行你的第一次 CF 训练之前，提前知道这些事情可以降低你在馆里低血糖、呕吐或者被吓得从此听到 CF 就绕道走的概率。
离你最近的 CrossFit 训练馆在哪里？
首先，如何找到离你最近的 CF 训练馆？如果你在国内一线城市，在点评 app 里输入 CrossFit 就是最快的方法，如果搜索结果中出现【综合训练】字样，它很有可能也是一个 CF 馆。只是未经 CF 官方认证。这不代表它是山寨——近几年有越来越多场馆认为自己不需要每年缴会费做这个认证，但大家训练的系统是一样的。
如果你在国外，除了谷歌，另一个方法是点进 crossfit.com 网页，在右上角 Find a gym 这里找到经过官方认证的场馆（对国内场馆同样适用，但也许网速会众所周知地慢一点）…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>克莱尔爱吃甜食</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Patterns in Software Development]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abdurrkhalid333/design-patterns-in-software-development-4b82</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abdurrkhalid333/design-patterns-in-software-development-4b82"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T19:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#tutorial #opensource #productivity #community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdur Rehman Khalid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Best Bike Locks (2022): U-Locks, Chain Locks, and Tips]]></title>
        <id>5f775dca65691defc2ab7d97</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-bike-locks/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Make life hard for bike thieves and shackle your precious with these U-locks and bike chains, plus tips on how best to secure it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Jancer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Best Mesh Wi-Fi Routers (2022): For Large Homes and Small Budgets]]></title>
        <id>615b126d272def4b666617ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-mesh-wifi-routers/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forget about that patchy internet connection and dead spots with one of these WIRED-tested mesh systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simon Hill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android Users Can Finally 'Like' Messages From iPhones]]></title>
        <id>6351e3e08a9aca4b129e65e9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/android-users-can-like-iphone-messages-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: Uber wants to serve ads during rides, and popular streaming services start cracking down on shared accounts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boone Ashworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok’s Security Threat Comes Into Focus]]></title>
        <id>632df46d995b6da54b57f02f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/tiktok-bytedance-americans-data-security-roundup/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: A Microsoft cloud leak exposed potential customers, new IoT security labels come to the US, and details emerge about Trump’s document stash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Slack Look and Feel Like Discord]]></title>
        <id>633f38475a49457c993f538a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-make-slack-look-feel-like-discord/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With your work in one place and your friends in another, here are some ways to familiarize the office app a bit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Pot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goats and Sheep Are Brawling in the Rockies. Blame Glacial Melt]]></title>
        <id>634d908804d20e5d7c550aea</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/goats-and-sheep-are-brawling-in-the-rockies-blame-glacial-melt/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The climate crisis may explain fights as disappearing ice fuels interspecies competition—with goats nearly always winning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Milman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Best Deals: Laptops, Phones, and Pet Gear]]></title>
        <id>6352dbbb06be0c3ca4a76443</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/weekend-deals-october-22-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrade your gadget stash on the cheap with this weekend's discounts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louryn Strampe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These 10 free APIs will take your programming projects to the next level 👇]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/elliot_brenyasarfo_18749/these-10-free-apis-will-take-your-programming-projects-to-the-next-level-5g24</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/elliot_brenyasarfo_18749/these-10-free-apis-will-take-your-programming-projects-to-the-next-level-5g24"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T08:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #programming #react #javascript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elliot Brenya sarfo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use open source commands in Powershell]]></title>
        <id>70241 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/set-path-powershell"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use open source commands in Powershell
Alan Smithee
Sat, 10/22/2022 - 03:00

            
When you launch an application on an operating system, there are certain code libraries and utility applications that your OS needs to use for that app to run. Your OS knows how to find these libraries and utilities because it has a system path, a map to common shared data that lots of apps need. Every OS has this, but users aren’t usually aware of it because they don’t usually need to care about it. However, when you start coding or using special network utilities or commands, you might care about your own PATH variable.

More great content
Free online course: RHEL technical overview
Learn advanced Linux commands
Download cheat sheets
Find an open source alternative
Explore open source resources
The …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Smithee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Needl — One app to search them all]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/needl</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/needl"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T04:22:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Wallpaper Does NOT Exist – 这些壁纸不存在。由 AI 设计生成的壁纸]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43700</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/this-wallpaper-does-not-exist/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T03:21:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This Wallpaper Does NOT Exist 是一个完全由 AI 设计生成的壁纸项目，拥有多种分类与颜色，每一次生成都是独一无二的壁纸。@appinn 其实这句话有问题，当 AI 生成了]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Predict Your Future in Notion — Generate love, career, and dream tarot readings in Notion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/predict-your-future-in-notion</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/predict-your-future-in-notion"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T03:20:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[事后诸葛：灵动岛为什么不好]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76350</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76350"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T23:15:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[写在前面
这个标题其实已经被我修改了一下，因为一边上学一边写稿偶尔真的拖延爆炸。在这之前，其实标题是：“灵动岛到底好不好”。如今我也算是吃了豹子胆，敢直接标题下结论。虽然已经离发布会过了很多天，当时的情绪也已经逐渐稀释，还是想尽可能理性的去一点点解释，为什么不好。
我并不想在文章的一开头就给自己贴上标签，一方面是不喜欢这样的做法，另一方面也是此时的我并没有什么拿得出手的名堂。很多观点都是超级主观的，但也很高兴你能来看看！谢谢你，我的朋友！希望你看的开心！

“好不好”的尺度
对于灵动岛，我感觉我们都有着一样的一条曲折心路：发布会前被剧透难看的感叹号挖孔，发布会时被灵动岛的亮相视频惊艳到再次对苹果重拾希望，但第二天起床琢磨过劲——这也是我们出现分歧的地方：我们都想知道这究竟是另一个 Touch Bar，还是一个能定义 iPhone 接下来几年发展的新设计。
要想搞清楚这个问题，我想讲个有些偏题的故事。
来到伦敦后，一个人住一个只有17平米的房子，空虚寂寞冷的时候也会想用音乐填满自己的房间。于是就在亚马逊上看了看各种音箱。我目前使用的电脑是14寸的 MacBook Pro，但长期会连着一个明基的显示器来用，所以我对这个音箱购买就列下了几条条件：

音质不能比 mac 本身差
必须有 aux，这样我能连接显示器用，受不了蓝牙的音画不同步
能放在显示器的正下方，所以不能太大
好看，别太贵…

在网上看了一圈，我特别喜欢 Marshall 的 EMBERTON II，当时加上一点学生优惠不到100英镑就能拿下。我觉得它小巧精致，光是凭借这好看的皮囊我就快按耐不住自己的购买欲了。可是它却有一个地方不能满足我的需求，它没有 aux，纯蓝牙。当时我的内心就出现了两股力量：一股力量准备 pua 自己，让自己接受蓝牙的延迟；另一股力量开始嘲讽 Marshall 这个品牌的一些关于“音质”和“品…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>生锈的不锈钢</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Soup-Throwing Climate Activists Got Right]]></title>
        <id>635189945d9f4a82b76d6098</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/what-the-soup-throwing-climate-activists-got-right/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: Pipeline vandals, ketchup on hot dogs, and a billion missing crabs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Knibbs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware the Distraction of the Twitter Mob Campaign]]></title>
        <id>635129452721236bcb15848f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hellena-taylor-bayonnetta-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A kerfuffle over Bayonetta voice actor Hellena Taylor’s pay reveals the often hollow structure of social media activism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katherine Cross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Quest to Treat Binge-Eating and Addiction—With Brain Zaps]]></title>
        <id>635023e62721236bcb158483</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/binge-eating-addiction-depression-deep-brain-stimulation-treatment/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Delivering small bursts of electric current via brain implants has long been used to treat Parkinson’s and epilepsy. Can it work for psychiatric conditions?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Mullin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Microsoft Exchange Server Is a Security Liability]]></title>
        <id>6350ac1d17fba1b3a9d6c023</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/microsoft-exchange-server-vulnerabilities/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Endless vulnerabilities. Massive hacking campaigns. Slow and technically tough patching. It's time to say goodbye to on-premise Exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine Enters a Dark New Era of Drone Warfare]]></title>
        <id>6351e056f1f6a083059bc075</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/russia-ukraine-drones-shahed-136-iran/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A series of deadly attacks using Iranian “suicide drones” shows Russia is shifting gears in the conflict.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Morgan Meaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazy Loading in images with React JS 😴]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/franklin030601/lazy-loading-in-images-with-react-js-4enm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/franklin030601/lazy-loading-in-images-with-react-js-4enm"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #javascript #performance #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Franklin Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eyes Guard – 开源定时提醒休息、护眼工具[Windows]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43693</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/eyes-guard-explorerol/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T08:24:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eyes Guard 是一个 Windows 应用程序，在你使用电脑时，根据设置的时间提醒你休息、保护眼睛。@Appinn Eyes Guard 开源护眼程序 无意中看到这款程序，被翻译萌到了R]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[未来的写作长啥样？LEX 用 GPT-3 AI 给你点儿颜色看看]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76362</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76362"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T08:22:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[我是在 Jarod 的知识星球里看到他推荐 LEX 这款在线编辑器。他问有没有人要邀请链接。我于是立即要来了一个。
实话实说，最近「玩具」有点儿多。
笔记软件，有 Tana ；浏览器，有 Arc；Readwise 新出的一站式阅读器 Reader ，也很不错。
原本，对这个新的在线编辑器，我是打算先留着，有空再仔细尝试。
但是，一进入 LEX 的界面，读了官方的介绍，我立刻就不淡定了。

其实，哪里只是我一个人不淡定啊？
Building the Second Brain 作者 Tiago Forte 说，自己已经看到要失业的迹象了。
因为，一篇文章里，他自己只写了 5 个词儿。剩下全是 AI 顺着往下编。

至于 Ali Abdaal 更是过分，他干脆搞了个「恶作剧」当成测试。好在事后，他向大家公开坦诚自己的行为。

这个几乎完全用 LEX 写就的帖子，数据表现是这样的：

当然，Ali 是名人，浏览量是有名人效应的。只不过，人工智能的作品几乎骗过了所有人的眼睛，还收获了这么多的点赞和转发，这就厉害了。
咱们别把眼睛只盯在这些大咖身上了。下面说说我自己的实际测试结果吧。红框里面的文字，是我写的：

然后后面的段落，全都是 Lex 自动补全的。
更厉害的是，根据这些内容，Lex 自动生成了若干标题，我只是从中选了一个而已。

原本 GPT-2 时代，人工智能自动补全已经大显神通了。GPT-3 的应用，就意味着写出来的东西更真假难辨了。

（图片来源：t.ly/DMxe）
原本你要用 GPT-3 ，还有一些障碍。例如说你需要获得 API 的使用权限，而且还得对每一次的调用付费。

而 LEX，至少在目前，是免费的。况且，它还是个在线编辑器。你啥都不用安装，直接打开，然后就能调用 GPT-3 帮你写东西了。

我当时就在想，这以后英语写作课的作业可怎么判呢？
好在老外开发这东西…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>玉树芝兰</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Observability-driven development with OpenTelemetry]]></title>
        <id>70253 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/observability-driven-development-opentelemetry"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Observability-driven development with OpenTelemetry
Ken Hamric
Fri, 10/21/2022 - 03:00

            
Observability-driven development (ODD) is being recognized as "necessary" for complex, microservice-based architectures. Charity Majors coined the term and has written about it in several articles, including Observability: A Manifesto. She explains the term in this quote:
Do you bake observability right into your code as you're writing it? The best engineers do a form of "observability-driven-development" — they understand their software as they write it, include instrumentation when they ship it, then check it regularly to make sure it looks as expected. You can't just tack this on after the fact, "when it's done".
OpenTelemetry provides the plumbing
The OpenTelemetry project has the indus…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Hamric</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一种尝试：文件管理的「中心化」原则]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76349</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76349"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T06:33:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[近几年区块链逐渐火热以后，「去中心化」的概念逐渐受到关注。
去中心化指的是：在一个分布有众多节点的系统中，每个节点都具有高度自治的特征。
回想一下，你的各种私有资料都储存在哪里？
文档都在 WPS 的云盘，或者散落在各种文件夹中；
音频文件可能分散在网易云音乐、QQ 音乐、酷狗等等音频平台，如果你喜欢音乐的本地化，也许会下载到某个文件夹中；
至于相片这种更为私人的东西，则有可能在手机本地相册或者选择百度网盘、iCloud 等等网络云盘中。
我们经常会把同类的文件分散在各处，当我们想去寻找的时候却往往难以在一个确定的地方查询；又或者遭遇到了平台倒闭，难以取回储存在云空间中的珍贵资料。
所以对于文件的「中心化」储存和管理，是一个值得尝试的文件管理形式。
我认为其中有三个核心：集中管理、本地优先、在线引用
将「中心化」概念运用到相册管理中
比如图片的管理，拿我的个人相册举例。
我们的手机每天都会有很多图片产生：屏幕截图、自拍、风景等等照片，但并非所有的照片都值得长期保存，所以要定期清理无关照片，备份重要的相片。

我从大学时期就开始使用谷歌相册管理我的手机相片，这个堪称当下功能最强大的在线相册，会智能地自动备份相机拍下的所有照片、屏幕截图，甚至还有其他 APP 中保存的图片。同时也可以一键清理本地已备份的图片，节省手机空间。
五年多过去了，我的谷歌相册中积攒了无数张相片，其中超过一半以上的图片都是无关的废片，混杂在各种较为重要的照片中，我花了很长时间都难以删除这些图片。
于是我国庆期间我批量下载了所有的相片，大约 5w 张，其中绝大部分图片都是各种被自动备份的无关照片，经过大约三天的筛选，最终保留下了差不多 7000 多张照片。
那么问题来了，如何让我的相册不再受到污染，能够自动备份到谷歌相册中，而且我希望能够保留一份相册在本地，在我删除本地照片的时候自动在云端也删除。
我采取的…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>日知录Rizl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Ultra 镜头下的桂林龙脊梯田]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76297</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76297"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T06:32:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2022国庆七天，秋高气爽良辰美景怎可辜负？驾驶着 Model 3，带上小米 11 Ultra，一路向西北从惠州到桂林。

Model 3 标续版提车于2021 年 12 月，表显续航 423 公里，1.6 万公里后表显降为 418 公里。
去程全长 627 公里，途径佛山百利达广场特斯拉超充站充电一次约 15 分钟，在贺州境内高速上充电一次约 25 分钟。
佛山百利达广场特斯拉超充站选址非常好，就在高速出入口附近，上下高速很方便。贺州境内高速上的快充表现不错，功率一度飙到充电 800 km/h 以上。

提车至今对 Model 3 的续航表现基本满意，天气凉爽的情况下表显多少就能跑出多少，甚至有时候实际续航还会超出表显，不同天气状况下的真实续航表现可以看我的 B 站自驾游视频。
晚霞迎接我们一路向西
到达桂林市临桂区已是晚上 10 点 15 分左右，办好入住第一件事就是去吃一碗桂林米粉。可能因为去的是商业步行街，美食比较商业化，即使当时比较饿了，这碗粉也没有给我带来美味的感觉。

重头戏在第二天的龙脊梯田之旅。龙脊梯田位于桂林龙胜县东南部和平乡境内的龙脊山。龙脊梯田距龙胜县城27公里，距桂林市80公里，景区面积共66平方公里，梯田分布在海拔300至1100米之间，坡度大多在26至35度之间，最大坡度达50度。
从临桂区去龙脊梯田景区大门口要一个半小时左右，桂林真大啊，查了下比北京还要大 1 万多平方公里
根据疫情防控要求，散客只能在景区收费处外面的广场购票，票价 80 元/成年人，和售票处价格一致。
工作人员告知我们，双向单车道的蜿蜒的山路加上堵车，从景区售票处到龙脊梯田里的几个寨子还要差不多 1 个小时的车程。国庆期间人特别多，如果按常规路线开车去名气最大的大寨，开车到坐缆车的地方要 1 个多小时，排队花钱坐缆车还要1个多小时，工作人员收费给我们指明了一条别的路去千层天梯，美景不打折，还可以开车到达。

工作人员收费指明的这条路应该是尚未完全开发的新路，路上看到了多处没有做固化工程的山坡，不少路段有落石和滑坡泥土，还有一个地方路面塌方，行驶起来要格外小心。
使用长焦拍下这张照片，脑海里突然响起《断背山》的配乐，给人一种氛围宁静的感觉
一个多小时后终于达到千层天梯，话不多说欣赏美景吧，看看小米 11 Ultra 记录的龙脊梯田，先来一张全景图。

这张全景图是在千层天梯处拍的，当天天空中飘着淡青蓝色的烟雾，有一种烟雨朦胧的感觉，阳光洒在稻田上勾勒出明暗的分界线，小米 11 Ultra 非常好地还原了真实的色彩和光影。
当时在梯田附近一家民宿停车吃饭，两荤一素一共三个菜（牛蛙+鱼+青菜+米饭）加免费停车 120 元左右，坐在民宿楼下的台阶上吃饭吹风欣赏美景十分惬意，可以说物超所值。

使用小米 11 Ultra 以来最满意的就是它的长焦表现，镜头压缩空间集中表达内容可以拍出非常有故事感的照片。以下照片应该都是 5x-30x 范围内拍摄的（具体记不清了），画质表现超出预期，当天的良好光线也功不可没。
 后期调色套了滤镜
11 Ultra 的主摄表现不错，成片有光影层次，色彩过渡自然，数码味和锐化较少，和肉眼所见十分接近。

当然，小米 11 Ultra 拍照也不是十全十美的，成像慢、多颗摄像头切换动画生硬、逆光自拍效果一般、超级夜景容易糊等等。不过考虑到 3699 元的价格，这些问题也都可以忽略了。
最后附上一些桂林游玩期间的美图（部分有后期），推荐大家去桂林玩，一座现代和古典，先锋流行和土著闲适相结合的奇妙城市，当地人比较友善，这次去也没遇到宰客行为，花费物超所值，值得一去。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>浪浪浪的海</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maccy – macOS 剪贴板历史记录的管理与使用]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43683</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/maccy-for-macos/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T05:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maccy 是一款轻量级的开源 macOS 剪贴板管理工具，它能帮你记录剪贴板历史，并可以快速找到之前的剪贴板内容，快捷键操作，简单快捷。@Appinn Maccy -轻量级剪贴板管理器 Maccy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OneWidget 来帮你探索灵动岛的新玩法]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76343</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76343"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T03:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[灵动岛是今年iPhone的热点更新。我们在早期的时候，看到了很多针对灵动岛的玩法，比如在岛的周围养宠物、用灵动岛打游戏、适配灵动岛的挖孔壁纸等。
但是，这些玩法从系统和功能层面，并没有用到真正的“灵动岛接口”。在苹果开发者文档中，灵动岛实际上是一种“实时活动”。在某些用户需要实时关注状态变化的场景下，为用户展示信息。比如实时更新比赛数据、实时更新外卖进度、实时更新计时器、实时更新地图导航指引等等。
如果iPhone安装了iOS 16.1系统，在iPhone 14 Pro机型上，实时活动可以在灵动岛和锁屏界面展示；而在非iPhone 14 Pro机型，则只在锁屏界面展示。

OneWidget如何定位灵动岛？
仔细阅读苹果开发者文档之后，我们发现实时活动的实现方式和小组件有非常多重叠的地方。同时，不管在锁屏界面还是“展开的”灵动岛位置，它的尺寸都很像中尺寸的桌面小组件。再者，实时活动不能够交互、也不能有动画、不能随时刷新，这些和小组件都太像了。所以，我们最终把实时活动定位成“一种特殊的小组件”。
当我们把“灵动岛”定义为“实时展示的小组件”，那么一切就更简单了，原则上小组件能够实现的它都可以实现。只是我们需要额外思考，在锁屏和灵动岛这两个特殊的位置，用户凭什么要展开来用它。
OneWidget怎么做灵动岛功能？
在迭代产品的2年多时间里，OneWidget的各种类型的小组件从用户那里得到了很多不错的回馈。当我们复盘这些小组件，用户最关心的是三个关键词：实用、美观、趣味。所以，设计灵动岛这个特殊的小组件，我们应该做的也是实用、美观、趣味。另外补充一点，对于很多用户来说，美观、趣味也是一种实用价值，美观带来个性化的装饰、趣味带来功能的尝鲜探索。
从实用和便捷角度，我们设计了“启动之岛”和“健康之岛”。
从美观和趣味角度，我们设计了“宠物之岛”和“摆烂之岛”。

如何开启灵动岛？
如果iPhone更新到iOS 16.1以上，下载OneWidget 的3.6.0以上的版本之后，可以进入个人中心找到主入口。在灵动岛配置页面，选择需要开启的“岛屿”，当App进入后台或者切换到其他App，实时活动就已经开启在了锁屏界面和灵动岛区域。
配置入口我们还单独设计了一些细节：会动的海平面、开启后的彩色提示框、预览效果等。

宠物之岛
用户可以在“宠物之岛”领养一个自己的电子宠物，它每天陪你玩、会饿、会困、会渴，在不同的状态下用户需要点击不同的操作。我们给宠物取了一个名字叫做“岛岛”，领养之后，在App内还会显示领养的天数。岛岛除了不同的状态，也有可能会出去玩耍，只有等他回来才能再次跟他互动。为了满足个性化，宠物“岛岛”还允许自定义颜色，现在我们支持了7种颜色的切换。

启动之岛
“启动之岛”可以允许用户添加快速启动App或者小程序的入口，常驻在锁屏界面和灵动岛里，展开之后即可点击一键直达的App。用户可以添加1~6的常用启动入口，根据添加的数量变化，图标和间距会自动调整来适应合适的布局。和锁屏小组件、桌面小组件一行，这里的启动器入口支持添加常用的App、微信支付宝的二级路径、微信和支付宝的小程序入口。

摆烂之岛
“摆烂之岛”将随机展示一些“反鸡汤”的插画和文案。这个功能为了满足“趣味性”，该卷的时候卷，该躺的时候也要好好躺。偶尔摆烂无可厚非，休息是人之常情。

健康之岛
“健康之岛”实时展示用户当天的健康数据，比如步数、运动时间、消耗能量、身高、体重等。尤其是对于每日会更新变动的数据，是可以查看更新数据的（不过目前系统刷新问题，会有较多延迟）。

 
以上就是OneWidget关于灵动岛功能的思考和功能的介绍。希望帮助大家了解灵动岛，也能够帮助大家通过这些小功能体验到灵动岛（实时活动）的用法。我们将继续做好一个“装修产品”，带来更多实用、美观、有趣的功能。
回见。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>好个科技</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine Could Never Afford to Bet on Starlink]]></title>
        <id>635026f3f1f6a083059bc054</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-starlink-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The internet service tool was essential in the early days of the war with Russia. But the caprices of SpaceX CEO Elon Musk have exposed dangerous flaws.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katherine Cross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High-Tech Cars Are Killing the Auto Repair Shop]]></title>
        <id>63489043acf5cc5989c35185</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/high-tech-cars-killing-the-traditional-auto-repair-shop/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many independent auto shops can’t afford the equipment needed to fix today’s complex vehicles. Prepare to wait longer for repairs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aarian Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New 3,200-Megapixel Camera Has Astronomers Salivating]]></title>
        <id>634dad426c255af47dbd5ed2</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/a-new-3200-megapixel-camera-has-astronomers-salivating/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Vera C. Rubin Observatory’s key instrument is almost ready to be installed on the telescope, where it will image tens of billions of cosmic objects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramin Skibba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Is an Ad Company Now]]></title>
        <id>63509e2ae87d0914ff59903d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/apple-is-an-ad-company-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pushing more ads at users would compensate for slowing smartphone sales but risks annoying Apple fans—and antitrust regulators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Clever Way to Map the Moon’s Surface—Using Shadows]]></title>
        <id>63508f422721236bcb15848e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/mapping-moon-shadows/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How shade is cast reveals details of the rugged lunar landscape, allowing NASA to create 3D models for astronauts and rovers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Theo Nicitopoulos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Vice Society Got Away With a Global Ransomware Spree]]></title>
        <id>633c99855ec45110c69a14a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/vice-society-ransomware-gang/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vice Society has a superpower that’s allowed it to quietly carry out attacks on schools and hospitals around the world: mediocrity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memos 一个开源且免费的自托管知识库]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76247</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76247"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T08:32:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi 大家好呀！我叫 Ask Term 。这是我来少数派写的教程系列文章的第一篇，给大家带来一个开源知识库 Memos 的部署教程，小伙伴们也许会问 Memos 什么？那么我就把官方对 Memos 的定义引用一下：

An open source, self-hosted knowledge base that works with a SQLite db file.

如何还是不太清楚这个是干嘛用的，那么体验一下官方的 Demo，体验过的小伙伴一定会觉得这不就是 Flomo 吗？确实，这算是非官方 Flomo 的开源替代品，鉴于 Memos 的开源特性你可以随意的部署在自己的服务器上去使用。
Memos 的部署也很简单，一条 Docker 命令就能启动，但是对于不熟悉 Docker 的小伙伴或许还是有些难度的，为此我写了这篇入门级的教程，让小伙伴能够轻松完成 Memos 的部署。
Flomo 和 Memos 的功能对比


对比FlomoMemos
收费方式免费有限制开源自托管
API 接口Pro 版免费使用免费开放
每日回顾Pro 版支持支持
微信输入支持不支持


通过对比我认为 Memos 除了在微信输入上欠缺了一点，在其它方面是胜过 Flomo 的，虽然不能够原生的支持微信输入，但是 Memos 官方开放了 API 接口，通过这个接口去连接个人的微信服务号或许可以实现微信输入的功能，网上也有类似通过 Telegram 进行输入的教程。
 
🔞注意：本次的部署环境为： Ubuntu 22.04.1 LTS
Docker 的安装
附上 Docker 官方部署文档（如果需要更详细的安装流程，请参考官方文档）
如果已经存在旧版本的 Docker并且想要卸载请执行卸载命令（非必要）
sudo apt-get remove docker docker-engine dock…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AskTerm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Desktop Pets – 那只羊，桌面宠物 macOS 版本]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43679</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/desktop-pets-for-macos/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T08:10:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Desktop Pets for macOS 是今天介绍的《eSheep 64bit – 来自 Windows 95 桌面宠物 STRAY SHEEP 流浪绵羊复刻版》的 macOS 版本，不是同一个]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 open source editors I use for my writing]]></title>
        <id>70260 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/open-source-editors"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[4 open source editors I use for my writing
Alan Formy-Duval
Thu, 10/20/2022 - 03:00

            
I've done a lot of writing throughout my career, mostly as an IT consultant creating product documentation as client deliverables. These documents generally provide instructions on installing various operating systems and software products.
Since 2018, I've contributed to opensource.com with articles about open source software. Of course, I use open source editors to write my pieces. Here are the four open source editors that I have used.
1. Vi
Vi, also referred to as Vim, is the first open source editor that I learned. This was the editor taught by my computer science classes and that I used for all of my C programming. I have used it as my de facto command line editor since the mid-1990s. Th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Formy-Duval</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eSheep 64bit – 来自 Windows 95 桌面宠物 STRAY SHEEP 流浪绵羊复刻版]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43673</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/desktop-pet-esheep-64bit/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T06:33:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[eSheep 64bit 是一款复刻了 Windows 95 时代 16/32 位程序 STRAY SHEEP 的开源软件，功能完全相同，一只漂亮的绵羊会在你的屏幕上走来走去，偶尔还会摔下去，就没有然]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Re-Wrote These 10+ Single Lines of JavaScript Code, the Team Lead Praised the Code for Being Elegant]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rida/i-re-wrote-these-10-single-lines-of-javascript-code-the-team-lead-praised-the-code-for-being-elegant-ec</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rida/i-re-wrote-these-10-single-lines-of-javascript-code-the-team-lead-praised-the-code-for-being-elegant-ec"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T04:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #beginners #programming #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rida F&amp;#39;kih</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run your README.md like a notebook in VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sourishkrout/run-your-readmemd-in-vs-code-50l7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sourishkrout/run-your-readmemd-in-vs-code-50l7"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T01:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#vscode #opensource #beginners #devops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Tiedtke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran's Internet Blackouts Are Part of a Global Menace]]></title>
        <id>634db7f67e817d200a6cc6ba</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/iran-mahsa-amini-internet-shutdown/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Repressive regimes are teaching each other how to control protesters' web access with increasingly surgical precision.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yasmin Green</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[War Is an Ecological Disaster—but Ukraine Can Build Back Greener]]></title>
        <id>634ef97908a267a4aad8c076</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/war-is-an-ecological-disaster-but-ukraine-can-build-back-greener/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russia’s invasion is reversing years of environmental progress. But the world can help Ukraine reconstruct its damaged landscape and energy systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Simon, Gregory Barber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Tool for Eruption Forecasting: Carbon-Catching Drones]]></title>
        <id>6349aee973d8e1a1ebea929d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/a-new-tool-for-eruption-forecasting-carbon-catching-drones/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the future, remote-controlled quadcopters might mean that researchers won’t have to crawl inside volcanoes to collect carbon dioxide anymore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katrina Miller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gig Law Causing Chaos in California Strip Clubs]]></title>
        <id>634f1e30e81217c42cd9fb0e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/gig-economy-strip-clubs/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dancers say a law to protect people working at ride-hailing and food delivery apps has been used to undercut their livelihoods.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Morgan Meaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PicWish for Windows — AI remove background, unblur images, bulk photo editor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/picwish-for-windows</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/picwish-for-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T07:17:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[城市收藏夹 | 法兰克福：在欧洲门户吃喝玩乐]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76261</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76261"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T05:44:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[法兰克福是欧洲的金融中心之一，地理位置也在中部，有着非常繁忙的机场。无论是金融还是空港，都扮演着欧洲门户的角色。九月底，时隔多年再次来到这座城市，终于弥补了之前匆匆而过的遗憾。
住宿&交通🚌
市区住宿：Best Western Plus Welcome Hotel Frankfurt

📍 Leonardo-da-Vinci-Allee 2, 60486 Frankfurt am Main, Germany
⏳ 入住：下午3点，退房：上午11点
🔗 https://www.bestwestern.de/

这家宾馆距离机场十几分钟的车程，和市中心罗马广场也是差不多的距离。宾馆的旁边有超市，可以购买水果和零食。宾馆的马路对面就是轻轨车站，可以乘坐17路去往市区，换乘地铁可以到达罗马广场，交通还算便利。如果是在入住时间前到达的宾馆，可以先把行李寄存在一楼。运气好的话，有房间空出来的时候，也可以在早晨就办理入住。
和宾馆相隔一个街区，就是一个公园。公园的入口处有几家小餐馆。公园里有篮球场，能看到很多青少年在玩儿街头篮球，也有不少推着婴儿的家庭来这里活动。
从房间往外看，能看到金融区的高楼大厦
小镇住宿：PK Parkhotel Kurhaus

📍 Kurhausstraße 28, 55543 Bad Kreuznach, Germany
⏳ 入住：下午3点，退房：上午11点
🔗 http://www.parkhotelkurhaus.com/

Bad Kreuznach是距离法兰克福约一小时车程的一个温泉镇，也是很多人们来度假的地方，所以宾馆不少。PK Parkhotel Kurhaus是一家四星级宾馆，但不巧的是入住的时候宾馆正在翻新，遇到了暖气不热等问题。这家宾馆毗邻一条河，附近有一座建于中世纪的桥，是个散步的好去处。
德语里有些词汇和英语拼写一样，但意思不同…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sholmes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 年软粉，为何重新用回 MacBook Pro]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76201</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76201"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T05:31:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[十一长假结束后，我打算使用 Surface Laptop 3  剪辑旅途中拍摄的视频素材。由于素材不多，分辨率也不高，我想它应该能够胜任简单的剪辑任务，结果不遂我愿。剪辑过程中这台电脑多次出现视频预览卡顿、Pr 莫名闪退等问题。在忍受了 7 年 Surface 系列笔记本的大小毛病后，我在苹果官网下单了一台 14 英寸 MacBook Pro。
这篇文章阐述了我认为以 Surface 为代表的 Windows 平台笔记本的通病，提供了一些不成功的解决方案，并展示更换到 MacBook 后的使用体验。

如果你和我一样是一名研究生，日常工作内容主要是阅读文献、写论文（撰写 Latex 代码）、写代码以及做 PPT。读完这篇文章，也许你想试试使用 MacBook Pro 继续你的工作
如果你被近期新发布的 Surface 系列笔记本吸引，正在持币观望，不妨读完这篇文章再决定是否入手最新的 Surface 系列

为什么倒戈来得这么晚
我的软粉生涯开始于 2015 年，彼时 Surface Pro 4 发布。全新的二合一形态笔记本让我觉得手里的 MacBook Air 瞬间不香了。2016 年，拿到大学录取通知书的那天晚上，我下单了一台 Surface Pro 4，从此开始了我的 7 年 Surface 使用生涯。在这期间有无数理由让我不再使用 Surface 系列， 而让我留下的理由只有一个——迷人的外观。
最开始购买了一台丐版 Surface Pro 4，在我大二转入计算机专业后，这台 Surface Pro 4 的性能就捉襟见肘了。 于是我将它换成了一台顶配的 Surface Book 1。这台 Surface Book 1 伴随了我 5 年多的时间，更换过一次屏幕，两次底座（均为内部电池发生鼓包）。在日常使用时，这台电脑经常发热（有时候合上盖子风扇也不停），时不时还会出现…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jiaozi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made a full-stack and type-safe personal site using the t3-stack (Next.js)!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/asheeshh/i-made-a-full-stack-portfolio-site-using-nextjs-and-tailwind-366d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/asheeshh/i-made-a-full-stack-portfolio-site-using-nextjs-and-tailwind-366d"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T18:22:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #beginners #react]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ashish</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Workers Lose Another Union Vote as Management Digs In]]></title>
        <id>634dece77fa81ffa8c2b0122</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/amazon-workers-lose-another-union-vote-management-digs-in/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T18:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three warehouses have voted on joining the Amazon Labor Union, but organizers prevailed in only one—and the retail giant’s heavily funded opposition continues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caitlin Harrington</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[租房也努力精致一点：房屋小改小造计划]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76216</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76216"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T15:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[作为在大城市工作的年轻人，租房是一个永远都绕不开的“时髦”话题。能够拥有一个舒适的小窝，让自己在忙碌一天之后彻底放松和沉静下来，对我来说应该是每天最触手可及的快乐。但是，租来的房子总有各种不尽如人意的地方，而且受限于房东的要求、时间、财力等问题，也不可能像小红书家居博主的租房视频一样进行大改，所以，我将我的小屋改造计划关键词定为：小改小造。当然，所谓的修补也不可能是一步到位的，经过了小半年的边住边搞，到现在才基本完成了一开始的大部分设想。如果你和我一样也有想要小改小造的想法，那么我希望这篇文章可以对你有一些帮助。
（本文有可能巨长，请耐心地看这篇流水账~）
租来的基本状况
本着不在路上花过多时间，并且要最大化个人生活空间的原则，我选择租公司附近两公里范围内的一室户，这不可避免地限制了我的很多租房想法。除去价格不菲的商用公寓和城中村，几乎就已经没有其他的选项，所以选来选去，只能做出妥协，定了一个小区里的公寓楼。
户型状况
我租到的是一室一厅的户型，但这栋公寓都有一个致命的缺点——客厅不见光。没有办法，租房不可能样样完美，考虑到白天几乎都在工作，周末和假期也尽可能逼迫自己出门浪而不是在家里发霉，所以也就勉强接受了这个缺陷。总的来说，这个户型面积相对可观，除了一些无法改动的分区（例如卫生间和厨房），其余还是有很多空间可以利用。
我家的简单户型图
室内状况
这栋公寓大多数房源，都归属于几个来深圳避寒的东北大姐，难得我这间的房东是一个系那个对年轻的国企深二代。但房东自己并不是一个乐于布置的人，房间里大多数的设施都是为了方便他做铲屎官，所以除了还算认真地定制了柜子、装了电视以及摆了一个还能用的沙发。
总的来说，租来的状况仅仅是个凑活，对我而言还远远不能达到拎包入住的状态。好在我个人也有一些从上一个家带来的“资产”，和一些软装的小计划，因此这个水平也刚好给了我一些发挥的空间。于是，漫漫“…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EricYoung</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Section 230’s Fate Belongs With Congress—Not the US Supreme Court]]></title>
        <id>634d5fefd8c7bf0344fc40bf</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/section-230-scotus-gonzalez-google/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A case heading to SCOTUS claims platforms should be held responsible for their algorithmic recommendations. A history of the statute suggests otherwise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Kosseff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Best Password Managers (2022): Features, Pricing, and Tips]]></title>
        <id>5ce3031cfd8c3451c5008275</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-password-managers/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keep your logins locked down with our favorite apps for PC, Mac, Android, iPhone, and web browsers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gilbertson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China's WeChat Is a Hot New Venue for US Election Misinformation]]></title>
        <id>633b13c1c81a2bcfbbb7731c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/chinese-american-misinformation-midterm-elections-wechat/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of US midterms, activists are fighting falsehoods circulating in Chinese-language communities that they fear will distort the vote or suppress turnout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Conrad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Is Finally Considering Protections Against Salmonella]]></title>
        <id>63489547c54652e29defa0a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-us-is-finally-considering-protections-against-salmonella/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bacteria, which contaminate poultry meat, sicken 1.35 million Americans every year. But there’s very little the federal government can do to stop it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maryn McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Video Game Store with Medusa and Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/medusajs/how-to-build-a-video-game-store-with-medusa-and-nextjs-kem</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/medusajs/how-to-build-a-video-game-store-with-medusa-and-nextjs-kem"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T11:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #programming #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekekenta Odioyenfe .C, Medusa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Unnatural Future of Physics]]></title>
        <id>6346eaba136a8fc35853e3f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/unnatural-future-physics/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To get a sense of how physicists might solve the “naturalness problem,” I contacted one who calls himself “a deviant by default.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KC Cole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ebola Is Back—and Vaccines Don’t Work Against It]]></title>
        <id>634dcaa6d540a0d4bba0cce6</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/uganda-ebola-outbreak-vaccine/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Public health officials are racing to contain an outbreak in Uganda. It’s an urgent warning to the rest of the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esther Nakkazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the World Will Know If Russia Is Preparing to Launch a Nuclear Attack]]></title>
        <id>63485a876c255af47dbd5eb1</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/russia-ukraine-nuclear-attack-surveillance/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While tensions over a possible nuclear attack on Ukraine remain high, experts say surveillance will likely catch Russia if it plans to do the unthinkable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is CORS?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jpomykala/what-is-cors-11kf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jpomykala/what-is-cors-11kf"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T09:36:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #react #webdev #typescript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakub Pomykała</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【键微知著】当我们使用Alice配列时我们在追求什么？]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76233</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76233"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T07:14:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[本文仅代表个人观点。
欢迎评论区友好讨论。虽然都是些浅短的认识，但是分享出来也算是一种体验，非常感谢大家的观看和意见。

大家好我是车不能快，一个有点闲的键盘爱好者，很高兴和大家再次见面。这次开启了一个新栏目《键微知著》，这个栏目主要是分享一些我自己对于跟键盘有关的想法和看法，比较主观，所以观看的时候还望大家海涵 ，不过这个栏目的更新频率不会太高，因为确实比较需要时间去沉淀，也算是我玩键盘留下的一些痕迹。
切入正题，今天就来讲讲前段时间异军突起的小众配列——Alice。

FOFO拍摄
想必这把键盘大家都不会陌生，Spring这把键盘在今年可谓是「声名远扬」，凭借优秀的手感表现成功突围，同时也带动了Alice这个小众配列再次火了一把，连量产环境都受到了一定的影响，出现了许多量产的Alice键盘以供玩家选择。
例如：akko Alice、 Keychron Alice、FEKER Alice等

SnVittarius 拍摄 akkoAlice

feker Alice
第一眼看到Alice键盘的感觉是「怪异」，对于变形的抗拒、对于传统的坚守，是的，说来惭愧，作为一个客制化的玩家，很多时候我还是秉持着传统的观念去看待这些新奇的产品，不过我觉得这也是客制化对我最大的意义所在，有机会去尝试这些新鲜事物，思想上也能从传统保守的观念束缚中得以抽身。都什么年代，还在玩传统键盘？
然而在经过将近一年的使用之后，我对于Alice配列的疑惑不减反增。这个配列好在哪？为什么会有这么多的玩家能接受和使用它？
回头看，那些曾经贴在它身上的标签「人体工学键盘」、"裂开的键盘"、「独具美感的键盘」，究竟哪些词汇形容这把键盘最为贴切？
为了寻找答案，我开始了漫长的搜寻之旅，敲击着手上的Alice配列，答案仿佛就在指尖。

当我们介绍Alice配列时，印象最为深刻的点是什么？
人体工学键盘
在讨论如今的A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>车不能快</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[在小宇宙听了 1000 小时后，我做了这个小工具]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76248</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76248"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T07:06:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[前段时间突然收到小宇宙的系统通知：小宇宙陪伴你 1000 小时啦。在听博客这段期间，遇到有趣的嘉宾，总想听听与他相关的其他节目，于是尝试开发了一个小工具：中文播客通讯录，采用类似通讯录的方式，基于主播姓名来查看播客内容。
主播模式

目前只录入了部分内容，逐步添加中；部分 shownotes 主播信息不是特别清楚
 
节目模式
 
其他

iOS 支持跳转小宇宙（安卓没有测试过）
主播界面支持单期节目图
主播支持添加到桌面，桌面图标会自动选择最新一期的封面图
节目支持添加到桌面，桌面图标会选择界面 logo

使用
地址：https://xyz.bln.cn
二维码访问

 
未来计划

目前都是个人手工录入，所以数量还比较少（一派目前已经全部录入），未来会开放录入能力，大家一起来迭代

有任何建议，欢迎评论~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>desenmeng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bruce Willis Deepfake Is Everyone’s Problem]]></title>
        <id>634d9b9173d8e1a1ebea929e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/bruce-willis-deepfake-rights-law/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T18:19:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a fight brewing over how Hollywood stars can protect their identities. But it’s not just actors who should be paying attention.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Bedingfield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Iodine Pills Can—and Can’t—Help Against Radiation]]></title>
        <id>634470e22c2c7a7522a985fc</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/iodine-pills-nuclear-radiation/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[East European governments are starting to distribute the tablets as a precaution, but there are limits to the protection they offer, and who might need them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Mullin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a chat app with Socket.io and React Native 🤯]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/novu/building-a-chat-app-with-socketio-and-react-native-k1b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/novu/building-a-chat-app-with-socketio-and-react-native-k1b"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T11:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #programming #reactnative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevo David, novu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Crypto Alchemist Made Me an Accidental Billionaire]]></title>
        <id>6349a52b6c255af47dbd5ecd</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/valentin-broeksmit-incognito-cryptocurrency/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Valentin Broeksmit tried to exploit crypto vulnerabilities to squeeze money out of thin air. The catch is, he couldn’t cash out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gian M. Volpicelli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If You Don’t Already Live in a Sponge City, You Will Soon]]></title>
        <id>6344609067bdca87bfc36100</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/if-you-dont-already-live-in-a-sponge-city-you-will-soon/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Less pavement and more green spaces help absorb water instead of funneling it all away—a win-win for people and urban ecosystems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Restful API with Golang practical approach]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/firdavs_kasymov/restful-api-with-golang-practical-approach-420a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/firdavs_kasymov/restful-api-with-golang-practical-approach-420a"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T08:42:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#go #tutorial #microservices #devops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Firdavs Kasymov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM PASS PWN (二)]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11768</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11768"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T08:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM PASS PWN (二)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hunt for Wikipedia's Disinformation Moles]]></title>
        <id>634587f52c2c7a7522a9860e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/wikipedia-state-sponsored-disinformation/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Custodians of the crowdsourced encyclopedia are charged with protecting it from state-sponsored manipulators. A new study reveals how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Masha Borak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[忍不了了，做了个插件让 OneNote 支持 Markdown]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76228</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76228"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T07:22:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

一年多前，由于工作原因，主力开发机换成了 Windows，还入了 Office 365 全家桶。于是在时隔多年后，再次用起了 OneNote。不得不说，都 2022 年了，OneNote 的码字体验还停留在十多年前，一堆大大小小的遗留问题。但我实在懒得折腾什么 Notion、Obsidian（没有复杂的知识管理需求），只想找个本地/靠谱/大厂出品/开箱即用的笔记软件，简单记录下工作相关内容。 毕竟人一旦习惯了 markdown 的符号 # 和 -，就真的回不去了。于是研究了下 OneNote 的 api，决定自己动手，丰衣足食。OneMark 由此诞生。
实时渲染
废话不多说，直接上动图。

简单来说，OneMark 实现了基于行的实时渲染，每次按回车时会触发渲染当前行。当然，这个实时 跟新世代编辑器字符级别的没法比，但已经足够好用了。
不仅如此，终于在 OneNote 上实现了可用级别的代码高亮，输入``` 创建代码块后，每敲一行自动着色。用过 OneNote 的都懂，之前插入代码需要诸多操作，繁琐到想摔键盘。

以及 LaTex 转换到 OneNote 原生的数学公式（不是图片）。

除此之外，还支持TOC / todo / 水平线 / 脚注 等常见的语法，直接拿已有的 markdown 内容粘贴到 OneNote 中， 然后按 F5 渲染，大概率是可以完美还原的。

 
没有美美的样式主题，怎么能算一个合格的笔记软件呢？众所周知，OneNote 本身的样式功能十分鸡肋，用户很难自定义主题，只能默默忍受一成不变的素面朝天。于是我花了好大力气，实现了解析 css 样式的功能，从此 OneNote 的笔记颜值终于能打了。

双向编辑
你可能会问：这种转换是单向的吗？我如果有一天想导出 markdown 纯文本怎么办？在我看来，原始 markdown 丢失是绝对不能接受的，所以我花了很大力气来解决这个问题：笔记中每个段落的 markdown 原文都以某种格式隐藏存储在自身之中，可以随时读取，不依赖外部文件，任意编辑也不会破坏。而且这种格式是公开透明的，只需要用 OneNote api 拿到 XML 格式的笔记内容，所有秘密一览无余。
更重要的是，渲染后的内容可以原地随意增删修改，不必再重新切换回 markdown 形态编辑；而且在导出 markdown 时，内容也会相应更新——是的，实现了双向更新。当然，如果由于某些原因，你想切换回 markdown 形态编辑，也是支持的。按 ctrl + , ，即可在编辑和预览之间切换。

结语
OneMark 目前只支持 OneNote Windows 桌面版，不支持 UWP 版本以及 Mac 版本（好消息是微软正着手将 UWP 版本的功能迁移到桌面版，以后会只保留桌面版，最近的更新频率也让广大 OneNote 使用者倍感惊喜）。官网 https://onemark.neuxlab.cn/， 欢迎大家试用反馈。
后记：我为什么选择 OneNote
有人会问：不是有很多专业的 markdown 笔记软件吗，为什么还要用 OneNote？
我个人的感悟是：我首先需要的是一个自由轻松的笔记软件，其次是 markdown。我是一个懒人，无论是日常生活，还是工作学习，都没有那么 organized，十分不擅长把东西整理并保持得井井有条。我的笔记中，有一些认真记录和思考产出的内容，但更多时候，是很随意、很碎片、很当下的信息记录。我试过，当面对一个专业的 markdown 笔记软件时，我会变得十分紧张不自在，不知道该把这些零碎、混乱的信息放到哪里。一旦产生了这种情绪，想要记录的念头也随即不了了之。
而 OneNote 简单直接的界面、清晰的笔记结构、自由的无限画布，让我使用起来没有任何心理压力。唯一的缺点就是当需要认真输出内容时，没有 markdown 这件趁手的兵器，确实有点力不从心。补齐了这点之后，对于我个人而言就别无他求了。
其实十多年前，OneNote 刚推出的时候也曾惊艳四座， 那时的设计理念和体验还是很超前的，有了现在流行的 block level 编辑器的雏形，无论是列表、段落、表格，书写和调整起来都非常得心应手。也多亏了这些设计，结合 markdown 之后居然毫不违和，整体体验下来有点现代编辑器的味道了。个中玄妙，就待各位亲自上手把玩了。
> 下载 少数派 2.0 客户端、关注 少数派公众号，解锁全新阅读体验 📰 
> 实用、好用的 正版软件，少数派为你呈现 🚀]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>siyu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【键多识广】国风好设计——GLOVE × DOMIKEY繁文生肖键帽评测]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76193</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76193"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T06:42:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[本专栏所使用资料来源于网络以及群友和个人的一些看法，欢迎友好讨论。虽然都是些浅短的认识，但是分享出来也算是一种体验，非常感谢大家的观看和意见。（该专栏写于2022.6，最新的dmk热升华水平请参考wob评测）

切入正题，本篇专栏来讲讲我最近自己入手的一套的键帽——
《繁文生肖》

来自IC
说实话这套键帽一开始并没有引起我的注意，因为热升华的PBT键帽在色彩表现力上是远不如二色成型工艺的键帽。但在我往下翻阅的时候，渲染图直接抓住了我的心。

IC
毫无疑问，这是第一套有繁体中文字根设计的键帽，并且确实是超出常规的设计，可以说手套哥的设计水准确实不是盖的。

打样
但随之而来的就是几个问题在我心头萦绕。

1·工艺问题
本次代工是高端键帽大厂DOMIKEY。对于dmk的实力和做工，我是非常认可的，但问题在于，这是dmk的第一套pbt热升华键帽，此前他们从未有生产过热升华键帽，虽然在我的前一篇科普关于热升华工艺键帽我个人的一些理解 - 哔哩哔哩 (bilibili.com)已经简略介绍了一些有关于PBT热升华的知识，但是这些只是纸上谈兵罢了，高端热升华键帽之所以是高端热升华，是因为随着价格的提升，消费者的要求也随之提升——遮光性、字符清晰度、手感、键帽弯曲等等瑕疵不能出现。如果价格来到了这个价位，那么这些要求我认为也是合情合理的。
2·价格问题
厂虎的价格是499小全套，个性纹样129。这个价格，真心不算低了，即便是目前所谓的顶级热升华键帽CRP,价格也是600目前涨价之后。DOMIKEY第一次做热升华键帽，便开出如此顶级的价格，虽然是比二色要便宜一些，但热升华的成本并不算高，这么看来dmk应该是对于自己工艺非常有信心，并且有着对这套键帽设计极高的预期。事实证明，他的确押对宝了。
这套限时不限量的键帽在三天的开车预售时间内卖出了800+的惊人成绩。同时再一次证明了我的观点，买…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>车不能快</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[不算成功的探索，寻找 macOS 本地音乐播放管理软件]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76158</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76158"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T06:17:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

作为 macOS 用户，本地音乐管理一直是我感到头疼的问题。虽然大部分时间都在 macOS 系统下，但我目前的音乐资料库，是在 Windows 系统上使用 Musicbee 整理而成，文件夹结构是：歌手/专辑/单曲，并且自定义了各类的播放列表（m3u 格式），这些内容都通过群晖 NAS 在各个设备上同步。
资料库中大部分是从 CD 导入，这样做的好处是可以很容易的抓取正确歌曲名，轨道信息及专辑封面等内容。网上下载的音乐信息会相对混乱，但在导入时我也会手动进行整理，因此资料库 90% 以上的音乐经过整理、拥有专辑封面。
macOS 中不管是曾经的 iTunes 或现在的 Apple Music 都不支持直接导入 Flac 格式文件，需要转换成 ALAC 或者 WAV 格式才能使用，非常繁琐。给我心中埋下了需要寻找全新应用的种子。
而在没有寻找本地音乐软件前，我使用 Audio Station ——群晖官方提供的音乐套件。在 iOS 上也有对应的 app 可以访问资料库在线播放。但 Audio Station 并没有桌面软件，只能通过浏览器访问，不是很方便，同时远程访问音乐难免会遇到网络问题，总没有直接存储在本地来的方便。
Audio Station 网站截图
于是我希望找到一个好用的音乐软件来解决这些问题，总结来说，我对它有这几点畅想：

可以导入指定位置音乐文件，并无需复制至其他位置，或打乱原有文件顺序；
兼容大部分常见的音乐格式；
可以导入 m3u 格式的播放列表，并且正确关联音乐文件；
优美的界面展示，可以显示专辑封面；
合理…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>johnbens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to write a good README]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/merlos/how-to-write-a-good-readme-bog</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/merlos/how-to-write-a-good-readme-bog"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T04:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#github #git #writing #documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merlos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一种隐蔽的利用Django中间件（Middleware）留后门的方法]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11766</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11766"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T02:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一种隐蔽的利用Django中间件（Middleware）留后门的方法]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IIS下.Net 的预编译模式]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11765</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11765"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T02:09:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IIS下.Net 的预编译模式]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SystemTap在应急排查中的应用]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11764</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11764"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T01:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SystemTap在应急排查中的应用]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why We're Breaking Up with CSS-in-JS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/srmagura/why-were-breaking-up-wiht-css-in-js-4g9b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/srmagura/why-were-breaking-up-wiht-css-in-js-4g9b"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T19:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #react #css #typescript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Magura</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Drives Galaxies? The Milky Way’s Black Hole May Be the Key]]></title>
        <id>633b18c891ba135542e3d5b6</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-milky-ways-black-hole-may-be-the-key-to-what-drives-galaxies/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supermassive black holes are engines of galactic evolution, but new observations of our galaxy and its central hole don’t quite match expectations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Lewton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Passkeys in Google Chrome and Android]]></title>
        <id>63499d7b04d20e5d7c550aad</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-use-passkeys-google-chrome-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google wants to make your digital life—in its ecosystem, anyway—passwordless and more secure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Nield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Cool Things Boring Old HTML Can Do 🤯]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/6-cool-things-boring-old-html-can-do-3160</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/6-cool-things-boring-old-html-can-do-3160"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T07:17:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #programming #html #javascript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapajyoti Bose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Just Got Even More Awesome]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dayvster/react-just-got-even-more-awesome-f15</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dayvster/react-just-got-even-more-awesome-f15"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T15:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #webdev #javascript #typescript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dayvster 🌊</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s SpaceX Bails on Starlink Funding for Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>63499d6c7e817d200a6cc672</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-starlink-funding-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: Hackers hit the Mormon Church, Signal plans to ditch SMS for Android, and a Fat Bear election erupts in scandal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Couts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Delhi Is Teeming With Mosquitoes]]></title>
        <id>63445ca42c2c7a7522a985fb</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/why-delhi-is-teeming-with-mosquitoes/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[City residents have long resorted to low-cost, do-it-yourself remedies that may be harmful to human health.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Monika Mondal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM PASS PWN（一）]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11762</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11762"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T05:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM PASS PWN（一）]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apache  Commons Text]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11761</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11761"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T13:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache  Commons Text]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[对Java CMS的审计的一次尝试]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11760</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11760"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T13:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[对Java CMS的审计的一次尝试]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What If the Metaverse Is Better Without Virtual Reality?]]></title>
        <id>6348464408a267a4aad8c051</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/plaintext-metaverse-better-without-virtual-reality/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: How Mark Zuckerberg fell in love with VR, the fake future of documentaries, and Armageddon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Algorithms Promote Self-Harm, Who Is Held Responsible?]]></title>
        <id>63481a7c8e4a6cd698dd9f5c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/molly-russell-suicide-platforms-mental-health/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A British court ruled that teenager Molly Russell died in part because of online content—but holding platforms accountable is complicated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eleanor Cummins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Reboot of the Maxwell’s Demon Thought Experiment—in Real Life]]></title>
        <id>6348a9bbd8c7bf0344fc40b7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/maxwells-demon-thought-experiment-reboot/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Physicists just reconstructed a 19th-century paradox that seems to violate the second law of thermodynamics (but really doesn’t).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resin内存马逆袭之路]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11758</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11758"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T03:09:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Resin内存马逆袭之路]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recycled Battery Materials Can Work as Well as New Ones]]></title>
        <id>6346fdfe136a8fc35853e3f9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/recycled-battery-materials-can-work-as-well-as-new-ones/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an independent test, cathode components Redwood Materials made from reused metals matched the performance of those made from raw ones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Barber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The $1 Billion Alex Jones Effect]]></title>
        <id>63483cd27e817d200a6cc669</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/alex-jones-1-billion-damages-free-speech-moderation/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T16:33:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Infowars host now knows the cost of “free speech”—but does the landmark judgment signal a crackdown on disinformation?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The $1 Billion Alex Jones Effect]]></title>
        <id>63483cd27e817d200a6cc669</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/alex-jones-1-billion-damages-free-speech-moderation/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T16:33:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Infowars host now knows the cost of “free speech”—but does the landmark judgment signal a crackdown on disinformation?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[记一次简单的src挖掘]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11757</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11757"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T15:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[记一次简单的src挖掘]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Zero to DevOps Engineer - DevOps Roadmap for YOUR specific background 🔥]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/techworld_with_nana/from-zero-to-devops-engineer-devops-roadmap-for-your-specific-background-4h8n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/techworld_with_nana/from-zero-to-devops-engineer-devops-roadmap-for-your-specific-background-4h8n"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T13:35:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#devops #career #cloud #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TechWorld with Nana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Shouldn’t Compete With Workers—It Should Supercharge Them]]></title>
        <id>633f467992468d5a8855add9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ai-shouldnt-compete-with-workers-it-should-supercharge-them-turing-trap/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The economy could get a boost if machine learning engineers switched from copying human abilities to augmenting them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clive Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Shouldn’t Compete With Workers—It Should Supercharge Them]]></title>
        <id>633f467992468d5a8855add9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ai-shouldnt-compete-with-workers-it-should-supercharge-them-turing-trap/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The economy could get a boost if machine learning engineers switched from copying human abilities to augmenting them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clive Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awesome tools for Coding Practice]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-tools-for-coding-practice-4l49</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-tools-for-coding-practice-4l49"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T11:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #beginners #react #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Vishwakarma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s VR Headset Harvests Personal Data Right Off Your Face]]></title>
        <id>6345d480d01ed05afa60f977</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/metas-vr-headset-quest-pro-personal-data-face/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cameras inside the device that track eye and face movements can make an avatar’s expressions more realistic, but they raise new privacy questions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khari Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Pharma Says Drug Prices Reflect R&D Cost. Researchers Call BS]]></title>
        <id>634777aa7fa81ffa8c2b0106</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/drug-research-pricing/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study finds no correlation between research and development spending and outlandish drug prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grace Browne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius Exchange Data Dump Is a Gift to Crypto Sleuths—and Thieves]]></title>
        <id>6345b95754f8c6faa9d67d3c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/celsius-user-data-dump-crypto-tracing-scammers/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By releasing half a million users’ transactions in a bankruptcy court filing, the company has opened a vast breach in its users’ financial privacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Search for a Pill That Can Help Dogs—and Humans—Live Longer]]></title>
        <id>633de7e0fe6027f6ad16e5bd</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-search-for-a-pill-for-dog-and-human-longevity/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People have been searching for a fountain of youth for thousands of years. Celine Halioua thinks she’s found one—for canines. Be patient, we’re next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Simonite</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Made My Portfolio with Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/j471n/how-i-made-my-portfolio-with-nextjs-2mn3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/j471n/how-i-made-my-portfolio-with-nextjs-2mn3"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T09:24:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #beginners #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jatin Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should we hire junior developer advocates?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/blackgirlbytes/should-we-hire-junior-developer-advocates-13m2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/blackgirlbytes/should-we-hire-junior-developer-advocates-13m2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T01:08:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#discuss #devrel #career #management]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rizèl Scarlett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What It Means to ‘Feel Normal’ Online]]></title>
        <id>632ae3b036c33c0247a2f0b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/psychology-data-surveillance-normality-personality/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A personalized, authentic experience is an unquestioned building block of digital infrastructure. But what does that really involve?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tung-Hui Hu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Chip Sanctions ‘Kneecap’ China’s Tech Industry]]></title>
        <id>63444b96136a8fc35853e3e7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/us-chip-sanctions-kneecap-chinas-tech-industry/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The toughest export restrictions yet cut off AI hardware and chipmaking tools crucial to China’s commercial and military ambitions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Chip Sanctions ‘Kneecap’ China’s Tech Industry]]></title>
        <id>63444b96136a8fc35853e3e7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/us-chip-sanctions-kneecap-chinas-tech-industry/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The toughest export restrictions yet cut off AI hardware and chipmaking tools crucial to China’s commercial and military ambitions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Pixel 7 and Pixel 7 Pro Pack New Android VPN and Tensor G2, Titan M2 Chips]]></title>
        <id>634592230b299b05896f7c1c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/google-pixel-7-pixel-7-pro-tensor-g2-android-vpn/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T19:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company says it hardened the security of its new flagship phones—and plans to release a built-in Android VPN.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Signal for Help I Created Went Viral. Now It Could Be Misused]]></title>
        <id>633ada06e0fe4cc825d3a56c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/domestic-violence-artificial-intelligence-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well-meaning efforts to integrate the hand signal with digital technology could expose vulnerable people to detection and escalated violence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrea Gunraj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Signal for Help I Created Went Viral. Now It Could Be Misused]]></title>
        <id>633ada06e0fe4cc825d3a56c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/domestic-violence-artificial-intelligence-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well-meaning efforts to integrate the hand signal with digital technology could expose vulnerable people to detection and escalated violence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrea Gunraj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advice for Junior Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jeroendedauw/advice-for-junior-developers-30am</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jeroendedauw/advice-for-junior-developers-30am"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T12:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#beginners #productivity #codenewbie #learning]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeroen De Dauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building THE MOST practical Todolist with React and Websockets 🪄✨]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/novu/building-the-most-practical-todolist-with-react-and-websockets-18hd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/novu/building-the-most-practical-todolist-with-react-and-websockets-18hd"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T10:07:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #javascript #webdev #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevo David, novu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to eliminate if-else chain, for long life software]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/smuhammed/how-to-eliminate-if-else-chain-for-long-life-software-3ea3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/smuhammed/how-to-eliminate-if-else-chain-for-long-life-software-3ea3"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T23:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#cleancode #programming #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sameh Muhammed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 Now Offers Automatic Phishing Protection]]></title>
        <id>63374abad90aafbd66b0c6cb</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/windows-11-automatic-phishing-protection/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’re safer than ever—here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Nield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are the best platforms to write technical articles?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/surajondev/what-are-the-best-platforms-to-write-technical-articles-37fn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/surajondev/what-are-the-best-platforms-to-write-technical-articles-37fn"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#discuss #javascript #react #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Vishwakarma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Remote Tech Workers Secretly Juggle Multiple Jobs]]></title>
        <id>6340bd5b7683076f6363ecac</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/remote-tech-workers-secret-multiple-jobs/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working from home makes it easier to take on several full-time posts. The extra cash is nice—but simultaneous Zoom meetings can be tricky.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Carnegie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Yourself If Your School Uses Surveillance Tech]]></title>
        <id>633c99e6f9498791684f713b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-protect-yourself-school-surveillance-tech-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colleges and K-12 campuses increasingly monitor student emails, social media, and more. Here’s how to secure your (or your child’s) privacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pia Ceres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hurricane Ian Destroyed Their Homes. Algorithms Sent Them Money]]></title>
        <id>6340bf58eb69b9d725e55ae2</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hurricane-ian-destroyed-homes-google-algorithms-sent-money/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's AI scanned satellite imagery to identify the worst-hit neighborhoods—helping direct aid to residents' phones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Yourself If Your School Uses Surveillance Tech]]></title>
        <id>633c99e6f9498791684f713b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-protect-yourself-school-surveillance-tech-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colleges and K-12 campuses increasingly monitor student emails, social media, and more. Here’s how to secure your (or your child’s) privacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pia Ceres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hurricane Ian Destroyed Their Homes. Algorithms Sent Them Money]]></title>
        <id>6340bf58eb69b9d725e55ae2</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hurricane-ian-destroyed-homes-google-algorithms-sent-money/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's AI scanned satellite imagery to identify the worst-hit neighborhoods—helping direct aid to residents' phones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Yourself If Your School Uses Surveillance Tech]]></title>
        <id>633c99e6f9498791684f713b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-protect-yourself-school-surveillance-tech-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colleges and K-12 campuses increasingly monitor student emails, social media, and more. Here’s how to secure your (or your child’s) privacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pia Ceres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[:where :is CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mustapha/where-is-css-20nk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mustapha/where-is-css-20nk"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T08:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#css #webdev #beginners #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mustapha Aouas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turn around your Git mistakes in 17 ways]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/smitterhane/turn-around-your-git-mistakes-in-17-ways-2mn1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/smitterhane/turn-around-your-git-mistakes-in-17-ways-2mn1"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T12:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#git #productivity #github #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Smitter hane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why It’s the Age of the Investor-Entrepreneur]]></title>
        <id>633f414181222da12cb0d9f1</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/investor-entrepreneur/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plural's Taavet Hinrikus says early-stage VC funds need to set a founder to catch a founder.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Armstrong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe’s Plan to Beat Silicon Valley at Its Own Game]]></title>
        <id>633f415585e7a4cc2f80227b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/europe-beat-silicon-valley-startups/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WIRED spoke with Skype cofounder Niklas Zennström about why the burgeoning European startup scene is poised to lead the technological revolution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Armstrong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made 1,000x faster TypeScript Validator Library]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/samchon/typescript-json-is-10-1000x-times-faster-than-zod-and-io-ts-8n6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/samchon/typescript-json-is-10-1000x-times-faster-than-zod-and-io-ts-8n6"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T16:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #typescript #opensource #benchmark]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeongho Nam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paranoia Threatens to Upend Professional Chess]]></title>
        <id>633f2a90058264dd3ee9304a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/magnus-carlsen-hans-niemann-cheating-chess-fide/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Magnus Carlsen–Hans Niemann cheating scandal points to abuses and suspicion at the highest levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg Keener</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Hackers Minted $569M in Crypto—Then It Got Complicated]]></title>
        <id>634019df81222da12cb0da05</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/binance-hackers-minted-569-million/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: The US warns of a mysterious military contractor breach, a "poisoned" version of the Tor Browser is tracking Chinese users, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman, Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in Tel Aviv]]></title>
        <id>633dee8185e7a4cc2f802274</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-in-tel-aviv-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Home to Silicon Wadi and a long-running streak of mega-money exits, the Tel Aviv tech scene leads with innovative applications of robotics, AI and medtech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Armstrong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in Amsterdam]]></title>
        <id>633def4820105ba57106995f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-amsterdam-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amsterdam continues to punch well above its weight, combining tech powerhouse status with being one of the most livable cities on the continent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gian M. Volpicelli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Makes a Champagne Vintage Great? Ask a Deep Learning Model]]></title>
        <id>6340b2c1d01ed05afa60f88b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/what-makes-a-champagne-vintage-great-ask-a-deep-learning-model/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bollinger is data mining its meticulous records to predict vintage years and weather the challenges of climate change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Barber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Uber Data Breach Conviction Shows Security Execs What Not to Do]]></title>
        <id>633ee35881222da12cb0d9a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/uber-joe-sullivan-conviction/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T19:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Uber security chief Joe Sullivan’s conviction is a rare criminal consequence for an executive’s handling of a hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden’s Privacy Order Slaps a Band-Aid on the EU-US Data Crisis]]></title>
        <id>634078763099da4d4e0dd65d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/biden-eu-us-data-privacy-executive-order/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T19:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new executive order tries to reassure Europeans that their data is safe on US soil, despite government surveillance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Morgan Meaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Turned My Startup Into Open-Source]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nevodavid/i-turned-my-startup-into-open-source-4efh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nevodavid/i-turned-my-startup-into-open-source-4efh"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T18:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #programming #webdev #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevo David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Deepfake Bruce Willis Doing in My Metaverse?]]></title>
        <id>633f03e57e8d589e28665ae3</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/plaintext-bruce-willis-deepfake-metaverse/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: The future as seen from 1991, Google fights Apple for your wrist, and nuclear war.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Async & Await]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maximization/understanding-async-await-22o6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maximization/understanding-async-await-22o6"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T12:28:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #beginners #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maxim Orlov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 GitHub Repositories to Contribute for Hacktoberfest 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/atapas/15-github-repositories-to-contribute-for-hacktoberfest-2022-215d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/atapas/15-github-repositories-to-contribute-for-hacktoberfest-2022-215d"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T09:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#opensource #hacktoberfest #webdev #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapas Adhikary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are You Sure You Know What Revenge Porn Is?]]></title>
        <id>633ca4055a49457c993f5331</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/revenge-porn-platforms-grindr-queerness/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forty-eight states have passed protections against revenge porn—but their narrow definition of such content leaves many people exposed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Gilden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awesome tools for Open Source Contribution]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-tools-for-open-source-contribution-36cm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-tools-for-open-source-contribution-36cm"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T11:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#opensource #beginners #javascript #react]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Vishwakarma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Needs to Recognize Intimate Privacy as a Civil Right]]></title>
        <id>6317a57979f10149f7bb9f4a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/privacy-intimacy-civil-rights-danielle-citron/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital privacy invasion isn’t just a consumer protection issue. It’s inextricably linked to equality, with urgent implications for women and minorities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danielle Keats Citron</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Change your old methods for writing a JavaScript Code - Shorthand's for JavaScript Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devsimc/change-your-old-methods-for-writing-a-javascript-code-shorthands-for-javascript-code-54hp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devsimc/change-your-old-methods-for-writing-a-javascript-code-shorthands-for-javascript-code-54hp"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T12:51:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #beginners #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>simc dev CSM®</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn this before React]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jps27cse/learn-this-before-react-4hpl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jps27cse/learn-this-before-react-4hpl"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T04:47:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #javascript #webdev #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Pritom Soren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Created a File Sharing Website using Simple JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/varshithvhegde/how-i-created-a-file-sharing-website-using-simple-javascript-355g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/varshithvhegde/how-i-created-a-file-sharing-website-using-simple-javascript-355g"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T04:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#html #javascript #css #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Varshith V Hegde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16 Libraries You Should Know as a React Developer 💯🔥]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/madza/16-libraries-you-should-know-as-a-react-developer-4f1k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/madza/16-libraries-you-should-know-as-a-react-developer-4f1k"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T15:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #coding #react #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Madza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamers Use Playlists to Control the Music Industry]]></title>
        <id>6320aa3940fe1e8870aa3a85</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/spotify-streaming-playlists-music/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recorded music market is regaining its former hourglass shape—this time with platforms like Spotify at the center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Giblin, Cory Doctorow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opendoor’s iBuyer Model Is a Canary in the Economic Coal Mine]]></title>
        <id>633b79b8b1070500c040c678</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/opendoor-ibuyers-housing-market/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company is losing huge sums of money on cookie-cutter homes—suggesting a fundamental weakness in the US housing market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing a secure API]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vaultree/designing-a-secure-api-4059</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vaultree/designing-a-secure-api-4059"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T04:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#beginners #api #design #security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Aravena, Vaultree</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Focus within & 4 other webdev tips you may want to know 🚀]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mustapha/5-webdev-tips-you-may-want-to-know-3-1fi7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mustapha/5-webdev-tips-you-may-want-to-know-3-1fi7"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T07:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #css #html]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mustapha Aouas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tremor - Free React Library for Dashboards]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sm0ke/tremor-free-react-library-for-dashboards-3gm9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sm0ke/tremor-free-react-library-for-dashboards-3gm9"/>
        <updated>2022-10-02T17:42:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #opensource #dashboards]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sm0ke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Cool HTML Elements Nobody Uses]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/7-cool-html-elements-nobody-uses-330c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/7-cool-html-elements-nobody-uses-330c"/>
        <updated>2022-10-02T04:44:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #html #javascript #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapajyoti Bose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktoberfest is here — and this is the lowdown]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devteam/hacktoberfest-is-here-and-this-is-the-lowdown-3d76</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devteam/hacktoberfest-is-here-and-this-is-the-lowdown-3d76"/>
        <updated>2022-10-01T15:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#hacktoberfest #meta #opensource #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Halpern, The DEV Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made an admin dashboard for React using Typescript! Use it for free!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fredy/i-made-an-admin-dashboard-for-react-using-typescript-use-it-for-free-49fh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fredy/i-made-an-admin-dashboard-for-react-using-typescript-use-it-for-free-49fh"/>
        <updated>2022-10-01T13:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#showdev #typescript #webdev #react]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fredy Andrei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My AWS Solution Architect Professional study guide]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/my-aws-solution-architect-professional-study-guide-2i05</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/my-aws-solution-architect-professional-study-guide-2i05"/>
        <updated>2022-10-01T02:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My AWS Solution Architect Professional study guide]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sri, AWS Community Builders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tech communities you should join! (online and in person)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/juliafmorgado/tech-communities-you-should-join-online-and-in-person-4nba</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/juliafmorgado/tech-communities-you-should-join-online-and-in-person-4nba"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T14:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#techtalks #webdev #community #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julia Furst Morgado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are You a Victim of Crypto Crime? Good Luck Getting Help]]></title>
        <id>632b64c600704d14b5ffb9a3</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cryptocurrency-cybercrime-law-enforcement/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Local law enforcement isn’t ready to deal with this new type of fraud, even with shady scams on the rise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Rizzo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How trigger browser to make a PDF from HTML using window.print()]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/climentea/simple-way-to-generate-pdf-from-html-21mh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/climentea/simple-way-to-generate-pdf-from-html-21mh"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T11:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alin Climente</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are your git aliases?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/imjoseangel/what-are-your-git-aliases-43om</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/imjoseangel/what-are-your-git-aliases-43om"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T20:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#git #beginners #tutorial #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Angel Munoz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let me understand how JavaScript works under the hood]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/inancakduvan/let-me-understand-how-javascript-works-under-the-hood-3ibf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/inancakduvan/let-me-understand-how-javascript-works-under-the-hood-3ibf"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T12:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>İnanç Akduvan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tech Companies Are Reconsidering an Old Enemy]]></title>
        <id>632db7bff2203b5586fac00d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/friction-social-media-moderation/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody likes being asked to wait, but recent political history has shown that a completely frictionless internet has its own dangers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yasmin Green</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Love Twitter Bots and I Cannot Lie]]></title>
        <id>632aefbdc9bb1af7ef249866</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/bots-twitter-art-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t judge a bot by the troll farms—some make the internet a weirder and more wonderful place.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caroline Sinders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Kanban board with Node.js, React and Websockets 📝 ✨]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/novu/building-a-beautiful-kanban-board-with-nodejs-react-and-websockets-39dk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/novu/building-a-beautiful-kanban-board-with-nodejs-react-and-websockets-39dk"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T10:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #webdev #javascript #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevo David, novu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[0ctf2022 hessian-only-jdk writeup jdk原生链]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11732</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11732"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T08:51:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[0ctf2022 hessian-only-jdk writeup jdk原生链]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[警惕破解软件！APS 窃密木马已感染万余台设备]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11740</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11740"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[警惕破解软件！APS 窃密木马已感染万余台设备]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API安全漏洞靶场crapi的基本介绍与解题思路]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11734</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11734"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T08:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[API安全漏洞靶场crapi的基本介绍与解题思路]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Faster Programmer]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marcinwosinek/how-to-become-a-faster-programmer-hp9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marcinwosinek/how-to-become-a-faster-programmer-hp9"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T05:46:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcin Wosinek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Unlikely Cure for Burnout? A Second Job]]></title>
        <id>63221a4d036b54662b5104d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/overemployment-work/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Overemployment” sounds like more of the same old grind, but its underlying philosophy is critical of work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fadeke Adegbuyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[某json 1.2.80 漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11727</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11727"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T08:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[某json 1.2.80 漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[关于HTTP Request Smuggling（HTTP请求夹带）的二三事]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11728</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11728"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T06:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[关于HTTP Request Smuggling（HTTP请求夹带）的二三事]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>