<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-10-17T10:56:14.880Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-10-17T10:56:14.880Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[StoreWise — Tools needed to deliver best-in-class in-store execution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/storewise</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/storewise"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T10:12:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://youtu.be/r-vhggl4yzA 
A Brand 'case study' video: https://youtu.be/2sGk8x_P8rc  

thanks a ton!
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vagrant for Beginners: Getting Started with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kennibravo/vagrant-for-beginners-getting-started-with-examples-jlm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kennibravo/vagrant-for-beginners-getting-started-with-examples-jlm"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T10:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vagrant is an automation tool that helps in easily creating virtual machines and automating them while saving time and increasing productivity. 
Based on https://www.vagrantup.com/intro, Vagrant is a tool for building and managing virtual machine environments in a single workflow. With an easy-to-use workflow and focus on automation, Vagrant lowers development environment setup time, increases production parity, and makes the "works on my machine" excuse a relic of the past.
Have you ever used VirtualBox or VMWare before? Vagrant helps us automate and quickly build the things you'd have used VirtualBox for; sounds easy, I know, right? 
We'd be learning about Vagrant by using it with Ansible; what is Ansible?
Ansible is an IT automation tool. It can configure systems, deploy software, and o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kehinde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kanye West is buying ‘free speech platform’ Parler]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/17/23408443/kanye-west-ye-parler-free-speech-social-media-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/17/23408443/kanye-west-ye-parler-free-speech-social-media-platform"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T09:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ye at Paris Fashion Week. | Photo by Edward Berthelot/Getty Images
    

  
Kanye West, the musician now known as Ye, is buying Parler, a social media platform that styles itself as a “free speech” alternative to Twitter. The acquisition was announced by Parler in a press release, which said that it has entered into an agreement in principle with Ye that’s expected to close later this year. 
“In a world where conservative opinions are considered to be controversial we have to make sure we have the right to freely express ourselves,” said Ye in a press statement. 
Parler’s parent company Parlement Technologies said the acquisition would help create “an uncancelable ecosystem where all voices are welcome.”
Parler was removed from Apple and Google’s app stores following the Capitol riots
Parler’s emphasis on free...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKR board for Jira — OKR management tool to organize your priorities efficiently]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/okr-board-for-jira-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/okr-board-for-jira-2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T09:42:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://marketplace.atlassian.co...

If you have any questions, we’re happy to help!

- Daria
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🕶 What it takes to build a Static Analysis tool]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/antoinecoulon/what-it-takes-to-build-a-static-analysis-tool-4p40</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/antoinecoulon/what-it-takes-to-build-a-static-analysis-tool-4p40"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey dear developer! Welcome to the first chapter of My journey of building Skott, an open-source Node.js library, a little series in which I'll talk about different steps I've been through building the Skott project.
Before diving into the subject of today, here is the blog post introducing the project which is not mandatory to read to make this article valuable though, but it can help providing some background.
Ok without further ado, let's talk about the topic of the day: building a static analysis tool.
A Static Analysis represents the process of analyzing the source code without running the application. You probably know many tools leveraging Static Analysis behind the scenes for example:
JavaScript/Node.js: ESLint

Python: Pylint

Rust: Clippy



Linters are a set of tools fully lever…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antoine Coulon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Landin — Stunning personal landing pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/landin</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/landin"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T09:35:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android 12 arrives on the two-year-old Chromecast with Google TV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/17/23408428/chromecast-with-google-tv-4k-android-12-update-camera-microphone-privacy-settings-frame-rate</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/17/23408428/chromecast-with-google-tv-4k-android-12-update-camera-microphone-privacy-settings-frame-rate"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T09:29:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chromecast with Google TV 4K, originally released in 2020. | Photo by Chris Welch / The Verge
    

  
Android 12 is rolling out for the 4K model of the Chromecast with Google TV, 9to5Google reports. The update for the 2020 streaming dongle follows the release of Google’s cheaper HD model last month, which shipped with Android 12 out of the box. To download the update on the 4K dongle, navigate to the profile icon at the top right of the interface, then hit Settings, System, About, and select System Update.
The update doesn’t add any major new features to the two-year-old streaming dongle, but it contains a couple of new settings that should improve playback in certain situations. FlatPanelsHD reports that the biggest is a new frame rate matching feature that should cut down on judder by allowing the Chromecast to match the frame rate of...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Handle quick phone authentication in Next.js using Appwrite and Twilio]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hackmamba/handle-quick-phone-authentication-in-nextjs-using-appwrite-and-twilio-569i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hackmamba/handle-quick-phone-authentication-in-nextjs-using-appwrite-and-twilio-569i"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T08:49:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phone authentication has provided a more accessible and secure way to validate users' identities during onboarding or security-sensitive operations. It involves sending a user an SMS with a secret key that a system can use to validate their identity.
In this post, we will learn how to authenticate a user with their phone number by leveraging Appwrite’s phone authentication APIs and Twilio. 
To fully grasp the concepts presented in this tutorial, the following requirements apply:
Basic understanding of JavaScript and React.
Docker installation.
An Appwrite (version 0.15.0) instance; check out this article on how to set up an instance locally. Appwrite also supports one-click install on DigitalOcean or Gitpod.
A Twilio account; sign up for a trial account is completely free.
We need to creat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Demola Malomo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktoberfest 2022: Win Swags for Quality Contributions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/astrodevil/hacktoberfest-2022-win-swags-for-quality-contributions-3o22</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/astrodevil/hacktoberfest-2022-win-swags-for-quality-contributions-3o22"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T08:49:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktoberfest 2022 is ongoing and you must have started the contribution. Everyone loves swags in the developer community. Let me tell you some good opportunities to grab cool swags by adding value to awesome projects during October'22. Contribute quality, and Get rewarded!
Hacktoberfest


Contribute to any hacktoberfest tagged repository on GitHub or GitLab during October to win official Hacktoberfest swags.
4 merged PRs will be eligible for swags
appwrite


There are different ways you can contribute to Appwrite. All accepted contributions qualify for receiving Appwrite Swag!
1 contribution: Original Appwrite sticker pack
2 contributions  : Original Appwrite sticker pack Limited edition Hacktoberfest sticker pack
3 contributions: Original Appwrite sticker pack Limited edition Hacktoberfe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Astrodevil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Restful API with Golang practical approach]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/firdavs_kasymov/restful-api-with-golang-practical-approach-420a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/firdavs_kasymov/restful-api-with-golang-practical-approach-420a"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T08:42:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we would be creating a Restful API with a practical approach of clean architecture and native Golang without any frameworks.
There are lots of tutorials out there, for Restful API but the issue they are facing is they don't have a clear structure and use various frameworks.
Those tutorials depend on the existence of some frameworks of Golang. With every external framework being used in the project, it comes with great responsibility. I don't have anything against these frameworks, but rather I prefer to minimize the use of external frameworks and stick with standard packages of Golang.
When a beginner starts learning Golang, most of them jump straight away to the famous external frameworks, such as Gin, Beego, Fiber and many more. Frameworks are good to implement somethin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Firdavs Kasymov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin Spring WebFlux, R2DBC and Redisson microservice in k8s 👋✨💫]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aleksk1ng/kotlin-spring-webflux-r2dbc-and-redisson-microservice-in-k8s-p98</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aleksk1ng/kotlin-spring-webflux-r2dbc-and-redisson-microservice-in-k8s-p98"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T08:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[👨‍💻 Full list what has been used:


Spring Spring web framework 
Spring WebFlux Reactive REST Services 
Spring Data R2DBC a specification to integrate SQL databases using reactive drivers 
Redisson Redis Java Client 
Zipkin open source, end-to-end distributed tracing 
Spring Cloud Sleuth auto-configuration for distributed tracing 
Prometheus monitoring and alerting 
Grafana for to compose observability dashboards with everything from Prometheus 
Kubernetes automating deployment, scaling, and management of containerized applications 
Docker and docker-compose 
Helm The package manager for Kubernetes 
Flywaydb for migrations


Source code you can find in the GitHub repository.
Kotlin, Spring WebFlux, PostgresSQL, and Redis with metrics and monitoring and deploying it to k8s. 
Spring Data R…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[能不能好好说话？- 划词翻译「社交平台」的拼音首字母缩写[油猴脚本]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43643</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/nbnhhsh-greasyfork/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T08:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[能不能好好说话？是一款油猴脚本，它通过划词翻译的方式，在微博、B站、百度、豆瓣等「社交平台」显示拼音首字母缩写的原文。@Appinn 其实有一段时间里，青小蛙会因为看不懂拼音缩写而烦恼。看不懂英文可以]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #792 AI 成为丹麦新成立的合成党党魁]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15150-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15150-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T08:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI 成为丹麦新成立的合成党党魁

合成党是今年 5 月丹麦成立的一个新的党派，倡导人类与 AI 的和谐共处。该党派正试图在今年 11 月的丹麦议会选举中赢得一个席位。令人吃惊的是，合成党的公众形象和挂名领袖是一个名叫 Leader Lars 的 AI 聊天机器人。它根据 1970 年以来丹麦各个边缘政党的政策编程，旨在代表 20% 不参加选举的丹麦人的价值观。它通过 Discord 与民众交流。但它不会参与投票。


消息来源：VICE



老王点评：这个党派唯一不足的地方就是，成员还是人类。🤣




AI 专家点评各大 AI

UNDARK 对纽约大学名誉教授 Gary Marcus 进行了采访，在采访中他对当前的几个主流 AI 进行了有趣的点评：GPT-3 “其实是一个自动完成系统，可以预测下一个单词和句子。就像你的手机一样，你输入一些东西，它就会继续。它并不真正理解它周围的世界。”谷歌的 LaMDA “没有知觉，它不知道自己在说什么东西”。无人驾驶汽车“仅仅记住你所见过的大量交通情况并不能表达你真正需要了解的世界”。OpenAI 的 DALL-E “利用了人类的非故意贡献，他们也许已经签署了‘服务条款’协议，但没有认识到这一切会导致什么”。


消息来源：Undark



老王点评：简直把当前热捧的 AI 批评的一无是处，人间清醒啊。




修好了电脑的 Linus Torvalds 呼吁内核开发人员别赶 Deadline

Linus Torvalds 发布了 Linux 内核 6.1 的第一个 rc 版本，对这个版本，Torvalds 说，“不算小，但比过去几个版本小”。内核的每一个新版本都有一个为期两周的合并窗口，“企鹅皇帝”说，“在我把我的机器整理好并赶上合并窗口后，我对各种迟到的拉取请求感到有些沮丧。我以前提到过这个，但是在合并窗口的最后几天收到相当多的拉动请求，这真的很烦人。”然后他抱怨内核开发人员们没有尽早提交代码，不要“在两周内匆匆忙忙地把一个分支放在一起，然后在第二周的星期五发给 Linus。……在截止日期前熬夜完成论文的做法在高中毕业后就应该被淘汰了。你知道我说是谁”。


消息来源:The Register



老王点评：有时候看内核邮件列表里面 Torvalds 每次的邮件也挺有意思的。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CloudFuze — Migrate channels from Slack to Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/cloudfuze-4</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/cloudfuze-4"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T08:10:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Started with Amazon Elastic Container Service with Fargate]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/makendrang/getting-started-with-amazon-elastic-container-service-with-fargate-32ko</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/makendrang/getting-started-with-amazon-elastic-container-service-with-fargate-32ko"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T08:03:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction



  
  
  What is Docker?


Image Source
Docker is a tool that makes it easy to build, deploy, and run applications using containers. 
Containers allow developers to package and deploy applications as a single package, along with all necessary components such as libraries and other dependencies.
This ensures that the program will run on any other Linux machine, regardless of your custom settings on the machine, which may be different from the machine you use to write and test the code.

Amazon ECS manages containers and allows developers to run applications in the cloud without configuring the environment to run their code. 
It allows developers with AWS accounts to deploy and manage scalable applications running on groups of servers called clusters through application progra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MakendranG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hunt for Wikipedia's Disinformation Moles]]></title>
        <id>634587f52c2c7a7522a9860e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/wikipedia-state-sponsored-disinformation/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Custodians of the crowdsourced encyclopedia are charged with protecting it from state-sponsored manipulators. A new study reveals how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Masha Borak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS open source news and updates, #131]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-131-nci</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-131-nci"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T07:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 17th, 2022 - Instalment #131


Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #131. This week's new projects include "metahub", a command line way to interact with AWS Security Hub, "somod" a framework for creating micro applications in serverless, "terraform-aws-guardduty-multiaccount" a Terraform module to help you automate your AWS Guard Duty configuration, "aws-glue-cdk-cicd" a sample project to automate the creation data pipelines using AWS Glue, "go-kafka-event-source" an Apache Kafka client in Go, "project-tools" a tool to help you get insights from your GitHub repo, "eks-event-watcher" a command line tool to tail your Amazon EKS logs, "listmonk-based-edm-solution" an example of how to deploy this open source mailing list tool, and many more.
From projects to blog posts,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ricardo Sueiras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starto — Free email design system for Figma with auto-layout]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/starto-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/starto-2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T07:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The fascinating Wave Function Collapse algorithm.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kavinbharathi/the-fascinating-wave-function-collapse-algorithm-4nc3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kavinbharathi/the-fascinating-wave-function-collapse-algorithm-4nc3"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T07:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is a wave function and why does it collapse?


Wave function collapse is a algorithm that can procedurally generate images, text, audio and almost anything that follows a pattern of a simple set of initial parameters and a set of rules. But the neat part is, wfc(short for wave function collapse) does all these without any artificial intelligence shenanigans. The output of wfc is a random showcase of the emergent behavior/rules built by you. This emergent behavior is what fascinates me! Now let's dive deeper into the nuances of wfc!
In this article we'll talk about image generation only, unless specified otherwise. The "wave function" is the initial state of the image where no pixel or "cell" has been "collapsed" yet. There are many quotes involved in the last sentence, so let's break …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kavin Bharathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open source DevOps tools in a platform future]]></title>
        <id>70243 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/open-source-devops-tools"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open source DevOps tools in a platform future
Will Kelly
Mon, 10/17/2022 - 03:00

            
The open source roots of DevOps tools are undeniable, even with a prediction that the global DevOps market will reach $17.8 billion by 2026. The changing world of work, security, and compliance concerns, along with venture capital firms, are pushing the market to DevOps platforms where development teams can access a complete end-to-end DevOps toolchain in the cloud.
The current state of open source DevOps tools
Let's get one thing straight: There's no way open source tools will disappear from the DevOps world. Right now, there's a balance between open source and vendor DevOps tools, with developers using what works for them. Indeed, there are plenty of cases when a development team chooses an ope…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why you should consider Rexx for scripting]]></title>
        <id>70240 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/rexx-scripting-language"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why you should consider Rexx for scripting
Howard Fosdick
Mon, 10/17/2022 - 03:00

            
How do you design a programming language to be powerful yet still easy to use? Rexx offers one example. This article describes how Rexx reconciles these two seemingly contradictory goals. 
History of Rexx programming language
Several decades ago, computers were shifting from batch to interactive processing. Developers required a scripting or "glue" language to tie systems together. The tool needed to do everything from supporting application development to issuing operating system commands to functioning as a macro language.
Mike Cowlishaw, IBM Fellow, created a solution in a language he named Rexx. It is widely considered the first general-purpose scripting language.
Rexx was so easy to use and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howard Fosdick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【键多识广】国风好设计——GLOVE × DOMIKEY繁文生肖键帽评测]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76193</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76193"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T06:42:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[本专栏所使用资料来源于网络以及群友和个人的一些看法，欢迎友好讨论。虽然都是些浅短的认识，但是分享出来也算是一种体验，非常感谢大家的观看和意见。（该专栏写于2022.6，最新的dmk热升华水平请参考wob评测）

切入正题，本篇专栏来讲讲我最近自己入手的一套的键帽——
《繁文生肖》

来自IC
说实话这套键帽一开始并没有引起我的注意，因为热升华的PBT键帽在色彩表现力上是远不如二色成型工艺的键帽。但在我往下翻阅的时候，渲染图直接抓住了我的心。

IC
毫无疑问，这是第一套有繁体中文字根设计的键帽，并且确实是超出常规的设计，可以说手套哥的设计水准确实不是盖的。

打样
但随之而来的就是几个问题在我心头萦绕。

1·工艺问题
本次代工是高端键帽大厂DOMIKEY。对于dmk的实力和做工，我是非常认可的，但问题在于，这是dmk的第一套pbt热升华键帽，此前他们从未有生产过热升华键帽，虽然在我的前一篇科普关于热升华工艺键帽我个人的一些理解 - 哔哩哔哩 (bilibili.com)已经简略介绍了一些有关于PBT热升华的知识，但是这些只是纸上谈兵罢了，高端热升华键帽之所以是高端热升华，是因为随着价格的提升，消费者的要求也随之提升——遮光性、字符清晰度、手感、键帽弯曲等等瑕疵不能出现。如果价格来到了这个价位，那么这些要求我认为也是合情合理的。
2·价格问题
厂虎的价格是499小全套，个性纹样129。这个价格，真心不算低了，即便是目前所谓的顶级热升华键帽CRP,价格也是600目前涨价之后。DOMIKEY第一次做热升华键帽，便开出如此顶级的价格，虽然是比二色要便宜一些，但热升华的成本并不算高，这么看来dmk应该是对于自己工艺非常有信心，并且有着对这套键帽设计极高的预期。事实证明，他的确押对宝了。
这套限时不限量的键帽在三天的开车预售时间内卖出了800+的惊人成绩。同时再一次证明了我的观点，买…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>车不能快</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managed Cloud Server — Cloudtechtiq - crafted to manage AWS cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/managed-cloud-server</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/managed-cloud-server"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T06:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[不算成功的探索，寻找 macOS 本地音乐播放管理软件]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76158</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76158"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T06:17:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[作为 macOS 用户，本地音乐管理一直是我感到头疼的问题。虽然大部分时间都在 macOS 系统下，但我目前的音乐资料库，是在 Windows 系统上使用 Musicbee 软件整理而成，文件夹结构是：歌手/专辑/单曲，并且自定义了各类的播放列表（m3u格式），这些内容都通过群晖 NAS 在各个设备上同步。
资料库中大部分是从 CD 导入，这样做的好处是可以很容易的抓取正确歌曲名，轨道信息及专辑封面等内容。网上下载的音乐信息会相对混乱，但在导入时我也会手动进行整理，因此资料库90%以上的音乐经过整理、拥有专辑封面。
macOS 中不管是曾经的iTunes或现在的 Apple Music 都不支持直接导入 Flac 格式文件，需要转换成 ALAC 或者 WAV 格式才能使用，非常繁琐。给我心中埋下了需要寻找全新应用的种子。
而在没有寻找本地音乐软件前，我使用 Audio Station - 群晖官方提供的音乐套件。在 iOS 上也有对应的 app 可以访问资料库在线播放。但 Audio Station 并没有桌面软件，只能通过浏览器访问，不是很方便，同时远程访问音乐难免会遇到网络问题，总没有直接存储在本地来的方便。
Audio Station网站截图
于是我希望找到一个好用的音乐软件来解决这些问题，总结来说，我对它有这几点畅想：

可以导入指定位置音乐文件，并无需复制至其他位置，或打乱原有文件顺序。
兼容大部分常见的音乐格式。
可以导入 m3u 格式的播放列表，并且正确关联音乐文件。
优美的界面展示，可以显示专辑封面。
合理的价格，并可以长期升级兼容最新系统。
如果可以配合 homepod 使用为加分项。

结合着这些需求，我开始寻找一款适合自己的软件。但出乎我意料的是，虽然这些要求看起来都非常简单，但真的能完美解决这些问题的似乎还真没有，我试用了一些受到网友推荐的软件，但截…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>johnbens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we developed our company website using NextJS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/josemukorivo/how-we-developed-our-company-website-using-nextjs-2ga5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/josemukorivo/how-we-developed-our-company-website-using-nextjs-2ga5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T06:17:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I sat down with my close friends that I had been working with for a while at the start of 2022 to discuss about starting a software company that merged aesthetics and functionality. We made the decision to combine our various skill sets to form that business, and complexus was established.
We completed a few projects for other clients before deciding to concentrate on our website. We began by conducting research on our target market, and then the team began to work on the initial iteration of the site's design.
In this article, I'll primarily discuss the tools we utilized and how we used them to create our dynamic website. These are the tools we typically employ for our clients' projects.





  
  
  Design


The design team used figma to create the site's design, and a screenshot of the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Mukorivo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Probooking — Quick, easy, professional scheduling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/probooking</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/probooking"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T04:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Science: Project Structure]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/azadkshitij/data-science-project-structure-5dh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/azadkshitij/data-science-project-structure-5dh"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T04:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why should you use project structure?



structure is of once preference but at the end of day all that matter is you should be comfortable moving around and writing code.
When we think about data science/analysis, we often think it is just about result, charts, figures, insights or visualization. While these end products are generally the main event, it's easy to focus on making the product look nice and forget about the quality of code and reusability and ability to collaborate with other and for that project structure matters.
That being said there is no correct method of structuring your project but you should at least have some structure that we can follow for all our project for standardization. You might be thinking why one should use a project structure!! Here are some reasons behi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azad Kshitij</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to write a good README]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/merlos/how-to-write-a-good-readme-bog</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/merlos/how-to-write-a-good-readme-bog"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T04:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The README file is the one-stop documentation file. Usually, it is not only the first file any person will read when reaching your project for the first time, but also it is the key document for your recurring visitors.
A few weeks back I had to install an open source project in my computer. It was the first time I was interacting with the project and experience was horrible, something that should have taken me no more than one or two hours to do, took me two days, and the main reason it took me so long was because it had a README file that could be improved to help developers new to the project to have a better first interaction. 
Integrate and use open source solutions, library or tools in our own projects is the day-to-day for many developers, and the starting point for this tasks is ar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merlos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Grad — A simple job board of new grad and internship positions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/new-grad</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/new-grad"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T04:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[中国制霸生成器 – 在地图上标记居住、游玩、去过的地方]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43638</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/china-ex-online/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T03:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[中国制霸生成器 是一个开源的在线小游戏，你可以在简化的中国地图上用不同颜色标记居住、游玩、去过的地方，然后生成一张图片。@Appinn 来自 @卜卜口 的推荐。 中国制霸生成器 – 中国三]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lex — AI-powered word processor, to help you write faster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/lex-3</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/lex-3"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T03:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux 中用于包管理的图形化应用]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15149-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15149-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T03:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[安装 Arch Linux 有一些挑战性。这就是为什么 有几个基于 Arch 的发行版 通过提供图形化的安装程序使事情变得简单。

即使你设法安装了 Arch Linux，你也会注意到它严重依赖命令行。如果你需要安装应用或更新系统，那么必须打开终端。

是的！Arch Linux 没有软件中心。我知道，这让很多人感到震惊。

如果你对使用命令行管理应用感到不舒服，你可以安装一个 GUI 工具。这有助于在舒适的图形化界面中搜索包以及安装和删除它们。

想知道你应该使用 pacman 命令 的哪个图形前端？我有一些建议可以帮助你。

请注意，某些软件管理器是特定于桌面环境的。

1、Apper



Apper 是一个精简的 Qt5 应用，它使用 PackageKit 进行包管理，它还支持 AppStream 和自动更新。但是，没有 AUR 支持。

要从官方仓库安装它，请使用以下命令：

sudo pacman -Syu apper



GitLab 上的 Apper


2、深度应用商店



深度应用商店是使用 DTK（QT5）构建的深度桌面环境的应用商店，它使用 PackageKit 进行包管理，支持 AppStream，同时提供系统更新通知。 没有 AUR 支持。

要安装它，请使用以下命令：

sudo pacman -Syu deepin-store



Github 上的深度商店


3、KDE 发现应用



发现Discover 应用不需要为 KDE Plasma 用户介绍。它是一个使用 PackageKit 的基于 Qt 的应用管理器，支持 AppStream、Flatpak 和固件更新。

要在发现应用中安装 Flatpak 和固件更新，需要分别安装 flatpak 和 fwupd 包。它没有 A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pomodoro Timer Online — Get more focused and productive while studying and working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/pomodoro-timer-online-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/pomodoro-timer-online-2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T02:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pomodoro Timer tool to help you study better and be more productive at work. We have been working for the past couple of days to create the best Pomodoro tool that we could think of.

Francesco Cirillo created the Pomodoro time management technique for a more productive way to work and study. You can find more information about it here: https://www.pomodorotechnique.com.

Our tool has these amazing features:

- 🖥 Web-based
- 🆓 Free to use
- 👤 No account needed
- 🛡️ Secure, all data is saved in your browser, and we don't send data to our servers
- ✨ Simple UI and easy to use
- 📱 Responsive design
- ✔️ Create tasks to manage your work
- 🌚 Dark mode enabled
- 🎵 Buttons and timer sounds
- 🔃 Enable automatic mode to keep producing
- ℹ️ Check the time left on the browser tab
- ⌨️ Keyboard shortcuts
- 💻 Desktop notifications
- ⚙️ Customize timers, music, theme, mode, and more

Please let us know what you think about it, and please share your feedback with us. We will keep improving the tool. Your feedback is valuable to us.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[开发你的第一个 Web 组件]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15148-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15148-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T02:11:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[不要做重复的工作；基于浏览器开发 Web App 时，需要制作一些可重用的模块。




Web 组件是一系列开源技术（例如 JavaScript 和 HTML）的集合，你可以用它们创建一些 Web App 中可重用的自定义元素。你创建的组件是独立于其他代码的，所以这些组件可以方便地在多个项目中重用。

首先，它是一个平台标准，所有主流的浏览器都支持它。

Web 组件中包含什么？


定制元素：JavaScript API 支持定义 HTML 元素的新类别。

影子 DOM：JavaScript API 提供了一种将一个隐藏的、独立的 文档对象模型（DOM）附加到一个元素的方法。它通过保留从页面的其他代码分离出来的样式、标记结构和行为特征对 Web 组件进行了封装。它会确保 Web 组件内样式不会被外部样式覆盖，反之亦然，Web 组件内样式也不会“泄露”到页面的其他部分。

HTML 模板：该元素支持定义可重用的 DOM 元素。可重用 DOM 元素和它的内容不会呈现在 DOM 内，但仍然可以通过 JavaScript 被引用。


开发你的第一个 Web 组件

你可以借助你最喜欢的文本编辑器和 JavaScript 写一个简单的 Web 组件。本指南使用 Bootstrap 生成简单的样式，并创建一个简易的卡片式的 Web 组件，给定了位置信息，该组件就能显示该位置的温度。该组件使用了 Open Weather API，你需要先注册，然后创建 APPID/APIKey，才能正常使用。

调用该组件，需要给出位置的经度和纬度：

<weather-card longitude='85.8245' latitude='20.296' />


创建一个名为 weather-card.js 的文件，这个文件包含 Web 组件的所有代码。首先，需…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IIS下.Net 的预编译模式]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11765</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11765"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T02:09:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IIS下.Net 的预编译模式]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SystemTap在应急排查中的应用]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11764</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11764"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T01:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SystemTap在应急排查中的应用]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aragorn AI — Single platform for vendor integration and user provisioning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/aragorn-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/aragorn-ai"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T01:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comcast is shutting down its gamer-centric G4 channel, again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/16/23407909/g4-tv-shutdown-again-comcast</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/16/23407909/g4-tv-shutdown-again-comcast"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T23:06:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image: G4 TV
    

  
Comcast is shutting down G4 after attempting to relaunch the gaming channel last year, according to a report from Deadline. The channel first appeared on linear cable back in 2002 until it met its demise as the final studio shows were axed in 2012, and it was eventually replaced by the Esquire Network.
Dave Scott, the CEO of Comcast’s Spectacor division, announced the shutdown in an internal memo obtained by Deadline before it was even sent, saying that the channel has had low viewership and has not “achieved sustainable financial results.”


I don't have a job anymore! Looking for new opportunities if anyone is interested in a social/digital content producer   https://t.co/cgeaOCj7x2
— Kendelle Lyn (@KendelleLyn) October 16, 2022



A...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sniffnet — Analyze your network traffic with ease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/sniffnet</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/sniffnet"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T21:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://github.com/GyulyVGC/snif...) for more information on how to install, build and run it, as well as a bunch of other useful details!
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android’s audio output switcher may soon let you pick cast devices, too]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/16/23407553/android-audio-output-switcher-pick-cast-devices-google</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/16/23407553/android-audio-output-switcher-pick-cast-devices-google"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T20:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Amelia Holowaty Krales / The Verge
    

  
Google may soon start letting you pick from cast devices when using the audio output switcher on Android 13, according to Esper’s Mishaal Rahman. The output switcher, which was first introduced in Android 11, currently only lets you swap between media playback sessions on paired Bluetooth devices, such as wireless headphones or a speaker.
But an update to the Google Cast SDK (software development kit), suggests that Android 13’s output switcher could allow for local-to-remote, remote-to-local, and remote-to-remote transfers. As pointed out by Rahman, “local” refers to transfers involving paired Bluetooth devices, while “remote” refers to cast devices.


FINALLY! Google is reviving a feature originally planned for Android 11: the ability...

  
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LETA — You can type faster with alternative keyboard layouts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/leta</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/leta"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T18:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Music’s spatial audio is coming to  select Mercedes-Benz models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/16/23407129/apple-music-spatial-audio-dolby-select-mercedes-benz-models</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/16/23407129/apple-music-spatial-audio-dolby-select-mercedes-benz-models"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image: Mercedes-Benz
    

  
Mercedes-Benz announced today that it’s bringing support for Apple’s Music’s spatial audio to certain vehicles. Apple Music launched spatial audio with Dolby Atmos last year on a range of devices, including the iPhone, Mac, HomePod, and Apple TV, but this is the first time it’ll be available natively in a car.
As you might have guessed, the integration doesn’t come cheap. Mercedes-Benz started adding Dolby Atmos to its top-of-the-line Maybach, S-Class, as well as electric EQS and EQE models that come with the automaker’s latest MBUX interface and the 31-speaker Burmester 3D or 4D sound system. While the vehicles themselves cost upwards of $100,000, this doesn’t even include the additional $4,550 (3D) or $6,730 (4D) Burmester sound system...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mercedes-Benz EQE SUV is a more down-to-earth luxury electric vehicle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/16/23404802/mercedes-benz-eqe-suv-range-price-specs</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/16/23404802/mercedes-benz-eqe-suv-range-price-specs"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The EQE SUV will be out by 2023. | Image: Mercedes-Benz
    

  
The Mercedes-Benz EQE has been SUV-ified. The German automaker revealed a higher riding, more utility-focused version of its EQE sedan, and while the price is still being kept under wraps, the EQE SUV is expected to hit US dealerships starting in 2023. 
We’ve known that we’d be getting an SUV version of the EQE sedan since it was first revealed last year. Mercedes did the same for its flagship EV, the EQS, coming out with the SUV version earlier this month. It’s the fourth EV to be built on the automaker’s new EV platform. 
Mercedes says the EQE SUV will be “the most spacious representatives of its class”
With the EQE SUV, we’re getting three trim levels — one rear-motor and two dual-motor versions — as well as an AMG performance...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surge — The easiest to use anonymous p2p filesharing app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/surge-6b023ad8-9149-482e-8a4b-7e5bc4badaa9</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/surge-6b023ad8-9149-482e-8a4b-7e5bc4badaa9"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T17:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dolpin — Decentralized & Encrypted cloud storage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/dolpin</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/dolpin"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T17:06:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://app.arcade.software/shar...]
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Costan — One stop solution for content creators or influencers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/costan</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/costan"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T16:11:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[www.costan.in

AMA! I'm around :)
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[类似 Notion 的 Markdown 笔记应用黑曜石推出测试版]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15147-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15147-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T15:58:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[黑曜石 1.0 做了重新设计，带来了有价值的新功能。




黑曜石Obsidian 是一款强大的笔记应用，可以用来制作知识图谱，同时还提供 Notion 类似的功能。

在 1.0 更新之前，我们已经有一篇关于它的 详细文章。

黑曜石 1.0 的发布标志着该应用在桌面和移动体验方面的发展迈出了关键一步。


💡 黑曜石不是一个开源的应用程序，但可以在 Linux 上使用。


让我们来看看它的桌面版提供的新功能。

🆕 黑曜石 1.0 的新功能



1.0 版本增加了大量的新功能、主要的视觉变化和错误修复，其中一些亮点包括：


改良的用户界面

新的外观设置

带有标签堆叠的标签功能

大修的主题画廊

各种错误的修复


🎨 用户界面的改造



用户界面已经得到了全面改造，这使得用户体验更加直观和强大。



除此之外，黑曜石现在还有一个专门的外观设置部分。它包含了切换显示内联标题、标签标题栏、改变重点颜色等选项的设置。



带有标签堆叠的标签功能



现在你可以在黑曜石中打开多个标签，并使用热键来帮助你在忙碌的一天中完成多个任务。

一个额外的好处是，即使你退出黑曜石，它也会记住你曾经打开的标签和你在这些标签中的活动状态。



标签也可以分组形成堆叠，并在它们之间进行切换，从而使工作空间变得更加整齐。

🛠️ 其他变化

其他值得一提的变化包括：


改变缩放级别的能力

改进了黑曜石的同步

内存泄漏修复

用于折叠行的折叠命令


你可以通过 发布说明，以及 发布公告 来了解更多的细节。

📥 下载黑曜石 1.0

你可以到 官方网站 下载黑曜石 1.0。在手机上，也可以在谷歌应用商店和苹果的应用商店上找到它。

为 Linux 用户提供了三个软件包：AppImage、Flatpak 和 Snap。

开发者还澄清说，他们不会向个人用户收取黑曜石的使用费。

💬 你对黑曜石 1.0 有什么看法？一个值得替代其他记事本的应用程序吗？


via: https://news.itsfoss.com/obsidian-1-release/

作者：Sourav Rudra 选题：lkxed 译者：wxy 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Maker Toolkit — Helping you launch your ideas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/digital-maker-toolkit</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/digital-maker-toolkit"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T15:43:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FindMyRemoteJobs — Discover the best remote jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/findmyremotejobs</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/findmyremotejobs"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T15:07:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PH Leads — Convert your Product Hunt upvoters to paying customers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ph-leads</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ph-leads"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T15:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoPro Hero 11 Black Review: Vertical Video]]></title>
        <id>6334714a00704d14b5ffba18</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/gopro-hero-11-black/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The biggest name in action cams is back with a taller sensor optimized for a world of vertical video.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gilbertson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16 Best Gaming Mice and Mousepads (2022): Wireless, Wired, and Under $50]]></title>
        <id>5d4b6daf6e37da0008c9e948</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-gaming-mouse/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’re into esports or casual fragging, these are the greatest gaming mice we’ve tested.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Ravenscraft, Jaina Grey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Drives Galaxies? The Milky Way’s Black Hole May Be the Key]]></title>
        <id>633b18c891ba135542e3d5b6</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-milky-ways-black-hole-may-be-the-key-to-what-drives-galaxies/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supermassive black holes are engines of galactic evolution, but new observations of our galaxy and its central hole don’t quite match expectations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Lewton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[海外兴起微创业交易平台]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76211</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76211"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T11:17:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[每个创业者的目标都是成功退出，而传统的退出路径包括IPO上市，或者被并购。
TechCrunch的一项调查显示，创业公司从成立到成功退出的平均时长接近6年。
各地区从创业到退出年限的平均数、中位数
这无疑增加了创业门槛，意味着一旦选择创业，需要6年时间才能收获结果。这尤其对奉行精益创业理念的小微创业企业（Micro Startup）或者超级个体不友好，导致这些创业者要么继续做大直到退出，要么慢慢变成一个“副业”。
你可能会问，做大有什么不好？有的创业者适合指挥千军万马，而有的创业者更擅长抓住每一个灵感闪现。例如，以色列号称Startup Nation，大批创业者完成产品0-1搭建后就把公司卖给大企业，然后继续投入新的创业中，反而坚持做大到IPO的比较少，这与以色列的市场规模和地理位置有关。
所以，不断降低创业者成功退出的门槛，让专注创新的创业者持续创新，让擅长增长的创业者不断增长，对激活创业生态至关重要。
为小微创业者提供便捷、低门槛的推出服务，已成为海外SaaS创业中一个重要的细分方向。海外正在兴起一批相关的平台，但国内却还没有对应的趋势，值得国内创业者们分析和借鉴。
Flippa：最大的数字资产交易平台
Flippa成立于2009年，现在已经是全球第一大的数字资产交易平台，有超过300万注册用户，可以交易的资产包括网站、app、域名、网店、自媒体账号、甚至是SaaS应用等等——这也正是广大微创业或超级个体们最活跃的领域。
Flippa在售的个人网站
与传统的二手商品相比，数字资产交易最大的挑战一是如何估值，二是如何保障信息的真实性。
Flippa平台为卖家提供了一个估值机器人工具，它的算法参考多个因素，包括卖家所售业务模式、运营时间、绩效表现、增长率、类别等。卖家在上传商品时，也需要提供近12个月的运营数据。
Flippa也提供尽职调查的服务，卖家可以选择授权买家查看他…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>创业斯基</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whatsapp Files Bot — Say goodbye to losing files on WhatsApp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/whatsapp-files-bot</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/whatsapp-files-bot"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T11:10:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RMNDM — Voice notes and reminder app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/rmndm</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/rmndm"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T11:09:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #791 谷歌宣布推出 Rust 开发的 KataOS 操作系统]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15146-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15146-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T11:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[谷歌宣布推出 Rust 开发的 KataOS 操作系统

谷歌本周宣布发布 KataOS，它是用于进行机器学习的嵌入式设备的操作系统。KataOS 从设计上就具备安全考虑，不但几乎完全是由 Rust 实现的，而且是建立在 seL4 微内核的基础之上，seL4 在数学上被证明是安全的，具有保证保密性、完整性和可用性。


消息来源：谷歌



老王点评：谷歌的操作系统之心不死啊，时不时的就发布一个操作系统，然而，Linux 仍然是谷歌用的做到的操作系统。




谷歌搜索 emoji 相关词汇时会报错

有网友发现，在谷歌上搜索“how many emojis on iOS”、“how many emojis on windows” 等内容时，谷歌搜索引擎会极其罕见的报服务器错误：“处理您的请求时，似乎出现了内部服务器错误”。据分析，这是出现在结果中的一个特定网页可能导致了这个错误，很可能是 Emojipedia.com 网站。谷歌已经修复了该问题。


消息来源：Bleeping Computer



老王点评：这真是太罕见了，我是第一次听说谷歌会因为某个搜索结果而导致服务器内部错误。




Pine64 宣布了一款不到 10 美元的 Linux 单板计算机

这款名为 Ox64 的单板计算机有一个双核 RISC-V 处理器，64MB 的嵌入式内存，支持高达 128Mb 的闪存和一个用于额外存储的 MicroSD 卡。预计它将支持 RTOS 和 Linux，模糊了微控制器和极低功率的单板电脑之间的界限。它预计将在 11 月上市销售，RTOS 版本起价为 6 美元，Linux 兼容型号起价为 8 美元。


消息来源：Pine64



老王点评：这个单板机看起来不错，还挺便宜。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LiveWire S2 Del Mar Review: Fun, Fast, Limited Range]]></title>
        <id>63493e5eb39f0f5de4157aa8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/review-livewire-s2-del-mar/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harley-Davidson’s second all-electric motorcycle seduced WIRED’s editor in chief—but sadly can’t go the distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gideon Lichfield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Passkeys in Google Chrome and Android]]></title>
        <id>63499d7b04d20e5d7c550aad</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-use-passkeys-google-chrome-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google wants to make your digital life—in its ecosystem, anyway—passwordless and more secure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Nield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sourcery 2.0 — Continuous code review to make your code more maintainable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/sourcery-2-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/sourcery-2-0"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T10:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@brendan_maginnis, @nick_thapen, and I are back and we’re very excited to be sharing the new version of Sourcery with you all. 

Sourcery sits in the background while you work analyzing your code, finding problems, and suggesting improvements to make sure it’s following best practices. You can think of it as the first layer of code review, catching mistakes before a human reviewer needs to take a look. As always - Sourcery runs fully locally, so your code is private.

Here’s what’s new:

1. Extend Sourcery to handle your best practices. You shouldn’t have to make the same comment more than one time in a code review. When you see issues coming up frequently you can create a Sourcery rule, and these issues will get caught for your whole team before the code is merged. 

2. Leverage Pre-Built Rulesets. We’ve taken the Google Python Style Guide and made it available as a (set of Sourcery rules). Pick and choose the rules that make sense for you (and customize them how you want) or add in the full ruleset.

3. CLI for bulk review. We’ve extended the Sourcery CLI to make it more powerful (and much quicker) for reviewing multiple files, or your entire repo. With a single command you can scan hundreds of files, identify common issues, and make bulk changes to improve your code.  

4. Review every commit with Sourcery in CI. Let Sourcery handle the first layer of your code reviews by adding it to your CI. Sourcery is easily configurable to run only on changed code to help cut down on noise from legacy code. 

Anyone can start using Sourcery for free, and teams coming through ProductHunt with promo code PRODUCTHUNT2022 can use the full team version (includes full use in CI or as a pre—commit hook - see more details at https://sourcery.ai/team/) for free for 2 months.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incognito Browser — Surf the internet with sharing minimum information possible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/incognito-browser</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/incognito-browser"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T08:33:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ezy Peazy — A good job done at a fair price]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ezy-peazy</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ezy-peazy"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T08:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallel — Listen to music together and chat with friends]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/parallel-a50c402f-f4ba-4d61-bb16-aa37d83497b9</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/parallel-a50c402f-f4ba-4d61-bb16-aa37d83497b9"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T08:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[support@parallelsocial.net, our twitter page, or right here!
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[利用 Windows 10/11 原生语音输入功能，实现无限量、免费「语音转文字」]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43633</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/speech-to-text-windows10-and-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T07:52:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10、11 系统自带了一个语音输入功能，可以实现将麦克风的语音输入，实时转换为文字。那么利用系统声音设备的输入输出切换，就可以实现一个系统原生的、免费、无限量的语音转文字功能。@App]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FolderCode — The future of carrying files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/foldercode</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/foldercode"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T07:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PlaSees — A fun way to find places of interest near you using AR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/plasees</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/plasees"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T07:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Audience Thief — 499+ engage worthy Twitter influencers listed on ClickUp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-audience-thief</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-audience-thief"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T07:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in GNOME 43?]]></title>
        <id>70230 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/whats-new-gnome-43-linux"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in GNOME 43? 
Jim Hall
Sun, 10/16/2022 - 03:00

            
I love the GNOME desktop, and I use it as my daily Linux desktop environment. I find with GNOME, I can focus on the stuff I need to get done, but I still have flexibility to make the desktop look and act the way I want.
The GNOME Project recently released GNOME 43, the latest version of the GNOME desktop. I met with GNOME developer Emmanuele Bassi to ask a few questions about this latest release:
Jim Hall (Jim): GNOME has lots of great desktop features. What are some of the new features in GNOME 43?
Emmanuele Bassi (Emmanuele): GNOME 43 has a complete redesign of the system status menu in the Shell. The new design is meant to give quick and easy access to various settings: network connections and VPNs; audio input and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Hall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[如何在 Fedora、CentOS、RHEL 中启用 RPM Fusion 仓库]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15145-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15145-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T03:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[本指南解释了在 Fedora Linux 发行版中启用第三方软件仓库 RPM Fusion 的步骤。


RPM Fusion 软件仓库是一个社区维护的软件仓库，它为 Fedora Linux 提供额外的软件包，这些软件包不是由 Fedora 官方团队分发，例如 DVD 播放、媒体播放、来自 GNOME 和 KDE 的软件等。这是因为许可证、其他法律原因和特定国家/地区的软件规范而导致的。

RPM Fusion 为 Red Hat Enterprise Linux（RHEL）以及 Fedora 提供了 .rpm 包。

本指南介绍了在 Fedora Linux 中启用 RPM Fusion 仓库所需的步骤。本指南适用于所有 Fedora 发行版本。

这在所有当前支持的 Fedora 版本（35、36 和 37）中进行了测试。



如何在 Fedora Linux、RHEL、CentOS 中启用 RPM Fusion 仓库

RPM Fusion 有两种版本的仓库：自由和非自由。

顾名思义，自由版包含软件包的自由版本，非自由版包含封闭源代码的编译软件包和“非商业”开源软件。

在继续之前，首先检查你是否安装了 RPM fusion。打开终端并运行以下命令。

dnf repolist | grep rpmfusion


如果安装了 RPM，你应该会看到如下所示的消息。就不用下面的步骤。如果未安装，你可以继续执行以下步骤。



打开终端并根据你的操作系统版本运行以下命令。请注意，这些命令包含自由和非自由版本。如果你愿意，你可以在运行时省略下面的任何一个。

Fedora

自由版：

sudo dnf install https://download1.rpmfusion.org/free/fedora/rpmfusion-fre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Changelly — Exchange, buy and trade crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/changelly-4</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/changelly-4"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T01:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyLint 的优点、缺点和危险]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15144-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15144-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T01:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[充分利用 PyLint。


敲黑板：PyLint 实际上很好！

&ldquoyLint 可以拯救你的生命”，这是一句夸张的描述，但没有你想象的那么夸张。PyLint 可以让你远离非常难找到的和复杂的缺陷。最差的情况下，它只可以节省测试运行的时间。最好的情况下，它可以帮你避免生产环境中复杂的错误。

优点

我不好意思说这种情况是多么普遍。测试的命名总是那么奇怪：没有人关心这个名称，而且通常也找不到一个自然的名称。例如以下代码：

def test_add_small():
    # Math, am I right?
    assert 1 + 1 == 3
    
def test_add_large():
    assert 5 + 6 == 11
    
def test_add_small():
    assert 1 + 10 == 11


测试生效：

collected 2 items                                                                         
test.py .. 
2 passed


但问题是：如果你覆盖了一个测试的名称，测试框架将愉快地跳过这个测试！

实际上，这些文件可能有数百行，而添加新测试的人可能并不知道所有的名称。除非有人仔细查看测试输出，否则一切看起来都很好。

最糟糕的是，被覆盖测试的添加、被覆盖测试造成的破坏，以及连锁反应的问题可能要几天、几月甚至几年才能发现。

PyLint 会找到它

就像一个好朋友一样，PyLint 可以帮助你。

test.py:8:0: E0102: function already defined line 1
     (function-redefi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pasty — Smart clipboard manager for macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/pasty</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/pasty"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T23:07:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://pasteapp.io, and it was a very powerful tool that I bought and keep supporting until the company decided to go subscription. As a freelancer, you ended up subscribing to many services like Adobe CC, Envato Elements, Render forest, etc... Once you get to the cap of your monthly payments budget, you can't keep adding tools that require monthly payments as well! So I was looking for an alternative powerful enough to handle my needs and that doesn't offer a subscription only deal. I found Pasty! This app was more powerful than Paste, and it also offers a one time payment deal. It changed my life and put me back on track, giving me the productivity speed and useful features I was used to with Paste app. If you're like me and need an alternative without a monthly payment, Pasty is without a doubt better, faster and super useful. I recommend this app 100%. (It's so good that it moves me to create my first post here in Product Hunt and I don't even know the developer!)
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“The hell with it”—Elon Musk to keep funding Ukrainian Starlink service [Updated]]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890216</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890216"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T21:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["we'll just keep funding Ukraine govt for free."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Petiwo — Pet owners & pet lovers community]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/petiwo</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/petiwo"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T21:22:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Northstar Search — Find your way across the web]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/northstar-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/northstar-search"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T19:11:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[announcement blog for more details, and please feel free to post any questions (or service integration requests) here!

Get Northstar Search now!
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Life OS — Manage work & life more effectively in Notion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/life-os-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/life-os-2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T13:57:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[23 Best STEM Toys for Kids (2022): Make Learning Fun]]></title>
        <id>5bea0c51798a4365ec16fdca</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-stem-toys-for-kids/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We found lots of math-filled and science-rich toys for tiny nerds to disassemble, set on fire, and then rebuild.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simon Hill, Gear Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Next-Gen Video Chat Tech Is Ready for the Real World]]></title>
        <id>634982058e4a6cd698dd9fdd</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/google-project-starline-iphone-roller-coasters/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: iPhones are calling the cops from roller coasters, Polestar has a new electric SUV, and Meta makes another big bet on VR.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boone Ashworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s SpaceX Bails on Starlink Funding for Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>63499d6c7e817d200a6cc672</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-starlink-funding-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: Hackers hit the Mormon Church, Signal plans to ditch SMS for Android, and a Fat Bear election erupts in scandal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Couts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neural Formula — Power-up spreadsheets with artificial intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/neural-formula</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/neural-formula"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T12:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Google Pixel Phone (2022): Which Model to Buy, Cases and Accessories, Feature Drops]]></title>
        <id>5f7b6765126693e1dc256c36</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-google-pixel-phone/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a guide to all the models—plus case recommendations and hidden software tricks to try.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian Chokkattu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Wi-Fi 6E, and How Is It Different from Wi-Fi 6? (2022)]]></title>
        <id>61f1438202a1a063b050612f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/what-is-wi-fi-6e/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many ways to make your internet faster, but the specifics depend on what you’re willing to spend right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simon Hill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why India's Capital Is Teeming With Mosquitoes]]></title>
        <id>63445ca42c2c7a7522a985fb</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/why-delhi-is-teeming-with-mosquitoes/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[City residents have long resorted to low-cost, do-it-yourself remedies that may be harmful to human health.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Monika Mondal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New, transparent AI tool may help detect blood poisoning]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889636</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889636"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T11:31:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The algorithm scans electronic records and may reduce sepsis deaths.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Undark Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #790 Canonical 在 apt 命令中为其 Ubuntu Pro 打广告]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15143-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15143-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T10:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canonical 在 apt 命令中为其 Ubuntu Pro 打广告

之前我们 报道 过，Canonical 公司提供的 Ubuntu Pro 支持现在可供多达五台机器免费使用，为这些机器提供十年的支持服务。这本来是一件好事，但如果你从命令行用 apt 命令更新时，你就会看到 Canonical 发布的宣传这项免费服务的广告。这让一些用户非常恼火。Canonical 在自作主张向 Ubuntu 用户显示广告方面“劣迹斑斑”。上一次在服务器的登录屏幕中显示了促销信息，而在十年前，它还在桌面搜索结果中显示了亚马逊的广告。


消息来源：The Register



老王点评：我觉得，可能 Canonical 的初衷或许是好的，但是这种侵入式广告的方式太糟糕。或许，Ubuntu 应该在其桌面版和服务器版中专门提供一个通告服务，以使关注 Ubuntu 相关信息的人可以主动订阅。




黑客利用无人机，通过 Wi-Fi 远程渗透了金融公司内网

安保人员在美国东海岸一家专注于私人投资的金融公司的大楼顶层发现了两架 DJI 无人机，一架虽然炸机但仍在运行，而另一架实现了安全着陆。两架无人机上被加装了渗透套件，包含一台树莓派、GPD 迷你笔记本电脑、4G 调制解调器、Wi-Fi 设备、几块电池，以及一套网络渗透测试设备。攻击者利用该装置拦截了该公司员工的凭据，利用员工 MAC 地址和访问凭据、从屋顶侵入了该公司的内网。


消息来源：The Register



老王点评：这真是无孔不入，之前曾经有黑客靠近办公室渗透 Wi-Fi 的，现在居然连无人机都用上了。




PostgreSQL 15 发布

新版本进一步改进了性能，主要新特性包括：支持 SQL MERGE 命令；改进内存中和磁盘上的排序性能，最高提升 400%；启用了 Zstd 和 LZ4 压缩支持，并支持写前日志文件；支持 pg_basebackup 期间执行服务器端压缩；等等。


消息来源：Phoronix



老王点评：我当时学习的第一个开源数据库就是 PG，可惜后来它的风头被 MySQL 抢走了，但是实际上 PG 更优秀。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[服务器支持 IPv6 的原因]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15142-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15142-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T07:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[我一直在努力学习关于 IPv6 的相关知识。一方面，IPv6 的基础概念是很简单的（没有足够的 IPv4 地址可以满足互联网上的所有设备，所以人们发明了 IPv6！每个人都能有足够的 IPv6 地址！）

但是当我试图进一步理解它时，我遇到了很多问题。其中一个问题是：为什么 twitter.com 不支持 IPv6。假设，网站不支持 IPv6 并不会造成很多困难，那么为什么网站需要支持 IPv6 呢？

我在 Twitter 上询问了很多人 为什么他们的服务器支持 IPv6，我得到了很多很好的答案，我将在这里总结一下。事先说明一下，因为我对 IPv6 基本上毫无经验，所以下面所总结的理由中可能会有写得不准确的地方，请大家多多包涵。

首先，我想解释一下为什么 twitter.com 可以不支持 IPv6，因为这是最先让我困惑的地方。

怎么知道 twitter.com 不支持 IPv6 呢？

你可以使用 dig 命令以 AAAA 的选项查询某一个域名的 IPv6 地址记录，如果没有记录，则表明该域名不支持 IPv6。除了 twitter.com，还有一些大型网站，如 github.com 和 stripe.com 也不支持 IPv6。

$ dig AAAA twitter.com
(empty response)
$ dig AAAA github.com
(empty response)
$ dig AAAA stripe.com
(empty response)


为什么 twitter.com 仍然适用于 IPv6 用户？

我发现这真的很令人困惑。我一直听说因为 IPv4 地址已经用完了，从而很多互联网用户被迫要使用 IPv6 地址。但如果这是真的，twitter.com 怎么能继续为那些没有 IPv6 支持的人提供服务呢？以下内容…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IG Scraper & Email Finder — Scraper tool that will help you get more B2B clients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ig-scraper-email-finder</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ig-scraper-email-finder"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T07:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM PASS PWN（一）]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11762</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11762"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T05:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM PASS PWN（一）]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoodSync 12 首次限免，跨平台文件同步工具]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43628</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/goodsync-12/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T04:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GoodSync 是一款老牌的数据同步工具，支持在 Windows、macOS、Linux 之间同步数据，以及在 iOS、Android 设备上读取数据。近日新版本 GoodSync 12 首次限免，]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Playbook for Tiktok — A detailed guide on everything you need to grow on Tiktok]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/master-playbook-for-tiktok</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/master-playbook-for-tiktok"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T04:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VirtualBox 7.0 发布，支持安全启动和全加密虚拟机]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15141-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15141-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T02:10:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VirtualBox 7.0 是自其上次大版本更新以来的一次重大升级。有一些不错的进步！




对 VirtualBox 来说，这是一次大的升级。这个版本值得关注，因为我们在最近几年没有看到过它的大版本更新。

对于那些不熟悉 VirtualBox 的人来说，它是一个由 甲骨文公司 开发的虚拟化软件。

随着 VirtualBox 7.0 的推出，增加了许多新功能。

让我们来看看其中最关键的一些。

VirtualBox 7.0 的新内容



VirtualBox 7.0 是一次有益的升级。有图标更新、主题改进，以及一些关键的亮点，包括：


一个显示运行中的客体Guest的性能统计的新工具。

支持安全启动。

支持全加密虚拟机Full VM Encryption（通过 CLI）。

重新设计的新建虚拟机向导。


通过命令行管理的全加密虚拟机

虚拟机（VM）现在可以完全加密了，但只能通过命令行界面。

这也包括加密的配置日志和暂存状态。

截至目前，用户只能通过命令行界面对机器进行加密，未来将增加不同的方式。

新的资源监控工具



新的实用程序可以让你监控性能统计，如 CPU、内存使用、磁盘 I/O 等。它将列出所有正在运行的客体的性能统计。

这不是最吸引人的补充，但很有用。

改进的主题支持

对主题的支持在所有平台上都得到了改进。在 Linux 和 macOS 上使用原生引擎，而在 Windows 上，有一个单独的实现。

对安全启动的支持

VirtualBox 现在支持安全启动，增强了对恶意软件、病毒和间谍软件的安全性。

它还将防止虚拟机使用损坏的驱动程序启动，这对企业应用非常重要。

使用那些需要安全启动才能运行的操作系统的用户现在应该能够轻松创建虚拟机了。

其他变化

VirtualBox 7.0 是一次重大的升级。因此，有几个功能的增加和全面的完善。

例如，新件虚拟机向导现在已经重新设计，以整合无人值守的客体操作系统安装。



其他改进包括：


云端虚拟机现在可以被添加到 VirtualBox，并作为本地虚拟机进行控制。

VirtualBox 的图标在此版本中得到了更新。

引入了一个新的 3D 栈，支持 DirectX 11。它使用 DXVK 来为非 Windows 主机提供同样的支持。

支持虚拟 TPM 1.2/2.0。

改进了多显示器设置中的鼠标处理。

Vorbis 是音频录制的默认音频编解码器。


你可以查看 发行说明 以了解更多信息。

如果你正在寻找增强的功能，如更好的主题支持、加密功能、安全启动支持和类似的功能添加，VirtualBox 7.0 是一个不错的升级。

💬 你对这次升级有什么看法？你会使用较新的版本还是暂时坚持使用旧版本的虚拟机？


via: https://news.itsfoss.com/virtualbox-7-0-release/

作者：Sourav Rudra 选题：lkxed 译者：wxy 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[find() vs filter() in JavaScript – Differences Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/find-vs-filter-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/find-vs-filter-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T22:22:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A common interview question that JavaScript developers often get asked is to explain the difference between the find() and filter() methods.  In this tutorial today, I'll walk you through what these methods are and when you should use them. What is the filter() method? This method returns all the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aman Kalra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Removing notes from Mendelssohn overture shows plight of humpback whales]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890094</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890094"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T22:19:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hebrides Redacted is meant to show "how human activities have silenced nature.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Since Crew Dragon’s debut, SpaceX has flown more astronauts than anyone]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890316</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890316"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T21:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Thank you for an incredible ride up to orbit and an incredible ride home."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Copy Text to the Clipboard with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/copy-text-to-clipboard-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/copy-text-to-clipboard-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T21:18:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building advanced web pages and applications, you'll sometimes want to add the copy feature. This lets your users simply click a button or icon to copy text rather than highlighting the text and clicking a couple of buttons on the keyboard. This feature is mostly used when someone]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s AR/VR headset will scan your iris when you put it on]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890235</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890235"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T20:50:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's headset will also scan users' legs for inclusion in virtual space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AT&T to pay $23M fine for bribing powerful lawmaker’s ally in exchange for vote]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890282</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890282"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T20:24:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AT&T said it's "committed to ensuring that this never happens again."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GeniusWire — Browse quality e-commerce brands, handpicked by real people]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/geniuswire</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/geniuswire"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T19:33:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Equifax surveilled 1,000 remote workers, fired 24 found juggling two jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890244</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890244"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T19:06:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Equifax used its own worker surveillance product to spy on workers fired.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Belanger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BA.5 is finally fading—sublineages BQ.1 and BQ.1.1 rise from variant stew]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890232</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890232"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T18:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BQ.1 and BQ.1.1 now account for 1-in-10 US COVID infections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Add to an Array – JS Append]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-add-to-an-array-js-append/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-add-to-an-array-js-append/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T18:29:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use arrays in JavaScript to store a group of variables, often referred to as elements or items of the array. Each of these elements will have an index number assigned to them starting from zero.  By default, you can use the index of an element in an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ResumAI by Wonsulting — Your resume, your story - perfected]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/resumai-by-wonsulting</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/resumai-by-wonsulting"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T17:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pixel 7 tests out 64-bit-only Android, can’t run 32-bit apps]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890107</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890107"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T17:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[64-bit only Android promises better performance and security, if we can get there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dwarf Fortress, the most inscrutable game of two decades, is getting a tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890123</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890123"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T17:38:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Start off in a mineral-rich play area with hints, rather than primordial chaos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Purdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazil court orders Apple to reimburse customers for charger-less iPhones]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890112</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890112"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T17:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iPhones sold without chargers is an "abusive practice," São Paulo judge says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scharon Harding</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia will “unlaunch” the 12GB RTX 4080, says it’s “not named right”]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890156</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890156"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T17:23:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia had taken heat for announcing two 4080 cards with wildly divergent specs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers make cyborg cockroaches that carry their own power packs]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890143</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890143"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T17:19:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solar cell and a battery can keep the cyborg's electronics running for weeks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Contributors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ultra — Fast JavaScript package manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ultra-241a7c40-a06f-450e-abac-321f614e6bee</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ultra-241a7c40-a06f-450e-abac-321f614e6bee"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T17:16:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Only PC players need a registered phone number for Modern Warfare 2]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890131</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890131"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T16:33:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security measure comes on top of Ricochet's required kernel-level drivers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[拒绝 All-in-one，应用也许应该各司其职]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76192</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76192"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T16:31:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[我是如何选择应用的
我的工作流与其他少数派作者相比起来，简直是小巫见大巫了。我并没有独特的电脑技巧，也没有什么私藏的应用。我所得知的应用都基本上是通过少数派的派评系列文章。不过，当我尝试了一些app之后，有好有坏，也花了不少冤枉钱。所以，有时候我都想开一个叫“持续追踪”的栏目以专门反馈后续各个应用的使用情况和想法。
在我苦哈哈地写完小米那篇文章之后，我非常反感那些不稳定且复杂的系统，而且也花了不少冤枉钱，尝到了很多功能繁复且声称能达到很多种效果的应用。我不知道 all-in-one 是什么时候开始的，又是什么时候流行的。
在一些工具群或者相关话题的评论区，提到效率工具，大部分网友都会all in one变成使自己“效率”标签存在的信仰，而对那些没有 all-in-one 的工具嗤之以鼻。这正是令我一直感到奇怪的事情。All-in-one 是否不仅仅只限于工具？如果仅限于工具，这是否未免有些太过工具理性了？我认为，工具的 all-in-one 反倒是弱化了使用者的存在，而为这些工具服役。手机就是一个典型的例子。
另外，从行为学的角度来说，一个东西仅对我产生一个刺激，是最有效的学习方案。在这里，我不想深入探讨行为学背后的各种复杂和千丝万缕的概念，而只是利用两个最基本的概念：一个是桑代克的刺激-反应理论（S-R theory), 即学习是刺激和反应相关联的结果。简单来说，就是培养习惯。
另一个是斯金纳的 Discriminative stimuli，即一种能产生特定反应的刺激，且这种反应更加迅速，不会被轻易替换和消退。这也是我为什么讨厌all in one应用的原因，因为他们的刺激无法令我快速的形成或者产生相对应的刺激。所以，他们大大地降低了我的效率。
所以，为了让自己以后不再花冤枉钱，我为生产力或者效率软件做出了三个规则：

简洁：不简单，美观
易用：用起来不是很复杂，上手简单…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>南山居氪</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Microsoft blunder opened millions of PCs to potent malware attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889745</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1889745"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T16:26:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft said Windows automatically blocked dangerous drivers. It didn't.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok made money from getting Syrian refugees to beg in livestreams]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890110</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890110"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T16:22:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A BBC investigation found that TikTok was taking up to 70% of profits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Belanger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UX vs UI – What's the Difference? Definition and Meaning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ux-vs-ui-whats-the-difference-definition-and-meaning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ux-vs-ui-whats-the-difference-definition-and-meaning/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T16:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing a website or an app, the finished product needs to be functional, intuitive, and aesthetically pleasing. This is where UX and UI design come in. UX and UI design are two technical terms that can often be confusing. Many people may use these two terms interchangeably, incorrectly, or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Developer Journey – How I Learned to Code with Dyslexia and ADHD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/developer-journey/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/developer-journey/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T16:01:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone, I'm Jalmari Ikävalko, a software developer in my early 30s. In this article, I’ll share my whole journey from my first contact with code to becoming the professional developer I am today.  I'll start from my childhood when I first got interested in programming. My Introduction to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jalmari Ikävalko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The next Ford Mustang won’t be easy to tune; blame cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890108</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890108"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T15:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of digital security might be your new car eternally remaining stock.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[blogic — The no-code blog builder Notion users have dreamed of]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/blogic</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/blogic"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T15:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vijay, Founder of Blogic, coming with the second product on Product Hunt. I am excited to launch Blogic on Product Hunt today. I started working on Blogic last year, and life got in the way. To be honest, my second kid 👶 is awesome, by the way.  I got back to working on beta and had 300+ beta signups and lots of customer feedback; I mean a lot, which is insanely awesome. It's finally ready to be shipped. Thanks for the early testers; Blogic wouldn't come this far without you; I seriously mean it. It's one thing I avoided for so long, talking to customers, but it's worth it. Sorry, back to business. 

How did it start?
I am a big fan of Notion; it's one of the products that you can't shut up with your family and colleagues at your office. I have introduced Notion to many teams at my work, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft preps DirectStorage 1.1 with GPU decompression for faster game loads]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890079</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890079"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T15:42:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update is "coming soon" but requires use of all-new compression format.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time Machine — Genealogy management system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/time-machine-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/time-machine-2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T15:41:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk is under federal investigation for merger conduct, Twitter tells judge]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890082</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890082"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T15:15:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musk refuses to produce communications with SEC and FTC, Twitter tells court.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big pharma says drug prices reflect R&D cost. Researchers call BS]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890068</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1890068"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T14:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study finds no correlation between R&D spending and outlandish drug prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apache  Commons Text]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11761</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11761"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T13:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache  Commons Text]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Readsy — Read web content faster via auto-highlighted text]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/readsy-3</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/readsy-3"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T13:06:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[对Java CMS的审计的一次尝试]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11760</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11760"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T13:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[对Java CMS的审计的一次尝试]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What If the Metaverse Is Better Without Virtual Reality?]]></title>
        <id>6348464408a267a4aad8c051</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/plaintext-metaverse-better-without-virtual-reality/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: How Mark Zuckerberg fell in love with VR, the fake future of documentaries, and Armageddon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tern NBD S5i Review: Cruise It Out]]></title>
        <id>632b32e8995b6da54b57efd8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/tern-nbd-s5i/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This easy-going little electric bike has a step-through frame so low that anyone can cruise it out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrienne So</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up a Greenscreen on a Budget (2022): Stands, Materials, Lighting]]></title>
        <id>61f1c814b92104f9e83d16f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-build-green-screen/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All it takes is a few lights and some fabric to transport yourself anywhere on camera.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Ravenscraft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Algorithms Promote Self-Harm, Who Is Held Responsible?]]></title>
        <id>63481a7c8e4a6cd698dd9f5c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/molly-russell-suicide-platforms-mental-health/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A British court ruled that teenager Molly Russell died in part because of online content—but holding platforms accountable is complicated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eleanor Cummins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Best Android Phones (2022): Unlocked, Cheap, Foldable]]></title>
        <id>5ad9f8845ac0d714a1b64321</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-android-phones/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shopping for a new phone can be an ordeal. Let us take some of the pain out of it with these WIRED-tested picks and tips.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian Chokkattu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Future Fitness App Review: Virtual Personal Training Sessions]]></title>
        <id>633f673c5a49457c993f539f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/future-fitness-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The subscription-based fitness platform winningly combines old-school one-on-one training and modern-day mobile technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #789 微软发布免费的 AI 图像合成软件]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15140-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15140-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T11:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[微软发布免费的 AI 图像合成软件

微软宣布了基于 OpenAI 的 DALL-E 2 模型的应用 Designer。用户可通过输入文字提示生成一系列图像。Designer 有免费版和付费版，将提供给微软 365 个人和家庭订阅用户。目前 Designer 作为一个免费的 Web 应用供公众测试和获取反馈，类似的技术将整合到 Edge 浏览器和 Bing 搜索引擎中。


消息来源：ARS Technica



老王点评：AI 图像生成已经势不可挡，虽然目前还有一些道德瑕疵，但是这总是能解决的。




GNU 工具链考虑将其基础设施转移到 Linux 基金会

GNU 工具链是 GNU/Linux 生态系统、云和嵌入式环境的基石。红帽公司资助的 SourceWare.org 多年来一直在托管 GNU 工具链的大部分基础设施，但最近有提议将其基础设施转移到 Linux 基金会提供的 IT 服务下。Linux 基金会的 IT 服务将管理 Git 存储库、邮件列表、错误跟踪器、网站、CI/CD 以及相关的基础设施。GNU 工具链的领导层已经正式表态支持这一提议。


消息来源：Phoronix



老王点评：这件事 Linux 基金会做的不错，毕竟有专门的组织来负责维护，总比红帽员工兼职维护更可靠些。毕竟，现在这种基础软件的安全一旦动摇，影响的范围已经不仅仅是个人爱好者了。




Debian GNU/Linux 14 代号已确定为“Forky”

Debian 方面今天宣布，计划 2027 年发布的 Debian 14 将被称为 “Forky”。Debian 的代号是以《玩具总动员》系列中的玩具命名的。即将在 2023 年发布的 Debian 12 代号为“Bookworm”，而 2025 年发布的 Debian 13 的代号是 “Trixie”。


消息来源：Phoronix



老王点评：不知道《玩具总动员》中有多少个的有名字的玩具，要是用完了怎么办。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Reboot of the Maxwell’s Demon Thought Experiment—in Real Life]]></title>
        <id>6348a9bbd8c7bf0344fc40b7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/maxwells-demon-thought-experiment-reboot/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Physicists just reconstructed a 19th-century paradox that seems to violate the second law of thermodynamics (but really doesn’t).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FineCam – 让手机变身电脑高清网络摄像头[Win/macOS]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43617</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/finecam-lz/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T09:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FineCam 是一款可以从 iPhone、iPad、GoPro、连接电脑的网络摄像头捕捉视频，并添加滤镜、特效，或改变背景的工具，支持 Windows 与 macOS。是低清晰度 USB 摄像头的良]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generated Humans – 100,000 张不存在的人类全身照片，免费、无肖像权]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43613</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/generated-humans/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T07:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generated Humans 发布了 100,000 张通过 AI 生成的，不存在的人类全身照片，免费、无肖像权，可在个人非商业项目中随意使用。@Appinn 不知道还有多少人记得这个项目：《这个]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Kubernetes help solve automation challenges?]]></title>
        <id>70236 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/kubernetes-solve-automation-challenges"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can Kubernetes help solve automation challenges?
Rom Adams
Fri, 10/14/2022 - 03:00

            
I started my automation journey when I adopted Gentoo Linux as my primary operating system in 2002. Twenty years later, automation is not yet a done deal. When I meet with customers and partners, they share automation wins within teams, but they also describe the challenges to achieving similar success at an organizational level.
Most IT organizations have the ability to provision a virtual machine end to end, reducing what used to be a four-week lead time to just five minutes. That level of automation is itself a complex workflow, requiring networking (IP address management, DNS, proxy, networking zones, and so on), identity access management, hypervisor, storage, backup, updating the operatin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rom Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPhone 14 系列相机操作指南]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76181</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76181"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T06:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[从 iPhone X 开始，每年我都会为新的 iPhone 写一篇操作指南，一晃已经到了 iPhone 14 系列。在过去的几年里，智能机的影像理念无论是大方向还是品牌的个性化都在发生着翻天覆地的变化，iPhone 自然也是如此。不过 iPhone 更为难得的是一种在变化和不变中的把控。
是的，不变。
在我看来，「不变」比「变化」更能考验一款产品对于影像技术发展的思考与判断。不过，这个问题我想留在最后再讨论。
使用 iPhone 14 Pro 系列拍摄
相比评测，这篇操作指南我会更多分享我使用 iPhone 14 系列的创作经验。过去的一段时间里，我们使用 iPhone 14 系列拍摄了大量不同主题、不同风格的作品，其间也围绕今年的重要更新——4800 万像素——做了大量探索和尝试。
使用 iPhone 14 Pro Max 拍摄
许多惊喜，当然也有一点问题。我们就先从 4800 万像素带来的第一个改变，50mm 开始。
（注：受平台上传图片大小限制，文章照片均经过压缩。）
延续的系统，新增的焦距
一个重要的逻辑是，当我们谈论手机摄影时，本质上应该把手机作为「相机」在讨论。换言之，无论是相机还是手机，当我们在拍摄时，指导我们的再也不是所谓的参数，而是摄影理念本身。
iPhone 14 Pro 系列 1× 镜头拍摄iPhone 14 Pro 系列 3× 镜头拍摄
对于焦距的认知就是一个最好的例子。
本质上任何的相机都是由机身和镜头两部分组成，其中镜头直接影响着你的取景范围。而取景范围意味着「拍摄题材的选择」。从 iPhone 11 Pro 系列升级为三颗镜头，之后 iPhone 的整个影像理念开始强调「系统性」。整个相机的理念重点是三颗镜头之间的协作。
但如果我们切换为「相机」的认知，目前的 iPhone 就可以理解为一套「定焦镜头组」。在 iPhone 13 Pro 系列上…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>果核Group</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[写给所有 Mac 用户的摸鱼指北]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/75805</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/75805"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T06:41:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

这篇文章真的在试图提高你使用 Mac 的效率，让你能节省出时间好好摸鱼。
本文分为三大部分，共计一万余字，下方导读部分在尽最大可能帮你找到感兴趣的内容：

上篇：基础铺垫。介绍一些桌面端操作系统的基础概念，以及一些 macOS 特有的功能和修饰键。例如「程序坞」、「菜单栏」、「Option」、「Command」等。
中篇：使用场景。从打开或切换软件，浏览信息或操控电脑等具体的使用场景展开，级级提高，层层深入地介绍各种提高操作效率的技巧或软件。
下篇：软件推荐。聚焦于分享不同类型的软件，覆盖了同类别下的付费及免费软件。

如果你刚接触 Mac，那么我真诚地建议从「基础铺垫」开始阅读，这会帮助你在后续的进阶阅读中如鱼得水，能够明白文章中的专有名词是什么意思。
如果你看过很多类似的文章，适当跳读「基础铺垫」，从「使用场景」开始阅读会更加节省时间且不减少收获。
如果你和我一样苦于找不到一篇成体系地介绍 Mac 高效技巧和实用软件的文章，那么恭喜你，建议全文朗读并背诵。
又或者你对以上所有概念解析和技巧分享都不太感冒，只对好用的软件感兴趣，那么「软件推荐」部分和这一份 macOS 精选软件集 或许是你的菜。
上篇：基础铺垫
macOS 概念解析

macOS 中的一些基础概念，适当了解能够在众多的技巧中不迷失方向，始终知道这个技巧对应的那种类型。

桌面、窗口和标签页之间的关系
呈现在「桌面」上的 Safari App 的一个「窗口」，在窗口中打开了两个「标签页」
首先是桌面（Desktop）
现实生活中的桌面是一个实体，一般用来摆放工作的…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>毕大业</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magicul X - Design File Editor — Edit Adobe XD and Figma files for free online.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/magicul-x-design-file-editor</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/magicul-x-design-file-editor"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T05:53:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[www.magicul.io). We decided to step it up a notch and embark on our next journey. 

Our latest product Magicul X is a design file editor, which can open almost any design file. The first release we will support opening Adobe XD and Figma files. Compatibility with Sketch, Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator files should follow shortly after the launch.

We are extremely curious to hear what you guys think and what feature you think would set us apart from Figma and Adobe XD (wait aren't they the same now 😅☠️).

The product is still under heavy development, but you can sign up for a wait list to get early access. In particular we wanted to collect early feedback from the community... so here we go, fire away 🚀
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resin内存马逆袭之路]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11758</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11758"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T03:09:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Resin内存马逆袭之路]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gather: Your Desk Simplified — Magnetic organization that streamlines your desk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/gather-your-desk-simplified</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/gather-your-desk-simplified"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T02:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bells and Wishes — Online group greeting cards, perfect for office occasions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/bells-and-wishes-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/bells-and-wishes-2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T00:41:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recycled Battery Materials Can Work as Well as New Ones]]></title>
        <id>6346fdfe136a8fc35853e3f9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/recycled-battery-materials-can-work-as-well-as-new-ones/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an independent test, cathode components Redwood Materials made from reused metals matched the performance of those made from raw ones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Barber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pixel 7 and Pixel 7 Pro Review: Even Better Value]]></title>
        <id>633f9b397e8d589e28665b11</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/google-pixel-7-pixel-7-pro/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These phones remain unbeatable when it comes to sheer value.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian Chokkattu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Avoid Prop Drilling with the React Context API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/avoid-prop-drilling-with-react-context-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/avoid-prop-drilling-with-react-context-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T16:52:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The React Context API provides a way to pass data through multiple nested levels of components without having to manually pass that data to each level.  React context is one sure way of globally managing your data in your app, and it's a good way to avoid prop drilling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[53 Best Prime Day Deals Still Going Strong (2022): Phones, Laptops, Espresso Machines]]></title>
        <id>62cea7a49e1cc6cbc9061e41</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-amazon-prime-day-leftover-deals-2022-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T16:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon's big event is over, but a few of our favorite things are still on sale, like robot vacuums, laptops, Pixel phones, and Apple watches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gilbertson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Pixel 6, Pixel 6 Pro, and Pixel 6A Are All on Sale Right Now]]></title>
        <id>609210b917a7c892e1464319</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/google-pixel-6-deal-october-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T16:39:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pixel 7 is here, which means you can buy last year’s flagship Android smartphones for cheap. Better yet, the Pixel 6A is also on sale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian Chokkattu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The $1 Billion Alex Jones Effect]]></title>
        <id>63483cd27e817d200a6cc669</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/alex-jones-1-billion-damages-free-speech-moderation/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T16:33:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Infowars host now knows the cost of “free speech”—but does the landmark judgment signal a crackdown on disinformation?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The $1 Billion Alex Jones Effect]]></title>
        <id>63483cd27e817d200a6cc669</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/alex-jones-1-billion-damages-free-speech-moderation/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T16:33:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Infowars host now knows the cost of “free speech”—but does the landmark judgment signal a crackdown on disinformation?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[记一次简单的src挖掘]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11757</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11757"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T15:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[记一次简单的src挖掘]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code a project three different ways (JavaScript + REST API + Database)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-project-three-different-ways-javascript-rest-api-database/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-project-three-different-ways-javascript-rest-api-database/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T14:06:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you code a similar project using different methods it helps you understand each method more. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to code a flight widget in JavaScript using multiple methods. First you will learn to create the project using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Zero to DevOps Engineer - DevOps Roadmap for YOUR specific background 🔥]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/techworld_with_nana/from-zero-to-devops-engineer-devops-roadmap-for-your-specific-background-4h8n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/techworld_with_nana/from-zero-to-devops-engineer-devops-roadmap-for-your-specific-background-4h8n"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T13:35:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#devops #career #cloud #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TechWorld with Nana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Shouldn’t Compete With Workers—It Should Supercharge Them]]></title>
        <id>633f467992468d5a8855add9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ai-shouldnt-compete-with-workers-it-should-supercharge-them-turing-trap/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The economy could get a boost if machine learning engineers switched from copying human abilities to augmenting them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clive Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Shouldn’t Compete With Workers—It Should Supercharge Them]]></title>
        <id>633f467992468d5a8855add9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ai-shouldnt-compete-with-workers-it-should-supercharge-them-turing-trap/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The economy could get a boost if machine learning engineers switched from copying human abilities to augmenting them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clive Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hestan Cue Induction Cooktop and Smart Probe: Long-Term Test]]></title>
        <id>633f675b85e7a4cc2f80228e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hestan-cue-smart-probe-long-term-test/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest additions to Hestan’s app-controlled countertop burner system show how this sector of the smart kitchen is progressing, and where it still lags.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Ray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Is Still Betting on a VR Revolution That May Never Come]]></title>
        <id>6345f6fc54f8c6faa9d67d45</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/gadget-lab-podcast-570/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, we discuss Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg’s ambitions for growing virtual reality as a platform, and how the new Quest Pro headset fits into that vision.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awesome tools for Coding Practice]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-tools-for-coding-practice-4l49</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-tools-for-coding-practice-4l49"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T11:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #beginners #react #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Vishwakarma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s VR Headset Harvests Personal Data Right Off Your Face]]></title>
        <id>6345d480d01ed05afa60f977</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/metas-vr-headset-quest-pro-personal-data-face/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cameras inside the device that track eye and face movements can make an avatar’s expressions more realistic, but they raise new privacy questions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khari Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Pharma Says Drug Prices Reflect R&D Cost. Researchers Call BS]]></title>
        <id>634777aa7fa81ffa8c2b0106</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/drug-research-pricing/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study finds no correlation between research and development spending and outlandish drug prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grace Browne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius Exchange Data Dump Is a Gift to Crypto Sleuths—and Thieves]]></title>
        <id>6345b95754f8c6faa9d67d3c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/celsius-user-data-dump-crypto-tracing-scammers/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By releasing half a million users’ transactions in a bankruptcy court filing, the company has opened a vast breach in its users’ financial privacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Search for a Pill That Can Help Dogs—and Humans—Live Longer]]></title>
        <id>633de7e0fe6027f6ad16e5bd</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-search-for-a-pill-for-dog-and-human-longevity/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People have been searching for a fountain of youth for thousands of years. Celine Halioua thinks she’s found one—for canines. Be patient, we’re next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Simonite</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Made My Portfolio with Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/j471n/how-i-made-my-portfolio-with-nextjs-2mn3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/j471n/how-i-made-my-portfolio-with-nextjs-2mn3"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T09:24:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #beginners #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jatin Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[中国AI绘画行业调查报告——技术，用户，争议与未来]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76141</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76141"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T08:19:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[前言
多家机构在近期都发布了 AIGC 报告，这个尚在萌芽的赛道获得了巨大的关注，但在更早一些的时候，其中一些更细，更窄的领域，就已经发生了惊天动地的变化，我们将专注其中一个赛道，即 AIGC 中的「生成式文生图」领域，从技术发展，用户调研，商业模式和争议，以及对未来的一些展望，为大家呈现这份报告。
报告的数据及来源包括公开新闻媒体文章，第三方统计数据，6pen 自身数据，以及我们收回的 2398 份问卷调查和对部分行业资深人士的深度访谈。我们的问卷通过 6pen 自有渠道，即刻，微博，以及行业 KOL 分发，最终有效收到 2398 个提交，它们可能是这个行业首次的大批量对用户的直接调查，并聚焦在国内市场，我们认为其具有相当的参考性。
利益相关：本报告由 6pen 调查发布，作为行业从业者，本报告将更多从技术，用户及行业整体视角出发。
 
AI绘画技术发展的简要脉络
GAN时代
在 diffusion 被广泛运用于AI绘画之前，这种艺术形式的主要实现方式 GAN （Generative Adversarial Nets ），以NVlabs的SPADE为例：用户提供草图，由GAN模型将其转化为真实的风景图像。这听起来有点像AI绘画里的img2img，但在这类模型里，用户无法通过文本影响生成结果。

直到类似 CLIP 这种跨模态的图文模型出现，才让用户有办法用文字实现AI作画。后来者如VQGAN+CLIP 或StyleCLIP，均是因为CLIP打通文本和图形域(domain)，用户输入的文本与GAN生成的结果真正有了「可比较性」，这使得计算二者误差并迭代效果成为了可能。

GAN在模拟分布方面有着天然的优势，因此它在人脸属性编辑、风格模仿等领域大放异彩，例如给人戴上墨镜、加上胡子、生成动漫脸、模仿小说风格。也正因如此，它也很容易陷入模型坍缩(Model Collapse)，即…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>调皮的王登科</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[自由与角色：如何应对「身不由己」的窘境？]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76151</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76151"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T08:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[我们大部分人总会身处在一种「身不由己」的状态里，然后内心有一些向往的生活状态，但是现实很残酷，导致自己现在无法去达到目标，于是陷入到了焦虑和无奈的情绪中。
在国庆的节假日里，我见了一个很久未见的朋友。他的孩子已经两岁了，在聊天时，我能感觉到他因为有了孩子后，产生了很大的压力和焦虑。他说，因为有了孩子以后，以往的时间都不由自己来做主了，然后未来所有的计划都变了，已经买好的不错的房子，会因为学区房做改变的计划，然后自己也舍不得消费，想把挣到的钱给孩子准备上。他是一个很负责的人，也希望能多陪孩子，努力工作把孩子养大。但是他觉得自己牺牲了自己看电影、健身，以及和爱人出门旅游的机会，如果要恢复这些，要等孩子长到18岁的成年以后，也就是说，还要等16年。说到这里，他的眼神里露出了一丝无奈。
听到这里，我总觉得哪里不太对，于是产生了一些疑问，面临这样的不由己状态，我们只能无奈或者焦虑？我希望通过这篇文章，呈现出我对这个问题的完整思考，希望你看完后，能够从新的视角去看待自己的问题。
我们不妨先问一个问题：我们为什么讨厌「不由己」的感觉？
答案是：每个人的内心都在追寻某种「自由」。人为什么要追寻自由？其实不仅是人，只要是生物，就会追求自由，追求一种随性地、自然地、丰富地生长。任何人都不希望自己的眼睛永远只盯着一个地方，耳朵只能听见一成不变的音色和音调；不希望身体被禁锢在一个狭小幽闭的空间里不能动弹，不希望思想停止运行，因为当思考停止，就意味着自己不再存在。
自由是人的天性，也可以说，自由是我们不得不接受的权利。
说了那么多自由的不可或缺，那什么才算自由？
一、什么才算自由？
提到自由，我最先想到的是时间和地点的自由。比如做一个旅行 up 主，可以随时出去旅游，想去哪儿就去哪儿，这叫自由。而每天在格子间上班，按照准确的时间上下班打卡，一天里重要的时间都交付给公司和老板，这叫不自由。
这个定义准…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>猴猴说话</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What you need to know about compiling code]]></title>
        <id>70247 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/compiling-code"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What you need to know about compiling code
Alan Smithee
Thu, 10/13/2022 - 03:00

            
Source code must be compiled in order to run, and in open source software everyone has access to source code. Whether you've written code yourself and you want to compile and run it, or whether you've downloaded somebody's project to try it out, it's useful to know how to process source code through a compiler, and also what exactly a compiler does with all that code.
Build a better mousetrap
We don't usually think of a mousetrap as a computer, but believe it or not, it does share some similarities with the CPU running the device you're reading this article on. The classic (non-cat) mousetrap has two states: it's either set or released. You might consider that on (the kill bar is set and stores po…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Smithee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asynchronous programming in Rust]]></title>
        <id>70228 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/asynchronous-programming-rust"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asynchronous programming in Rust
Stephan Avenwedde
Thu, 10/13/2022 - 03:00

            
Asynchronous programming: Incredibly useful but difficult to learn. You can't avoid async programming to create a fast and reactive application. Applications with a high amount of file or network I/O or with a GUI that should always be reactive benefit tremendously from async programming. Tasks can be executed in the background while the user still makes inputs. Async programming is possible in many languages, each with different styles and syntax. Rust is no exception. In Rust, this feature is called async-await.
While async-await has been an integral part of Rust since version 1.39.0, most applications depend on community crates. In Rust, except for a larger binary, async-await comes with zero costs.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephan Avenwedde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一日一技 | 怎样将 iPhone 备份保存到 Mac 的外部存储设备]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76016</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76016"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T06:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

一、问题描述
前段时间碰到一个问题，我 iPhone 背板碎了，需要走 AppleCare 交给苹果返厂维修，而我的 iPhone 是 512GB 的，在备份数据时候麻烦了，我笔记本本身就是 512GB 空间的，肯定不够用呀。
而备份 iPhone 默认的存储位置是在本机的硬盘上，我有个 14T 的硬盘，那么如何将默认的备份位置改到外部存储设备上呢。

二、如何设置备份位置到外部存储器
默认的备份位置在下面这个目录
~/Library/Application Support/MobileSync/Backup
其目录是这样的，Backup 里面就是你的每个设备每次的备份记录

我们要做的就是将这个位置映射到你的移动硬盘上去。
1. 确定你的移动硬盘位置
你需要知道自己硬盘的完整文件路径：

打开终端，
输入 cd 然后将你的硬盘图标拖到终端中，就会看到它的路径了
回车进入到移动硬盘目录下，指令 ls -al 能看到硬盘中的所有文件（图片中的 ll 是我自定义的一个指令）
我的就是 /Volumes/Kyle 14TB/ （在终端的路径需要转义空格，所以能看到终端中名字空格前面有个 \）

2. 移动硬盘中新建一个备份文件夹
在你的移动硬盘中新建一个备份文件夹，用于存储接下来的手机备份文件。
mkdir Backup
此时能看到目录中多出一个名为 Backup 的文件夹
 

进入这个文件夹并展示它的绝对路径
cd Backup
pwd
能看到我的这个文件夹的绝对路径是 /Volumes/Kyle 14TB/Backup，这个会在下…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青枫</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GestureSign – 开源鼠标手势工具，支持触摸版、触摸屏、触控笔、鼠标[Windows]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43604</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/gesturesign/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T03:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GestureSign 是一款开源的 Windows 电脑鼠标手势工具，同时支持触控板、触摸屏、触控笔、鼠标，自定义度很高，支持全局手势、指定应用手势，可以发送指令、快捷键、运行程序等。@Appinn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[19 Best Deals From Best Buy’s Flash Sale (2022): Headphones, TVs, Apple Devices]]></title>
        <id>6345d9710b299b05896f7c21</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-buy-flash-sale-prime-day-rival-sale-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T00:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon isn’t the only one in a prime position to unleash killer discounts on smart TVs, headphones, and Apple devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Jancer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[37 Best Prime Day Deals Under $50 (2022): Cheap Tablets, Streaming Devices, and iPhone Cases]]></title>
        <id>62bc601330b57f91eba20c7c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-amazon-prime-day-deals-under-50-2022-6/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T00:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are the best bargains to scratch your shopping itch without breaking the bank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Medea Giordano, Gear Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[84 Absolute Best Prime Day Deals (2022): Prime Early Access Sale]]></title>
        <id>62bef56c06a26f633de99ff8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-prime-day-deals-2022-9/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T23:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Prime Early Access Sale is here. From Alexa-powered Echo Dots to laptops, here are all the greatest discounts we’ve found.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gear Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[27 Best Prime Day Deals on Amazon Devices (2022): Early Access Sale]]></title>
        <id>62bdc4a0042ab1ffde99c523</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-amazon-device-deals-prime-day-2022-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T22:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Echo smart displays and speakers to Kindles and Fire tablets, snag the retailer’s own hardware on sale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brenda Stolyar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Machine Learning Model in Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-machine-learning-model-in-rust/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-machine-learning-model-in-rust/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T22:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning is a really interesting concept in computer programming. It involves using data to train a computer program to carry out tasks.  During the process, the program learns from data by discovering patterns. This reduces the need for programmers to hard code rules in some applications. Languages like]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chigozie Oduah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Email Alias – How to Set Up a Professional Email for Free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/email-alias-set-up-a-professional-email-for-free/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/email-alias-set-up-a-professional-email-for-free/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T22:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I needed to log in to AWS. But my main email address was rejected. Apparently I'd done this in the past and the account had been irreversibly deleted.  No reset option – just a message saying the account was permanently deleted: There are about a million ways to get]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hoppy Copy — Write high-converting emails, 10x faster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/hoppy-copy</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/hoppy-copy"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T18:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Visualization Tools – 2022 Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-visualization-tools-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-visualization-tools-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T17:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data visualization is the process of interpreting or representing data graphically. Generally, it is the graphical or visual representation of data using charts, tables, histograms, and other info-graphics.  Data plays a major role in any type of organization. Data visualization helps us understand certain trends and insights, and make]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dastia — Track, route & automate leads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/dastia</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/dastia"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T17:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lab-Grown Human Brain Tissue Works in Rats]]></title>
        <id>63446d8054f8c6faa9d67d25</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/lab-grown-human-brain-tissue-works-in-rats/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tiny cell clusters called organoids integrated with the animals’ own tissue, a step toward developing sophisticated mini-models of the brain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Mullin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What It Means to ‘Feel Normal’ Online]]></title>
        <id>632ae3b036c33c0247a2f0b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/psychology-data-surveillance-normality-personality/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A personalized, authentic experience is an unquestioned building block of digital infrastructure. But what does that really involve?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tung-Hui Hu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一二三四，打开心智]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76149</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76149"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T11:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[现今社会高速发展，充满了不确定性。我们置身于时代的洪流中，被裹挟着不知冲向何处。诚然，时代给了我们更多的选择，同时也让我们更加迷茫，仿佛处在一个有无数岔路的迷宫里，不知道自己将走向何方。
「如何在不确定的风浪里，实现确定性的成长？」这应该是现今大多人所关注的问题吧。
关于成长，市面上有很多方法论，但它往往都不讲背后的原理。不知道大家是否也和我一样，看到一些方法或者教程，经常会收藏起来，跟练一段时间，但大多都是半途而废，坚持一阵子后又打回原形了。
为什么会这样呢？因为每个人的情况不同，适用的方法也不同。如果只是知其然不知其所以然，那只有不断地尝试各种方法，不断地去磨合，才能找到适合自身的。这个尝试的过程，其实就是通过外界的方法，来获得自身的反馈，从而更了解自己。
但如果我们换个角度，一开始就从了解自己出发，再剖析方法背后的原理，那是不是更容易找到适合自己的方法呢？所以我认为，知其然又知其所以然，反倒是一条捷径。
要了解自己，就得先知道我们的心智是怎么运作的。所谓「心智」，就像是大脑里一个可以不断升级的系统，包含了我们对外部世界的所有认知，也包括因此所造就的思维方式。我们的认知和感觉，其实也只是心智对外部世界的投射而已。
前不久出版的一本新书——《打开心智》，正是围绕「心智」这个概念展开的。兵书有云，「知己知彼，百战不殆」。书中先是阐述了大脑的四个基本原理，帮助我们了解心智是怎么运作的，此为「知己」；然后又围绕情绪、习惯、动力、学习、思考和创造等方面，剖析背后的原理，此为「知彼」。不仅如此，它还提供一套行之有效的方法，让我们能更好地实现自己的目标。所以，这是一本帮助我们认识自我、突破自我的书籍，知己知彼，我们才能更有效实现自我成长，去应对时代的不确定性。
书籍作者是李睿秋（Lachel），一名深度思考践行者，常年专注于心理学、认知科学与心智研究，同时也是虎嗅年度十大作者、36氪…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>1A君</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Chip Sanctions ‘Kneecap’ China’s Tech Industry]]></title>
        <id>63444b96136a8fc35853e3e7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/us-chip-sanctions-kneecap-chinas-tech-industry/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The toughest export restrictions yet cut off AI hardware and chipmaking tools crucial to China’s commercial and military ambitions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Chip Sanctions ‘Kneecap’ China’s Tech Industry]]></title>
        <id>63444b96136a8fc35853e3e7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/us-chip-sanctions-kneecap-chinas-tech-industry/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The toughest export restrictions yet cut off AI hardware and chipmaking tools crucial to China’s commercial and military ambitions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gas Drilling Is Disrupting Animal Migration]]></title>
        <id>6344484d7b75d692a43c0054</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/gas-drilling-is-disrupting-animal-migration/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists are investigating why large animals like the mule deer of Wyoming go where they go—and how humans can get out of their way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Barber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VocalRemover – 强大的在线音频处理工具：人声分离、变调、剪辑、合并、录音、卡拉OK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43598</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/vocalremover/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T10:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VocalRemover 是一款拥有中文界面的在线音频处理工具，主要用来进行人声分离，也支持变调、剪辑、合并、录音、卡拉OK 等功能。@appinn 感谢 @noshit 同学的推荐：https://]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy applications using Foreman ACD]]></title>
        <id>70215 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/deploy-applications-foreman-acd"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy applications using Foreman ACD
Maximilian Kolb
Wed, 10/12/2022 - 03:00

            
When you manage your IT infrastructure using Foreman and Katello, the smallest unit to operate on is generally a host. You can provision hosts, deliver versioned content, and set configurations. Using Foreman ACD, you can use your Foreman instance to deploy applications consisting of multiple services spanning multiple hosts. This blog post briefly introduces the Foreman ACD plugin and explains how it can help you deploy a Prometheus and Grafana stack. If you want to know more about deploying an ELK stack consisting of an Elasticsearch cluster and Kibana, look at Deploying an ELK Cluster with Application Centric Deployment.
Introduction to Foreman and Katello
You can use Foreman and Katello to manag…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maximilian Kolb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CleverPDF – 44 个免费的 PDF 在线工具集：PDF 转 Word、提取图片、加密/解密、拆分、合并等]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43591</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/cleverpdf/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T04:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CleverPDF 是一款免费的在线 PDF 工具集，拥有 PDF 转文档、PDF 转图片、文档转 PDF、解密 PDF、拆分、合并等共计 44 个功能。@Appinn 感谢 @Sin.Yor. 同学]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[whalesync — Free Airtable, Webflow, & Notion templates to build web apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/whalesync</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/whalesync"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T01:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Pixel 7 and Pixel 7 Pro Pack New Android VPN and Tensor G2, Titan M2 Chips]]></title>
        <id>634592230b299b05896f7c1c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/google-pixel-7-pixel-7-pro-tensor-g2-android-vpn/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T19:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company says it hardened the security of its new flagship phones—and plans to release a built-in Android VPN.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Success! NASA Says DART Really Clocked That Asteroid]]></title>
        <id>6340a75cf93a1584dc57f351</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/success-nasa-dart-dimorphos-asteroid/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T18:52:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two weeks after the spacecraft collided with Dimorphos, researchers determined that it knocked the space rock 32 minutes off its old orbit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramin Skibba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iOS 翻译体验优化（欧路词典 + Shortcuts + Back Tap）]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76131</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76131"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T15:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[前言
本教程源于 @yetone 的一篇 推文 ，和 @Jack Huang 讨论后稍作修改。
苹果自带的翻译功能在几次版本更新之后已很好用，但需要多个步骤，对专业词汇的支持也没有欧陆词典好（欧陆词典可自行扩充词库）。本教程基于 iOS 自带的 Back Tap 功能，快速启动翻译软件，并支持截图 OCR 翻译。
前期准备
下载软件： 欧路词典 (Eudic) 和快捷指令 (Shortcuts)
「欧路词典」，是一款经典的翻译软件，可自行扩充词库，专业版需付费。
「快捷指令」是苹果官方的软件，前身是 Workflow Gallery，可以理解成一个无代码开发平台（No-Code Development Platform），不需要编程知识，就能完成很多自动化功能的实现。如果对这方面感兴趣，可访问 Shortcuts Gallery 。
安装 Shortcuts
在 Safari 中打开以下两个链接，点击「获取捷径」，再点击「添加快捷方式」。
Clipboard Translate: https://www.icloud.com/shortcuts/b643ecb89dbd4468b8679cd4888b13d9
Image Translate: https://www.icloud.com/shortcuts/02bf2bb484a54f50897b8a3f315d48fd
设置快捷方式
点击「设置」- 辅助功能 – 触控 – 轻点背面（Back Tap）- 设置如图所示：

使用
Clipboard Translate：轻点手机背面两次，自动读取「剪切板」中的文本，并跳转欧路词典翻译。
Image Translate: 轻点手机背面三次，自动截屏，并识别图片中的文本，跳转欧路词典翻译。
扩展：

上文是通过 Back Tap 实现的，日常使用中偶尔会有误触的可能，也可以通过「辅助触控」，俗称「小白点」实现。
macOS 上的全文翻译可参考这篇文章：一种几乎永不失效的网页中英对照翻译方案]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Another_Dayu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Ada Lovelace Day! Here are our favorite tech books for kids]]></title>
        <id>70245 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/ada-lovelace-day-tech-books-kids"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Ada Lovelace Day! Here are our favorite tech books for kids
Lauren Pritchett
Tue, 10/11/2022 - 11:00

            
Tech is everywhere! And it's important to remember, everyone is a beginner once. The industry is continually growing, looking for new folks to add valuable perspectives. How do we inspire our next batch of tech contributors?
In honor of Ada Lovelace Day, we asked our community of writers if they had any resources or books they recommend for young programmers or enthusiasts. Here's what they had to share.
Start from Scratch
I recommend Coding Games in Scratch: A Step-by-Step Visual Guide to Building Your Own Computer Games by Jon Woodcock and Code Your Own Games!: 20 Games to Create with Scratch by Max Wainewright. Being a LEGO family, all of my kids have spent time with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Pritchett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Signal for Help I Created Went Viral. Now It Could Be Misused]]></title>
        <id>633ada06e0fe4cc825d3a56c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/domestic-violence-artificial-intelligence-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well-meaning efforts to integrate the hand signal with digital technology could expose vulnerable people to detection and escalated violence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrea Gunraj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Signal for Help I Created Went Viral. Now It Could Be Misused]]></title>
        <id>633ada06e0fe4cc825d3a56c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/domestic-violence-artificial-intelligence-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well-meaning efforts to integrate the hand signal with digital technology could expose vulnerable people to detection and escalated violence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrea Gunraj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robots Are Helping Immunocompromised Kids 'Go to School']]></title>
        <id>633dca06669c7202654d7d3d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/robots-education-sick-kids/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sure, my telepresence robot had some issues—but for students like me who can’t make it to campus because of disability or illness, these tools open new doors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gillian Okimoto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advice for Junior Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jeroendedauw/advice-for-junior-developers-30am</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jeroendedauw/advice-for-junior-developers-30am"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T12:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#beginners #productivity #codenewbie #learning]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeroen De Dauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Sci-Fi Visions for Interstellar Travel Just Might Work]]></title>
        <id>633f4ebe058264dd3ee9304c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/travelers-guide-to-the-stars-interstellar-travel/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Les Johnson, author of the new book A Traveler’s Guide to the Stars, talked to WIRED about solar sails and more ways to get farther into the final frontier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramin Skibba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building THE MOST practical Todolist with React and Websockets 🪄✨]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/novu/building-the-most-practical-todolist-with-react-and-websockets-18hd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/novu/building-the-most-practical-todolist-with-react-and-websockets-18hd"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T10:07:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #javascript #webdev #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevo David, novu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Habits Garden — A gamified habit tracker to achieve your goals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/habits-garden</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/habits-garden"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T07:48:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[免费虚拟机软件 VirtualBox 7.0 发布，距离上一个大版本发布已相隔 4 年]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43585</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/virtualbox-7-0/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T07:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VirtualBox 是一款著名的跨平台虚拟机软件，昨日（2022-10-10）正式发布 VirtualBox 7.0 版本，距离上一个大版本 6.0 发布已相隔 4 年。新版本带来了完全加密的虚拟机]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[用另一种方式执行「断舍离」]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76120</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76120"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T07:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[当我第一次接触「断舍离」这个概念的时候，不仅对它描绘的图景所震撼，而且深切认为这就是我想要的生活。于是我在家里翻箱倒柜的搜索可以丢弃物品，从没用的数据线到大件的废纸箱，只要是能扔的我都直接从家中扔了出去。
也许是一次性丢弃的东西过多，还没等到我开始审视剩下的东西要不要留下，家中有些东西就已经告急了，无奈又开始了买买买的旅程。当我检查购物订单，发现其中含有已经丢弃的物品，我才意识到出现了问题。例如有一次，我需要同时充电多个设备，需要多根数据线，但为了实现「断舍离」，只保留了一根。那时我发现，很多我所丢弃的东西不是不需要的，而是在扔东西那一刻我认为不需要。
仔细想想，这种丢完东西后，又重新买的行为不正是商家所乐意看到的吗？把这种观念作为生活的准则似乎是从另一个方面掉入了消费主义的陷阱。为此我重新审视、省察了「断舍离」这个概念和我所想象的生活，并重新制定了一套可行、节俭的规则。
谨慎购买物品
谨慎购买物品应该是我认为最能体现「断舍离」后生活的方法了。毕竟，我希望看到的是一个没有过多杂物和没用物品的家。既然我无法将所有东西都丢弃，那么就控制新增物品的数量。先对已有物品尽可能收纳，让空间看起来不那么杂乱，再对每个想买的东西进行衡量，如果不是必须的，那就对它说不。
当然，谨慎购买物品也要购买物品。例如：平时生活需要用的牙膏、毛巾等必需品直接买就可以了，买时尽可能货比三家，选择合适的价格和种类。真正应该谨慎购买的是那些看起来有大用，但实际到手可能不会使用的东西。
这里可以分享几个我自己的衡量方法作为参考：
谨慎购买「美好生活」
例如，当我在网上看到了一个洗碗机的广告，它不断的宣传购买洗碗机后解放双手的美好。如果按照宣传所描述的，我是可以购买后有更多的时间去干其他的事情。然而，我回顾日常生活后发现我平时并没有洗大量碗的需求，也就是说，在没看到这个广告前我是不会想象到它所描绘的「美好生活」，…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vuhe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Groovy vs Java: Connecting a PostgreSQL database with JDBC]]></title>
        <id>70221 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/groovy-vs-java-sql"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Groovy vs Java: Connecting a PostgreSQL database with JDBC
Chris Hermansen
Tue, 10/11/2022 - 03:00

            
Lately, I've been looking at how Groovy streamlines the slight clunkiness of Java. This article examines some differences between connecting to a PostgreSQL database using JDBC in Java versus Groovy.
Install Java and Groovy
Groovy is based on Java and requires a Java installation. Both a recent/decent version of Java and Groovy might be in your Linux distribution's repositories, or you can install Groovy by following these instructions. A nice alternative for Linux users is SDKMan, which provides multiple versions of Java, Groovy, and many other related tools. For this article, I'm using SDK's releases of:
Java version 11.0.12-open of OpenJDK 11
Groovy version 3.0.8
Back to the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hermansen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[因突发情况被困外地，怎样尽可能坐上正常航班离开？]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76106</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76106"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T06:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

设想这样一个情况吧：
你带着愉快的心情到了一个地方度假，结果在度假期间遭遇新毒株的新冠疫情爆发，全城宣布静默，城市道路、公共交通和出港港口全部封闭或停运。在配合社区每天的核酸检测和居家不出门同时，你也在仔细留意当地发布的相关信息 —— 十分幸运的是，尽管此刻的疫情还很严重，但当地已经宣布恢复机场运行，你似乎看到了一丝曙光，决定购买机票离开。
然而，事情似乎并没有你想象的这么简单。从恢复机场的商业化运行之后，到你真正坐上飞机离开这里的时间，却过去了一个月。那么这一个月里，到底发生了什么？
偶遇三亚疫情，与「幽灵航班」斗智斗勇
我和朋友在今年的 7 月 16 日回到三亚，开始为期一个月的旅居生活。然而半个月后，一起从崖州区爆发的境外输入疫情在短短几天内就席卷了整个三亚，然后迅速波及了整个海南岛内。受到疫情的影响，我和朋友只能决定提前结束旅居，在 8 月 5 日的晚上购买了 8 月 9 日从海口回广州的火车票，并决定在 8 月 6 日一早坐环岛高铁前往海口。
但计划总是赶不上变化。就在 8 月 6 日的凌晨 3 点 52 分，三亚发布发出通知，宣布全域进入静默状态。

自 2022 年 8 月 6 日凌晨 6 时起，全市实行临时性全域静态管理，除保障社会基本运行服务、疫情防控和紧急特殊情况外，全市范围限制人员流动，暂停城市公共交通。恢复时间另行通告。
原本 7 月最后一个周末还因为办音乐节而人流爆满的三亚后海主街，短短一周就变得萧条异常
好在 8 月 15 日之后，三亚宣布有序恢复凤凰国际机场国内客运航班商业化运行。这意味着，只要是符合…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>宛潼</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[基于CS的学习工作流构建思路]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76113</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76113"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T03:35:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[平时工作中往往会遇到新的知识点，这个时候需要我们快速学习并且进行最佳实践。往往是在真正学习了一段时间之后，才会发现有哪些地方可以优化，这样磨合出来的工作流才是最适合自己的。经过两年工作之余的学习后，我磨合出了以下学习工作流：

底层核心逻辑
一开始我学习新知识时会参考一些博客或者是视频，当我开始敲代码实践时往往会出现一些纰漏和错误，我开始意识到我参考的信息可能是错误的，毕竟发博客的门槛低，因此文章的可信度可能不高，于是我开始查阅一些相关的中文书籍。
中文书籍的确是比较全面且系统地讲解了知识点，但众所周知，技术更迭很迅速，又因为老美在 CS 方面一直都是灯塔，所以一般中文书籍里的内容会滞后于当前最新的知识，导致我跟着中文书籍实践会出现软件版本差异的问题。这时我开始意识到一手信息的重要性，有些中文书籍是翻译英文书籍的，一般翻译一本书也要一两年，这会导致信息传递的延迟，还有就是翻译的过程中信息会有损失。如果一本中文书籍不是翻译的呢，那么它肯定也是参考其他书籍的，参考的过程会带有对英文原著中语言和语义理解的偏差。
于是我就顺其自然地开始翻阅英文书籍。不得不说，整体英文书籍内容的质量是比中文书籍高的，一个原因是写英文书籍的作者更会写作，他们会用自己的话很详尽地解释一个知识点，而不是像一些中文书籍那样罗列知识点并且理所当然地以为读者能读懂而忽略一些细节的描述，还有一个原因就是知识很注重时效性，英文书籍的内容往往更新一点。后来随着学习的层层深入，以知识的时效性和完整性出发，我发现 源代码 > 官方文档 > 英文书籍 > 英文博客，最后我得出了一张 信息损失图

虽然一手信息很重要，但后面的 N 手信息并非一无是处，往往这 N 手资料里写了作者对源知识的转化——作者对知识基于某种逻辑的梳理（流程图、思维导图等）以及自己的一些理解（对源知识的抽象、类比、延伸到其他知识点），这些转化可以帮助我…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vacodwave</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[微信陪伴的九年间，我都用它做了什么？]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76096</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76096"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T02:03:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[如果说苹果发布会是每年一度的春晚，微信的间歇性更新就像不期而至的假期。在过去的十一年间，微信逐步从最初的简单样子一步步变迁为现在承载了许多功能和期待的国民软件。
而我作为一个非极客普通用户，在翻看朋友圈时蓦然发现这款软件自己也已经不知不觉得用了九年，发布了无数朋友圈内容和加入了许许多多的群聊。自己也从一个微信聊天使用者变成了公众号重度用户和创作者。不妨总结下过去这些年我是如何一步步从抗拒到全面使用微信的以及它带给了我日常生活哪些改变。
面朝屏幕的对话
毫无疑问，所有微信用户使用频率最高的一定是微信的基本功能：聊天。一对一或一对多，文字或语音。每个人都习惯了面对着屏幕表达自己。
加个微信
随着微信的普及，几乎没有朋友没有微信，以至于“加个微信”变成一个礼貌性和建立连接的标准动作。
我一开始并不理解为何微信会拿下偌大的市场，但过年回到老家后看到那么多中老年非QQ用户拿着微信发语音消息时，我才意识到它极大得拓宽了用户群体：“按住说话，松开发送” 简洁而易用。即便是我自己并不喜欢对面突如其来的数个60秒语音（希望微信语音能像子弹短信那样实现可以自动转为文字或者暂停播放的语音管理），但毕竟使用门槛大大降低了，而且简洁爽气的操作界面远远超过了当时花里胡哨的QQ。
所以几乎国内智能手机用户人均一个微信号时，加个微信，犹如一个登门入户的邀请，使得物理分离开之后，依旧保持了进一步交流的可能性，既有的情感更容易维系或加深。
当我们都拥有了一个便宜而高清的通讯渠道时，高昂的运营商资费带来的束缚瞬间被打破，许多亲人和朋友的联系变得频繁。当某个中秋和朋友们打着微信视频“云喝酒”，一起庆祝花好月圆夜时突然觉得科技的进步真好。如果哪一天能够启用Callkit（即像接听电话一样接听），微信电话或视频的体验应该会更好。
遇见陌生人
刚刚开始使用微信时的的朋友大多是熟人，群聊大多是家庭群，工作群，同学群。之后…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James_Tu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Physics of Smashing a Spacecraft Into an Asteroid]]></title>
        <id>633db9013099da4d4e0dd650</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-physics-of-smashing-a-spacecraft-into-an-asteroid/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NASA will soon release the results of its DART mission to find out whether crashing a probe into a space rock can deflect it. Here’s how they'll do the math.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhett Allain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 Now Offers Automatic Phishing Protection]]></title>
        <id>63374abad90aafbd66b0c6cb</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/windows-11-automatic-phishing-protection/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’re safer than ever—here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Nield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cities Need More Native Bees—Lots and Lots of Them]]></title>
        <id>633cbd4147233f8cddd753c7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cities-need-more-native-bees-lots-and-lots-of-adorable-bees/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These pollinators can help urban gardens grow. That will be critical for cooling cities as the planet warms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Remote Tech Workers Secretly Juggle Multiple Jobs]]></title>
        <id>6340bd5b7683076f6363ecac</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/remote-tech-workers-secret-multiple-jobs/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working from home makes it easier to take on several full-time posts. The extra cash is nice—but simultaneous Zoom meetings can be tricky.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Carnegie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Yourself If Your School Uses Surveillance Tech]]></title>
        <id>633c99e6f9498791684f713b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-protect-yourself-school-surveillance-tech-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colleges and K-12 campuses increasingly monitor student emails, social media, and more. Here’s how to secure your (or your child’s) privacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pia Ceres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hurricane Ian Destroyed Their Homes. Algorithms Sent Them Money]]></title>
        <id>6340bf58eb69b9d725e55ae2</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hurricane-ian-destroyed-homes-google-algorithms-sent-money/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's AI scanned satellite imagery to identify the worst-hit neighborhoods—helping direct aid to residents' phones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Yourself If Your School Uses Surveillance Tech]]></title>
        <id>633c99e6f9498791684f713b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-protect-yourself-school-surveillance-tech-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colleges and K-12 campuses increasingly monitor student emails, social media, and more. Here’s how to secure your (or your child’s) privacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pia Ceres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hurricane Ian Destroyed Their Homes. Algorithms Sent Them Money]]></title>
        <id>6340bf58eb69b9d725e55ae2</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hurricane-ian-destroyed-homes-google-algorithms-sent-money/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's AI scanned satellite imagery to identify the worst-hit neighborhoods—helping direct aid to residents' phones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildfire Smoke May Carry Deadly Fungi Long Distances]]></title>
        <id>633dc511058264dd3ee92ff8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/wildfire-smoke-may-carry-deadly-fungi-long-distances/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pathogens in soil are a danger to firefighters, but smoke may transport spores that cause valley fever and other infections into cities too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maryn McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Yourself If Your School Uses Surveillance Tech]]></title>
        <id>633c99e6f9498791684f713b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-protect-yourself-school-surveillance-tech-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colleges and K-12 campuses increasingly monitor student emails, social media, and more. Here’s how to secure your (or your child’s) privacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pia Ceres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[无门槛群晖 NAS 搭建指南]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/72672</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/72672"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T10:43:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[前段时间清理电脑，发现「坚果云」在电脑上缓存了 50GB 平时用不上的文件。在与技术人员沟通后，被告知自从 M1 芯片发布以来，「云桥模式」的接口就无法使用，缓存只能手动清理。于是萌生了自己搭建一个 NAS 服务器的想法。
什么是NAS

NAS (Network Attached Storage：网络附属存储) 是一种连接您家中或办公室网路的智慧储存装置。您可以将家人或同事的重要文件、珍贵的相片、影音收藏等档案储存于 NAS，仅需透过网页浏览器或手机应用程式，即可轻松存取档案并享有 NAS 提供的丰富服务。

NAS 也可以简单理解为：「不限速的个性化本地网盘」。
不知道你在日常生活中是否遇到过以下的情形：

电脑的储存空间不够用，想要使用文件，但不想把所有文件存在本地；
存在百度云盘的文件或视频，下载速度仅有 69KB/s；
急需从 OneDrive 下载一个文件，却发现 OneDrive 无法打开；
迅雷下载影片，进度超过 98% 之后下载速度只有 5KB/s；
无处安放的照片存在云相册，画质受到不可逆损伤；
MAC 内建备份功能「时间机器」无处备份个人数据；
无法忍受互联网大厂的隐私乱象；
团队协作交互讨论、修改、审批效率太低，大文件传输困难；

如果你在生活中遇到过以上痛点，这篇文章或许会给你提供一个解决思路。
如何选购 NAS
目前的 NAS 市场基本被群晖和威联通垄断，即便是采用 DIY 方案，也还是要使用黑群晖或黑威联通的系统（即破解版系统）。本文以本土化更好些的群晖NAS（Synology NAS）为例，介绍如何选购家用 NAS。
群晖桌上型较高阶NAS选型指南
「盘位」代表可以安装的硬盘数量，部分型号可以通过购买扩充装置的方法进行盘位扩展。
「双核和四核」表示可以同时运行的程序数量。
「2GB内存」代表程序运行的速度，部分型号可以进行扩展。但要注意，部分…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>白夜</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[:where :is CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mustapha/where-is-css-20nk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mustapha/where-is-css-20nk"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T08:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#css #webdev #beginners #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mustapha Aouas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[如何让特斯拉拥有 CarPlay？]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76097</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76097"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T07:38:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

我是特斯拉 Model 3 的用户，个人觉得特斯拉在大陆的导航和娱乐系统确实不太好用，当然可能也和我日常喜欢用高德导航、Spotify 听歌这些比较多有关系。相信很多特斯拉的用户也和我一样，非常希望能用上苹果的 CarPlay，但特斯拉的车机系统其实是 Linux 并且非常封闭，目前也不太存在破解和安装软件这种捷径的可能。
特斯拉 CarPlay
不过波兰的开发者 Michał Gapiński 前段时间给出了一个用树莓派的解决方法，实现了在特斯拉上使用 CarPlay。因为之前一直需要的两块树莓派的开发板，直到最近简化到了一个并且也简单稳定了不少，我也就做个教程和大家分享下。
准备工作
需要说一下，树莓派 4B 目前的价格依然比较高，整个过程也稍微有点麻烦，折腾的乐趣大于实际使用的意义，不太建议特意为这个去买树莓派，也不太建议不熟悉刷机的朋友尝试。
为了实现在特斯拉上使用 CarPlay 的效果，你需要准备：

树莓派 4B 开发板（需包含 SD 卡和读卡器）
HDMI 转 CSI-2 转接板
Micro HDMI to HDMI 连接线
车连易的 CarPlay 盒子
USB Type-C 数据线（用于刷机以及连接车供电）
一台电脑（用于给树莓派安装系统 Win Mac 都可以）
下载好系统 （版本：2022.38.1)

当然有些是可选的：比如树莓派的外壳和散热风扇，推荐选择塑料的外壳，因为金属的可能会屏蔽树莓派的 Wi-Fi 信号；如果想让特斯拉连接到树莓派的 Wi-Fi 的时候还能使用网络，则需要再购买一个 USB 4G…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>酱紫表</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defining an open source AI for the greater good]]></title>
        <id>70232 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/10/defining-open-source-ai"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defining an open source AI for the greater good
Stefano Maffulli
Mon, 10/10/2022 - 03:00

            
Artificial intelligence (AI) has become more prevalent in our daily lives. While AI systems may intend to offer users convenience, there have been numerous examples of automated tools getting it wrong, resulting in serious consequences. What's happening in the AI system that leads to erroneous and harmful conclusions? Probably a dramatic combo of bad AI combined with a lack of human oversight. How do we as a society prevent AI ethics fails?
The open source community has had, for well over 20 years, clear processes for dealing with errors ("bugs") in software. The Open Source Definition firmly establishes the rights of developers and the rights of users. There are frameworks, licenses, and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefano Maffulli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[不是你的怀旧助手：多亲 F22 Pro 两周体验]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76092</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76092"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T03:36:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[我的第一部手机是在去外地上初中时，从我妈那里淘汰下来的诺基亚 3100，之后是高中时用的诺基亚 5320XM。读中学时移动互联网才初露头角，5320XM 用 100 MB 流量的 EDGE 网套餐承载了我躲在宿舍床上的摸鱼时光，按键的漆也在一条条聊天短信里被磨掉。当时我的所有朋友都在用全拼打字，而我为了提高速度，把手指挪动更少的笔划输入法练得飞快。

后来我换了 Android 机器，在还有不少想去把玩的手机没试过时，迎来了 Symbian 与诺基亚的衰落，送走了滑盖、旋盖、全键盘。移动互联网改变了我们使用手机的习惯，也同样改变手机的形态——所以当我发现还有厂商在出实体数字键盘的智能机时，就一直想找个机会试试。赶上多亲 F22 Pro 新品发布，我付了款，等过了两周的疫情，终于把它拿到了手。
这份喜悦在到手的一小时内烟消云散。

青涩但合格的硬件设计
多亲 F22 Pro 的设计和前代的 F21 Pro 其实有很多不同。
除了处理器从 MT6761 / 虎贲 T310 一下跃升到 MTK G85 以外（虽然还是挺弱的），比较显眼的就是尺寸变化。屏幕从此前的 2.8 英寸 480*640 升级到了 3.5 英寸 640*960，这样的参数现在看来可能并不出色，但它和 iPhone 4 的那块 Retina 细腻程度其实一致，文字显示效果不错。而且由于用了几天只有三英寸的 Jelly 2，这块屏幕甚至让我有种换上大屏手机的错觉。

机身和之前的多亲手机一致，依然是与功能机一样的瘦长手感，再加上与 iPhone 4 一样的屏幕和圆形的导航键，整个手机颇有一种当年 iPhone 配上 Typo 键盘壳的感觉。手机的宽度也因为屏幕增大从 53 mm 扩展到 58 mm，和现在流行的尺寸相比，仍然很容易上手。
按键方面，F22 Pro 抛弃了上代采用的孤岛式按键，转向了一体式的按键设计…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>北鸮</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turn around your Git mistakes in 17 ways]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/smitterhane/turn-around-your-git-mistakes-in-17-ways-2mn1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/smitterhane/turn-around-your-git-mistakes-in-17-ways-2mn1"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T12:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#git #productivity #github #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Smitter hane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why It’s the Age of the Investor-Entrepreneur]]></title>
        <id>633f414181222da12cb0d9f1</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/investor-entrepreneur/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plural's Taavet Hinrikus says early-stage VC funds need to set a founder to catch a founder.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Armstrong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe’s Plan to Beat Silicon Valley at Its Own Game]]></title>
        <id>633f415585e7a4cc2f80227b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/europe-beat-silicon-valley-startups/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WIRED spoke with Skype cofounder Niklas Zennström about why the burgeoning European startup scene is poised to lead the technological revolution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Armstrong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🤖️ 如何逐步关闭 MIUI 无处不在的广告]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76076</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76076"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T02:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[如果你喜欢我的文章，希望点赞👍 收藏 📁 评论 💬 三连支持一下，谢谢你，这对我真的很重要！

最近需要给长辈置换一下手机，在有限的预算内，经过多次比较发现还是小米的硬件配置更好一些，最后也是下单了小米。
在 2022 年，Android 系统对手机权限的进一步限制，一些过往的卡顿问题都得到了一定的解决。但是在国内的定制版 Android 机上，和原生 Android 系统还是多了一些特色的东西：

无处不在的系统级广告，诱导用户点击/误触，从而去跳转/下载 APP
“不小心下载” 的 APP，占用宝贵的内存/硬盘资源，拖慢手机速度
国内特色的航母级 APP，一个 APP 占几个 G 的硬盘，有些小而美的应用甚至几十个 G

上面的三个问题中，前两个可以通过一定的努力解决大部分，第三个大家都没得选只能硬抗。本文就是聚焦于「关闭 MIUI 无处不在的广告」这个话题的。

虽然 MIUI 一直有 ADUI 的称呼，但是个人身处这个行业也能表示理解：
小米把硬件上的利润压到了最低，赚不到钱就要从其他路子上想办法，只能不停的“加点儿广告怎么了”

废话不多说，我们直接开始。

本文成文于 2022.09，使用的是 MIUI 13.0.4 版本，随着时间的推移，其它版本 MIUI 可能有操作不一致的情况，这点需要读者注意。

一、通过常规手段关闭广告推送
1.1 关闭系统广告
MIUI 的许多内置应用（例如 天气、万年历、音乐）和系统级页面（例如桌面文件夹）上都会推送一些贴片广告，诱导用户观看和点击。
可能用户反馈过于激烈，2019 年年末某个版本更新中，新增了「一键关闭系统广告」的功能。这个开关也很好找，我们直接进入「设置」，然后在搜索框里输入「系统广告」，然后点击进入新页面，把「系统工具广告」这个开关关上即可。
我们可以通过「查看涉及应用列表」查看涉及的 APP，然后去相关…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>卤蛋实验室</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[通过Tweetdeck打造属于自己的内容时间线]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76019</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76019"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T02:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[相信对于很多小伙伴来说，Twitter并非单纯是一个“社交”平台，而是“信息获取”平台。通过追踪各类名人、机构的账号来了解所关注领域的最新动向。比如最近火热的NFT、Web3.0社区中就有大量的意见领袖在Twitter发声。
然而从获取信息效率的视角来看，常规Twitter浏览界面并不是特别友好，时间线上有着各类广告，同时经常用着用着就发现自己迷失在几十个选项卡和搜索结果页中。如果你遇到过类似问题，并希望提高在Twitter获取信息的效率，我会强烈推荐Tweetdeck这个功能。
Tweetdeck是Twitter官方提供的在线工具，有模块化，高度自定义化的浏览界面，不仅适合专业的Twitter运营人员工作使用，也非常适合个人用户来改造优化自己的信息时间线。通过对比图片，可以很清楚的看到两种模式的差异。Tweetdeck可以在设置中选择 黑/白 两种显示模式，我个人更喜欢黑暗模式，看起来更轻松。
4K显示器下的twitter常规界面，大量留白非常浪费空间4K显示器下的tweetdeck界面
 
基础介绍
Tweetdeck和常规界面相比最重要的功能主要是3点：自动刷新、多列显示和自定义模块。自动刷新不需要过多解释，节省频繁刷新的操作和时间。自定义模块可以定制每一列种显示的内容，例如：

我想单独查看Elon Musk的所有推特或者他直发的内容。 - 单用户模式
我希望把多个账号归为一个主题，单独浏览，如：NBA球星们、实时股市新闻、NFT相关资讯。 - 清单模式
我想追踪网友对正在发生的热点事件的评论，如：WWDC大会、俄乌冲突事件等 - 搜索模式

多列显示则大幅度提升了屏幕利用率，让我们可以同时间追踪上述这些不同的主题。

上图是我最近使用Tweetdeck的截图，我通过Vivaldi浏览器“垂直平铺”功能在右边放置了Tesla AI Day的视频直播，在左边放置了Tweetdeck，并添加了：“tesla ai day”搜索结果列、“tesla bot”搜索结果列、Elon的个人内容列，和常用的市场资讯列。
 
模块选择
在Tweetdeck中，可以选择添加多种不同的模块，其中包含，
内容类模块：单用户模式、搜索模式、清单模式、正在流行内容等
功能类模块：通知、站内信、@我的、已预约内容等
我并没有做账户运营的需求，因此最常使用的还是：搜索结果、单个用户、多用户清单这几个内容类模块。
可添加模块截图
 
搜索模式：
显示关键词搜索结果配合自动刷新功能，达成“直播”的效果。并且可以通过设置条件对搜索结果进一步筛选，可设置条件包含：

按推文类型过滤：例如包含图片、视频、GIF等的推文；或者是否显示“转发”内容。
筛选内容的发布时间范围，最小单位可以精确到半个小时。
按照推文语言类型筛选，例如：中文、英文、日语等。
筛选推文发布者：选择特定的单个用户或者一组用户的搜索结果。
内容互动情况：显示至少有多少点赞、转发或评论的内容。

 
单用户模式 & 多用户清单：
这2个模式本质差别就是关注用户的多少，选定关注范围后的筛选条件选项完全一致。在这2个模块中，同样可以通过设置筛选条件，包含：

按推文类型过滤：例如包含图片、视频、GIF等的推文；或者是否显示“转发”内容。
关键词过滤：显示或排除包含指定关键词的内容。
用户筛选：由指定用户发布的内容 或 @特定用户的内容。

在Tweetdeck追踪的，不管是单用户还是清单，并不要求是关注的账户。这点非常贴心，也帮助我区分不同使用场景，我把大量“新闻资讯”类账号从关注列表中去除，放在Tweetdeck清单中，日常在手机上浏览就不会被刷屏，而更关注轻松的内容，坐在电脑前则可以追踪查看这些庞杂的资讯。
在Tweetdeck创建的清单可以选择设置为公开或者私有列表，同时这个列表也会同步到常规界面左侧的列表按钮中。

 
模块设置：
这几个内容模块中都可以单独设置“媒体展示尺寸大小”，可以大体理解为模块中每一条内容的高度。以及是否通过“声音”或者“桌面通知”的形式发送通知，提示关注的内容有更新。

Tweetdeck是简单，但又很强大的工具，给我带来了很多的便利，也希望分享给大家，打造适合自己的内容模块。
 
PS：
Tweetdeck访问地址：https://tweetdeck.twitter.com
今年Twitter官方下架了Tweetdeck的桌面客户端软件，仅提供网页版本，如果想在电脑上安装独立客户端可以使用Tweeten，有Windows和Mac版本，并且基于Tweetdeck提供了更多的功能。
Tweeten部分功能展示
题图源自：Brett Jordan on Unsplash
更多内容欢迎访问我的个人博客：「假设检验」]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>johnbens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made 1,000x faster TypeScript Validator Library]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/samchon/typescript-json-is-10-1000x-times-faster-than-zod-and-io-ts-8n6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/samchon/typescript-json-is-10-1000x-times-faster-than-zod-and-io-ts-8n6"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T16:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #typescript #opensource #benchmark]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeongho Nam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paranoia Threatens to Upend Professional Chess]]></title>
        <id>633f2a90058264dd3ee9304a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/magnus-carlsen-hans-niemann-cheating-chess-fide/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Magnus Carlsen–Hans Niemann cheating scandal points to abuses and suspicion at the highest levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg Keener</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Hackers Minted $569M in Crypto—Then It Got Complicated]]></title>
        <id>634019df81222da12cb0da05</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/binance-hackers-minted-569-million/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: The US warns of a mysterious military contractor breach, a "poisoned" version of the Tor Browser is tracking Chinese users, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman, Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why ‘Carbon Emissions’ Are Now ‘Climate Pollution’]]></title>
        <id>633b185ffe6f3e53574722ab</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/why-carbon-emissions-are-now-climate-pollution/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[California activists fought to frame climate change as an air quality problem. Now it’s federal law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in Tel Aviv]]></title>
        <id>633dee8185e7a4cc2f802274</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-in-tel-aviv-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Home to Silicon Wadi and a long-running streak of mega-money exits, the Tel Aviv tech scene leads with innovative applications of robotics, AI and medtech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Armstrong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in Amsterdam]]></title>
        <id>633def4820105ba57106995f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-amsterdam-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amsterdam continues to punch well above its weight, combining tech powerhouse status with being one of the most livable cities on the continent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gian M. Volpicelli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in Helsinki]]></title>
        <id>633ded7447233f8cddd753e7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-in-helsinki-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a small city, but investment in its startups is growing apace, thanks to an international mindset and a sturdy support system for local founders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in Dublin]]></title>
        <id>633debe681222da12cb0d9a1</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-in-dublin-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The city is celebrating more local talent than ever, as being the only English-speaking country in Europe tempts new founders and drives outside investment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Makes a Champagne Vintage Great? Ask a Deep Learning Model]]></title>
        <id>6340b2c1d01ed05afa60f88b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/what-makes-a-champagne-vintage-great-ask-a-deep-learning-model/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bollinger is data mining its meticulous records to predict vintage years and weather the challenges of climate change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Barber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Uber Data Breach Conviction Shows Security Execs What Not to Do]]></title>
        <id>633ee35881222da12cb0d9a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/uber-joe-sullivan-conviction/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T19:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Uber security chief Joe Sullivan’s conviction is a rare criminal consequence for an executive’s handling of a hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden’s Privacy Order Slaps a Band-Aid on the EU-US Data Crisis]]></title>
        <id>634078763099da4d4e0dd65d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/biden-eu-us-data-privacy-executive-order/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T19:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new executive order tries to reassure Europeans that their data is safe on US soil, despite government surveillance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Morgan Meaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Turned My Startup Into Open-Source]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nevodavid/i-turned-my-startup-into-open-source-4efh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nevodavid/i-turned-my-startup-into-open-source-4efh"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T18:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #programming #webdev #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevo David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Deepfake Bruce Willis Doing in My Metaverse?]]></title>
        <id>633f03e57e8d589e28665ae3</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/plaintext-bruce-willis-deepfake-metaverse/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: The future as seen from 1991, Google fights Apple for your wrist, and nuclear war.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Deepfake Bruce Willis Doing in My Metaverse?]]></title>
        <id>633f03e57e8d589e28665ae3</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/plaintext-bruce-willis-deepfake-metaverse/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: The future as seen from 1991, Google fights Apple for your wrist, and nuclear war.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Far Would You Have to Tunnel Underground to Lose 20 Pounds?]]></title>
        <id>632869f7c9bb1af7ef249857</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-far-would-you-have-to-tunnel-underground-to-lose-20-pounds/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In What If? 2, Randall Munroe explains that evading gravity can reduce your weight—but let’s do the math to see how far you have to go.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhett Allain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Async & Await]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maximization/understanding-async-await-22o6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maximization/understanding-async-await-22o6"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T12:28:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #beginners #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maxim Orlov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Says It Has Busted More Than 400 Login-Stealing Apps This Year]]></title>
        <id>633dce494bb7933eb618317d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/meta-facebook-login-stealing-android-ios-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company plans to alert 1 million Facebook users that their account credentials may have been compromised by malicious software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in Barcelona]]></title>
        <id>633de9fd47233f8cddd753e5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-in-barcelona-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The city is a global hub for investors, startups, and larger companies seeking sunnier climes and a business-friendly atmosphere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Armstrong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in Stockholm]]></title>
        <id>633dea4b92468d5a8855add5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-in-stockholm-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A city famed for friendliness also has a booming startup scene—and that network of founders supporting founders has led to a slew of firms taking the lead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Christian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in Lisbon]]></title>
        <id>633dea32f9498791684f71d8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-in-lisbon-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The reinvention of the Portuguese capital is picking up speed, as a slew of government incentives is making it an attractive base for new arrivals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joao Medeiros</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Time to Treat Housing Insecurity as a Health Risk]]></title>
        <id>633faa5d81222da12cb0d9ff</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cancer-housing-deprivation/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study shows that cancer patients in precarious living situations are twice as likely to die from their illness, underscoring the harms of unstable housing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kasra Zarei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fight to Cut Off the Crypto Fueling Russia's Ukraine Invasion]]></title>
        <id>633d947e4bb7933eb6183179</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/russia-ukraine-cryptocurrency-funding/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain investigators have uncovered at least $4 million—and counting—in cryptocurrency donations to Russia’s violent militia groups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 GitHub Repositories to Contribute for Hacktoberfest 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/atapas/15-github-repositories-to-contribute-for-hacktoberfest-2022-215d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/atapas/15-github-repositories-to-contribute-for-hacktoberfest-2022-215d"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T09:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#opensource #hacktoberfest #webdev #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapas Adhikary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Rethinks the Philosophy of the Facebook Feed]]></title>
        <id>633e13295ec45110c69a14b5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/meta-rethinks-facebook-news-feed/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WIRED spoke with the head of Facebook about competition from TikTok and his theory that algorithms can enhance our personal relationships.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are You Sure You Know What Revenge Porn Is?]]></title>
        <id>633ca4055a49457c993f5331</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/revenge-porn-platforms-grindr-queerness/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forty-eight states have passed protections against revenge porn—but their narrow definition of such content leaves many people exposed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Gilden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Can’t You Tickle Yourself? Neuroscientists Unravel the Mystery]]></title>
        <id>6332304b00704d14b5ffba02</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/neuroscientists-unravel-the-mystery-of-why-you-cant-tickle-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Playfulness and tickling aren’t always considered “serious” subjects, but a new study shows how they can address key questions about the brain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max G. Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awesome tools for Open Source Contribution]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-tools-for-open-source-contribution-36cm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-tools-for-open-source-contribution-36cm"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T11:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#opensource #beginners #javascript #react]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Vishwakarma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are the 100 Hottest Startups in Europe in 2022]]></title>
        <id>633de90f669c7202654d7d43</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/100-hottest-startups-europe-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Entrepreneurs across the continent are embracing new ways of working—and there’s a perceptible shift in what startups choose to focus on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Startups in London]]></title>
        <id>633de7e981222da12cb0d99e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hottest-startups-in-london-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fallout from Brexit isn’t in the rearview mirror just yet, but the UK capital is forging ahead regardless.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joao Medeiros</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Is Totally Wrong About Population Collapse]]></title>
        <id>633e0b514bb7933eb618318b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-population-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla’s outspoken CEO thinks the biggest threat facing the planet is people not having enough babies. Demographers disagree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swatted: A Shooting Hoax Spree Is Terrorizing Schools Across the US]]></title>
        <id>633da05620105ba571069956</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/swatting-schools-us-september-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sixteen states collectively suffered more than 90 false reports of school shooters during three weeks in September—and many appear to be connected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruv Mehrotra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Needs to Recognize Intimate Privacy as a Civil Right]]></title>
        <id>6317a57979f10149f7bb9f4a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/privacy-intimacy-civil-rights-danielle-citron/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital privacy invasion isn’t just a consumer protection issue. It’s inextricably linked to equality, with urgent implications for women and minorities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danielle Keats Citron</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Change your old methods for writing a JavaScript Code - Shorthand's for JavaScript Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devsimc/change-your-old-methods-for-writing-a-javascript-code-shorthands-for-javascript-code-54hp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devsimc/change-your-old-methods-for-writing-a-javascript-code-shorthands-for-javascript-code-54hp"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T12:51:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #beginners #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>simc dev CSM®</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The FCC's Rules on Space Junk Just Got Stricter]]></title>
        <id>633764fba546819a4885f46f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-fccs-rules-on-space-junk-just-got-stricter/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new and contentious five-year limit for getting rid of dead satellites could slow the growing orbital litter problem—if people actually abide by it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramin Skibba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slides 6 — Static website generator, create animated websites easily]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/slides-6</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/slides-6"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T07:36:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New?
Everything about Slides is new with this release: the online app, design, functionality, page organization, settings, and more.

- Brand new look and feel Editor, for convenience and speed of development.
- Set your colors in the new Colors tab, which allows you to add more color classes.
- Seamlessly integrate useful services in Integration tab to all your pages.
- Directly add Examples to your Page Template.
- 75 new Slides have been added. More to come!
- 5 new templates have been added with ability to add Slides and Examples to Templates. More to come!
- Addition of a Scroll Magnetic to the list of Effects, where slides stick to the top of the screen.
- Your projects can be seamlessly hosted to static.app.
- Projects and Pages views are eliminated and integrated into the Editor for quick access.
- The new Code Editor enables full-screen viewing and quick switching between all of your slides and panels.
- Custom Fonts styles are sync through all your projects.
- Device Preview mode was added to help you quickly adapt your page to various screens.
- New font size classes give you more control over your fonts.
- SVG connects as a separate file, improving the look and loading time of the source code.
- And more… see the changelog for details. 🤗

💡 Our Solution
Slides is an online app that helps you create static websites. It fits all kinds of projects thanks to customizable and ready-made modules and templates.

🤯 So simple?
Don’t believe it? Watch this short video.

📝 Suggestions
I really hope you like it. We’re adding more features and improvements every day.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn this before React]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jps27cse/learn-this-before-react-4hpl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jps27cse/learn-this-before-react-4hpl"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T04:47:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #javascript #webdev #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Pritom Soren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Created a File Sharing Website using Simple JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/varshithvhegde/how-i-created-a-file-sharing-website-using-simple-javascript-355g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/varshithvhegde/how-i-created-a-file-sharing-website-using-simple-javascript-355g"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T04:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#html #javascript #css #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Varshith V Hegde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16 Libraries You Should Know as a React Developer 💯🔥]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/madza/16-libraries-you-should-know-as-a-react-developer-4f1k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/madza/16-libraries-you-should-know-as-a-react-developer-4f1k"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T15:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #coding #react #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Madza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamers Use Playlists to Control the Music Industry]]></title>
        <id>6320aa3940fe1e8870aa3a85</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/spotify-streaming-playlists-music/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recorded music market is regaining its former hourglass shape—this time with platforms like Spotify at the center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Giblin, Cory Doctorow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opendoor’s iBuyer Model Is a Canary in the Economic Coal Mine]]></title>
        <id>633b79b8b1070500c040c678</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/opendoor-ibuyers-housing-market/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company is losing huge sums of money on cookie-cutter homes—suggesting a fundamental weakness in the US housing market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden's AI Bill of Rights Is Toothless Against Big Tech]]></title>
        <id>6335f8bac554667379f2da78</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/bidens-ai-bill-of-rights-is-toothless-against-big-tech/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The draft's tenets include allowing citizens to opt out of algorithmic decisionmaking, which could reshape federal government—but not the private sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khari Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing a secure API]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vaultree/designing-a-secure-api-4059</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vaultree/designing-a-secure-api-4059"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T04:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#beginners #api #design #security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Aravena, Vaultree</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s Half-Baked Robot Is a Clunky First Step]]></title>
        <id>633b0db69149b25103844a45</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musks-half-baked-robot-is-a-clunky-first-step/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T20:56:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla’s Optimus robot did not dazzle robotics experts and can’t yet walk. But if the project delivers, it could give the company an edge in manufacturing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The High Cost of Living Your Life Online]]></title>
        <id>6336feb9a546819a4885f45d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/privacy-psychology-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Constantly posting content on social media can erode your privacy—and sense of self.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thor Benson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tremor - Free React Library for Dashboards]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sm0ke/tremor-free-react-library-for-dashboards-3gm9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sm0ke/tremor-free-react-library-for-dashboards-3gm9"/>
        <updated>2022-10-02T17:42:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #opensource #dashboards]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sm0ke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Cool HTML Elements Nobody Uses]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/7-cool-html-elements-nobody-uses-330c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/7-cool-html-elements-nobody-uses-330c"/>
        <updated>2022-10-02T04:44:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #html #javascript #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapajyoti Bose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktoberfest is here — and this is the lowdown]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devteam/hacktoberfest-is-here-and-this-is-the-lowdown-3d76</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devteam/hacktoberfest-is-here-and-this-is-the-lowdown-3d76"/>
        <updated>2022-10-01T15:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#hacktoberfest #meta #opensource #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Halpern, The DEV Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made an admin dashboard for React using Typescript! Use it for free!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fredy/i-made-an-admin-dashboard-for-react-using-typescript-use-it-for-free-49fh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fredy/i-made-an-admin-dashboard-for-react-using-typescript-use-it-for-free-49fh"/>
        <updated>2022-10-01T13:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#showdev #typescript #webdev #react]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fredy Andrei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Exchange Server Has a Zero-Day Problem]]></title>
        <id>63373e41d90aafbd66b0c6ca</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/microsoft-exchange-zero-day-cia-spies-security-roundup/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: CIA failures allegedly got US informants killed, a former NSA worker is charged under the Espionage Act, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman, Dhruv Mehrotra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Challenge of Cracking Iran’s Internet Blockade]]></title>
        <id>633715a5010e2be68af5d47e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/subvert-iran-internet-blackout/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T21:16:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People around the world are rallying to subvert Iran's internet shutdown, but actually pulling it off is proving difficult and risky.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go Update iOS, Chrome, and HP Computers to Fix Serious Flaws]]></title>
        <id>63363df7af6115289c0e5f70</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ios-chrome-hp-whatsapp-critical-update-september/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: WhatsApp plugs holes that could be used for remote execution attacks, Microsoft patches a zero-day vulnerability, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate O'Flaherty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Matrix Update Patches Serious End-to-End Encryption Flaws]]></title>
        <id>63349aecc554667379f2d9f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/matrix-patches-vulnerabilities-that-completely-subvert-e2ee-guarantees/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The messenger protocol had gained popularity for its robust security, but vulnerabilities allowed attackers to decrypt messages and impersonate users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin, Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tech communities you should join! (online and in person)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/juliafmorgado/tech-communities-you-should-join-online-and-in-person-4nba</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/juliafmorgado/tech-communities-you-should-join-online-and-in-person-4nba"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T14:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#techtalks #webdev #community #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julia Furst Morgado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are You a Victim of Crypto Crime? Good Luck Getting Help]]></title>
        <id>632b64c600704d14b5ffb9a3</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cryptocurrency-cybercrime-law-enforcement/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Local law enforcement isn’t ready to deal with this new type of fraud, even with shady scams on the rise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Rizzo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mystery Hackers Are ‘Hyperjacking’ Targets for Insidious Spying]]></title>
        <id>633458ef995b6da54b57f057</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hyperjacking-vmware-mandiant/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For decades, security researchers warned about techniques for hijacking virtualization software. Now one group has put them into practice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How trigger browser to make a PDF from HTML using window.print()]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/climentea/simple-way-to-generate-pdf-from-html-21mh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/climentea/simple-way-to-generate-pdf-from-html-21mh"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T11:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alin Climente</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are your git aliases?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/imjoseangel/what-are-your-git-aliases-43om</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/imjoseangel/what-are-your-git-aliases-43om"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T20:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#git #beginners #tutorial #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Angel Munoz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let me understand how JavaScript works under the hood]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/inancakduvan/let-me-understand-how-javascript-works-under-the-hood-3ibf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/inancakduvan/let-me-understand-how-javascript-works-under-the-hood-3ibf"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T12:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>İnanç Akduvan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tech Companies Are Reconsidering an Old Enemy]]></title>
        <id>632db7bff2203b5586fac00d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/friction-social-media-moderation/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody likes being asked to wait, but recent political history has shown that a completely frictionless internet has its own dangers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yasmin Green</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Love Twitter Bots and I Cannot Lie]]></title>
        <id>632aefbdc9bb1af7ef249866</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/bots-twitter-art-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t judge a bot by the troll farms—some make the internet a weirder and more wonderful place.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caroline Sinders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Kanban board with Node.js, React and Websockets 📝 ✨]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/novu/building-a-beautiful-kanban-board-with-nodejs-react-and-websockets-39dk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/novu/building-a-beautiful-kanban-board-with-nodejs-react-and-websockets-39dk"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T10:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #webdev #javascript #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevo David, novu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[0ctf2022 hessian-only-jdk writeup jdk原生链]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11732</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11732"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T08:51:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[0ctf2022 hessian-only-jdk writeup jdk原生链]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[警惕破解软件！APS 窃密木马已感染万余台设备]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11740</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11740"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[警惕破解软件！APS 窃密木马已感染万余台设备]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API安全漏洞靶场crapi的基本介绍与解题思路]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11734</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11734"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T08:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[API安全漏洞靶场crapi的基本介绍与解题思路]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Faster Programmer]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marcinwosinek/how-to-become-a-faster-programmer-hp9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marcinwosinek/how-to-become-a-faster-programmer-hp9"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T05:46:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcin Wosinek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Unlikely Cure for Burnout? A Second Job]]></title>
        <id>63221a4d036b54662b5104d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/overemployment-work/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Overemployment” sounds like more of the same old grind, but its underlying philosophy is critical of work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fadeke Adegbuyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[某json 1.2.80 漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11727</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11727"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T08:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[某json 1.2.80 漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[关于HTTP Request Smuggling（HTTP请求夹带）的二三事]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11728</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11728"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T06:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[关于HTTP Request Smuggling（HTTP请求夹带）的二三事]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Things to Consider When Working On a Personal Project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maxr96/7-things-to-consider-when-working-on-a-personal-project-78d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maxr96/7-things-to-consider-when-working-on-a-personal-project-78d"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T22:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#beginners #programming #career #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Dev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Dear Unicorn Friend is Going on Vacation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devteam/our-dear-unicorn-friend-is-going-on-vacation-idm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devteam/our-dear-unicorn-friend-is-going-on-vacation-idm"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T19:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#meta #design #ux]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Halpern, The DEV Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web workers cheatsheet & 4 other webdev tips you may want to know 🚀]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mustapha/5-webdev-tips-you-may-want-to-know-2-41e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mustapha/5-webdev-tips-you-may-want-to-know-2-41e"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T13:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #css #html #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mustapha Aouas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Therapy Is Broken]]></title>
        <id>6328a9f4d884b4dcc941652d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/therapy-broken-mental-health-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone is telling one another to “get help,” but few acknowledge that the practice is often flawed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eleanor Cummins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Growing Old Online]]></title>
        <id>632a559feecde8c117e7f4f0</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/growing-old-online/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Millennials, the first generation to be online as kids, are starting to feel like we’ve aged out. Is there a way to age gracefully on the internet?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helena Fitzgerald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 HTML Tags for SEO🔍]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sampadsarker/10-html-tags-for-seo-9ib</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sampadsarker/10-html-tags-for-seo-9ib"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T06:46:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#html #seo #searchengine #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sampad Sarker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continue Using .env Files As Usual.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wiseai/continue-using-env-files-as-usual-2am5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wiseai/continue-using-env-files-as-usual-2am5"/>
        <updated>2022-09-24T13:46:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #node]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahmoud Harmouch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Local Storage Explained!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dboatengx/javascript-local-storage-explained-1di6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dboatengx/javascript-local-storage-explained-1di6"/>
        <updated>2022-09-24T09:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #beginners #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boateng Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quiet Quitting is About Loyalty]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codenameone/quiet-quitting-is-about-loyalty-1d6m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codenameone/quiet-quitting-is-about-loyalty-1d6m"/>
        <updated>2022-09-24T09:23:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#watercooler #culture #career]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shai Almog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[某开源堡垒机历史漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11721</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11721"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T15:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[某开源堡垒机历史漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘Surveillance Solutionism’ of Putting Cameras in NYC Subways]]></title>
        <id>632b3054d884b4dcc941655d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-surveillance-solutionism-of-putting-cameras-in-nyc-subways/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When “if you see something, say something” becomes “we see everything,” everyone loses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Fox Cahn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Awesome Notion Templates for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/surajondev/free-awesome-notion-templates-for-developers-43mh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/surajondev/free-awesome-notion-templates-for-developers-43mh"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T11:34:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #beginners #react]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Vishwakarma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Database GUIs in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/janproch/database-guis-in-javascript-2dpb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/janproch/database-guis-in-javascript-2dpb"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T10:27:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#database #sql #node #javascript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jan Prochazka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Your Productivity: Best Software For Dev Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jamieswift90/boost-your-productivity-best-software-for-dev-teams-476g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jamieswift90/boost-your-productivity-best-software-for-dev-teams-476g"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T08:24:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #programming #productivity #devops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Swift</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System Design: Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/system-design-netflix-3d9g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/system-design-netflix-3d9g"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T02:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#distributedsystems #architecture #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karan Pratap Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System Design: Twitter]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/system-design-twitter-865</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/system-design-twitter-865"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T02:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#distributedsystems #architecture #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karan Pratap Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-33980命令执行漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11723</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11723"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T15:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-33980命令执行漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[从前端代码审计挖掘未授权进入后台到文件上传拿下某色情网站]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11729</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11729"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T15:52:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[从前端代码审计挖掘未授权进入后台到文件上传拿下某色情网站]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dll劫持注入从原理到白加黑漏洞利用]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11711</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11711"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T15:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dll劫持注入从原理到白加黑漏洞利用]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Dangerous Meme in US Politics Is Over a Century Old]]></title>
        <id>6328bee136c33c0247a2f0ab</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/america-first-meme-politics/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many associate the “America First” movement with Trump, but its origins—and rebirth—are more complicated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED Ideas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System Design: WhatsApp]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/system-design-whatsapp-fld</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/system-design-whatsapp-fld"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T05:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#distributedsystems #architecture #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karan Pratap Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I'll teach you 7 Array methods. (with animations!)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fredysandoval/ill-teach-you-7-array-methods-with-animations-549c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fredysandoval/ill-teach-you-7-array-methods-with-animations-549c"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T21:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #array #beginners #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fredy Sandoval</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[对writeObject流程动点手脚]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11720</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11720"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T15:59:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[对writeObject流程动点手脚]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[关于"linux capability"的两个特殊案例]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11716</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11716"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T15:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[关于"linux capability"的两个特殊案例]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GenieACS CVE-2021-46704认证前RCE漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11722</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11722"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T15:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GenieACS CVE-2021-46704认证前RCE漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Games, Mysteries, and the Lure of QAnon]]></title>
        <id>63288cb640fe1e8870aa3b0e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/qanon-games-alternate-reality-conspiracy-theories/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What do puzzles, video games, and conspiracy theories have in common?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Hon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Every Blogger Should Save These 10 Insanely Useful Websites 👇]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hr21don/every-blogger-should-save-these-10-insanely-useful-websites-44ad</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hr21don/every-blogger-should-save-these-10-insanely-useful-websites-44ad"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T09:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#productivity #programming #webdev #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helitha Rupasinghe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Using .env Files Now!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gregorygaines/stop-using-env-files-now-kp0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gregorygaines/stop-using-env-files-now-kp0"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T21:04:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #node #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Gaines</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[goby指纹提取与yara逆向.md]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11701</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11701"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T15:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[goby指纹提取与yara逆向.md]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[记一次较为详细的某CMS代码审计]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11714</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11714"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T15:53:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[记一次较为详细的某CMS代码审计]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making a fast website is SUPER EASY 😏]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/enterspeed/making-a-fast-website-is-super-easy-9lb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/enterspeed/making-a-fast-website-is-super-easy-9lb"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T07:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #performance #programming #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kasper Andreassen, Enterspeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Figma Alternatives For A Blazingly Fast Increase In Your Productivity.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wiseai/9-figma-alternatives-for-a-blazingly-fast-increase-in-your-productivity-3g40</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wiseai/9-figma-alternatives-for-a-blazingly-fast-increase-in-your-productivity-3g40"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T07:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#design #uiweekly #productivity #ux]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahmoud Harmouch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Best UI Component Libraries/Frameworks in 2022 for Frontend Developers🔥]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aviyel/top-9-best-ui-component-librariesframeworks-in-2022-for-frontend-developers-b48</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aviyel/top-9-best-ui-component-librariesframeworks-in-2022-for-frontend-developers-b48"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T07:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #css #tailwindcss #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pramit Marattha, Aviyel Inc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop writing API functions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/saeedmosavat/stop-writing-api-functions-3693</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/saeedmosavat/stop-writing-api-functions-3693"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T23:22:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #codequality #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saeed Mosavat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>