<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-11-17T10:41:10.161Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-11-17T10:41:10.161Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[See how far Pokémon Go creator Niantic’s AR gaming ambitions have come]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/17/23463988/niantic-qualcomm-augmented-reality-glasses-ar2-gen-1-processor-platform-snapdragon-spaces</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/17/23463988/niantic-qualcomm-augmented-reality-glasses-ar2-gen-1-processor-platform-snapdragon-spaces"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T10:38:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pokémon Go developer Niantic has unveiled its latest tech demo showing off what it thinks could be the future of augmented reality gaming. The trailer, which apparently depicts “actual headset gameplay” shows a handful of players wearing AR glasses as they interact with shared virtual objects, including game elements as well as more practical virtual signage, while out and about. A couple of the players appear to be interacting with the game using handheld motion controllers, but there’s no sign of anyone needing to directly use a smartphone to play.
The trailer was released to coincide with several announcements made at this year’s Qualcomm Snapdragon Summit. These include a new processor from the mobile chip giant, a new reference...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In One Minute : CodeIgniter]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rakeshkr2/in-one-minute-codeigniter-pf4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rakeshkr2/in-one-minute-codeigniter-pf4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CodeIgniter is an open-source php web application framework created by EllisLab Inc and it is now a project of British Columbia Institute of Technology. The framework implements a modified version of the Model-View-Controller design pattern. It is praised for its performance and the quality of its documentation. It's currently licensed under the MIT License, although the previous version was released under the Open Software License ("OSL") v. 3.0.
CodeIgniter is loosely based on the popular Model-View-Controller development pattern. While view and controller classes are a necessary part of development under CodeIgniter, models are optional.
With more than 18.2k stars on Codeigniter's repository, it's also among the most starred PHP Framework on Github.com




These are generally regarded as pros of the framework:
Nearly zero configuration & No restrictive coding rules
Small footprint
Performance
Easy to learn
Great documentation
No restrictive coding rules
These are generally regarded as cons of the framework:
No built-in ORM
No built-in templating
Doesn't utilize namespaces
Doesn't utilize PHP's auto-loading feature
Application code is tightly-coupled with the framework
Official documentation
Official Wiki
CodeIgniter Wikipedia Article
Source Code on GitHub
Codeigniter forums
Best Library
Codeigniter .htaccess examples Github
Download latest version 4.1.3]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rakesh KR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lyft Aspired to Kill Car Ownership. Now It Aims to Profit From It]]></title>
        <id>63728f1d2ea97fb0c6f28a35</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/lyft-aspired-to-kill-car-ownership-now-it-aims-to-profit-from-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company once claimed that ride-hail services and robotaxis would make personal cars obsolete. Mounting losses have prompted a rethink.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aarian Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voltswagen's Star Trek Chair — A mobile office chair built for a Start Trek captain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/voltswagen-s-star-trek-chair</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/voltswagen-s-star-trek-chair"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T09:45:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataTable.dev — A grid library for instant big data processing.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/datatable-dev</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/datatable-dev"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T09:10:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Bcrypt. How to use it to hash passwords]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/documatic/what-is-bcrypt-how-to-use-it-to-hash-passwords-5c0g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/documatic/what-is-bcrypt-how-to-use-it-to-hash-passwords-5c0g"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T09:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bcrypt npm package is a JavaScript implementation of the bcrypt password hashing function that allows you to easily create a hash out of a password string. Unlike encryption which you can decode to get back the original password, hashing is a one-way function that can’t be reversed once done.
When the user submits a password, the password will be hashed and your JavaScript application needs to store the hash in the database. Later when the user wants to authenticate his or her account, you need to compare the password input with the hash stored in your database to see if it matches.
The bcrypt library makes the process easy by providing you with methods to hash and compare passwords.
** To start using the library, you need to install it with your package manager: **
npm install bcrypt
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubham Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Chatbot Using Python, Django]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/documatic/build-a-chatbot-using-python-django-46hb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/documatic/build-a-chatbot-using-python-django-46hb"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A ChatBot has become one of the must-have features of modern-day web applications. It plays a huge role in customer service which was once traditionally held by human beings. Through ChatBot, you can automatically generate a response to a user’s input by making use of different machine-learning techniques.
Note:- If you encounter any issues throughout the tutorial, you can check out the code in the GitHub repository.
Prerequisite
Project Configuration
WebSockets Using Django Channels
Tailwind CSS Configuration
Frontend - Create a WebSocket Connection
Enable a Channel Layer
Backend - WebSocket Consumers
ChatterBot - Generate Automated Response
ChatterBot Training
Offload Automated Response Generation to Celery
Conclusion



This guide assumes that you have intermediate-level Django knowledg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hana Belay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pokémon Violet and Scarlet are the vast open worlds the series has been building to]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/23462858/pokemon-violet-scarlet-review-nintendo-switch</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/23462858/pokemon-violet-scarlet-review-nintendo-switch"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A trainer riding Koraidon, one of the new additions to Pokémon Violet and Scarlet. | Image: Nintendo
    


  		 
The latest Pokémon release is a big, expansive adventure that also pushes the Nintendo Switch to its limits.  
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Development JWT Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/baize1998/web-development-jwt-practices-59cn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/baize1998/web-development-jwt-practices-59cn"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T08:42:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Foreword


The previous post briefly introduced a high-performance Go HTTP framework - Hertz. This article is based on a demo from the Hertz open-source repository. tree/main/bizdemo/hertz_jwt), which describes how to use Hertz to complete the JWT authentication and authorization process.
It should be noted here that hertz-jwt is one of many external extensions to Hertz, it is forked from gin-jwt and adapted to Hertz.
Hertz's rich extension ecosystem is a great convenience for developers and worth exploring beyond this article.

Use hz to generate code
Use JWT to complete login and authentication
Use Gorm and MySQL




  
  
  Download





git clone https://github.com/cloudwego/hertz-examples.git
cd bizdemo/hertz_jwt

hertz_jwt
├── Makefile # Generate hertz scaffolding code using the hz c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>baize</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[通过 SSH 在远程 Linux 系统上执行命令]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15263-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15263-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T08:39:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[通过安全的网络连接在远程计算机上调用命令或程序。


有一天，我正在测试如何在 将文件或目录复制到多个位置和系统时保持完整的文件权限。当我想检查远程系统上的文件权限时，我必须通过 SSH 登录它并检查属性。从远程系统多次登录和注销的过程让我有点烦，我想，如果我可以在远程 Linux 系统上通过 SSH 执行命令就好了。

幸运的是，在浏览了 ssh 命令的手册页后，我找到了一个解决办法。

如果你想知道如何本地运行远程系统上运行命令或脚本，而不登录到远程系统，下面的内容会告诉你如何做。

1、通过 SSH 在远程 Linux 系统上执行命令

从本地系统通过 SSH 在远程系统上运行命令或脚本的典型方法是：

$ ssh <username@IP_Address-or-Doman_name> <Command-or-Script>


允许我给你们举几个例子：

1.1、通过 SSH 在远程系统上运行单个命令

假设你想要 查找远程 Linux 系统的内核详细信息。为此，只需运行：

$ ssh sk@192.168.225.22 uname -a


这里，


sk 是远程系统的用户名，

192.168.225.22 是远程系统的 IP 地址，

uname -a 是我想在远程系统上运行的命令。


示例输出：



看到没？我并没有实际登录到远程系统，但通过 SSH 在远程系统上执行了 uname 命令，并在本地系统的终端上显示了输出。

你还可以像下面这样用引号指定命令。

$ ssh sk@192.168.225.22 "uname -a"


或者，

$ ssh sk@192.168.225.22 'uname -a'


如果你已经 更改了 SSH 协议的默认端口，只需使用 -p 参数指定它。

…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building recursive logic with Step Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/building-recursive-logic-with-step-functions-3hm5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/building-recursive-logic-with-step-functions-3hm5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T08:20:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can create serverless iteration solutions like pagination with Step Functions. This way, we won't face the Lambda functions' timeout limit and can process many items without interruptions.
Bob just got the task to write a logic that backfills some fields in a 3rd party application. The solution should get secret agent data from the database, then transform and upload them to the 3rd party application.
Bob decided to create a Lambda function to run the script. He allocated it a large memory and added the 15 minutes maximum timeout. We should address a restriction: the 3rd party API has a rate limit cap and can only accept two requests per second. Considering the number of agents Bob's company stores in the database, he believes 15 minutes should be enough for the migration to complete.
B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arpad Toth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1000 Email Marketing Ideas — Monthly list of fun and effective ideas to inspire emails]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/1000-email-marketing-ideas</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/1000-email-marketing-ideas"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T08:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://1000emailideas.com
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[rfrd — Personalized videos for an enhanced customer journey]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/rfrd</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/rfrd"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T08:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git concepts in less than 10 minutes]]></title>
        <id>70314 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/git-concepts"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git concepts in less than 10 minutes
Dwayne McDaniel
Thu, 11/17/2022 - 03:00

            
Git has become the default way to store and transport code in the DevOps generation. Over 93% of developers report that Git is their primary version control system. Almost anyone who has used version control is familiar with git add, git commit, and git push. For most users, that’s all they ever plan to do with Git, and they're comfortable with that. It just works for their needs.
However, from time to time, almost everyone encounters the need to do something a little more advanced, like git rebase or git cherry-pick or work in a detached head state. This is where many devs start to get a bit nervous.
[ Read next How to reset, revert, and return to previous states in Git ]
I'm here to tell you it is …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dwayne McDaniel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux commands: Drop these old utilities for modern alternatives]]></title>
        <id>70274 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/modern-linux-commands"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux commands: Drop these old utilities for modern alternatives
Seth Kenlon
Thu, 11/17/2022 - 03:00

            
Linux has a good track record for software support. There are about 60 commands in man section 1 of Unix 1st edition, and the majority still work today. Still, progress stops for no one. Thanks to vast global participation in open source, new commands are frequently developed. Sometimes a new command gains popularity, usually because it offers new features, or the same features but with consistent maintenance. Here are ten old commands that have recently been reinvented.
1. Replace man with cheat or tealdeer
The man page is functional, and it works well for what it does. However, man pages aren't always the most succinct at demonstrating how to use the command you're trying to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Kenlon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evernote 被 Bending Spoons 收购]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43917</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/evernote-joining-bending-spoons/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T07:56:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evernote 宣布被来自意大利的开发商 Bending Spoons 收购，交易预计将于 2023 年初完成。@appinn Evernote 是著名且老牌的笔记工具，曾经估值高达 10 亿美元，]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ahsuite Client Portals — Embed Anything in an Easy-to-Use Client Portal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ahsuite-client-portals</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ahsuite-client-portals"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T07:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #823 印象笔记被出售]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15262-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15262-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T07:52:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[印象笔记被出售

意大利移动应用开发商 Bending Spoons 公司今天宣布收购印象笔记（Evernote）。在收购的新闻稿中说，“印象笔记拥有约 1 亿美元的经常性收入，数百万付费客户，以及使用其跨平台应用程序创建的近 110 亿条笔记。”印象笔记曾经是最流行的笔记应用之一，但在 2016 年开始限制免费用户的使用。在同一年还宣布开发了可以审查用户笔记的 AI，以及让其员工可以访问用户笔记，虽然在招致巨大反对后取消了计划，但也导致了大量用户流失。如今，在 iOS 上，它甚至没有跻身生产力应用程序的前 100 名。收购宣告没有公开收购金额等细节。


消息来源：The Register



老王点评：这个曾经兴盛一时的应用，也算是画上了一个逗号，或者，句号。还有人在用它吗？




AlmaLinux 9.1 紧随 RHEL 9.1 发布

红帽企业 Linux（RHEL）9.1 今天正式发布，RHEL 9.1 将 PHP 8.1 作为支持的应用流，扩展了多级安全支持，支持将容器嵌入到镜像构建器蓝图中等等一系列更新增强。而仅仅半天后，作为 RHEL 9.1 的自由构建版本，AlmaLinux 9.1 就发布了。


消息来源：Phoronix



老王点评：我觉得 CentOS 的结束至少有一个好处，RHEL 的自由版本发布的更快了，以前都需要几周。




KDE 宣布新的社区目标：可访问性、环境可持续性、自动化

在今年的 KDE 年度开发者大会上，KDE 宣布了新的社区目标。他们希望把重点放在确保 KDE 软件对所有人都是无障碍的。之前的 KDE 社区目标是围绕着一致性、对 KDE 应用程序的关注和 Wayland 支持。


消息来源：Phoronix



老王点评：我还是觉得之前的目标更务实一些，目前的 KDE 虽然已经很棒了，但是距离最好还有一些距离。


回音


Fedora Linux 获准 进行现代 C 语言的 移植工作，这些变化包括删除隐式函数声明、删除隐式整型、删除旧式函数声明等不符合 C99 规范的部分。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is local a bad part in Perl?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yukikimoto/is-local-a-bad-part-in-perl-ffg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yukikimoto/is-local-a-bad-part-in-perl-ffg"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T07:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Q. Is local a bad part in Perl?


A. In my opinion, Yes. local is a bad part in Perl. If I could re-implement Perl, I will not implement local.
local $foo;

A. This is because the variable that is the operand of local is a global variable although at a glance it looks like a local variable in C.
int32_t foo;

Using my in all Perl programs is recommended strongly.
my $foo;

This is called a lexical variable. This is strange name we don't usually hear in daily life.
Q. I want to say No, but in some cases, local is used in current days. One is to save and restore predefined global variable.
{
  # Save
  local @ARGV;
}

# Restore @ARGV at the end of the scope

Tow is to get the whole content of a file.
my $content = do { local $/; <$fh>; };

Ugly, user experience is worse than other programing languages, but most efficient way because Perl doesn't have the function to get the whole content of a file.
The efficient is sacrificed, the following code can be written.
my $content = join('', <$fh>);

Yes, using Scope::Guard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yuki Kimoto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve Product Discoverability with New Walmart Item Spec v4.X]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/themagentohumor/improve-product-discoverability-with-new-walmart-item-spec-v4x-1lfo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/themagentohumor/improve-product-discoverability-with-new-walmart-item-spec-v4x-1lfo"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T07:34:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Walmart will no longer entertain any item setup and maintenance requests via Item Spec 3.2 from 1st October 2022. This Walmart API update announcement came in 2021 for sellers using an API-based third-party Integration for selling on Walmart. But still, many sellers haven’t moved their product catalog to the new Walmart Item Spec v4.X!
As per Walmart’s announcement, this new API will bring many benefits to your store, like improved inventory & order management, better product visibility & discoverability in search results, increased traffic, and much more. So, if you haven’t upgraded your product catalog yet, you are missing all these benefits plus any chance to earn a higher profit margin during the upcoming festive season sale. So, now is the best time to upgrade to the new Walmart Item …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Magento Humor Society</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Replicate the way Elon and Peter think — Mindset absorption smashed with AI and spaced repetition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/replicate-the-way-elon-and-peter-think</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/replicate-the-way-elon-and-peter-think"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T07:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One of the ways to use Context API]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/giorgiparunov/one-of-the-ways-to-use-context-api-65f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/giorgiparunov/one-of-the-ways-to-use-context-api-65f"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T06:44:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you know a lot of developers replaced redux with react context feature. So I want to show you how I am using it in my products.
We will create a Todo list using context API (based on typescript). 
I will use bootstrap for design._

Final view of our code.
At first, we must create our context in the contexts folder.
TodoContext.ts
import { createContext } from "react";

export interface ITodo {
    name: string;
    completed: boolean;
}

interface ITodoContext {
    data: ITodo[];
    updateData: Function;
}

export const TodoContext = createContext<ITodoContext>({
    data: [],
    updateData: (data: ITodo[]) => {
        throw new Error('updateData not implemented')
    }
})

Here we can see that we are creating an interface for todo items, and also for todo context.
My context has tw…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giorgi Parunov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kore.ai Experience Optimization Platform — Build powerful bots to automate support and engage leads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/kore-ai-experience-optimization-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/kore-ai-experience-optimization-platform"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T06:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Monolith to Microservices Using the Strangler Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mkurzeja/php-monolith-to-microservices-using-the-strangler-pattern-14g4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mkurzeja/php-monolith-to-microservices-using-the-strangler-pattern-14g4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T06:33:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with the legacy system can be a real pain, both for developers and for business owners. It comes with a handful of consequences: longer time-to-market, difficult-to-debug issues, performance problems, and higher development effort - just to name a couple of them.
Sticking to a monolithic architecture might also be one of the "legacy" issues to have. It usually hits bigger companies, where the development is split between multiple teams.
Let's quickly imagine a legacy monolithic application that was built when the company was smaller, and then extended rapidly as the company grew. Now developed by four teams that need to share the same codebase. As always (in legacy systems), there is spaghetti code, and the modules are tightly coupled. The overall software architecture is rather po…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michał Kurzeja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MerLoc - Debug Lambdas with real data — Switch where your Lambda runs like you switch lanes!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/merloc-debug-lambdas-with-real-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/merloc-debug-lambdas-with-real-data"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T06:23:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Dubai MetaMask Workshop]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/httpjunkie/web3-dubai-metamask-workshop-4afh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/httpjunkie/web3-dubai-metamask-workshop-4afh"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T06:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Dubai MetaMask Workshop (Follow Along)


Workshop GitHub Repo
NodeJS & NPM
Code Editor
Git & GitHub account 
MetaMask Extension Installed
Knowledge of JavaScript, TypeScript and React (is a plus)
Eagerness to learn NextJS, Solidity smart contracts, Truffle and Ganache




npm i truffle ganache -g

Welcome to the Web3 Dubai Metamask Workshop, to get started, please clone the workshop repo on your machine and checkout the start branch:
git clone https://github.com/metamask/web3-dubai-mm-workshop && 
cd web3-dubai-mm-workshop && 
git checkout start && npm i

With our repo cloned and our dependencies installed we should take minute to discuss our choices for the decisions and architecture of this web3 project.
A mono repo using Turbo 


Incremental bundler/build system optimized for mono …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Bishard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Answer.dev v0.3.0 released!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/answerdev/answerdev-v030-released-4cff</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/answerdev/answerdev-v030-released-4cff"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T06:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to our contributors! Answer.dev 0.3.0 has already been released, which contains some bug fixes, optimizations, and improvements. Let's together see more details.
Added timezone and locale support
Added Administrator dashboard
Added version check feature that keeps your Answer always updated
Added installation guide; now you can install Answer with just one click!
Improved search support for the Administrator
User interface language does not meet expectations #75

Dashboard will remind you how to configure SMTP  #64 #44 
Fix bug for problem search #71 
Fix bug for delete problem #68 
Change upload directory
#77 
Answer is still under very active development. Watch on GitHub to receive updates.
Being highly scalable and modern, Answer.dev is an open-source knowledge-based community software with which you can efficiently build various Q&A communities, ranging from customer support to user communication. 
For more information on past and future versions of Answer.dev, please see: https://github.com/answerdev/answer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Answer.dev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A glance at Turbopack]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dailydevtips1/a-glance-at-turbopack-epd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dailydevtips1/a-glance-at-turbopack-epd"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T05:58:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Turbopack got announced with the release of Next 13, and is deemed to become the successor of Webpack.
If you're currently using Webpack for bundling, you might know the struggles of long first boots and generic slow bundling.
But bundling certainly could happen faster, so the creators of Webpack, Vercel, and Next came together and introduced us to Turbpack.
At the time of writing, it's still in the alpha phase, so not ready for production, but a perfect time to explore it.
Turbopack can already be used with Next 13; in the future, you can also migrate your non-Next projects to it.
To test out Turbopack, you can start an example code with the following command.
npx create-next-app --example with-turbopack

Now run the dev server by running:
npm run dev

Your startup and update time should …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bongers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blizzard will suspend World of Warcraft in China over licensing dispute]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/17/23463818/blizzard-netease-china-hearthstone-diablo-world-of-warcraft-unavailable</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/17/23463818/blizzard-netease-china-hearthstone-diablo-world-of-warcraft-unavailable"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T05:15:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blizzard
    

  
Blizzard will suspend games in China because it can’t reach an agreement with its licensing and publishing partner NetEase, it said in a press release. World of Warcraft, Hearthstone, Overwatch 2, Starcraft, Heroes of the Storm, Diablo III, and Warcraft III: Reforged won’t be available in China after January 23, 2023.
Blizzard will suspend the sale of games and offer guidance to Chinese players “in the coming days,” according to the press release, which did not offer a specific timeline. Development of Diablo Immortal is in a separate agreement and will continue, NetEase said in a statement. Upcoming releases, including the latest World of Warcraft expansion, Dragonflight, and the second season of Overwatch 2, “will proceed later this...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fluent Search – 支持工作流的高颜值 Windows 搜索启动器]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43914</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/fluent-search/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T04:11:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[本文来自发现频道，作者：@L_hiil，原文链接：https://meta.appinn.net/t/topic/38094 Fluent Search 是 Windows 下一款有着高颜值且可以自定]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SavvyCal Time Zone API — Never have to debug time zone insanity again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/savvycal-time-zone-api</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/savvycal-time-zone-api"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T03:31:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[selling your by-products was penned by @jasonfried:

“The software and web industry can learn a lot from the lumber industry, the oil business, and corn and soybean farmers. Lumber was originally cut for boards for building. Oil was originally drilled for fuel. Corn and soybeans were originally farmed for food. But today these industries have figured out how to use the waste to make even more products.”

When we took a look around our codebase, we realized we were sitting on some pretty useful sawdust!

This project came to life when we set out to build a time zone selector for SavvyCal that humans could actually use (a pretty important thing for a scheduling app!)

It turns out, deduplicating and sourcing reasonable names for the 595 worldwide time zones is a lot trickier than it might seem!

We’ve spent hundreds of hours aggregating, normalizing, and organizing all the ridiculous time zone nuances. For example: Nepal runs on GMT+5¾, Hawaii and Arizona ignore Daylight Savings Time, and UTC+12 and UTC–12 are the same time zone… with a different date.

Use the SavvyCal Time Zone API to fetch everything you need to incorporate time zone elements in your app, such as human-friendly names, abbreviations, UTC offsets, and exemplar cities. Query the API right from your JavaScript front-end (using a public API token), or from your backend — wherever you need to use the data!

Check out the documentation and let me know what you think.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WayAway — Find cheap flights and get cashback on all your travel deals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/wayaway</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/wayaway"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T03:26:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Only the iPhone 15 Pro will get a speed upgrade with USB-C, says analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/16/23463612/iphone-15-pro-usb-c-high-speed-rumors-quo-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/16/23463612/iphone-15-pro-usb-c-high-speed-rumors-quo-2023"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T02:44:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A longstanding criticism of the pro phones is that it takes forever to get data off of them. | Photo by Amelia Holowaty Krales / The Verge
    

  
The iPhone 15 Pro models are in line for a massive upgrade to their wired transfer speeds with the switch to USB-C, according to noted analyst Ming-Chi Kuo. Unfortunately, he doesn’t believe that benefit is coming to the regular 2023 iPhones. He predicts that the 15 and 15 Plus will also swap in USB-C ports but, just like the 2022 10th-gen iPad, they’ll be stuck with the same USB 2.0 speeds they had with Lighting. 
Kuo made the prediction in a series of tweets on Wednesday and says the information is from his “latest survey.” (The analyst is known for getting information from supply chain sources.) He specified by predicting that the “15 Pro & 15 Pro Max will support at least USB 3.2 or Thunderbolt 3.” If that’s true, that’d mean they...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm has a new chip brand]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/16/23463632/qualcomm-has-a-new-chip-brand</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/16/23463632/qualcomm-has-a-new-chip-brand"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T02:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm has announced a new subbrand of CPUs for its Snapdragon family of products, called Oryon. The new CPU will be released in 2023 and available to manufacturers to use in devices such as Windows PCs, smartphones, and other applications. The company announced the new CPU at its Snapdragon Summit on Wednesday, but provided few details about what it entails.
The company has made Snapdragon-branded chips for Windows and Chrome OS computers for a few years now but has had slow traction getting them into many Windows devices. The few ultraportable computers that have used Qualcomm’s Arm chips have been niche, premium devices that appeal to a specific subset of PC buyers, but not the broader market.
Image: Qualcomm
     ...
  
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[在 VS Code 和 Codium 中编写 Python 程序]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15261-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15261-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T02:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[如果你正在寻找一个优秀的、通用的、开源的、带有 Python 集成的代码编辑器，那么你可以尝试一下 Codium。


在过去几年内，我有幸和中学生们一起，并带他们入门 Python 开发 和树莓派 400。这一切都很有趣，树莓派对于学生和我来说都是一个很好的平台。我们使用了 Code with Mu，并且一切都很成功。我们的 Python 技能随着经验的增长而增长，因此最近我开始寻找给这些学生提供更多东西的方法。

我参与了一个 Python 课程并在课程中接触了微软的 Visual Studio Code。我在课程中学到了很多关于如何为 Python 设置虚拟环境，以及如何为 Python 编程配置 VS Code 的知识。在学习过程中，我也认识了 Codium，它基本上是没有微软品牌和遥测的 VS Code。

如果你正在寻找一个优秀的、通用的、开源的、带有 Python 集成的代码编辑器，那么你可以尝试一下 Codium。下面是我在 Linux 系统上为 Python 设置 Codium 的方法。

在 Linux 上安装或更新 Python

首先，确保你正在运行最新版本的 Python。你可以使用你的软件包管理器来完成这项工作。在 Debian 和基于 Debian 的系统上：

$ sudo apt install python3-pip


在 Fedora、CentOS、Mageia、OpenMandriva 和类似的系统上：

$ sudo dnf update python3


在某些系统上，你可能还需要安装创建 Python 虚拟环境的软件：

$ sudo apt install python3.10-venv


安装 Codium

接下来，在你的电脑上 安装 Codium。在 Linux 上，你可以下载一个包…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple makes iCloud.com look like an iPad’s homescreen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/16/23463422/apple-icloud-website-redesign-update</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/16/23463422/apple-icloud-website-redesign-update"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T01:45:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a very new look for Apple’s online portal to your documents, pictures, and more.
    

  
Apple has updated iCloud.com to make the site look and feel significantly more modern, adding widget-like tiles that show you information from photos, notes, mail, and more (via MacRumors). It’s a big change from the previous version of the site, which basically just showed a handful of icons that acted as links to web apps, and should be a welcome upgrade for anyone who has to regularly access their iCloud data from a browser rather than an app running on an iPhone or Mac.
With the new design, which was available to beta testers last month, you can customize your iCloud.com homepage, adding tiles that can show your most recent photos, emails, documents, calendar events, notes, and more. Like with most iOS widgets, though, you’ll still...
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Verge -  All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[如何在 RHEL 9 上安装 Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15260-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15260-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T01:22:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[在这篇文章中，我们将逐步解释如何在 RHEL 9 系统上安装 Node.js。


Node.js 基于谷歌的 V8 JavaScript 引擎构建，它是一个自由开源的跨平台 JavaScript 运行时环境，主要用于构建服务器端应用。它使用事件驱动和异步模型，帮助开发人员构建高度可扩展的数据密集型的实时应用（RTA）。你可以使用 NodeJS 来构建前端和后端应用。

Node.js 通常用于构建以下应用：


聊天应用

流媒体应用

浏览器游戏

命令行工具

嵌入式系统


在其技术栈中使用 NodeJS 的顶级公司包括 PayPal、NetFlix 和 Uber 等等。

安装 Node.js 主要有以下三种方式：


从 NodeSource 仓库安装 Node.js

从发行版的官方仓库安装 Node.js

使用 NVM 安装 Node.js


让我们看看如何使用这些方法在 RHEL 9 上安装 Node.js。

先决条件：


最小化安装的 RHEL 9 系统

具有管理员权限的 sudo 用户

互联网连接

Red Hat 订阅或本地配置的仓库


从 NodeSource 存储库安装 Node.js

NodeSource 是一家技术公司，旨在帮助组织运行生产就绪的 Node.js 应用，关注资源使用以及增强的安全性和应用程序性能。它提供了最新版本的 Node.js 和 NPM。

要从 NodeSource 安装 Node.js，首先，按如下所示更新系统包。

$ sudo dnf update -y




接下来，安装这期间所需的构建工具。其中包括 GCC C/C++ 编译器、Perl 和 Python 调试器等等。

$ sudo dnf groupinstall 'Dev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standerd Figma UI Kit — Standerd is a simple Figma design system.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/standerd-figma-ui-kit</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/standerd-figma-ui-kit"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T01:12:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Record number of parents miss work as respiratory illnesses spike in kids]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898421</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898421"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T23:34:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though there are signs things could get worse, the White House has a rosy outlook.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Random Picker — Deciding 'who goes next' made a little easier.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/random-picker</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/random-picker"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T23:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://chrome.google.com/websto...

Demo: 

Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blast Mic (by Blast Radio) — A professional radio broadcast studio in your hand.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/blast-mic-by-blast-radio</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/blast-mic-by-blast-radio"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T22:59:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New test shows loose RTX 4090 power connectors cause overheating and melting]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898349</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898349"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T22:50:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Failure is rare, but can be caused by any kind of 12VHPWR cable or adapter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MARBLE — A business dashboard + Link-in-bio for content creators.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/marble-5</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/marble-5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T22:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coolors  — Super fast color schemes generator for cool designers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/coolors-4</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/coolors-4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T22:37:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia and Microsoft team up to build massive AI cloud computer]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898351</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898351"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T22:24:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI supercomputer will use "tens of thousands" of Nvidia A100 and H100 GPUs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stake Social - World Cup Predictor — Challenge your friends to be the Last Man Standing ⚽]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/stake-social-world-cup-predictor</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/stake-social-world-cup-predictor"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T22:10:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brand API — The ultimate API to retrieve any company's brand assets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/brand-api</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/brand-api"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T21:23:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon begins layoffs of up to 10,000 jobs, blames “uncertain” economy]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898348</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898348"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T21:16:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon confirms Devices & Services layoffs; warehouse jobs apparently safe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A cosmic hourglass: Webb captures image of protostar swathed in dark clouds]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898238</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898238"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T19:40:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New image offers window into what our Sun and Solar System looked like in infancy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LiveAlerts Shopify App — iOS Inspired Popups to Collect Email + SMS contacts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/livealerts-shopify-app</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/livealerts-shopify-app"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T19:28:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the deal with Formula 1 and sustainable fuels?]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898301</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898301"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T19:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[F1's CTO, Pat Symonds, explains the sport's plans to be carbon neutral by 2030.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Producter — Product Management Tool for customer-centric SaaS startups]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/producter-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/producter-2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T18:58:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@mervecankizcoruh and I worked as Product Managers/Designers at a B2B SaaS startup. 

We were trying so hard to find a balance between our product vision and customer needs. That's why we quit our full-time jobs and started Producter together 🚀

Today, we're so excited to launch Producter for the first time on Product Hunt ⚡️

Your thoughts and feedback mean a lot to us. Thank you! 

How can you become customer-centric and win your customers' hearts with Producter?

💬 Feedback Management
Collect product feedback from your customers and teammates.

 🖍️ Issue Management
Manage your tasks/epics, and run effective sprints with your team.

 📄 Product Documentation
Keep your product-related docs where you make the most critical decisions. 

🎙️ Public Feedback Board 
Give your users a place to submit their feedback on your user portal.

📣 Changelog
Share your product updates on your user portal. 

🛣️ Public Roadmap
Keep your users and stakeholders up-to-date with your public roadmap.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) – Explained With an Analogy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/aws-iam-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/aws-iam-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T18:51:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS IAM (Identity and Access Management) gives you control over who can access your AWS services and resources based on some predefined permissions.  The two keywords here are “who” and “permissions”. “Who” refers to a specific identity, which can be a user, group or role. “permissions” refer to the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix gives account holders the ability to kick freeloaders]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898280</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898280"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T18:40:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's about password sharing, sure, but security, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cabinet — Find great apps and games hand-picked by Android specialists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/cabinet</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/cabinet"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T18:31:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EcommChecklist Notion Template — Create eCommerce conversion roadmap using drag & drop system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ecommchecklist-notion-template</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ecommchecklist-notion-template"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T18:26:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fowl Language by Duolingo — Cheer on or insult teams in other languages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/fowl-language-by-duolingo</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/fowl-language-by-duolingo"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T17:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Lab-Grown Meat Startup Gets the FDA’s Stamp of Approval]]></title>
        <id>637520f6d0a7e54d87737b2b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/lab-grown-meat-approval/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T17:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US regulatory body has signed off on Upside Foods’ cultivated meat—but the company is still figuring out how to make enough of it to sell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tool Finder by No Code Founders — Easily find the right no-code tool(s) for your project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tool-finder-by-no-code-founders</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tool-finder-by-no-code-founders"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T17:25:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DropForm — Build interactive forms, give NFT rewards, get 3x responses!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/dropform-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/dropform-2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T17:24:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DuckDuckGo’s anti-tracking Android tool could be “even more powerful” than iOS]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898199</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898199"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T17:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[App Tracking Protection blocks outbound traffic to listed tracking firms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Purdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measles outbreak jumps to 7 Ohio daycares, 1 school—all with unvaccinated kids]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898258</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898258"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T17:13:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The highly contagious virus is spreading amid slipping vaccination rates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Razer doubles its latest Blade laptop’s USB speeds with a firmware update]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898209</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898209"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T17:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New update lights up functionality present in all of AMD's Ryzen 6000 CPUs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Modern Documentation Site with VitePress]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-modern-documentation-site-with-vitepress/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-modern-documentation-site-with-vitepress/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T17:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Documentation is a crucial aspect of software development. But developers often neglect it because it can be a hassle to maintain. This is why it's important to use tools that help simplify this process.  In this tutorial, you'll learn how to build a complete docs site quickly by utilizing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Eke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the PS5’s DualSense controller is failing disabled players]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898244</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898244"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T16:55:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two years after PS5 launch, Sony doesn't offer accessible-control alternatives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State of Bitcoin — Track and learn about Bitcoin with widgets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/state-of-bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/state-of-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T15:56:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alloy Sports — Create winning sports betting systems in seconds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/alloy-sports</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/alloy-sports"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T15:53:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brad@alloysports.com

We are currently operational in the United States, Canada, Europe, Israel, India, Australia, and New Zealand, and we plan to launch in more countries as we grow.

📲 Sign up and Download the app here!
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laser-driven fusion’s internal energies not matching up with predictions]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898219</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898219"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T15:42:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a change in behavior when the plasma starts burning, and nobody knows why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nastix Design — Free browser-based application for quick design of clothes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/nastix-design</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/nastix-design"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T15:31:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://nastix-design.com/) where there is a minimum of design, and the main task is to fold the product details like a puzzle and choose a fabric.

Since the application is free and browser-based, it is available to everyone without any additional installations.

The set of parts and templates that I uploaded to the applications may only partially coincide with the assortment of the enterprise. So I added a new feature. Its essence is that you can prepare an archive with your own templates. And then upload it to the application while working with it. And then you can assemble the product both from my default parts and your own.

At the same time, I did not give the opportunity to save them in the application, so as not to take responsibility for the safety of storing other people's designs. This is less convenient for the client, but he can be calm that his ideas will not be stolen.

But the target audience is not only sales managers of garment factories.

I realized that the site is convenient in the educational process.

Teachers often have to show mock-ups of products. Of course, this can be done using pre-prepared pictures. But with the help of my application, he is free to change the look of the product - add a pocket, change the fabric, and so on. The same can be achieved with the help of respected graphic editors, but there such operations will take much more time.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AdScale: Facebook Ads, Google Ads & SMS — Run first-party data ads on Google Ads, Facebook Ads & SMS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/adscale-facebook-ads-google-ads-sms</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/adscale-facebook-ads-google-ads-sms"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T15:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[City birds are changing their tune]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898208</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898208"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T15:14:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many urban-dwelling birds have modified their songs in response to human-generated noise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Knowable Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[bagel — Web3-Native communication app for using NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/bagel-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/bagel-2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T15:03:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telehealth Sites Put Addiction Patient Data at Risk]]></title>
        <id>63189c13036b54662b510390</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/substance-abuse-telehealth-privacy-tracking-tech/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research found pervasive use of tracking tech on substance-abuse-focused health care websites, potentially endangering users in a post-Roe world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lindsey Ellefson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telehealth Sites Put Addiction Patient Data at Risk]]></title>
        <id>63189c13036b54662b510390</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/substance-abuse-telehealth-privacy-tracking-tech/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research found pervasive use of tracking tech on substance-abuse-focused health care websites, potentially endangering users in a post-Roe world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lindsey Ellefson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk tells Twitter staff: Agree to work “long hours at high intensity” or quit now]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898200</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898200"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T14:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musk's all-staff email: "Click yes on the link below" to keep your job.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tusmo — A daily and multiplayer word game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tusmo</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tusmo"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T14:26:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[20 Best Viral TikTok Gifts We Found, and Love (2022)]]></title>
        <id>618d379a665f24682a2d21e9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-viral-tiktok-gadgets/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We tried out the gadgets that kept showing up in our feeds. Here are the ones that deserve the hype—and would make awesome presents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brenda Stolyar, Gear Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Stereotype of the Woke Teen Is 'Tárring' Art]]></title>
        <id>63725ab8845dc8670fda4f71</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/tar-art-social-media-stereotypes/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An archetype culled from the depths of social media seems to be short-circuiting screenwriters’ creativity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katherine Cross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AweMyFace — AI skincare app and your guide on the way to the glow skin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/awemyface</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/awemyface"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T13:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blarb 2.0 — Ephemeral microblogging for unfiltered sharing.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/blarb-2-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/blarb-2-0"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T13:34:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nocs NS1100 Air Review: Great Wireless Sound, Sharp Design]]></title>
        <id>6372c04db25bbf8e38fd5bc8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/nocs-ns1100-air/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These wirefree earbuds from the Swedish brand have a comfy fit and great sound, plus they don’t cost an arm and a leg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Calore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started on Mastodon]]></title>
        <id>6372f2137268ef35e219ba11</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-get-started-use-mastodon/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interested in trying the social network everyone's flocking to? Here's what you need to know to find your way around and build community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Pot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Product Coach — Meet on-demand with proven product experts.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/product-coach</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/product-coach"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T12:19:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juisci — Freshly squeezed science]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/juisci</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/juisci"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T12:18:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ISP deploys fiber service with a wrinkle—the users themselves own each network]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1896595</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1896595"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T12:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite costly Silicon Valley project, CEO says this isn't just for wealthy areas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Want to Archive Twitter? Good Luck With That]]></title>
        <id>6372872a8cea9c3346926042</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-archive-elon-musk/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The platform's meltdown has shed light on the steep challenge of preserving social media data. But not everything is worth saving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amanda Hoover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Alzheimer’s Scientists, the Amyloid Debate Has No Easy Answers]]></title>
        <id>636a91f27484c01b9b6e9661</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/for-alzheimers-scientists-the-amyloid-debate-has-no-easy-answers/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, potential therapies that attack this brain protein have failed to help patients in clinical trials. Now—surprisingly—a new drug shows promise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grace Huckins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to COP27. Thank You for Not Protesting]]></title>
        <id>6373bbfc454b677de6f65e6e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cop27-protest-restrictions/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At this year’s UN climate conference in Egypt, activists are unable to demonstrate without permission, limiting their ability to voice criticism of the COP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Barber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PLAYΞRS: living 3D avatars  — Kick off the 2022 World Cup in the metaverse with PLAYΞRS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/play-rs-living-3d-avatars</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/play-rs-living-3d-avatars"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T10:56:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quizwiz.io — Ready-to-use quiz decks for your next social event]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/quizwiz-io</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/quizwiz-io"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T10:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tweep — Distinguish b/w Twitter Blue & Verified Users]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tweep</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/tweep"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T10:37:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[优化 Windows 下的多屏体验]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76841</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76841"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T10:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[虽然现在多屏用户逐渐变多，但仍是小众，Windows 也并没过对多屏使用进行太多的优化。所以只好自己动手，于是有了以下一些个人自用的优化设置。
窗口出现位置优化
Windows 系统仅对多屏用户提供了简单主显示器的设置，默认情况下所有新打开的窗口都只会出现在主显示器上，即使你在使用另一个的显示器。而「基于显示器连接记住窗口位置」只能记住上次关闭时所在的屏幕，实用性并不高。

这时微软自家的 Power Toys 里的 FancyZones 就可以派上用场了，除了我们熟知的窗口布局设置外，它还可以调整窗口行为，在这里我们可以通过启用「将新创建的窗口移动到当前 活动的监视器（实验性）」来达到这一效果，美中不足的是动画不够优雅。

内容显示优化
现在 Windows 下大部分的应用都适配高 DPI 的，少部分不支持的，也可以通过 Windows 自带的属性 - 兼容性选项来调整。

但对于我们网上冲浪必备的浏览器，它的缩放是固定的，且只有一个设置选项。不知道有没有人跟我一样两个屏幕的缩放比例是不一样的，在两个屏幕间移动浏览器时，网页内容并不会根据 DPI 而变化，导致观感割裂。在这里我推荐一个 FireFox 浏览器插件：ffreszoom，它可以实时感知屏幕宽度的变化，当宽度超过指定值时，自动调整到指定缩放比例。设置前先通过这个网站查看自己的屏幕宽度：http://whatismyscreenresolution.net/，需要将 Firefox 浏览器移动到不同显示器上刷新。

如图所示我的外屏宽度是 1728 px，笔记本内屏为 1024，所以我在两者之间随意取了一个值用于判断，若当前屏幕宽度超过 1600 px，就自动设置缩放为 1.5，也即 150%。若小于 1600 px，则使用浏览器设置里的值。两种缩放无缝切换，只会多了一个缩放的动画。由于本人没使用 Chromium 类浏览器，并没有对应的插件推荐，不过其用户这么多，应该会有类似的插件。

利用「闲置的」触摸板
不知有没有跟我一样喜欢使用笔记本键盘的，且平时一些简单的操作直接用触摸板直接操作。现在 Windows 11 已经支持自定义触摸板多指手势了，但其不能根据不同应用设置不同的手势，例如：A 软件可以用 Ctrl  + W 关闭，但 B 软件只能用 Alt + F4，同一个操作有不同的快捷键。

这时就需要第三方软件了，这里我推荐 GestureSign，界面虽然是 Windows 10 风格，但不影响使用，毕竟设置完就不用再看了。它可以为不同应用的不同快捷键键设置相同的触控手势，手势类型也不再仅限于横平竖直，可以自由发挥。同时软件也内置了一些常用的命令供选择。

上图是我的一些设置，双指一般使用系统默认就不添加上去了。其中个人最爱的是三指滑动切换标签，体验比鼠标点击更加符合人的直觉。对于频繁使用搜索启动器的我，把三指上滑指定为搜索启动器的快捷键，方便呼出。
 
对了，设置前记得把系统自带的相关手势取消掉，不然会冲突。若你仍不习惯使用触摸板，该软件也支持鼠标手势，具体可以自行下载体验。
结尾
以上便是我在使用多屏时遇到的问题，及相关解决方法，希望对多屏用户有帮助。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Not_your_user</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #822 电子书的“磨损”速度快于实体书]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15259-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15259-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T09:32:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[电子书的“磨损”速度快于实体书

一百年前的实体书如果保存良好，可以正常阅读。但十年前的电子书今天去阅读极有可能会遇到各种问题。电子书需要不断维护，从文件格式到存储介质的不断变化，需要不断重新处理。电子书是脆弱且受到威胁的。


消息来源：Archive



老王点评：这是一个违反直觉的事情，但是确实如此，所以，我们应该用一种明文的开放格式来承载这些电子书。




16 台晶圆级芯片计算机集群组成千万核超算

制造世界上最大的芯片 —— 晶圆级引擎 2（WSE-2）的公司 Cerebras 今天公布了其仙女座超级计算机。仙女座是由 16 个 WSE-2 芯片组成的，共有 1350 万个计算核心，比世界顶级超级计算机 Frontier 系统多出百分之六十，AI 算力与 Frontier 相当。全套系统功耗 500 千瓦，这比同等级的超级计算机的功率要低得多。


消息来源：Venture Beat



老王点评：16 块脸盆大的芯片组成的超算，在 AI 算力上与世界第一超算相当。




美国的 Frontier 超算继续占据 TOP500 榜首

第 60 版 TOP500 显示，Frontier 系统仍然是名单上唯一拥有 Exaflop 级别算力的超级计算机。Frontier 的 HPL 分数和之前一样，1.102 EFlop/s，但是确是第二名的三倍。之前连续两年占据榜首的日本富岳超级计算机依旧保持第二名。中国排名前十的两台超算依旧是神威-太湖之光和天河-2A。


消息来源：Top500



老王点评：很多超算是不参加排名的。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA gets its mojo back with a stunning nighttime launch of the SLS rocket]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898017</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898017"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T08:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US space agency had not launched an orbital rocket since 2011.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[在少数派，你甚至可以聊足球之卡塔尔世界杯观赛指南]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76813</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76813"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T08:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[卡塔尔世界杯开幕式将于11月21日即下周一举行，在接下来的一段时间，将是全世界足球迷的狂欢月，无论你是不是足球迷，你都将会在各种媒体和社交网络上看到世界杯的信息，从球员的球场表现，到场外的花边新闻；有老将的“老骥伏枥，志在千里”，也有新人的横空出世；有冠军登顶后的春风得意，也有亚军距成功一步之遥却又失之交臂的遗憾……在世界杯举办的一个月里，将诞生许多热血与感动的故事，也少不了令众人津津乐道的段子，总之，这一切都让人无比期待。
世界杯赛程赛制
2022年世界杯将在中东国家卡塔尔举办，这是历史上首次在中东地区举办世界杯。
小组赛分组（来源：国际足联官网）
本届世界杯将有32支球队参加，分成8个小组。

A组：卡塔尔，厄瓜多尔，塞内加尔，荷兰
B组：英格兰，伊朗，美国，威尔士
C组：阿根廷，沙特阿拉伯，墨西哥，波兰
D组：法国，澳大利亚，丹麦，突尼斯
E组：西班牙，哥斯达黎加，德国，日本
F组：比利时，加拿大，摩洛哥，克罗地亚
G组：巴西，塞尔维亚，瑞士，喀麦隆
H组：葡萄牙，加纳，乌拉圭，韩国

世界杯31支参赛队伍由各个洲世界杯预选赛选出，其中欧洲拥有13个参赛名额，非洲5个名额，亚洲4.5个名额，南美洲4.5个名额，北美及加勒比地区3.5个名额和大洋洲0.5个名额。其中的半个名额是附加赛名额，澳大利亚和哥斯达黎加通过附加赛获得世界杯参赛资格。东道主卡塔尔自动获得参赛资格。
世界杯遵循杯赛赛制，分为小组赛和淘汰赛，与欧冠、亚冠等冠军联赛不同，世界杯小组赛为单回合制，每支队伍踢3场小组赛，积分前2名晋级淘汰赛。淘汰赛不再抽签，A组第一对阵B组第二，B组第一对阵A组第二，C组第一对阵D组第二，D组第一对阵C组第二，以此类推，同时，小组前二的两支队伍将分在上下两个半区，保证决赛前不再相遇。
淘汰赛对阵（来源：懂球帝APP）
小组赛将于北京时间11月21日至12月3日凌晨进行，淘汰赛…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>吃饭Bu洗碗</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How open source powers innovation]]></title>
        <id>70323 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/open-source-innovation"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How open source powers innovation
Gordon Haff
Wed, 11/16/2022 - 03:00

            
Where do people come together to make cutting-edge invention and innovation happen?
The corporate lab
One possible answer is the corporate research lab. More long-term focused than most company product development efforts, corporate labs have a long history, going back to Thomas Edison's Menlo Park laboratory in New Jersey. Perhaps most famous is Bell Labs' invention of the transistor—although software folks may associate it more with Unix and the C programming language.
But corporate laboratories have tended to be more associated with dominant firms that could afford to let large staffs work on very forward-looking and speculative research projects. After all, Bell Labs was born of the AT&T telephone monop…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gordon Haff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to address challenges with community metrics]]></title>
        <id>70306 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/organizational-technical-challenges"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to address challenges with community metrics
Georg Link
Wed, 11/16/2022 - 03:00

            
The previous two articles in this series looked at open source community health and the metrics used to understand it. They showed examples of how open source communities have measured at their health through metrics. This final article brings those ideas together, discussing the challenges of implementing community health metrics for your own community.
Organizational challenges
First, you must decide which metrics you want to examine. This requires understanding your questions about reaching your goals as a community. The metrics relevant to you are those that can answer your questions. Otherwise, you risk being overwhelmed by the amount of data available.
Second, you need to anticipate how …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Georg Link</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tomcat回显学习第一弹]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11851</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11851"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T07:21:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tomcat回显学习第一弹]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA’s Huge SLS Rocket Finally Launches the Artemis 1 Moon Mission]]></title>
        <id>636a94143505151fbc0b01e1</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/artemis-1-nasa-moon-mission-launch-sls-rocket-orion/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T07:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the first time since the Apollo era, the agency is preparing for crewed visits to our lunar neighbor. Missions with astronauts are next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramin Skibba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Runestone Text Editor – 文本编辑器：直接编辑 iOS 文件.app 里的文本文件]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43910</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/runestone-text-editor/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T07:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Runestone Text Editor 是一个用来在 iOS 的 文件.app 应用里直接编辑文本文件的小工具，简单易用。@Appinn 感谢 @小南同学在 Appinn Talk 群组的推荐：]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[如何上好一堂线上课？这是我的实践与思考]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76839</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76839"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T06:31:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐 
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。 
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

10 月的国庆小长假刚一结束，准备告诫学生们及时收心、恢复学习状态的长篇大论还没来得及打好腹稿，便伴随着疫情的到来再没机会说出口。小长假结束到校第二天，我所在的城市便由于疫情不得不陆续发出居家线上学习的通知，原本以为一周就能结束的线上学习，一晃眼已经进行了整整 5 周，在这 5 周里，我已经习惯了每天起床一杯咖啡后直接坐到桌前，开始一天的线上课程准备。
教师线下如何授课
在介绍我的线上授课经验之前，有必要先对我当前线下授课的方式进行简单介绍，我所在的小学使用的硬件设备是希沃白板，日常完成备课后，我会到教室使用希沃白板打开 PPT 进行授课。希沃白板的便利之处在于，即便你不使用内置的同名应用「希沃白板」进行备课、授课，它仍然支持打开课件后，直接在课件上使用不同颜色的画笔进行标记、圈画，并支持橡皮擦功能，大大节省了备课时间。
此外，希沃白板通常会配备有投影仪，一般我会在习题讲评课上利用投影仪播放练习单或是课堂作业，来完成习题讲评课；或是在随堂课上实时对学生的作业、作品进行展示。希沃白板还内置了多种工具，我使用频率较高的是其内置的倒计时功能，当课堂上需要进行限时练习或讨论时，它便能派上用场。
居家授课如何复制线下经验
我手上的电脑设备一共有两台，对于使用 Windows 电脑的用户而言，在电脑上直接下载前文提到过的「希沃白板」应用，便能把制作好的课件直接导入希沃（或直接利用希沃制作课件）实现实时圈画、倒计时等常用功能。而我的 Windows 电脑借给了同样有网课需求的同事，因此我可以用来上网课的主要设备就是一台 16+256G 的 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peggy_</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ora Funky Cat Review: Cute, Cheap, but Half-Baked]]></title>
        <id>637264e60ae5a121565fd737</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/review-ora-funky-cat/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite its adorable design, low price, and tech add-ons, we didn’t fall in love with this first Western offering from the Chinese car brand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Goy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1800元，打造我的 iPad 数字阅读器]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76830</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76830"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T04:24:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐 
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。 
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

本文提供了一个使用 iPad 进行数字阅读的低成本实用方案。
使用数字工具建立工作流基本上都遵循「收集-整理-阅读-输出」这样一个基本流程。在少数派上已经有很多文章关注了获取信息、收集整理、笔记输出等方面的方法论，但似乎比较少有人专门关注「阅读」这件事情。
阅读好像是一项不言自明、人人具备的技能，但是在数字时代，如何打造自己的数字阅读方案仍然是一个值得讨论的问题。虽然数字设备摆脱了纸质材料笨重的束缚，提供了更多的内容信息来源，但是也带来了新的难题。电脑、平板、手机……什么才是更好的阅读设备？书籍、报刊杂志、网页、社交媒体信息，如何更好的整合多源信息？
我认为，一个好的数字阅读方案应当满足以下要求：

简洁实用、舒适方便，专注于阅读本身；
提供一体化的阅读平台，既能广泛容纳各类来源、形式的内容，又能方便地记录标注笔记，对接后续内容输出；
成本较低，能够为更多人所用。

围绕这些目标，这篇文章介绍了我是如何从自己的需求出发，尝试用 iPad 打造适合自己的阅读工具的，希望能够给大家提供一些参考。
关于数字阅读：我需要什么样的工具
选择有效的工具必须先明确自己的需求。作为一个社科博士研究生以及数字工具的爱好者，我的日常阅读内容与来源大致包括这几个方面：

与个人研究议题相关的中英学术书籍、论文以及报告；
其他书籍，包括人文社科经典、人物传记、非虚构类作品、小说等；
专业媒体与官方资讯，个人关注的信源如财新、晚点、联合早报、澎湃、各类官媒等；
其他互联网信息，来自微信、微博等社交媒体以及其他网站。

在过去，我的阅读方式大致是这样的：…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>littleiron</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PicGo 2.3.1 版本更新发布，来看看更新了什么]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76811</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76811"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T03:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PicGo，一个用于快速上传图片并获取图片 URL 链接的工具。
今年是 PicGo 的五周年，虽然我真的很想推出一个大的正式版 (2.4.0) ，但是平时工作实在忙碌，只能抽空在闲暇时间写写 PicGo，因此没能交出一个让自己满意的答卷。所以本次时隔一年的更新只能以一个小版本更新。
不过对于用户来说，这个小版本还是修复了不少问题以及带来了不少新功能，我挑了其中一些比较有代表性的，快来看看吧。
Features
macOS arm64 的构建版本
从 2.3.1 版本开始，PicGo 也为 arm64 版本的 mac 带来适配的构建版本。为此，PicGo 更新了底层的 Electron 版本，跨越非常大，没少做适配。不过 arm64 版本的原生应用确实速度非常快。
如果你是 macOS 用户，但是遇到了安装、使用的问题，可以参考 PicGo 的 FAQ 最后一条进行处理。
多语言支持
一直以来 PicGo 只有简体中文的界面。从 2.3.1 版本开始，引入了 简体中文 \ 繁體中文 \ English 三种语言的界面。你可以在设置界面中切换语言。如果你想为 PicGo 添加更多的语言支持，欢迎参考贡献指南。
i18n 多语言设置
使用内置剪贴板上传
PicGo 对于剪贴板图片一直是采用脚本的方式获取的，同时不同平台的脚本不一样。但是不同的系统、用户环境会带来脚本执行结果不一定符合预期的情况。例如某些 Windows 用户使用「剪贴板上传」的时候就会遇到脚本报错或者进程残留的问题。因此这个版本新增了一个配置项，可以使用 Electron 提供的剪贴板 API 进行剪贴板图片获取以及上传。如果你遇到了上述的问题，不妨开启这个选项。
使用内置剪贴板上传
日志文件大小控制
2.3.0 版本优化了一些启动相关的日志，但是由于代码和系统的原因，某些用户会遇到写入日志死循环的问题，导致日…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PiEgg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora Linux 37 发布]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15258-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15258-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T02:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[今天我很兴奋地与大家分享成千上万的 Fedora 项目贡献者的辛勤工作成果：Fedora Linux 37 版本来了！让我们看看这个最新版本给你带来了什么。一如既往，在从以前的版本升级之前，你应该确保你的系统是完全最新的。迫不及待地想开始了吗？在你阅读的同时 下载！


下载 Fedora Linux 37


两个新的版本

Fedora 的各个“版本Edition”是针对某一特定“市场”的旗舰产品。在 Fedora Linux 37 中，我们增加了两个新版本：Fedora CoreOS 是你可能还记得的 Atomic Host 的后续版本。从 Project Atomic 和 CoreOS 的初始的工作中汲取营养，它提供了一种自动更新机制，以托管基于容器的工作负载。通过原子更新和简单的回滚，它为你的基础设施增加了安全感。

Fedora Cloud 也作为一个版本回来了。云计算工作组的活动已经重新开始了。Cloud 版本提供了一个很棒的 Fedora 基础，可以在你喜欢的公共或私有云中运行。AMI 将在本周晚些时候在 AWS 市场上提供，在社区频道上现在已经可以使用。请查看 此网站 以了解可以在其他云供应商或你自己的云上运行的镜像！

桌面的改进

Fedora Workstation 专注于桌面体验。像往常一样，Fedora Workstation 采用了最新的 GNOME 版本。GNOME 43 在设置中包括一个新的设备安全面板，为用户提供关于系统中硬件和固件的安全信息。在上一个版本的基础上，更多的 GNOME 核心应用程序被移植到了最新版本的 GTK 工具包，提供了更好的性能和现代的外观。

在这个版本中，我们做了一些改变，让你的安装变得更精简。我们把 Firefox 浏览器的语言包分成了子包。这意味着如果你不需要本地化，你可以删除 firefo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wobo — Build & share interactive workbooks for online learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/wobo</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/wobo"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T01:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Mint 的更新管理器现在支持 Flatpak]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15257-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15257-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T01:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Mint 的更新管理器变得更有用了！




Linux Mint 的更新管理器是该发行版的一个重要组成部分，它使新用户可以获得更为方便简易的体验。

最近的一次更新 Linux Mint 21 推出了许多改进，包括更新管理器对 Flatpak 的支持。

你只需要更新你的系统就可以获得这些改进。

⭐ 更新管理器中支持 Flatpak



是的，你没看错。这终于实现了。

Flatpak 支持已被添加到更新管理器中，用户只需单击几下就能更新 Flatpak 应用程序和运行时。

这将为进一步改善用户体验的统一更新体验提供了帮助。

这对新用户来说很有好处，他们不需要熟悉终端命令就能更新 Flatpak。此外，你不需要将 Flatpak 与软件中心集成（对于 GNOME 而言）。

换句话说，Linux Mint 团队增强了你使用 Flatpak 应用程序的体验。

除了对 Flatpak 的支持，本次更新还包括对 Linux Mint 21 的更多增强，这是一个开箱即用的更新。

这些改进包括：

对角栏的改进



Linux Mint 21 中的 角栏Corner Bar 添加了两项新特性：


能够在角栏设置左键点击和中键点击的动作；你可以配置它以显示桌面、工作区选择器或桌面。

一个允许你将鼠标悬停在角栏上以显示桌面的新选项。


Nemo 的更新



Nemo 文件管理器做了一些调整；现在，当文件被选中时，只会高亮显示文件名，而不是图标和文件名。

如果你还不知道, 你也可以通过我们建议的一些调整来增强 Nemo 文件管理器的体验：


调整 Linux 中的 Nemo 文件管理器，让它更好用的 15 种方法


此外，桌面图标被垂直翻转，桌面上下文菜单中添加了一个新的快捷方式，可以快速打开显示设置。

更少的密码提示

这是很多人可能喜欢的另一个用户体验调整。

当删除 Flatpak 或任何快捷方式或本地应用程序时，它将不再要求你输入密码。

类似地，在新立得（LCTT 译注：Linux 下的一个包管理工具）和更新管理器的情况下，将使用 pkexec 来记住密码。

这样，用户就不需要每次执行多个操作时都输入密码。

你可以浏览 Linux Mint 月度博客 以了解其它变化。


via: https://news.itsfoss.com/linux-mint-update-manager/

作者：Sourav Rudra 选题：lkxed 译者：qfzy1233 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[如何快速做出一个合格的PPT：我的思考与实践]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76433</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76433"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T23:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[什么是合格的PPT？
我们做演示幻灯片（后用PPT指代）最好的结果是什么？就是让自己想要传达的目标与听众期待的目标尽量匹配，如何能达成这效果，那就能说这样PPT是合格的。

 
我们拿可以称之为每年“年度最佳PPT”的苹果发布会举例，苹果想要传达的是“我们又创造了一些NB的产品，快来买!"，而用户期待的是“今年又会拿什么让人惊叹的产品跟功能出来震撼到我”，苹果为了传达产品的厉害之处，会用大大的数字突出性能提升百分比，会通过一个个实际使用场景来说明新功能能够帮助用户解决痛点，会通过层层递进的方式，让爆点越来越大，惊喜接踵而来……通过一系列的手段来满足用户的期待，通过发布会让新产品特性，深刻的传达到用户脑中。

 
说完了飘在天上的，再来说些更加接地气的，例如打工人每年必须要做的年终总结PPT。
年终总结大部分人的目标应该是“快看我今年干了好多好多的事，没闲着，给我多点年终奖”，很多初入职场的打工人会把做过的所有事情堆进PPT中，来个十几页，希望领导看到，“我今年都干了这么多事情了，没有功劳也有苦劳吧”，但是这样的PPT不是领导所期望的。

领导其实期望看到的是“你为今年的目标做了什么，有什么成长，明年如何达成目标”，归根到底就是要表现出你这个人如何，有没有潜力，值不值得被激励。还有你的领导也需要对上汇报，你报告里的部分内容将会成为他的汇报内容，他要达成的汇报目标是“今年目标我们团队是这样达成的，整个团队在成长，明年我们将会达成更高的目标”，他要表现出自己是一个合格的团队领导，能够带领团队完成目标，他也希望拿到更多的年终奖或者升职。
看完上面的分析，我想你应该清楚一个合格的年终总结PPT应该怎么做了吧，多写自己是如何的优秀，如何帮助完成了团队年终目标，自己的成长以及明年的计划，对于一些与团队目标关系不大的工作，可以简单带过。
大而广之，其实做任何内容输出，都不要脱离或者偏离自己…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>陈勇_Dennis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 Best Outdoor Deals From REI’s 'Gear Up Get Out' Sale]]></title>
        <id>637296467268ef35e219ba01</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/rei-gear-up-get-out-sale-outdoor-deals-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T23:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The retailer usually skips Black Friday, so snag these discounts now through November 21 on our favorite outdoor gear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Jancer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Snapdragon 8 Gen 2 brings Wi-Fi 7, sticks with some 32-bit support]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897640</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897640"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T23:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Features 32-bit support, Wi-Fi 7, the AV1 codec, and hardware ray tracing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hobbyist adds a hinge to the Game Boy Pocket, delighting everyone]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898074</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898074"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T22:24:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No, it's not a Game Boy Advance SP. This is the monochrome Pocket with hinge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study: Ötzi the Iceman probably thawed and refroze several times]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897727</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1897727"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T22:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This would increase the odds of finding another prehistoric human body in melting ice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Provision a Home Lab with Oracle Cloud and Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/provision-home-lab-with-oracle-cloud-and-ansible/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/provision-home-lab-with-oracle-cloud-and-ansible/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T21:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine for a moment that you been working hard to setup a website, protected with SSL, and then your hardware fails. This means that unless you have a perfect backup of your machine, you will need to install all the software and configuration files by hand. What if it's not]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Right-wing doctor group led by anti-vaccine insurrectionist implodes in scandal]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898062</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1898062"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T21:24:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simone Gold used charity funds to buy $3.6M house, group leaders claim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL DATE – Function, Query, Timestamp Example Format]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-date-function-query-timestamp-example-format/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-date-function-query-timestamp-example-format/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T18:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dates are an integral part of any programming language, and SQL is no exception. When you insert data into your SQL database, you can add a date and query the database based on that date. In this article, you’ll learn about DATE functions in SQL and how to query a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ConvertKit Pack for Coda — Manage and grow your ConvertKit audience from Coda.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/convertkit-pack-for-coda</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/convertkit-pack-for-coda"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T18:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bunny Studio ONE — Unify your content creation needs.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/bunny-studio-one</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/bunny-studio-one"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T16:54:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add ESLint to an Angular Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-eslint-to-an-angular-application/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-eslint-to-an-angular-application/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T16:39:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll build a web application using the latest version of  Angular [https://angular.io/]. Then we'll add ESLint [https://eslint.org/] which analyzes the JavaScript code statically to find any problems. Prerequisites Before you start, you need to install and configure the tools below (if you don't already have them]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rodrigo Kamada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Stratified Random Sampling? Definition and Python Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-stratified-random-sampling-definition-and-python-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-stratified-random-sampling-definition-and-python-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T16:33:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we wish to conduct an experiment on a population – for example, the entire population of a country – it is not always practical or realistic to include every subject (citizen) in the experiment.  Instead, we rely on a sample, which is a subset of the population, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ibrahim Abayomi Ogunbiyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malloc VPN: Privacy & Security — Enjoy privacy and spyware protection at the same time.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/malloc-vpn-privacy-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/malloc-vpn-privacy-security"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T16:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YepCode Recipes — JavaScript snippets to connect any service, database or API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/yepcode-recipes</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/yepcode-recipes"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T16:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://yepcode.io/book-a-demo/)

We would love to hear feedback from the PH community about our product ❤️. If you have any questions, feel free to post them here and we'll be happy to answer them.

Some other useful links:
* 👩‍🎓 Docs platform: https://docs.yepcode.io/
* ❓ FAQs: https://yepcode.io/faqs/
* 📅 Book a demo: https://yepcode.io/book-a-demo/
* 🙋‍♂️ Create your FREE account: https://cloud.yepcode.io/

Thanks a lot 🙏  and happy coding 🧑‍💻
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cannot use import statement outside a module [React TypeScript Error Solved]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cannot-use-import-statement-outside-a-module-react-typescript-error-solved/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cannot-use-import-statement-outside-a-module-react-typescript-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T15:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When building a web application, you may encounter the SyntaxError: Cannot use import statement outside a module error.  This error might be raised when using either JavaScript or TypeScript in the back-end. So you could be working on the client side with React, Vue, and so on, and still]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage State in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manage-state-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manage-state-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T15:17:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React state management is a process for managing the data that React components need in order to render themselves. This data is typically stored in the component's state object. When the state object changes, the component will re-render itself. React state management is basically half of a React app. It]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Square Off Pro Chessboard Rekindled My Love of Chess]]></title>
        <id>636d0dec3bb084d7eff58796</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/square-off-pro-chessboard-rave/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Square Off Pro is an internet-connected board you can roll up to take anywhere—and to play with opponents around the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian Chokkattu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Best Cheap Smartphones (2022): iPhone, Android, 5G]]></title>
        <id>5a8f727d213ac83aca7f0a36</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-cheap-phones/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s little reason to pay top dollar for a smartphone. These iPhones and Android devices—ranging from $150 to $500—stood up to WIRED’s testing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian Chokkattu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benchmade Three-Piece Chef's Knife Set Review: Light and Sharp]]></title>
        <id>61faa5c876dc596711677884</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/benchmade-three-piece-chef-knife-set/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pocketknife brand takes on the kitchen with this surprisingly excellent chef's knife set.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gilbertson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Infinite Cloud Is a Fantasy]]></title>
        <id>636287740b9dedd635bdb041</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cloud-data-storage-climate/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's all too easy to believe in the illusion of neverending data storage and streaming. But it's destroying the natural world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Gonzalez Monserrate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Talent Ferret — Revolutionising the future of creative talent discovery.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/talent-ferret</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/talent-ferret"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T13:54:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Translation App Helped My Mother and Me Say ‘I Love You’]]></title>
        <id>633f48cbbcdcb5ab4377293e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/how-translation-app-helped-me-say-i-love-you-my-mother/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Through the app, my mom and I shared emotional words we hadn’t dared utter before.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jean Trinh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple TV 4K (2022) Review: Better Every Watch]]></title>
        <id>636c1447ab9086067e9f2687</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/apple-tv-4k-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you hate your TV interface but love your iPhone, this is probably the device for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Parker Hall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Will Pay the Price for Big Tech’s Hubris?]]></title>
        <id>63724ad4b25bbf8e38fd5bb9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/who-will-pay-the-price-for-big-techs-hubris/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WIRED’s editor in chief mulls what lies in store for Elon Musk and Sam Bankman-Fried, plus more thoughts on the past week’s headlines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gideon Lichfield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe’s Cities Are Getting More Crowded—That’s a Good Thing]]></title>
        <id>637318978cea9c334692604f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/europe-cities-populations/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sprawling mass of suburbia has been a disaster for the environment. But now smaller, denser cities herald a renaissance in city living.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WIRED's 2022 Wish List: 42 Incredible Gifts to Give and Get]]></title>
        <id>6361584300e08e244b10a51b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/wish-list-2022-incredible-gifts/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From a tricked-out ebike to speakers that sound like a dream, these are all the presents you’ll need to supercharge the holidays.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gear Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hunt for the Dark Web’s Biggest Kingpin, Part 4: Face to Face]]></title>
        <id>63503ad72721236bcb158484</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/alphabay-series-part-4-face-to-face/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The team uses a secret technique to locate AlphaBay’s server. But just as the operation heats up, the agents have an unexpected run-in with their target.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[如何在 Linux 中确定运行的是那种初始化系统]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15256-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15256-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T10:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[你可以通过以下方式确定你的 Linux 发行版中是否正在运行 systemd 或其它初始化系统。


首个进程在你启动 Linux 发行版时开始运行，它称为初始化进程 init（初始化initialization的缩写）。它的进程标识符为 1（即 pid=1）。基于 Unix 的系统中的所有进程和应用程序都是这个初始化进程的后代。

根据功能和特性，存在不同类型的初始化进程。例如，systemd、Runit、OpenRC、sysVinit 等。其中，systemd 是最流行和最现代的一种，被包括 Ubuntu 和 Fedora 在内的所有现代 Linux 发行版使用和采用。

与传统的基于 Unix 的初始化系统相比，systemd 及其性能一直存在争议。但这就是另外一个话题了。

让我们看看如何确定在 Linux 发行版中运行的是 systemd 还是其它初始化系统。

systemd 还是其它初始化系统？

不幸的是，没有直接的命令可以找到它。你可以从初始化进程追溯它，它基本上是到 /sbin/init 的符号链接，即 pid=1。

使用 strings 命令打印嵌入在二进制文件 /sbin/init 中的文本并使用以下命令搜索 init：

strings /sbin/init | grep init


示例 1

在下面的输出中，它是一个运行 Debian（Peppermint OS）的 sysVinit 系统。如你所见，它清楚地显示了 init 进程名称。

strings /sbin/init | grep init




如果在上述同一个系统中找 systemd，那么不会有任何结果。因此，你可以得出结论，你正在运行 sysVinit 而不是 systemd。

示例 2

如果你在 systemd 系统中运行上述命令，你可以在输出的第一行轻松看到 systemd 及其版本。

strings /sbin/init | grep systemd




示例 3

你也可以尝试使用 pstree 命令打印进程树，它应该会显示第一个进程名称。它应该是 systemd 或 init，如下例所示。

pstree






这就好了。这样你就可以轻松找出你的发行版是使用 systemd 还是其他的。


via: https://www.debugpoint.com/systemd-or-init/

作者：Arindam 选题：lkxed 译者：geekpi 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[硬核观察 #821 手写代码导致美国宇航局的水手号探测器失败]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15255-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15255-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T08:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[手写代码导致美国宇航局的水手号探测器失败

1962 年夏天，美国宇航局启动了水手 1 号任务，这是一项无人驾驶的任务，该装置将飞过金星并探测数据。当时的工程师通常在纸上写出他们的代码。然后这些代码通过一个复杂的系统被翻译成计算机可读的卡片，然后通过计算机执行该程序。这种手工使得意外错误率变得很高。缺失的符号与字符最终导致了水手 1 号任务的彻底失败。这次任务在当时花费了大约 1800 万美元，相当于今天的 1.5 亿美元。


消息来源：Slash Gear



老王点评：计算机发展早期，不说流程，就是工具也很简陋。但是就是这样，也送上天那么多飞行器。




一个简单的安卓锁屏漏洞获得了 7 万美元

研究人员发现，任何能拿到谷歌 Pixel 手机的人都可以通过换上自己的 SIM 卡，并输入预设的恢复代码，从而绕过安卓操作系统的锁屏保护。这个漏洞的利用非常简单，但谷歌花了大约五个月的时间来修复。谷歌为此向他支付了 7 万美元的奖金。


消息来源：Tech Crunch



老王点评：看似这个钱挣的容易，但是实际上研究人员投入了大量精力才可能遇到这样一块“狗头金”。




英特尔推出深度伪造实时检测工具

深度伪造视频现在无处不在，你可能见过名人做或说他们实际上从未做过的事情的视频。英特尔开发了 FakeCatcher，这项技术能够以 96% 的准确率检测虚假人脸视频。这是世界上第一个实时深度伪造检测器，它可以在几毫秒内返回结果。该工具是通过检测视频像素中微妙的“血流”信号，在真实视频中寻找真实的线索。当心脏泵血时，人的静脉会改变颜色，这些血流信号是可以从面部各处收集的，算法将这些信号翻译成时空图。然后，利用深度学习，就可以立即检测出一个视频是真的还是假的。


消息来源：PC Gamer



老王点评：果然魔高一尺，道高一丈。不过我想深度伪造可能很快就会学会添加血流信号。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UPack压缩的PE文件头解析及调试]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11847</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11847"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T08:47:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPack压缩的PE文件头解析及调试]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My favorite tricks for navigating the Linux terminal faster]]></title>
        <id>70317 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/navigate-linux-terminal-faster"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My favorite tricks for navigating the Linux terminal faster
Anamika
Tue, 11/15/2022 - 03:00

            
One of the advantages of working in a terminal is that it's faster than most other interfaces. Thanks to the GNU Readline library and the built-in syntax of shells like Bash and Zsh, there are several ways to make your interactions with the command line even faster. Here are five ways to make the most of your time in the terminal.
1. Navigate without the arrow keys
While executing commands on the command line, sometimes you miss a part at the beginning or forget to add certain tags or arguments toward the end. It's common for users to use the Left and Right arrow keys on the keyboard to move through a command to make edits.
There's a better way to get around the command line. You can m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anamika</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What do you do with community metrics?]]></title>
        <id>70300 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/what-do-you-do-community-metrics"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What do you do with community metrics?
Georg Link
Tue, 11/15/2022 - 03:00

            
In my previous article, I provided an overview of possible community health metrics. I look at what you can do with those metrics in this article. You'll see several examples from different communities, some of which you may be familiar with.
Contribution metric
I'll start with the "new contributors and contributions" metric, which measures developers joining and leaving a community. I can measure this by seeing which developers made a commit during a specific period. Someone who shows up for the first time joined. Someone who hasn't contributed for a while has probably left.
It is natural for developers to leave a project. Maybe they change jobs, have a change in priorities, or have personal reasons fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Georg Link</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Distill Web Monitor – 监控网页「任意区域」变化，实时提醒]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43906</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/distill-web-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T07:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Distill Web Monitor 是一款专门用来监控网页任意区域变化，并发出实时提醒的工具，支持 Chrome、Firefox、Opear，以及拥有 Android 与 iOS 客户端。@App]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[赶海观察日记：专业赶海人如何赶海？]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76797</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76797"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T06:20:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[会呲水的猫眼螺、遇盐出洞的蛏子、卧沙总是卧一半的蛤蜊……
如果你经常看赶海视频的话，对这些出镜率极高的海洋生物都不会感到陌生。近年来生活类自媒体的蓬勃发展，使得赶海1这一沿海地区的常见活动也得以进入镜头，并逐渐为大众所熟知。
然而，赶海真的像视频里那样，一袋食盐、一把小铲，在沙滩上挖几下，就能轻松收获一桶海鲜吗？镜头之外的真实赶海生活，是什么样子的呢？专业赶海人都如何赶海呢？
居住在北方某沿海城市的我，虽然不是一个专业的赶海人，但几次赶海下来，倒是收获了一肚子见闻，遂整理出这篇观察日记，以飨读者。
赶海群体：什么人在赶海？
第一类是专业赶海人。专业赶海人从外观上是最容易辨别出来的群体，他们的装备专业且齐全，从头戴式探照灯到防水雨裤，从钓竿到抽虾筒。他们干活熟练麻利，且通常不会聚集作业，而是分散开来、独自行动，一人承包一片区域，维持着互不侵犯、心照不宣的默契。对他们来说，赶海是经济收入的重要来源，他们所收获的海产品可用于贩卖，有时也会「拿回自己家做着吃」。
夜钓的大爷，穿着雨裤方便下海放鱼饵。交谈中大爷自述是因身背负债而每晚赶海。摄于10月29日。
第二类是业余赶海人，以村民和游客为主，他们的熟练程度、赶海目的也各不相同。
附近村庄的居民对赶海更熟悉些，更善于寻找海洋生物的呼吸孔。尽管装备不如专业赶海人那么齐全，但他们仅凭一把小铲子和一个小桶，也能有相当不错的收获，足够做一顿饭。一次赶海时，我们碰见了一对年轻的小情侣，听口音像是附近的村民，女生向我展示了当晚的收获——小半桶的狗虾，并「打算回去拿椒盐炒着吃」。
游客则多半是抱着玩乐的心态，将赶海当成一次有趣的家庭活动。
图片来源：网络
赶海攻略：时间，装备和收获
赶海时间
赶海前需要提前查好当地的潮汐时间表，重点关注水位高度和涨潮、落潮时间。每天的落潮时间有所不同，一般初一、十五会落大潮，海水退得更远，给赶海人提供了更广阔的探…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>katejate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（九）番外篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11845</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11845"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T06:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（九）番外篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fluent Search | 一款高颜值 Windows 搜索软件]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76810</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76810"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T06:08:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[平台：Windows 10/11
下载：官网、微软商店（部分功能受限）

Fluent Search 一款不满足于只提供「Fluent 流畅」搜索体验，还想在外观、交互、工作流上进一步拓展的高颜值搜索软件。
Fluent 设计 + 个性化
相关设置页面：外观、特效、主页
颜值就是生产力，这句话在 Windows 平台似乎并没有得到很好的验证，关注 Windows 的用户都知道微软虽有设计规范，但对软件生态的掌控力约等于没有，连自家应用也不一定会及时跟进，更何况第三方软件，因此在 Windows 平台上一款遵守规范且好看的应用是可遇不可求的。身为一款随时随地都有可能跟用户打交道的应用，好看的设计会让用户体验更上一层楼。以下是其三种搜索窗口基础样式：
搜索栏 + 自定义图标、水印窗口窗口 + 主页 = 类开始菜单风格
Fluent Search 不仅自带不同风格的主题，同时也提供大量的选项让其更具个性化，从浅色、深色模式，到窗口样式、大小、字体、图标、水印、颜色、透明材质、动画等都可调整。不同于其它跨平台的应用，基于 C# 开发的 Fluent Search 可以快速跟进 Windows 新设计的同时仍有着原生的性能表现。

「流畅」搜索
相关设置页面：搜索、文件、标签、屏幕、应用内搜索、上下文、网页、进程、应用程序、UI
搜索可以说是该类软件的基本功，一个优秀的索引器决定着它的基础用户体验，Fluent Search 的索引器除了可以搜索文件、目录、设置、进程、应用程序、浏览器（火狐需要安装插件）书签和历史记录，还可以对部分格式进行全文搜索，当你只想查相关内容时，通过 files content 标签即可进行搜索，不过受限于性能，搜索内容需要超过 3 个字符才会进行搜索。
全文搜索
作为一款外国软件， Fluent Search 也提供了中文搜索，全拼、拼音首字母搜索都支持，…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Not_your_user</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APTV – 直播流播放器，播放在线 m3u8 视频，支持回放[iPhone/iPad/AppleTV]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43903</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/aptv-m3u8-player/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T04:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[APTV 是一款可实时预览的直播流播放器，用于播放在线 m3u8 视频，或本地 m3u8 文件，对于支持的源，还可以进行回放，支持 iOS、iPadOS、tvOS、macOS。@Appinn 感谢 @]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring环境下的回显总结]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11844</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11844"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T03:42:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spring环境下的回显总结]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一次对基于thinkphp开发程序的审计]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11838</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11838"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T02:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一次对基于thinkphp开发程序的审计]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter’s SMS Two-Factor Authentication Is Melting Down]]></title>
        <id>6372ad717268ef35e219ba02</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-two-factor-sms-problems/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T01:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Problems with the important security feature may be some of the first signs that Elon Musk’s social network is fraying at the edges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter’s SMS Two-Factor Authentication Is Melting Down]]></title>
        <id>6372ad717268ef35e219ba02</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-two-factor-sms-problems/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T01:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Problems with the important security feature may be some of the first signs that Elon Musk’s social network is fraying at the edges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion AI — Meet your new partner in thought]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/notion-ai-alpha</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/notion-ai-alpha"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T22:12:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Declare an Array in JavaScript – Creating an Array in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-declare-an-array-in-javascript-creating-an-array-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-declare-an-array-in-javascript-creating-an-array-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T21:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, an array is one of the most commonly used data types. It stores multiple values and elements in one variable. These values can be of any data type — meaning you can store a string, number, boolean, and other data types in one variable. There are two standard]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radiance Voice Chrome Extension — Record and share voice notes straight from your brower tab]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/radiance-voice-chrome-extension</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/radiance-voice-chrome-extension"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T20:24:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Radiance Voice Extension will be one of them.

😄*Why did we make this?*
All of us spend the majority of our time on web apps that help us work such as Sheets/Excel or Word/Docs, Notion/Confluence, Jira/Basecamp, Figma, Miro, Hubspot, Zoho, Salesforce, Gmail, etc. Many times we want to explain to others what we think about something on our screen, like a dashboard, a customer's account, or many times, the apps that we ourselves are building. I thought if there were a way to create voice notes straight from the browser and share them with others, the other person could listen to it in their own time, as opposed to getting on a call and discussing things.

🤨*What's so different about this extension?*
How many times do keep your camera off in our online meetings? I think many times. Especial…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Recursion in JavaScript?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/recursion-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/recursion-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T18:44:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recursion is a problem-solving technique in programming. In this article, you will learn how to use recursive functions in JavaScript. What is a Recursive Function? A recursive function is a function that calls itself somewhere within the body of the function. Below is a basic example of a recursive function.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nike Will Let People Design and Sell Sneakers for the Metaverse]]></title>
        <id>637286057268ef35e219b9fe</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/nike-will-let-people-design-and-sell-sneakers-for-the-metaverse/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T18:21:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swoosh members will compete to create digital kicks with the brand’s design staff and bag a royalty cut. But not even Nike knows how it’s going to work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francesca Perry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[浅析PHP GC垃圾回收机制及常见利用方式]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11843</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11843"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T16:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[浅析PHP GC垃圾回收机制及常见利用方式]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[为什么有时候域名的末尾有个点？]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15254-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15254-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T16:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[大家好！今年早些时候，我在写《DNS 是如何工作的》 时，有人问我——为什么人们有时在域名的末尾加一个点？例如，如果你通过运行 dig example.com 查询 example.com 的 IP，你会看到一下内容：

$ dig example.com
example.com.        5678    IN  A   93.184.216.34


执行完 dig 命令后，example.com 有一个 . ——变成了 example.com.！发生了什么？

有些 DNS 工具也要求传给它的域名后加一个 .：如果你在使用 miekg/dns 时传给它 example.com，它会报错：

// trying to send this message will return an error
m := new(dns.Msg)
m.SetQuestion("example.com", dns.TypeA)


最初我以为我知道这个问题的答案（“呃，末尾的点意味着域名是完全限定的？”）。这是对的 —— 一个完全限定域名fully qualified domain name（FQDN）是一个末尾有 . 的域名！

但是为什么末尾的点是有用且重要的呢？

在 DNS 的请求/响应中，域名的末尾并没有 “.”

我曾经（错误地）认为 “为什么末尾有一个点？”的答案可能是 “在 DNS 请求/响应中，域名末尾有一个 .，所以我们把它放进去，以匹配你的计算机实际发送/接收的内容”。但事实并不是这样！

当计算机发送 DNS 请求/响应时，域名的末尾并没有点。实际上，域名中没有点。

域名会被编码成一系列的长度/字符串对。例如，域名 example.com 被编码为这 13 个字节。

7example3com0


编码后的内容一个点也没有…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Care Platform by Nabla — The Machine Learning powered patient engagement platform.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/digital-care-platform-by-nabla</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/digital-care-platform-by-nabla"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T16:09:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[如何在没有互联网连接的情况下离线更新 Ubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://linux.cn/article-15253-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss</id>
        <link href="https://linux.cn/article-15253-1.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T15:29:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[本指南介绍了如何在没有互联网连接的情况下离线更新 Ubuntu 的步骤。


在很多情况下，你可能需要在没有互联网连接的情况下更新你的 Ubuntu 系统。你可能在外地不方便上网，也可能你需要更新一堆未联网的 Ubuntu，不管是哪种情况，保持你的系统更新最新的软件包总是需要的。

当然，始终建议通过联网来更新系统。

但有时，出于安全考虑，这是不行的。连接到互联网可能需要给你的系统进行额外的加固，以保护它们免受黑客和恶意软件的攻击。

以下的方法使用 apt-offline 来解决这些问题，并概述了在没有互联网的情况下离线更新 Ubuntu 的步骤。

准备环节


一台能连接到网络的 Ubuntu（你朋友的、咖啡馆、实验室系统）

存储了软件包的 U 盘

两个系统都安装了 apt-offline：一个系统离线，另一个系统联网


安装 apt-offline

在两个系统下安装 apt-offline。你可以使用以下命令安装：

sudo apt install apt-offline


如果你想在离线的目标系统安装 apt-offline，你可以提前下载到 U 盘里，然后复制到目标系统，再使用下面的命令安装。

Ubuntu 22.04 LTS 和其他版本的下载链接如下所示。你可以选择一个镜像并下载 deb 文件。


下载 .deb 文件 – apt-offline


sudo dpkg -i name_of_package.deb


如何更新 Ubuntu

在离线的目标系统上打开终端，使用以下命令创建一个 .sig 签名文件：

sudo apt-offline set ~/offline-data.sig




在这个刚创建的签名文件中，包含下载所需的软件包的路径和详细信息。



把签名文件复制到 U 盘中，再插到联网的 Ubuntu 系统上。

在联网的 Ubuntu 上创建一个目录（参见下面）来存放这些文件。

打开一个终端，运行以下命令来下载所需的软件包。记得根据你的系统，更改下载目录和 .sig 签名文件的路径。

apt-offline get -d ~/offline-data-dir offline-data.sig




你可以看到文件相应下载，然后复制整个下载目录到 U 盘，再插到离线的 Ubuntu 系统。

运行以下命令将下载的软件包安装到离线系统，记得根据你的系统更改目录路径。

sudo apt-offline install offline-data-dir/




如果一切顺利，你将获得一个更新完的 Ubuntu。

重复以上步骤，就可以保持你的离线 Ubuntu 为最新版本。

希望以上教程能帮到你更新离线的 Ubuntu 系统，如果你遇到任何问题，请在下面的评论框中告诉我。


via: https://www.debugpoint.com/how-to-update-or-upgrade-ubuntu-offline-without-internet/

作者：Arindam 选题：lkxed 译者：littlebirdnest 校对：wxy

本文由 LCTT 原创编译，Linux中国 荣誉推出]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>linux@linux.cn (linux)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[跨平台重构CobaltStrike的Beacon并使行为对主流杀软免杀]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11839</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11839"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T15:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[跨平台重构CobaltStrike的Beacon并使行为对主流杀软免杀]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cue Health Cue Reader Review: Accurate and Expensive Covid-19 Test Kit]]></title>
        <id>615482f44a470b3dd369cb42</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/cue-health-cue-reader/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This at-home diagnostic Covid-19 test kit is ridiculously expensive, but it's accurate and dead simple to use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brenda Stolyar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[14 Gift Ideas for the Home Chef (2022): Vitamix, Cookbooks, and More]]></title>
        <id>618149631c2f944a21fd2e93</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/gift-ideas-for-the-home-chef-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the real everyday pan to the best Instant Pot, we have ideas that will keep the curious cook in your life tinkering away.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gilbertson, Joe Ray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Phone Can Determine If a Bridge Is Busted]]></title>
        <id>636aa1756776a0176c76e56d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/your-phone-can-determine-if-a-bridge-is-busted/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any smartphone in any car can pick up a span’s unique vibrations. Tracking how that changes over time reveals hidden structural problems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pandemic Bike Boom Survives—in Cities That Stepped Up]]></title>
        <id>636c0e98557521d0988d4fe1</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-pandemic-bike-boom-survives-in-cities-that-stepped-up/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Covid lockdowns prompted a surge of new cyclists. But the trend has faltered in places that didn't build bike-friendly infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aarian Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Syng Cell Alpha Wireless Speakers Review: Spatial Sorcery, Bass Bother]]></title>
        <id>636e5d57557521d0988d5004</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/review/review-syng-cell-alpha-wireless-speakers/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a quest to reimagine the loudspeaker, this audio company has worked serious magic—but there's a big bass problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simon Lucas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Ebikes for Elderly Riders: Trek, Rad Power, Gazelle]]></title>
        <id>636c3829557521d0988d4fe6</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ebikes-for-elders/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electric bikes may seem like the perfect transport for active, aging folks, but do your homework before plugging into the trend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Pearson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Man Behind Mastodon, Eugen Rochko, Built It for This Moment]]></title>
        <id>636ed7f60ae5a121565fd72a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-man-behind-mastodon-eugen-rochko-built-it-for-this-moment/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People fleeing Twitter have turned to Eugen Rochko’s alternative. He says social networks can support healthy debate—without any one person in control.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The $6 Billion Shot at Making New Antibiotics]]></title>
        <id>636508c7c3bf45de80681ba9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-6-billion-dollar-shot-at-making-new-antibiotics-before-the-old-ones-fail/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Antimicrobials cost as much to develop as other drugs, but don’t earn the same returns. Congress could give drugmakers a boost, but time is running out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maryn McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No, Qatar’s World Cup Can’t Be Classed as Carbon-Neutral]]></title>
        <id>636edaf2a987df54c26b26ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/qatar-2022-world-cup-emissions/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite efforts to reduce emissions, the 2022 FIFA tournament is highly carbon-intensive. And its road to net-zero relies on questionable carbon credits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>William Ralston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awesome Productivity Tools for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-productivity-tools-for-developers-40lj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-productivity-tools-for-developers-40lj"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #beginners #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Vishwakarma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 metrics to track in your open source community]]></title>
        <id>70298 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/community-metrics"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[5 metrics to track in your open source community
Georg Link
Mon, 11/14/2022 - 03:00

            
The core of open source is about using, sharing, and collaborating in software creation. With its roots in the free software movement and ensuring the rights of software users, open source has evolved from being solely the work of volunteers and hobbyists to also include the enterprise.
Collaborative software development has taken on a new dimension in the last 5 to 10 years. Today open source makes up 58% of software in the enterprise. In fact, 63% of companies in a 2021 survey indicated wanting to increase their use and engagement with open source.
Open source is everywhere and forms the digital infrastructure we rely on. The US issued a directive mandating more software supply chain securit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Georg Link</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make swap better with zram on Linux]]></title>
        <id>70277 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/customize-zram-linux"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Make swap better with zram on Linux
David Both
Mon, 11/14/2022 - 03:00

            
Zram is a compressed RAM disk on Linux. Lately, it's been put to use for swap space on many distributions. In my previous article, I introduced zram and demonstrated how to use it. In this article, I cover some of the ways you can customize how your system puts zram to use.
Augmented swap
Zram swap can be augmented with standard secondary storage devices. Adding some traditional swap space can be especially useful on systems with low amounts of RAM. (Such augmentation isn't normally useful on hosts with very large amounts of RAM.)
If you do choose to augment swap with some type of storage device, hard drives do still work but are significantly slower than using SSD in either SATA or m.2 formats. However, t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Both</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023 年将至，该如何优雅地记录看过的书籍和电影]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76786</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76786"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T06:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2014 年，那时候我还在读大三，某一天突然萌发了一个想法，要将自己看过的书和电影记录下来。我隐隐约约感受到，沉淀自己的精神生活，竟然让我觉得人生充满意义。记录的瞬间让我觉得会有成就感；等哪天，拿起这份清单，我可以清楚回顾某段时间内看过了哪些书籍和电影，也从侧面知晓当时精神生活的丰富程度
从那时起，我的记录习惯从未断绝过，不知不觉已经 8 年。从最初的用豆瓣记录，到使用纯文本 Markdown 记录，到自己搭建博客，再到使用公众号留言自动生成博客的方式记录。有些方式比较 Geek，不适合普通人，直到去年，我开发了一款 App，来满足跟我有同样需求的普通用户
这就是「已阅：书影记录」，一款快速记录自己看过的书籍和电影的 App，并支持将精美的观影列表和书单海报一键分享给朋友。献给所有希望构建自己精神角落的人

细数曾经那些不够好用的工具
为什么要开发「已阅：书影记录」呢？我综合对比了市面上多款工具，发现如果想要记录自己看过的书籍或电影，使用的方式不外乎以下几类
Excel
这是一类以 Excel 为代表的纯手动记录工具，除了 Excel 还包括在线文档、Notion 甚至是手写到自己的笔记本等
这个方式无疑费时费力，且数据是死的，很难被二次利用（如灵活筛选、统计、分享等）
让人惊讶的是，用这个方式记录的人还真不少，毕竟大部分人找不到更好的办法
豆瓣
豆瓣很伟大，是中文互联网上最全面的书影音资料库。功能上非常丰富，但是正因为它太全了，很难在这个垂直功能上做到极致

豆瓣记录的步骤比较麻烦，且默认会被分享到公共领域，下图是豆瓣和已阅的记录界面对比

 
「豆瓣」和「已阅」的记录界面对比
无法快速回顾，比如我想查看 2022 年看过了哪些书或我看过的所有五星电影，豆瓣都无法支持
「已阅」可以方便地筛选
分享功能缺乏自定义，比如我想自定义分享 2022 年看过了哪些书或我看过的所有五…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>伊塔奇呀</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[影深 – 让 Firefox 变成小说阅读器，为 .TXT 文件自动生成目录、识别标题、主题样式。效果非常赞，书虫必备]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43899</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/yingshen-for-firefox/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T04:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[影深是一个开源的 Firefox 扩展，它能在打开 .txt 文本文件时自动生成目录、识别标题，并可以修改主题样式、字体大小，让 Firefox 瞬间变成小说阅读器，效果非常赞。@Appinn 来自发]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[通过反序列化利用JDBC后门]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11837</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11837"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T02:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[通过反序列化利用JDBC后门]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hunt for the FTX Thieves Has Begun]]></title>
        <id>6371149f0dce9984f0039c8b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ftx-hack-theft-crypto-tracing/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T23:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious crooks took hundreds of millions of dollars from FTX just as it collapsed. Crypto-tracing blockchain analysis may provide an answer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hunt for the FTX Thieves Has Begun]]></title>
        <id>6371149f0dce9984f0039c8b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ftx-hack-theft-crypto-tracing/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T23:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious crooks took hundreds of millions of dollars from FTX just as it collapsed. Crypto-tracing blockchain analysis may provide an answer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sortd 2.0 for Gmail — "Trello for Gmail” Assign & track email with Kanban in Gmail]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/sortd-2-0-for-gmail</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/sortd-2-0-for-gmail"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T20:48:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sortd 2.0 for Gmail.

Why we made Sortd

When we started Sortd, we wanted to change the way email is used to manage work. Since we first launched, we’ve learnt a lot more about our customers’ needs. In many companies IM has largely replaced email for internal communication. But for customer communication, it seems that email is here to stay.  The problem is - email is messy and hard to keep track of.

There just aren't many good tools for keeping track of email and customer-facing work.  The few tools that are good take you away from your email (giving you yet another tool to manage).

Unlike Trello, Asana, Monday, Clickup etc (all amazing tools, which primarily focus on internal collaboration), Sortd gives you a way to manage both internal and external work in the same place. Customer facing teams can use the same communication tool they use every day to work more cohesively with their partners, customers and suppliers (rather than constantly jumping between browser tabs).

We’ve spent countless hours grappling with how best to deal with the needs of a rapidly changing world. And… I think we just might have cracked the code! 🤞

While Sortd remains one of the most tightly email-integrated solutions on planet Earth, it’s now become far more than a workspace for managing tasks and email. Years of learning and speaking with thousands of customers have led us to what we now believe truly is the future of work.

Sortd is a blend of email, shared mailboxes, CRM, team Chat, task management & business workflows. All in one system, in Gmail where you are working already, and your entire team is comfortable.

We would love you to take Sortd for a spin. Please let us know what you think. Enjoy 🥰

[Update Sortd 2.0]
Faster, slicker, easier to use.
Now incorporates new Team mailbox features, Zapier integration and automations.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extensive List of Best Development Resources - 121 Links to Guides, Cheat Sheets and More List of Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/perssondennis/extensive-list-of-best-development-resourses-121-links-to-guides-cheat-sheets-and-more-list-of-resources-366l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/perssondennis/extensive-list-of-best-development-resourses-121-links-to-guides-cheat-sheets-and-more-list-of-resources-366l"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T15:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #beginners #productivity #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dennis Persson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Best USB-C Cables (2022): For iPhones, Android Phones, Tablets, and Laptops]]></title>
        <id>62b97bc32944b6cfb7625f47</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-usb-c-cables/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unravel the tangled world of cords and find the ones you need to charge your gadgets and transfer data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simon Hill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Best TV Streaming Devices for 2022 (4K, HD): Roku vs. Fire TV vs. Apple TV vs. Google]]></title>
        <id>5aeb210a4eef286ed17e4266</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-4k-streaming-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've tested dozens of ways to watch stuff on 4K or HD TVs. These are our favorites.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Medea Giordano, Jeffrey Van Camp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Formerly Incarcerated Job Seekers Need More Than Training]]></title>
        <id>6356aaa7e53b9bdcb463c5e9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/employment-prison-jobs-digital-reputation/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reentry programs help, but tech companies must also modify their hiring systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Lageson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three-Way Entanglement Results Hint at Better Quantum Codes]]></title>
        <id>63694685d7f2f1953e687022</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/three-way-entanglement-results-hint-at-better-quantum-codes/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A team of physicists has entangled three photons over a considerable distance, which could lead to more powerful quantum cryptography.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Parshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Anker MagGo Charger Defeated My Battery Anxiety]]></title>
        <id>636ecdfbc7672aac035d7a34</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/anker-maggo-charger-rave/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anker’s iPhone MagSafe accessories may look like power packs, but they are actually little bundles of life-changing joy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Speight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I'm Obsessed With Bloody Marys. This Is the Best Mix I've Tried]]></title>
        <id>635185da3363e916e706cdcc</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/haand-toma-bloody-mary-kit-rave/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You don't have to say a ghost's name three times in the mirror. The Haand x Toma Brunch Kit makes bloody brunches easy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Medea Giordano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[求将照片转为「手绘头像」的应用]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43895</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/photo-to-hand-painted/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T09:06:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[来自问题频道的问题：有没有一款将照片转为手绘头像的应用啊？免费的 @Good 同学推荐了下面这款应用： 波波头像 不要嫌弃，免费版应用也需要生存之道，波波头像有广告、需要联网使用，支持多种风格： 注意]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stand out in a React interview by rendering a list like a pro]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/andyrewlee/stand-out-in-a-react-interview-by-rendering-a-list-like-a-pro-1cn5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/andyrewlee/stand-out-in-a-react-interview-by-rendering-a-list-like-a-pro-1cn5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T08:18:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #javascript #webdev #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use a hashmap in Java]]></title>
        <id>70310 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/hashmap-java"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use a hashmap in Java
Seth Kenlon
Sun, 11/13/2022 - 03:00

            
In the Java programming language, a hashmap is a list of associated values. Java uses hashmaps to store data. If you keep a lot of structured data, it's useful to know the various retrieval methods available.

More on Java
What is enterprise Java programming?
An open source alternative to Oracle JDK
Java cheat sheet
Red Hat build of OpenJDK
Free online course: Developing cloud-native applications with microservices
Fresh Java articles
Create a hashmap
Create a hashmap in Java by importing and using the HashMap class. When you create a hashmap, you must define what constitutes a valid value (such as Integer or String). A hashmap holds pairs of values.
package com.opensource.example;
import java.util.HashMap;
public clas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Kenlon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Send to Telegram for Google Chrome – 发送网页、图片、链接、文字到 tg 机器人]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43891</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/send-to-telegram-for-google-chrome/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T07:55:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Send to Telegram for Google Chrome 是一款简单易用的 Chrome 扩展，用来在浏览器上发送网页、图片、链接、文字到 tg 机器人。@Appinn 感谢 @S 同学在]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Cheat Sheet with 40+ commands & concepts]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/git-cheat-sheet-with-40-commands-concepts-1m26</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/git-cheat-sheet-with-40-commands-concepts-1m26"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T05:51:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#git #github #programming #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapajyoti Bose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tools I Am Using On A Daily Basis]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yuridevat/tools-i-am-using-on-a-daily-basis-4kb7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yuridevat/tools-i-am-using-on-a-daily-basis-4kb7"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T21:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#tooling #productivity #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julia 👩🏻‍💻</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Introduces Twitter Mayhem Mode]]></title>
        <id>636e769e32968364ac1a7b69</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-twitter-security-mayhem-roundup/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: US midterms survive disinformation efforts, the government names the alleged Lockbit ransomware attacker, and the Powerball drawing hits a security snag.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruv Mehrotra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York Voted to Protect the Planet. California Did Not]]></title>
        <id>6369461a7484c01b9b6e9656</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/new-york-voted-to-protect-the-planet-california-did-not/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voters in two influential states came to opposite conclusions on climate-related ballot measures to fund environmental protections and electric vehicles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jackie Flynn Mogensen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Python: 7 of my favorite resources]]></title>
        <id>70285 at https://opensource.com</id>
        <link href="https://opensource.com/article/22/11/learn-python"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Python: 7 of my favorite resources
Don Watkins
Sat, 11/12/2022 - 03:00

            
I made a decision recently that I wanted to learn more Python so I could improve my instructional skills and broaden the horizons of my students. In the process, I have discovered these excellent resources that have me learning new code and improving my understanding of Python in general.
1. Teach your kids to code
I began the Python journey about seven years ago when I discovered connections between Apple LOGO and the Turtle module in Python. The Linux computer I was using at the time defaulted to Python 2.7, and I soon discovered that I wanted to use Python 3. I managed to get it installed and began writing some simple programs using the Turtle module. After reading Dr. Bryson Payne’s Teach Your Ki…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Don Watkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ultimate List of Startup Tools — The top 44 tools startup founders need to run their business]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ultimate-list-of-startup-tools</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/ultimate-list-of-startup-tools"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T22:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fallout of the FTX Collapse]]></title>
        <id>636e8d8e627a555fd99f22f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-fallout-of-the-ftx-collapse/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Sam Bankman-Fried's crypto empire crumbles, its customers, and other crypto traders, are paying the price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Khalili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Tech’s Layoffs Will Fuel the Industry's Future]]></title>
        <id>636d36b20757f7d06dd271f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/plaintext-big-techs-layoffs-will-fuel-the-industrys-future/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: The dotcom recovery, a history-making online purchase, and the highway to climate hell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Problem With Spinning Spacecraft]]></title>
        <id>635bc62be53b9bdcb463c64a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-problem-with-spinning-spacecraft/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To send astronauts on long-term space missions, it’ll take rotating habitats to produce artificial gravity. But that’s trickier than you might think.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhett Allain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring A Junior’s React Code - 43% Less Code With A Better Data Structure]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jkettmann/refactoring-a-juniors-react-code-43-less-code-with-a-better-data-structure-eam</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jkettmann/refactoring-a-juniors-react-code-43-less-code-with-a-better-data-structure-eam"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #javascript #webdev #frontend]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Johannes Kettmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Despite Big Layoffs, Tech Workers Are Still in Demand]]></title>
        <id>636c1c5bab9086067e9f2688</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/despite-big-layoffs-meta-twitter-stripe-tech-workers-are-still-in-demand/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tens of thousands of job cuts have rocked the industry, but unemployment among tech workers remains low—and plenty of companies are desperate for talent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amanda Hoover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter Is on a Collision Course With Europe]]></title>
        <id>636d5c60ab9086067e9f268d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-europe-elon-musk/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Layoffs leave only two people in the company’s Brussels office, just as Europe prepares to enforce sweeping new tech rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Morgan Meaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Great Truffle Shortage Is Coming]]></title>
        <id>636d5dfba3291a07ef8cdbd7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/climate-change-truffle-hunting/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harvests of the fungi are plummeting as Europe gets drier, pushing the prices of some varieties to eye-watering heights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Baraniuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Dark Ships’ Emerge From the Shadows of the Nord Stream Mystery]]></title>
        <id>636d7ff21f24b6f9091f7b8f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/nord-stream-pipeline-explosion-dark-ships/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Satellite monitors discovered two vessels with their trackers turned off in the area of the pipeline prior to the suspected sabotage in September.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[在外独居，我想分享下我如何面对孤独]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76378</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76378"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T10:49:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[前言
在经历了成都连续的半个月高温居家办公，以及两周的疫情封控后，我思考了一下关于城市生活与孤独的关系，以及如何排解孤独，理解孤独。在这一个多月中，我一直是一个人在屋子里，未曾踏出家一步。我不是一个爱做饭柴米油盐的人，就这样，在家中面对着日复一日的琐事，面对没有人可以说话的孤独，面对着工作、生活的焦虑。在与安静和极度的自由的碰撞里，除了偶尔的空虚与崩溃以外，我想分享一下我如何逐渐的找回自己的生活节奏，并喜欢上一个人安排自己的方方面面。
孤独是什么

如果我们所期待的人际关系数量和质量与我们当前实际情形存在较大差距，就会产生令人不悦的厌烦、悲伤和绝望的孤独体验（de Jong Gierveld et al.，2006）。

孤独有两种：
其一是社会隔离，指缺少朋友和熟人的社交。
你或许也有这样的感受，常常用「社恐」来武装自己，鲜少与人交流。那怕是点个外卖、出门买个东西都是能不交流就不交流。性格内向的人更喜欢和自己交流，陶醉在自己所热爱的精神世界之中。在周末和假期，相比和朋友出去游玩他们更倾向于选择在家中折腾自己的爱好，渐渐的在和陌生人交往时变的畏惧，不知所措。久而久之，除了身边寥寥无几的挚友以外，几乎没有任何的交流，孤独感进一步加深。
其二是情感隔离，指缺少亲密而深厚的情感关系。
人生活在社会中，总是会渴望着被他人理解的。有的人虽然辗转于各种聚会，时时刻刻都沉浸在热闹场合之中，但是浮于表面的热闹并不总是意味着有人真正了解自己。可能你真正渴望的目标无人诉说，心中的艰苦无人知晓。理解就像是人生的底色，我们渴望着，但却不可能有人能完全理解自己。
孤独的危害
对于大部分人来说，长期保持孤独是有一定危害的。
在生理上，长期孤独的人血压更高，更容易发生应激反应。在晚上的时候孤独也会让人辗转反侧，不仅睡眠质量下降，免疫力也会随之一起走下坡路。
在生活中，孤独有时候也会带来不少的麻烦，比如因…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dluck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenCore Legacy Patcher – 为老款 Mac 电脑（2006 年以后）安装最新 macOS Ventura 13 操作系统]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43886</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/opencore-legacy-patcher/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T09:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenCore Legacy Patcher 是一个开源项目，用来让老款 Mac 电脑（2006 年以后）也能安装最新 macOS 操作系统。@Appinn 感谢 @蚁工厂 的推荐。 在苹果不久前发]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[jpress代码审计分享]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11832</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11832"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[jpress代码审计分享]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Java安全]关于Rhino的一些姿势利用]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11831</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11831"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T04:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Java安全]关于Rhino的一些姿势利用]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[可逆打码 – 居然可以「涩图打码，付费解码」😂]]></title>
        <id>https://www.appinn.com/?p=43883</id>
        <link href="https://www.appinn.com/kenidama-for-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T04:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[可逆打码是一款有趣的 Windows 工具，它可以为图片添加马赛克，但只需要输入密码，即可去掉马赛克，还原图片。@Appinn 来自发现频道，开发者 @lzn1007 自荐：可以无损解码的打码软件。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>青小蛙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Things I Wish I'd Known When Starting My Coding Journey]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marisabrantley/10-things-i-wish-id-known-when-starting-my-coding-journey-3ga1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marisabrantley/10-things-i-wish-id-known-when-starting-my-coding-journey-3ga1"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T03:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #beginners #codenewbie #devjournal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marisa Brantley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C3P0反序列化常用方式及不出网利用]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11830</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11830"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T02:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C3P0反序列化常用方式及不出网利用]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s New Robot Sparrow Can Handle Most Items in the Everything Store]]></title>
        <id>636d46204af1e10e2d86c4ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/amazons-new-robot-sparrow-can-handle-most-items-in-the-everything-store/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T21:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sparrow could shift the balance between humans and machines in the company’s warehouses, using machine learning algorithms and a custom gripper.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s New Robot Sparrow Can Handle Most Items in the Everything Store]]></title>
        <id>636d46204af1e10e2d86c4ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/amazons-new-robot-sparrow-can-handle-most-items-in-the-everything-store/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T21:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sparrow could shift the balance between humans and machines in the company’s warehouses, using machine learning algorithms and a custom gripper.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia’s Sway Over Criminal Ransomware Gangs Is Coming Into Focus]]></title>
        <id>636bda4e06a9fc0e80b10a6d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/russia-ransomware-gang-connections/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T19:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Questions about the Kremlin’s relationships with these groups remain. But researchers are finally getting some answers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protest Is Risky at Egypt's COP27. That Won't Stop Activists]]></title>
        <id>636aadb5fb8d8044171209e5</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/protest-activist-risk-egypt-cop27-climate-talks/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T16:40:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the international climate summit in Sharm el-Sheikh, long-standing restrictions on protesters and dissidents are front and center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramin Skibba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Personalized Crispr Therapy Is Designed to Attack Tumors]]></title>
        <id>636ae1d90a504da323ffd05a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/crispr-personalized-cancer-therapy/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T16:32:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a small study, researchers modified patients’ immune cells to target their particular cancer—but it only worked for a third of volunteers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Mullin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Reason for Meta’s Massive Layoffs? Ghosts in the Machine]]></title>
        <id>636d260c0757f7d06dd271f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/meta-layoffs-overhiring/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T16:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The social media company's failed projects required thousands of staffers who swelled the ranks and never left.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk's Twitter Blue Verification Is a Gift to Scammers]]></title>
        <id>636d252677d2621bc8030710</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-blue-check-verification-buy-scams/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T16:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone can get a blue tick on Twitter without proving who they are. And it’s already causing a ton of problems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk's Twitter Blue Verification Is a Gift to Scammers]]></title>
        <id>636d252677d2621bc8030710</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-blue-check-verification-buy-scams/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T16:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone can get a blue tick on Twitter without proving who they are. And it’s already causing a ton of problems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia’s New Cyberwarfare in Ukraine Is Fast, Dirty, and Relentless]]></title>
        <id>636aa8641d1ddb0aa029e13c</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/russia-ukraine-cyberattacks-mandiant/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T15:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers see updated tactics and tools—and a tempo change—in the cyberattacks Russia’s GRU military intelligence agency is inflicting on Ukraine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Billion-Dollar Crypto Collective Is Tearing Itself Apart]]></title>
        <id>636c3adf77d2621bc8030707</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/makerdao-rune-christensen-decentralize/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the world’s biggest crypto groups just voted to back its enigmatic founder. The only problem is, no one understands his plan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Khalili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Tweet Before Dying]]></title>
        <id>636aa3553505151fbc0b01e2</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/tweet-dying-revolutionary-internet/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The revolutionary internet is over, and we don’t have much to show for it. A new start is out there, somewhere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Ford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 websites to learn Frontend-web development faster]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/qbentil/5-websites-to-learn-frontend-web-development-faster-3cid</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/qbentil/5-websites-to-learn-frontend-web-development-faster-3cid"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T11:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #html #css]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bentil Shadrack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I build a Documentation site using Docz]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/documatic/how-i-build-a-documentation-site-using-docz-57kk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/documatic/how-i-build-a-documentation-site-using-docz-57kk"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #beginners #react #javascript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Vishwakarma, Documatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Big Fight Over 403 Very Small Wasps]]></title>
        <id>636ab13d5835030b1507e8a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/big-fight-small-wasps-taxonomy-biodiversity/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earth is teeming with unknown species, and they’re dying off faster than ever. Now biologists are battling over an old question: how to catalog life?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brooke Jarvis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weblogic CVE-2020-2551 绕过NAT网络分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11825</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11825"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T02:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weblogic CVE-2020-2551 绕过NAT网络分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Hell Happened to FTX?]]></title>
        <id>636bf17f0757f7d06dd271ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ftx-collapse-binance-crypto-deal/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T18:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The collapse of crypto exchange FTX opens opportunities for rival exchange Binance—and raises questions about the sector’s sustainability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Khalili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Countries Hit Hardest by Climate Change May Finally Get Their Due]]></title>
        <id>636a3eae5835030b1507e8a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/cop27-climate-reparations/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T17:11:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After 30 years of talk about forcing wealthy polluters to compensate those bearing the brunt of climate damage, the COP27 conference seems poised to act.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Barber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[透过信息架构 看各笔记软件]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76736</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76736"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T15:18:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[我在 如何搭建知识库 中，将知识库的结构分为了「树状结构」和「网络结构」两种。
树状结构是自上而下的，网络结构是自下而上的。
但知识还有多少种结构呢？为什么是这两种？
知识本质上是信息的一种，想了解知识的结构，也可以类比信息的结构。一直以来我回答不好这个问题。
日复一日，在日常使用知识库和产品经理的工作中，无论是对知识库中的每一张知识卡片进行整理，还是在工作中经常需要查看数据库的数据结构，都将我指向一个词「信息架构」
于是，我想起了那本经典的的「北极熊」之书 —— 《信息架构 超越 Web 设计》
并且，我在这本三年前读过的书里，找到了现在的我想要的答案。

信息结构
在《信息架构》这本书中，将信息分为了以下三种结构
组织系统：组织结构可以分为互补的三种结构
层级结构
以数据库为导向的模式
超文本

信息结构会定义用户浏览的主要方式。适用于信息架构的主要组织结构包括层级结构 、以数据库为导向的模式和超文本，每种组织结构都有其优缺点。在某些情况下，只使用一 种是合理的。但在很多情况下，需要以互补的方式使用这 3 种组织 结构。 —— 《信息架构》第六章

看到这三个结构，我恍然大悟，觉得非常了不起。
简单的三种结构，几乎可以用来解释现在所有的笔记软件。
下面我将介绍每一种结构在知识库软件中的运用。结合我日常的使用经历，也给出一些建议。
（注：目前市面上可以作为知识库的软件有很多。我只选取我有使用过的软件作为本次功能的介绍。也就是 Notion、Obsidian、Logseq、wolai…）

信息结构会定义用户浏览的主要方式。适用于信息架构的主要组织结构包括层级结构 、以数据库为导向的模式和超文本， 每种组织结构都有其优缺点。

层级结构
层级结构，即是上一层级包括下一层级的结构。
层级结构的优势和劣势都很明显。优势是其层次清晰，劣势是维护成本高。
层级结构的广度和深度均不宜…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>潦草学者</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Quiet Invasion of 'Big Information']]></title>
        <id>636167b2079462a79d02d6c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/big-information-relx-privacy-surveillance-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google and Facebook's privacy violations are common knowledge. But the decisions of a less-known company, Relx, are also impacting people's everyday lives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Lamdan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collective Mental Time Travel Can Influence the Future]]></title>
        <id>63627db400e08e244b10a525</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/psychology-mental-time-travel-politics/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way people imagine the past and future of society can sway attitudes and behaviors. How might this be wielded for good?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shayla Love</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter Users Have Caused a Mastodon Meltdown]]></title>
        <id>636adc98e8c08909bfa4fcf9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-users-mastodon-meltdown/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The network’s servers are overrun by almost half a million new sign-ups, as Elon Musk’s Twitter takeover has thrust it into the spotlight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amanda Hoover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Great Crypto-Cop Brain Drain]]></title>
        <id>636b01903505151fbc0b01e9</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-great-crypto-cop-brain-drain/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hunting down crypto criminals is a dying art as law enforcement officers jump in-house.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gian M. Volpicelli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brace Yourself for a Triple Wave of Seasonal Viruses]]></title>
        <id>636adfae1bc1a3ed38dc3b02</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/covid-flu-rsv-tripledemic/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many people haven’t been exposed to common respiratory viruses following the pandemic, meaning they might be more vulnerable to getting ill this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Weiss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made 1200+ ⭐️ stars on a Github repo! Here are some simple tips that helped me!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fredy/i-made-1200-stars-on-a-github-repo-here-are-some-simple-tips-that-helped-me-4eom</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fredy/i-made-1200-stars-on-a-github-repo-here-are-some-simple-tips-that-helped-me-4eom"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T11:25:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #tutorial #react #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fredy Andrei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[jetty常用渗透总结]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11821</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11821"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T07:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[jetty常用渗透总结]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[凛冬将至，你准备好买羽绒服了吗]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76706</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76706"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T03:23:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐 
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。 
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

又到双十一购物节，说来有趣，每年双十一我都会关注羽绒服这一品类，原因大概是冬天即将到来，我隐约有添购衣服的担忧，可又因为此时我还身穿短袖，买羽绒服有种错季购物的感觉，在将羽绒服加入购物车后往往又放弃下单。于是这些年，每到双十一，我的购物车里的羽绒服更新一次，羽绒服照片成了淘宝的皮肤挂件，年年换新。
我当然是有买羽绒服，但往往不是购物车里那件，我在淘宝上浏览的是万元左右的始祖鸟、Moncler、加拿大鹅，加入购物车里的是两千元左右的北面，但最终购买的是千元以内的波司登和优衣库轻薄款，哦对了，还有老家线下店铺的以纯羽绒服。
不过长期以往，我倒是对羽绒服有了足够多的了解，足以写下这篇有参考价值的文章，帮助人们选购羽绒服。
羽绒服的历史
人类自古以来就有利用动物皮毛御寒的历史，早在原始社会时期，人类祖先就已经初步掌握了将兽皮制作成衣物的方法，用兽皮和树叶蔽体防寒，后来逐渐出现麻、棉、丝等纺织物，人类衣物变得丰富。相对来说，人类利用禽类羽毛御寒的历史要短得多，在唐朝，人们用鹅绒和布混合填充在被子中，在十三四世纪的欧洲，人们用鸭和鹅的羽毛填充进被套中。
直到 1940 年，现代羽绒服才被发明出来，主角是美国的艾迪·鲍尔，作为一名狂热户外运动爱好者，他在一次户外钓鱼过程中差点冻死，于是决心制作一件真正保暖的外套。鲍尔找到了鹅毛的羽绒，又恰逢杜邦实验室在 1938 年发明了尼龙，尼龙织物质地紧密，与棉布相比，尼龙面料可以防止羽绒「钻绒」，于是，他将二者结合，把羽绒填充进尼龙面料的衣服，绗缝锁绒，并将第一件羽绒外套命名为「Skyliner」，申…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>吃饭Bu洗碗</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[通过一个crackme学习逆向基础知识以及Delphi框架]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11818</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11818"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T02:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[通过一个crackme学习逆向基础知识以及Delphi框架]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Apple Pay or Google Wallet Instead of Plastic Cards]]></title>
        <id>636a9127f4db157fcdf20ff1</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/money-privacy-security-settings-apple-google-pay/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cash is safe—for now. Contactless payment methods, like Apple Pay or Google Wallet, are more of a threat to the existence of physical cards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reece Rogers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Race to Bridge the Analog Divide in US Politics]]></title>
        <id>636a86a41bc1a3ed38dc3afb</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/retail-politics-analog-divide/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T21:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing beats in-person efforts to boost a campaign. But rising platforms are helping connect politicians with the rest of us.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Laslo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facet 2.0 — Image creation, reimagined]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/facet-2-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/facet-2-0"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T18:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@effie_jia @kyleschaeffer @sophie_xie @m_l_stanton and so many more folks not on producthunt yet.
              ”
              
Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the MongoDB Atlas Hackathon 2022 on DEV!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devteam/announcing-the-mongodb-atlas-hackathon-2022-on-dev-2107</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devteam/announcing-the-mongodb-atlas-hackathon-2022-on-dev-2107"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T18:11:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#atlashackathon22 #mongodb #meta]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Bethencourt, The DEV Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React & NodeJS - Go LIVE with Full-Stack projects fast]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sm0ke/react-nodejs-go-live-with-full-stack-projects-fast-j0h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sm0ke/react-nodejs-go-live-with-full-stack-projects-fast-j0h"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T18:09:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #react #fullstack]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sm0ke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the ‘Election Integrity App’ Built to Purge US Voter Rolls]]></title>
        <id>63657b621bc1a3ed38dc3ace</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/true-the-vote-iv3-app-voter-fraud/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T15:59:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[True the Vote’s IV3 app is meant to catch election cheaters. But it has a fundamental flaw.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruv Mehrotra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the ‘Election Integrity App’ Built to Purge US Voter Rolls]]></title>
        <id>63657b621bc1a3ed38dc3ace</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/true-the-vote-iv3-app-voter-fraud/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T15:59:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[True the Vote’s IV3 app is meant to catch election cheaters. But it has a fundamental flaw.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruv Mehrotra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All your JavaScript code is polluted]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jankapunkt/all-your-javascript-code-is-polluted-3e8l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jankapunkt/all-your-javascript-code-is-polluted-3e8l"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T15:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jan Küster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pathfndr — Launch your own intelligent Travel Site in less than 15 mins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.producthunt.com/posts/pathfndr</id>
        <link href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/pathfndr"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T13:05:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion
            |
            Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists Are Uncovering Ominous Waters Under Antarctic Ice]]></title>
        <id>63693c6c7484c01b9b6e9653</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/scientists-are-uncovering-ominous-waters-under-antarctic-ice/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A super-pressurized, 290-mile-long river is running under the ice sheet. That could be bad news for sea-level rise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Fauci’s Sign-Off Message]]></title>
        <id>6361a5e7d58ae0592b0f00cf</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/anthony-faucis-sign-off-message/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While America’s top doc fought Covid, deniers fought him. He still can’t figure out why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[安卓APP抓包解决方案(教程)]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11817</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11817"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T06:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[安卓APP抓包解决方案(教程)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CS的RCE利用研究]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11815</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11815"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T02:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CS的RCE利用研究]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SpringBoot和SpringMvc中的Context]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11814</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11814"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T02:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SpringBoot和SpringMvc中的Context]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Secret Ballot Is US Democracy’s Last Line of Defense]]></title>
        <id>63651410f65e6e9328cbf0a7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/secret-ballot-voter-intimidation-2022-us-midterms/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T21:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voter intimidation has cropped up in places across the nation, but the voting booth remains the one place where nobody can get to you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IRS Seizes Another Silk Road Hacker’s $3.36 Billion Bitcoin Stash]]></title>
        <id>636948fa0d25973ba5f9bc5a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/silk-road-bitcoin-seizure-james-zhong/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T19:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A year after a billion-dollar seizure of the dark web market's crypto, the same agency found a giant trove hidden under a different hacker's floorboards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client-side Routing without the JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/client-side-routing-without-the-javascript-3k1i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-learning/client-side-routing-without-the-javascript-3k1i"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T16:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #solidjs #webdev #performance]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Carniato, This is Learning</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[想要逃离 Chrome？请收下这份 Firefox 终极隐私指南]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76688</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76688"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T15:41:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐 
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。 
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

前言
毋庸置疑，如今的 Chrome 及其他基于 Chromium 的 Blink 内核浏览器因其速度快、网页兼容性好的优点，以绝对的优势占据了浏览器市场的主导地位。但与此同时，因为 Chrome 与 Chromium 被一家号称「不作恶」但处处作恶的公司所拥有，所以经常被诟病存在隐私问题。许多想要逃离 Chrome 统治的人都转向了更加自由的 Firefox 浏览器，尽管其母公司 Mozilla 近年来也是骚操作不断，但 Firefox 仍然是除 Chromium 的 Blink 和 Safari 的 WebKit 外唯一选择。
我曾经也很喜欢用 Chrome（或者说是 Chromium），使用 ArchLinux 作为主力系统的我，官方软件源中使用开源 Chromium 代码编译出的 Chromium 浏览器在当时体验基本与谷歌官方的闭源 Chrome 一致。促使我转向使用 Firefox 的契机开始于一年多前，谷歌限制了第三方浏览器对其数据同步 API 的使用，这样一来各家发行版自行编译的 Chromium 浏览器都失去了账户同步功能，这在当时引起了很多不满。从那时开始，我就开始尝试使用 Firefox 替代 Chromium 作为我的主力浏览器，并最终彻底淘汰掉了 Chromium。
无独有偶，谷歌又宣布将会在 2022 年底彻底禁用 Manifest V2 规范（后来又推迟了半年），作为替代者的 Manifest V3 规范，用谷歌的话说是为了「保护用户隐私」，限制了浏览器扩展的很多权限，其中影响最大的是禁用了 We…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>so1ar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hexagonal architecture as a solution to the obsolescence of UI frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/drouianm/hexagonal-architecture-as-a-solution-to-the-obsolescence-of-ui-frameworks-ej2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/drouianm/hexagonal-architecture-as-a-solution-to-the-obsolescence-of-ui-frameworks-ej2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T13:18:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#vue #react #typescript #architecture]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthieu Drouian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter’s Ex-Election Chief Is Worried About the US Midterms]]></title>
        <id>6365c3d872734b280f7c5085</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-election-integrity-2022-midterms/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Edward Perez says that “manufactured chaos” by bad actors will be even riskier thanks to Elon Musk’s own mayhem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Stokel-Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s Reckless Plan to Make Sex Pay on Twitter]]></title>
        <id>6365442eaec2220e3ecb87f6</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-adult-content-sex-twitter-content-moderation/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T11:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A plan to monetize adult content could make sense from a business and social standpoint. In practice, Twitter won’t be able to pull it off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olivia Snow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust Easy! Modern Cross-platform Command Line Tools to Supercharge Your Terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/deepu105/rust-easy-modern-cross-platform-command-line-tools-to-supercharge-your-terminal-4dd3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/deepu105/rust-easy-modern-cross-platform-command-line-tools-to-supercharge-your-terminal-4dd3"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T09:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#rust #terminal #linux #macos]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deepu K Sasidharan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Commons JXPath 远程代码执行(CVE-2022-41852)]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11813</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11813"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T09:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Commons JXPath 远程代码执行(CVE-2022-41852)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PostgresQL JDBC Drive 任意代码执行漏洞(CVE-2022-21724)]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11812</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11812"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T08:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PostgresQL JDBC Drive 任意代码执行漏洞(CVE-2022-21724)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[我在 app 里做了一下「赛博朋克：边缘行者」里的拖影效果]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76679</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76679"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T07:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[本次更新：
前几天看了「赛博朋克：边缘行者」，觉得里面的拖影效果非常有趣，就在 app 里做了一下。

App 介绍：
CUBE 是一款结合 iOS 软硬件新特性来完成实时特效的 app ，希望大家在手机上就可以玩到有趣的特效。 以我看过的热门影音作品为灵感，已经完成下面三个主要特效：
LiDAR 扫描效果：
日本女团 Perfume 在 Flow 的 MV 中大量使用点云这种技术，而正好配备 LiDAR 的 iPhone 可以感知深度，生成点云。
 
采样实时图像与 LiDAR 扫描仪生成的深度图，生成 3D 粒子（点云）。至多可生成 3,000,000 个粒子。
将生成的 3D 粒子与现实世界的场景混合在一起，让你感觉身处超现实世界。

Matrix 效果：
之前 黑客帝国 4 上映，黑客帝国又变成热门话题，就很想复刻一下经典的 code rain 。
 
这一次会选蓝色药丸还是红色药丸？

液态金属效果：
 
既然都提到了黑客帝国，那么终结者也不能不提。贯穿全系列的液态金属杀手也是经典之一。CUBE 带你回到 1991 年，化身成为詹姆斯·卡梅隆所拍摄的电影「终结者 2：审判日」中的终结者 T-1000 。

App Store
 
兑换码：
如果你对上面三个特效感兴趣，你可以在这里找到兑换码。
（我把码都放到一个 notion page 里，可以回复用掉的兑换码编号，方便我编辑。）
https://boringseries.notion.site/CUBE-392d7f454b2a4ceabae44ef478c87f4b]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>少数派77122655</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[感受读书上瘾的快乐]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76659</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76659"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T07:07:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[如何让枯燥的读书像看剧、享受美食、打游戏一样快乐？
读书上瘾模型，让读书成为一个上瘾循环。

上学的时候我比较喜欢玩游戏，但是在图书馆有很好的学习看书的氛围，游戏玩得比较少。毕业后，不再有看书的氛围了，玩游戏的频率逐渐增加，从每周1天增加到2天、后来逐步增加到7天，每天都玩游戏。
那个时候我意识到已经游戏上瘾了，打游戏占据了太多的时间，所以决定戒掉游戏，经过几次尝试，终于在2020年把游戏戒掉了。

即从游戏上瘾转变为读书上瘾，读书包括输入和输出两个步骤。输入指的是看书，从去年开始在豆瓣记录读书情况，利用周末和工作日的被动等待时间，每个月最多读过11本书。
输出分为写、说、实践3种形式。

写，发表长篇博客或简短的书评。
说，分为线上和线下两种形式，线上指在各个自媒体平台发布读书视频；线下指面对面形式，1对1的交流沟通或1对多的分享。
实践，看书不应该只停留在改变认知的程度，还要实践、改变自己的行为习惯。比如看了一本关于运动的书，不仅要有每天都运动的认知，还要付诸于每天的实践行动。

上一次玩游戏是在2020年，接下来详细介绍如何从游戏上瘾转变为读书上瘾。
 
 
Part 1 什么是上瘾？
一 上瘾的原理
二 戒上瘾的思路

提高行动成本
模块说

Part 2 读书上瘾模型
三 Step 1：选一本我需要的书

3.1 分析我想要的是什么
3.2 选书的途径
3.3 适当难度：最高学习效率15.87%
3.4 选择自己能承受的成长模式

四 Step 2：创造时间

4.1 人生需要做减法
4.2 时间管理系统/任务管理系统，GTD
GTD step 1 捕捉
GTD step 2 整理
GTD step 3 执行

4.3 时间颗粒度
4.4 实例演示：如何使用GTD
时间管理相关软件
使用GTD的一天


五 Step 3：输入：寻找适合自己的阅读方式

5.1 拆…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jogging</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【键盘观望】看看最近有趣的键帽。2022.11（1）]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76531</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76531"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T06:07:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[本文仅代表个人观点，用于记录和观望一些键帽。

PBTFANS KABUKI-CHO 歌舞伎町
2022.4 
IC Base
这套键帽是由设计师OAY （罗马音？大概能翻译成哦呀，语气词）设计的第二套键帽，此前他还设计过pbtfans的深海来客，感兴趣的可以看我之前盘点的蓝色系键帽。
这套歌舞伎町键帽，灵感来源于日本的歌舞伎町——东京的娱乐中心之一。电影院、电玩舞厅、酒吧等等，从深夜到黎明，也是为数不多的大型红灯区，我对于歌舞伎町最深刻的印象则是来自于《银魂》中主角团所居住的歌舞伎町一条街。
配色：

这次的配色非常丰富，主要还是由于个性部分选用多种不同色彩。键帽整体底色以深蓝暗色调为主，而字符和个性选用明亮的色调，如同霓虹灯招牌的颜色，侧面烘托出歌舞伎町“不眠之街”的名号，到深夜依然灯火通明、灯红酒绿。
个性部分：
大货版本
这次的现货销售是直接将个性和base进行了捆绑，还包含了四个颜色的盖帽。
个性部分主要由歌舞伎、酒精和没事组成，以及歌舞伎町的招牌和著名的“一丁目”。颜色上也是选择非常丰富，盖帽倒是提供了一种略微复古但俏皮的感觉，七字回车则是意味着现代的电力为这般灯红酒绿提供了便利。
搭配展示：
该键帽已经开售有一段时间，所以已经有玩家提供了实拍的照片，有这些实物图，能更好的帮助我们来判断是否购入。
乐总拍摄阿门JV拍摄Vanthic Noel 拍摄
键帽信息：
材质：PBT材质
高度：原厂高度
工艺：二色工艺
厂商：PBTFANS
淘宝有售卖，据悉歌舞伎町卖的很好，货量有限，kbd自己的店铺已经卖完了，经销商仍有现货。 
个人评分:7-8（深色键帽非常耐看，歌舞伎町的主题也很新鲜，个性颜色丰富,PBTFANS代工水平不错）
购买建议：喜欢这个主题的值得入手，现货也无需等待

KeyKobo Poltergeist 吵闹鬼
2022.9

这套键帽是由设计师SXM…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>车不能快</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[白菜价的国产暗尖怎么样？12款3~15元钢笔横评对比]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76673</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76673"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T03:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[前言
仔细翻了翻我个人的钢笔产品分享，和大家讨论过的都是以著名品牌的钢笔产品为主，对于国内钢笔品牌主要还是分享英雄旗下的经典产品与创新之作，毕竟其它钢笔品牌以我个人的眼光去看，都是没有太多购买意义的产品。
对于钢笔入门我始终推荐白金preppy系列、白金小流星系列、百乐78g、凌美狩猎者这些海外品牌的平价款式。
但因为英雄的关系，国人对于暗尖结构的钢笔有着相当的偏好，并且海外知名品牌如今也没有任何纯粹的现产暗尖钢笔产品。所以如今暗尖钢笔的赛道上全是国产钢笔品牌，并且价位主战场就是十元上下的低端市场，本篇中，我在某多多以零售价格，购买了十余款销量出色的国产暗尖，文内将从暗尖钢笔的用料、设计、特点来对它们进行全面的横评对比，希望能为大家了解这些产品带来帮助。
暗尖钢笔的发源与如今价位分布

暗尖钢笔发源于人类历史上最为成功的钢笔派克51，其诞生于1939年，暨派克成立51周年，故因此得以型号命名。
派克51的暗尖结构，通过树脂包裹了笔尖，在当年革新性得提高了钢笔的气密性，并根据结构，设计了新一代的毛细供墨系统，达到了更为稳定的书写效果。
在当年，暗尖钢笔以这两点综合的超强实用性，得到了市场的一致认可，直至停产派克51累计销售4000万支，是人类历史上最为成功的系列钢笔。
之所以停产，是因为后续钢笔的气密性与供墨毛细结构材料随着现代工业不断革新，暗尖已经不再具备核心优势。
现在的暗尖钢笔从高到底个人认为是三个层次，首先是派克前年复刻了51，做了个包住明尖的假暗尖，是目前价格最高的笔款，但不怎么值得去买。其次是英雄100代表了国产暗尖金笔，曾经100多元的价格性价比非常好，如今价格普遍要200以上，还是可以买，但没曾经的极致性价比了；最后就是本篇讲的10元上下，国产的钢尖暗尖钢笔！
暗尖钢笔的特点

一、暗尖钢笔因为笔尖露出部分少，书写时可以产生形变的笔尖体积相对较小，所以书写时感…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>老木曾雪菜</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[从2022中科大hackgame web中学习pdflatex RCE和python反序列化]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11809</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11809"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T03:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[从2022中科大hackgame web中学习pdflatex RCE和python反序列化]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[shiro环境下的Servlet内存马注入踩坑日记]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11808</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11808"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T03:09:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[shiro环境下的Servlet内存马注入踩坑日记]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[最近碰到的 Python pickle 反序列化小总结]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11807</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11807"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T02:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[最近碰到的 Python pickle 反序列化小总结]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPhone 相机进化之路：38 款 iPhone 图像传感器型号确认（07 - 22）]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76639</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76639"/>
        <updated>2022-11-06T15:06:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix 首页推荐 
Matrix 是少数派的写作社区，我们主张分享真实的产品体验，有实用价值的经验与思考。我们会不定期挑选 Matrix 最优质的文章，展示来自用户的最真实的体验和观点。 
文章代表作者个人观点，少数派仅对标题和排版略作修改。

在 Android 手机的宣传稿中，我们经常能听到厂商宣传其所搭载的图像传感器型号，例如索尼 IMX***、三星 S5K***、豪威 OV**** 等。但在 iPhone 的宣传中，我们就不曾听过苹果声明 iPhone 使用的图像传感器型号，一般都是使用「传感器面积增大了百分之几」「像素更大更深」「全新的高速传感器」之类的比较模糊的用词，所以对于历代 iPhone 具体使用何种传感器，互联网上有诸多不能明确的信息。此文意在将我自己搜集到的相关信息进行梳理，试图考证它们的可靠性，为之后写作 iPhone 图像传感器进化打下基础。

首先给出我整理后的部分信息，点击图片可看原图，欢迎指正。
截自我的 Notion 页面
主要参考信源
互联网上关于 iPhone 图像传感器的信息参差不齐，大部分信息都没有给出出处，单纯引用某一信源难以有说服力，我综合了部分我比较认可的信源，各位可以自行甄别。
维基百科：Exmor
Exmor 是索尼公司应用在其部分 CMOS 图像传感器上的技术名称。维基百科上的 Exmor 词条收集整理了大量索尼 Exmor 图像传感器及其使用的机型，使用 Ctrl+F 可快速搜索 iPhone 关键词。我将其整理如下表。


Model numberNumber of effective pixelsSensor size (diagonal)Pixel sizeSubpixel layoutUtilizing devices

IMX1453264 x 2448 8Mp5.68 mm (1/3.2")1.40 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>太不巧</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFE-A卡横评及选购指南，「原厂」并不是最好选择！]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76663</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76663"/>
        <updated>2022-11-06T14:18:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[写在最前面，CFE卡贵谁都知道，但是这玩意性能是真的强，不管你现在用不用得着，都建议你收藏一下，虽然现在买不起，但是梦想还是要有的嘛！
CFE-A卡是索尼从A7S3开始使用的新一代高速存储设备，以应对越来越大的视频录制码率。早先使用CFE-A卡的机型都比较贵（A7S3,FX3,A1等），受众并不多。但从A7M4的大卖和FX30的发布，越来越多的用户开始使用支持CFE-A卡的相机，如何选购一张合适的CFE-A卡就成了许多用户头疼的问题。
懂数码的都知道，索尼虽然“爱好广泛”，但唯独没有生产研发存储产品的业务，也就是说索尼的卡都是其他厂家代工的贴牌产品，理论上是不可能干得过拥有独立生产研发存储颗粒的品牌的，所谓的索尼大法黑科技在存储领域也仅仅是索尼粉丝自己加上的滤镜而已。
由于CFE-A卡是索尼独占的新卡型，在发布之初的相当长一段时间里都只有索尼原厂的卡可以选择，因为缺少比较的竞品，让许多人养成了原厂=最好的固有印象。
如今第三方的CFE-A品牌越来越多，索尼原厂卡到底是个什么水平，终于可以有一个正经的横向比较了。
市面上可以做CFE-A卡的品牌有索尼，雷克沙，天硕，和至誉科技四家，笔者手里正好分别有一张拿来比较测试，他们是

索尼原厂的80G，官方售价699;
分别是雷克沙的320G，官方售价5599带读卡器;
天硕的80G，官方售价399；
至誉科技的120G，官方售价1599;

少数派不让带货就不放链接了。

之所以价格区间跨度很大，从几百到几千，主要是为了照顾不同经济实力的用户。
测试采用的读卡器是雷克沙的RW530，是一个CFA和SD卡双卡槽的读卡器，采用USB 3.2gen2接口，两个卡槽可以同时工作，可以实现互拷的功能。

一、性能对比
1、索尼80G

首先出场的是原厂的80G，由于这张卡是在套机里一起售卖的，拆机卡很多，只要六七百。买的人很多，不过大多数都舍…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>食肉库玛老师傅</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok’s Greatest Asset Isn’t Its Algorithm—It’s Your Phone]]></title>
        <id>63517a45470620c1e69a25e1</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/tiktok-phones-extended-mind-philosophy/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Escaping the platform's addictive grasp means first overhauling our relationship to our devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leo Kim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elevate Your Terminal Experience on The Mac 🧘‍♂️]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/duncanlew/elevate-your-terminal-experience-on-the-mac-3o3m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/duncanlew/elevate-your-terminal-experience-on-the-mac-3o3m"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T20:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #tutorial #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Duncan Lew</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 Icon websites for devs and designers!!!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ymhaah/top-5-icon-websites-for-devs-and-designers-53mh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ymhaah/top-5-icon-websites-for-devs-and-designers-53mh"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T19:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#design #beginners #webdev #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Youssef Hafnawy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An animated guide for Node.js event loop]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nodedoctors/an-animated-guide-to-nodejs-event-loop-3g62</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nodedoctors/an-animated-guide-to-nodejs-event-loop-3g62"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T18:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #node #beginners #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hu, Node Doctors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[快捷指令的野心与无奈]]></title>
        <id>https://sspai.com/post/76652</id>
        <link href="https://sspai.com/post/76652"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T14:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[作为一名iPhone用户，快捷指令是系统中我觉得很有趣但实际上用得不是很多的应用。
最初对快捷指令的理解仅限于将多个操作步骤简化成一个，最直观的应用就是在功能日益繁杂的APP中实现功能的一键直达，比如疫情期间的健康码。
但深入探究一番后，我认为快捷指令的本质其实是打破各个APP沙盒的壁垒，实现不同应用程序的能力互通，提升个人的自动化水平。
但事情情况并不尽如人意，虽然快捷指令编辑器提供了足够强大的编辑器，但三方应用对其支持并不好，大多数APP还是尽可能期望把用户圈在自己的生态中，没有开放足够的能力出来，这也是一款生态级应用的无奈。
想象中的快捷指令
现在应用商店的APP已经足够多，可以帮助人们解决足够多的问题，但有时候一款应用并不能完全解决某项任务，需要多个应用配合操作，如果用户可以随意调用应用中功能并组合成自己所需要完成特定任务的能力，那么用户体验和效率都将提升到新的高度。
想象一种场景，当我在观看自己感兴趣的外语视频时，因为语言的障碍可能不能足够理解视频内容，我需要一些辅助支持：我希望翻译软件能够帮我把外语翻译成母语，甚至希望语音合成软件将翻译后的语言读出来。孤立地看这个场景中的每个需求，都有应用能很好得实现：视频网站能够提供我感兴趣的内容，翻译软件能将语言进行较高准确度的翻译，语音合成软件能够将文字朗读出来。但是当这三个需求点分布在三个不同的APP时，用户就难以较高效率完成这个场景的任务。实际上每个APP的能力都被封锁在了自己APP里面。

上面说的这个场景我自己就有，但是因为没能使用现有工具很好使用，只得自己动手做了一个插件，可以朗读B站上面带有字幕的视频，因为微软的中文语音合成做得比较好，所以先放在Edge浏览器上了，目前还只支持带外挂字幕的视频，大家感兴趣也可以使用。

B站视频字幕朗读（中文同传）插件地址-> Microsoft Edge Addons
现实中的快捷指令
虽然当前快捷指令还不够优秀，但对于日常效率的提升还是有一定帮助的，特别是对于实现与苹果自带应用的互通。
举个使用的例子，每天早上我会用笔记软件记录一下昨日回顾、思考以及今日的计划，对于今日计划，我希望用待办应用去跟踪计划中事项的状态，但是手动把写过的东西在另一个APP里面再写一遍实在是太过愚蠢，于是我就写了快捷指令去实现。

实际使用中，只要选择对应的文本并在共享表单中点击对应的操作就可以同步到系统自带的提醒事项中，在mac上还可以添加快捷键一键实现（应该还可以通过「自动化」省去手动操作这一步）。
当前的快捷指令有三个亮点：

在快捷指令的编辑上采用图形化拖拽操作，相对于写脚本，这种操作显得更加友好，并且也可以支持自定义脚本的加入，甚至让我一度觉得学编程的第一个应用是用快捷指令写得；
在快捷指令的运行上打通了Siri、小组件以及共享操作，特别是后者，为与三方应用的结合提供了基础的平台；
加入了自动化功能，可以根据一定的规则直接省去了用户主动调用快捷指令这一步。

但要让更多的人在更多场景下使用快捷指令，还有着一些明显的不足：

上手使用上有一些门槛，官方没有详细的教程，虽然提供了一些案例，但是大多数人应该没有耐心仔细去看快捷中心中那些精选的指令是如何实现的，这点Mac上快捷指令前辈「自动操作」可能给点其启示，其中「录制」功能可以通过「我做给你看」自动识别操作中的事件；
快捷指令的分发做得还不够，既然不是每个人都能轻松使用快捷指令，那么获取现成的快捷指令则更加重要，但快捷指令中心中精选的指令本土化、个性化做得并不好，我觉得如果能根据用户所安装的APP来个性化分发常用的快捷指令会更友好；
三方应用的能力开放明显不足，大多数的使用场景还是围绕在苹果自带应用提供的能力，这点极大限制了快捷指令的应用场景；
使用Siri来激活快捷指令时对于指令的识别非常差，官方有说使用快捷指令的名称就可以通过Siri调用，但实际使用时不时语音识别不出来就是调用的指令不正确；

有趣的是，在WWDC2022中，我们看到苹果开始推广App Intent框架，通过为应用开发者提供更多系统级的入口曝光来吸引他们将其应用所能满足的用户意图曝光给系统，从而使得系统可以通过学习用户行为实现跨应用的能力整合。
结语
很多人即使生活中充满重复的事情也不会去探索提高效率方式，因为对比眼前简单的操作，去探究增进效率操作的所花费的学习努力带来的成本更加高，只是把时间线拉得足够远，才能看见效率提升所带来收益。
自动化所存在的意义是帮助人完成任务并节省时间，虽然我们每个人都已经拥有足够多的计算设备，但我们并没有充分发挥其拥有的算力，个人的自动化仍是一个尚待开发的领域。
期待未来的快捷指令能为个人的自动化增添更多的可能性。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>taofuns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[利用Selenium绕过前端js加密及验证码爆破]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11806</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11806"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T13:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[利用Selenium绕过前端js加密及验证码爆破]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（八）CSP篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11805</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11805"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T13:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（八）CSP篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Expands Flood and Wildfire Tracking to More Countries]]></title>
        <id>636458f56e26e2941c119d11</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/google-ai-wildfire-flood-tracking/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: Sony announces a release date and price for its next PlayStation VR headset, Google kills a couple more apps, and everything’s gone explosive at Twitter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boone Ashworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok Admits Staff in China Can Access Europeans’ Data]]></title>
        <id>636523a6dc213ea1c21ed12b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/tiktok-eu-privacy-policy-security-roundup/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: Liz Truss’ phone-hacking trouble, Cash App’s sex-trafficking problem, and the rising cost of ransomware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman, Andrew Couts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenRASP浅析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11803</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11803"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T05:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenRASP浅析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Has Fired Twitter’s ‘Ethical AI’ Team]]></title>
        <id>63651386d481f3fd793dde70</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/twitter-ethical-ai-team/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T16:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of a wave of layoffs, the new CEO disbanded a group working to make Twitter’s algorithms more transparent and fair.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Javascript Generators: A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/muqsitadam/javascript-generators-a-beginners-guide-1ojf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/muqsitadam/javascript-generators-a-beginners-guide-1ojf"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T23:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #beginners #webdev #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdulmuqsit Adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[最近遇到的Linux内核内存取证小分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11800</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11800"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T18:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[最近遇到的Linux内核内存取证小分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[webpagetest反序列化及ssrf漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11798</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11798"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T17:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[webpagetest反序列化及ssrf漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Artists: Do Not Fear AI Image Generators]]></title>
        <id>61ba7c7ba08cdc8657dc4958</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/artists-do-not-fear-ai-image-generators/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[True, new systems devalue craft, shift power, and wreck cultures and scenes. But didn’t the piano do that to the harpsichord?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Ford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Algorithms Quietly Run the City of Washington, DC—and Maybe Your Hometown]]></title>
        <id>63617b2dd5a8378824123f92</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/algorithms-quietly-run-the-city-of-dc-and-maybe-your-hometown/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report finds that municipal agencies in Washington deploy dozens of automated decision systems, often without residents’ knowledge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khari Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Soccer Fans, You're Being Watched]]></title>
        <id>636299d7a9269ef97e4efe41</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/soccer-world-cup-biometric-surveillance/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stadiums around the world, including at the 2022 World Cup in Qatar, are subjecting spectators to invasive biometric surveillance tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vas Panagiotopoulos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（七）技巧篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11795</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11795"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T08:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（七）技巧篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome扩展安全开发从零到一]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11794</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11794"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T04:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome扩展安全开发从零到一]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[某路由器固件模拟分析及栈溢出漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11793</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11793"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T03:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[某路由器固件模拟分析及栈溢出漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise of Rust, the ‘Viral’ Secure Programming Language That’s Taking Over Tech]]></title>
        <id>63582f1fbb31765d3acdfb15</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/rust-secure-programming-language-memory-safe/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T18:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rust makes it impossible to introduce some of the most common security vulnerabilities. And its adoption can’t come soon enough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lily Hay Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to add PayPal checkout payments to your React app]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/paypaldeveloper/how-to-add-paypal-checkout-payments-to-your-react-app-53aa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/paypaldeveloper/how-to-add-paypal-checkout-payments-to-your-react-app-53aa"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T17:25:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #react #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pato, PayPal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make the most of DEV if you’re over Twitter]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devteam/how-to-make-the-most-of-dev-if-youre-over-twitter-4567</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devteam/how-to-make-the-most-of-dev-if-youre-over-twitter-4567"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T13:24:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#watercooler #meta #twitter #career]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Halpern, The DEV Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seeking Psychedelics? Check the Data Privacy Clause]]></title>
        <id>635ae105a398fb738c4b9234</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/colorado-psychedelics-health-privacy-surveillance/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colorado's Proposition 122 wants to let people take psilocybin at healing centers. But sensitive data isn't covered by medical privacy protections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mason Marks</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Vulnerable Place on the Internet]]></title>
        <id>6361b2a70b9dedd635bdb001</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/submarine-internet-cables-egypt/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Underwater cables keep the internet online. When they congregate in one place, things get tricky.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips to become a great software engineer]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jamielivingstone/tips-to-become-a-great-software-engineer-10gf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jamielivingstone/tips-to-become-a-great-software-engineer-10gf"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T10:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#career #programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Livingstone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a registration and a login with two-factor authentication on React 🤩]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/novu/creating-a-registration-and-a-login-with-two-factor-authentication-on-react-2p2i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/novu/creating-a-registration-and-a-login-with-two-factor-authentication-on-react-2p2i"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T10:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #node #webdev #javascript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevo David, novu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[浅析NodeJS]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11791</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11791"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T07:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[浅析NodeJS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API安全漏洞靶场crapi的基本介绍和解题思路-第二篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11789</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11789"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T06:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[API安全漏洞靶场crapi的基本介绍和解题思路-第二篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML & CSS Features, Tips For a 10x Faster Page Loading Speed]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/koustav/html-css-features-tips-for-a-10x-fast-page-loading-speed-4jop</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/koustav/html-css-features-tips-for-a-10x-fast-page-loading-speed-4jop"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T05:19:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#news #webdev #html #css]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>devkoustav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（六）续集篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11788</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11788"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T04:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（六）续集篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（五）最终篇]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11790</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11790"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T02:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[一些BAT的XSS实例（五）最终篇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 7 Best React Component Libraries to Use in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/amrtcrypto/the-7-best-react-component-libraries-to-use-in-2022-11la</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/amrtcrypto/the-7-best-react-component-libraries-to-use-in-2022-11la"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T18:10:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #react #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amr Tawfik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Your Neighbor Turns You In]]></title>
        <id>635fdf932315f22f91833a36</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/authoritarian-us-neighbors-spy-report/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authoritarian societies depend on people ratting each other out for activities that were recently legal—and it's already happening in the US.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thor Benson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[通过边界代理一路打到三层内网+后渗透通用手法]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11784</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11784"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T02:08:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[通过边界代理一路打到三层内网+后渗透通用手法]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IPC$共享利用姿势]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11783</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11783"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T02:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IPC$共享利用姿势]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[初步理解Phar反序列化 + 分析POP链构造（2022 Bilibili 1024 程序员节第二题）]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11782</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11782"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T01:29:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[初步理解Phar反序列化 + 分析POP链构造（2022 Bilibili 1024 程序员节第二题）]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Need to Update Google Chrome, Windows, and Zoom Right Now]]></title>
        <id>635c5bbfa8552c961517a88e</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/google-chrome-windows-zoom-critical-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: Important patches from Apple, VMWare, Cisco, Zimbra, SAP, and Oracle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate O'Flaherty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Folder Structure for NodeJS & ExpressJS project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mr_ali3n/folder-structure-for-nodejs-expressjs-project-435l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mr_ali3n/folder-structure-for-nodejs-expressjs-project-435l"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T09:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#express #javascript #node #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vaibhav Mehta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Docker Extensions Every Developer Must Try]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/docker/9-docker-extensions-every-developer-must-try-1no2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/docker/9-docker-extensions-every-developer-must-try-1no2"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T07:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#docker #devops #kubernetes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pavan Belagatti, Docker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Shorthand Optimization Tricks every JavaScript Developer Should Know 😎]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/7-shorthand-optimization-tricks-every-javascript-developer-should-know-4fj5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/7-shorthand-optimization-tricks-every-javascript-developer-should-know-4fj5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-30T06:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #programming #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapajyoti Bose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Startups Have a Sellout Problem. There's a Better Way]]></title>
        <id>63481d9808a267a4aad8c050</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/startups-exit-community-ipo-business/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-29T13:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Startups like Meta and Twitter serve as digital infrastructure, but aren't accountable to users. Some startups are trying to chart a new way to exit that focuses on community—not shareholders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED Ideas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[某软件监控页面RCE漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11778</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11778"/>
        <updated>2022-10-29T13:22:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[某软件监控页面RCE漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art of Hitting Disinformation Where It Lives]]></title>
        <id>6356a50d3d83d1af9973abd3</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/disinformation-art-science/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Combating fake news with facts doesn't work because humans are wired for emotion. It's time for more creative tactics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Southern</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk’s Twitter Will Not Be the Town Square the World Needs]]></title>
        <id>635af6043d7842cc349a2206</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-twitter-town-square/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T12:54:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a moment to choose a different path, inspired by the lessons of thriving offline communities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Pariser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe Prepares to Rewrite the Rules of the Internet]]></title>
        <id>6359871f68addec416d5b940</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/europe-dma-prepares-to-rewrite-the-rules-of-the-internet/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Digital Markets Act will force Big Tech platforms to break open their walled gardens in 2023, says the EU’s new ambassador to Silicon Valley.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khari Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome Extensions of the Month - October 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/j471n/chrome-extensions-of-the-month-october-2022-1c0j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/j471n/chrome-extensions-of-the-month-october-2022-1c0j"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T06:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#productivity #webdev #javascript #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jatin Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Master The Art of Content Creation As a Developer?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/patilganesh1010/how-to-master-the-art-of-content-creation-as-a-developer-kpn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/patilganesh1010/how-to-master-the-art-of-content-creation-as-a-developer-kpn"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T03:18:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #tutorial #opensource #career]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Patil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 must-know tips for writing clean code with Javascript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexomeyer/8-must-know-tips-for-writing-clean-code-with-javascript-i4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexomeyer/8-must-know-tips-for-writing-clean-code-with-javascript-i4"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T13:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #refactorit #webdev #beginners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Omeyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Listening to Audiobooks Really Reading?]]></title>
        <id>6312405ea4a22698f6d24aaf</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/is-listening-to-audiobooks-really-reading/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WIRED’s spiritual advice columnist on bardic traditions for a modern age—and why book snobs worry about the wrong things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meghan O'Gieblyn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI's New Creative Streak Sparks a Silicon Valley Gold Rush]]></title>
        <id>635811513c668b3d581922aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ais-new-creative-streak-sparks-a-silicon-valley-gold-rush/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors have got the hots for "generative AI" that can make text and images. But so far, the hype runs ahead of the business results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a VS Code Extension "Todo Tree" can make your coding easier | Todo Tree Configuration | Highlighting Comments in VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/koustav/how-a-vs-code-extension-todo-tree-can-make-your-coding-easier-todo-tree-configuration-and-use-cases-11kc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/koustav/how-a-vs-code-extension-todo-tree-can-make-your-coding-easier-todo-tree-configuration-and-use-cases-11kc"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T05:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#news #vscode #programming #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>devkoustav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM PASS PWN (三)]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11775</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11775"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T01:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM PASS PWN (三)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Real Reason Elon Musk Wants You to Have More Babies]]></title>
        <id>61ba7bbc63820b7f88293089</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/real-reason-elon-musk-population-panic/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People who complain about population aren’t talking numbers—they’re fantasizing about tightening the reins on workers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Virginia Heffernan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[记一次某CMS代码审计]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11774</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11774"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T10:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[记一次某CMS代码审计]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-41852 Apache Commons Jxpath 漏洞分析]]></title>
        <id>https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11769</id>
        <link href="https://xz.aliyun.com/t/11769"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T07:29:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-41852 Apache Commons Jxpath 漏洞分析]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>先知安全技术社区</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hinge Will Try to Thwart Scammers With Video Verification]]></title>
        <id>6356e6b3a8552c961517a850</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hinge-selfie-verification-scammers-bots/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T14:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To combat the scourge of bots and fake accounts, the dating site will ask users to prove their humanity by capturing a video selfie.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Goode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made 10x faster JSON.stringify() functions, even type safe]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/samchon/i-made-10x-faster-jsonstringify-functions-even-type-safe-2eme</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/samchon/i-made-10x-faster-jsonstringify-functions-even-type-safe-2eme"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T12:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #programming #typescript #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeongho Nam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pandemic Uncovered Ways to Speed Up Science]]></title>
        <id>6346eb34f93a1584dc57f38b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/covid-19-open-science-public-health-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There doesn't have to be a trade-off between good research and fast research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saloni Dattani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Please do repeat yourself (DRY is dead)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ralphcone/please-do-repeat-yourself-dry-is-dead-1jbg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ralphcone/please-do-repeat-yourself-dry-is-dead-1jbg"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T20:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#productivity #beginners #codenewbie]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rafal Stozek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Notion-like system with Socket.io And React 😍]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/novu/building-a-notion-like-system-with-socketio-and-react-1hjg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/novu/building-a-notion-like-system-with-socketio-and-react-1hjg"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T12:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #webdev #react #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevo David, novu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awesome Websites For UI/UX Inspiration]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-websites-for-uiux-inspiration-5h75</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/surajondev/awesome-websites-for-uiux-inspiration-5h75"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#ux #css #beginners #javascript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Vishwakarma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a multi-language website using React in 3 minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/quocbahuynh/build-a-multi-language-website-using-react-in-3-minutes-4206</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/quocbahuynh/build-a-multi-language-website-using-react-in-3-minutes-4206"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T18:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #javascript #beginners #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>quocbahuynh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Javascript Shallow Copy - what is a Shallow Copy?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/smpnjn/javascript-shallow-copy-what-is-a-shallow-copy-1pc5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/smpnjn/javascript-shallow-copy-what-is-a-shallow-copy-1pc5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T19:43:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #javascript #typescript #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Johnny Simpson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Patterns in Software Development]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abdurrkhalid333/design-patterns-in-software-development-4b82</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abdurrkhalid333/design-patterns-in-software-development-4b82"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T19:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#tutorial #opensource #productivity #community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdur Rehman Khalid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Things Strong Developers Do That Drive Their Team Crazy]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jenc/things-strong-developers-do-that-drives-the-team-around-them-crazy-437a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jenc/things-strong-developers-do-that-drives-the-team-around-them-crazy-437a"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T14:40:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#career #senior #intermediate #productivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jen chan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New git guidelines: We have switched to Conventional Commits]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/visuellverstehen/new-git-guidelines-we-have-switched-to-conventional-commits-1p0c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/visuellverstehen/new-git-guidelines-we-have-switched-to-conventional-commits-1p0c"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T08:28:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#git #webdev #programming #opensource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Malte Riechmann, visuellverstehen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These 10 free APIs will take your programming projects to the next level 👇]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/elliot_brenyasarfo_18749/these-10-free-apis-will-take-your-programming-projects-to-the-next-level-5g24</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/elliot_brenyasarfo_18749/these-10-free-apis-will-take-your-programming-projects-to-the-next-level-5g24"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T08:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#webdev #programming #react #javascript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elliot Brenya sarfo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware the Distraction of the Twitter Mob Campaign]]></title>
        <id>635129452721236bcb15848f</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/hellena-taylor-bayonnetta-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A kerfuffle over Bayonetta voice actor Hellena Taylor’s pay reveals the often hollow structure of social media activism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katherine Cross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazy Loading in images with React JS 😴]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/franklin030601/lazy-loading-in-images-with-react-js-4enm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/franklin030601/lazy-loading-in-images-with-react-js-4enm"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#react #javascript #performance #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Franklin Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine Could Never Afford to Bet on Starlink]]></title>
        <id>635026f3f1f6a083059bc054</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-starlink-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The internet service tool was essential in the early days of the war with Russia. But the caprices of SpaceX CEO Elon Musk have exposed dangerous flaws.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katherine Cross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Re-Wrote These 10+ Single Lines of JavaScript Code, the Team Lead Praised the Code for Being Elegant]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rida/i-re-wrote-these-10-single-lines-of-javascript-code-the-team-lead-praised-the-code-for-being-elegant-ec</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rida/i-re-wrote-these-10-single-lines-of-javascript-code-the-team-lead-praised-the-code-for-being-elegant-ec"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T04:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#javascript #beginners #programming #tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rida F&amp;#39;kih</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run your README.md like a notebook in VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sourishkrout/run-your-readmemd-in-vs-code-50l7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sourishkrout/run-your-readmemd-in-vs-code-50l7"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T01:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#vscode #opensource #beginners #devops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Tiedtke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran's Internet Blackouts Are Part of a Global Menace]]></title>
        <id>634db7f67e817d200a6cc6ba</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/iran-mahsa-amini-internet-shutdown/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Repressive regimes are teaching each other how to control protesters' web access with increasingly surgical precision.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yasmin Green</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>